<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-06-09T01:49:55.247Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-09T01:49:55.247Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernize Your Mainframe Applications & Deploy Them In The Cloud]]></title>
        <id>6b1b29b8416988254d5bb4b9eb7bf37cc88ab414</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/modernize-your-mainframe-applications-deploy-them-in-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are launching AWS Mainframe Modernization service to help you modernize your mainframe applications and deploy them to AWS fully-managed runtime environments. This new service also provides tools and resources to help you plan and implement migration and modernization. Since the introduction of System/360 on April 7 1964, mainframe computers have enabled many industries […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at Cisco Live: Demos, Presentations, Experts, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-cisco-live-demos-presentations-experts-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-cisco-live-demos-presentations-experts-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re at Cisco Live, June 12-16. Find out more details in our pre-event blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo – OKRs (Objectives and Key Results)]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64394</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-okrs-objectives-and-key-results/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is vision?
The post DevOps Dojo – OKRs (Objectives and Key Results) appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Desktop App with React and Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56716</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/building-a-desktop-app-with-react-and-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow along as Principal Developer Advocate David Simmons uses Camunda Platform 8 and React to build an app that requests, fetches, and saves data.
The post Building a Desktop App with React and Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS MGN Update – Configure DR, Convert CentOS Linux to Rocky Linux, and Convert SUSE Linux Subscription]]></title>
        <id>5d64e7849cb97cd88b049a203409a40516c031fb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-mgn-update-configure-dr-convert-centos-linux-to-rocky-linux-and-convert-suse-linux-subscription/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just about a year ago, Channy showed you How to Use the New AWS Application Migration Server for Lift-and-Shift Migrations. In his post, he introduced AWS Application Migration Service (AWS MGN) and said: With AWS MGN, you can minimize time-intensive, error-prone manual processes by automatically replicating entire servers and converting your source servers from physical, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunsetting Atom]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-08-sunsetting-atom/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-08-sunsetting-atom/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are archiving Atom and all projects under the Atom organization for an official sunset on December 15, 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 private automation hub features about automation execution environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/8-private-automation-hub-features-about-automation-execution-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/8-private-automation-hub-features-about-automation-execution-environments"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1 introduced automation execution environments, which is a new way to package automation into a container runtime environment. In addition, private automation hub also joined the party by adding significant support for execution environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scale vs. Speed: Why organizations slow down]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42137</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698746098/0/sethsblog~Scale-vs-Speed-Why-organizations-slow-down/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T08:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you compare a Starbucks of ten years ago to a current one, they’re virtually the same. Compare this to the originals in Seattle, and the difference is startling. The same goes for the design of a typical McDonald’s. Apple launched the Mac with about a dozen full-time people working on its development. Today, they […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start your open source journey with Community Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-08-start-your-open-source-journey-with-community-exchange/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-08-start-your-open-source-journey-with-community-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T08:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a student who is new to open source or just starting your maintainer journey? GitHub Global Campus’ Community Exchange can help you make that first contribution or grow your open source project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regression testing your Java Agent Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/regression-testing-your-java-agent-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/regression-testing-your-java-agent-plugin"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to easily perform regression testing on your Java agent plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Shirazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create your own instrumentation with the Java Agent Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/create-your-own-instrumentation-with-the-java-agent-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/create-your-own-instrumentation-with-the-java-agent-plugin"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walk through using the Elastic APM Java Agent Plugin API to monitor any technology with custom instrumentation that will run automatically within the Java Agent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Shirazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regression testing your Java Agent Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/regression-testing-your-java-agent-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/regression-testing-your-java-agent-plugin"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For developers who’ve created their own instrumentation with the Java Agent plugin, the next phase of the process is regression testing. By performing regression testing, you can ensure that your plugin functions the way it’s supposed to after you’ve made code changes or updates. 

You’ll have your own plugin, but to illustrate regression testing in this article, I’ll use the plugin in our example repo.

The normal sequence of activity with a plugin
First, let’s understand the normal sequence of activity when the application is started with the Elastic APM (application performance monitoring) Java Agent and the plugin, using the -javaagent option on the command line (There are several ways to attach the agent. For this sequence, let’s assume the recommended -javaagent option.)

The Java …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Shirazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create your own instrumentation with the Java Agent Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/create-your-own-instrumentation-with-the-java-agent-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/create-your-own-instrumentation-with-the-java-agent-plugin"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The Elastic APM (application performance monitoring) Java Agent automatically instruments many frameworks and technologies to trace and monitor the performance of applications and track errors. Developers can also add code to instrument their own applications using the OpenTelemetry API (more on that below).

But if you can’t or don’t want to add code, and the technology you want to monitor is not automatically supported, there’s another option: use the Elastic APM Java Agent Plugin API to create your own instrumentation that runs within the Java Agent.

In this article, I’ll step through a straightforward example to show you how easy it is to create your own instrumentation that will run when both the Java Agent and the targeted technology is loaded in your application. The repo holding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Shirazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shuttle Skeleton]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2630/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2630/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/shuttle_skeleton.png" title="It's believed to be related to the Stellar Sea Cow." alt="It's believed to be related to the Stellar Sea Cow." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One developer’s journey bringing Dependabot to GitHub Enterprise Server]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-07-one-developers-journey-bringing-dependabot-to-github-enterprise-server/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-07-one-developers-journey-bringing-dependabot-to-github-enterprise-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A personal story about building the feature you want and sharing it with the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End-to-end Generative Pre-training for Multimodal Video Captioning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/end-to-end-generative-pre-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/end-to-end-generative-pre-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Paul Hongsuck Seo and Arsha Nagrani, Research Scientists, Google Research, Perception Team  
Multimodal video captioning systems utilize both the video frames and speech to generate natural language descriptions (captions) of videos. Such systems are stepping stones towards the longstanding goal of building multimodal conversational systems that effortlessly communicate with users while perceiving environments through multimodal input streams.  
 Unlike video understanding tasks (e.g., video classification and retrieval) where the key challenge lies in processing and understanding multimodal input videos, the task of multimodal video captioning includes the additional challenge of generating grounded captions. The most widely adopted approach for this task is to train an encoder-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Azure is Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Microsoft Azure is now available in public beta. Get started today with a secure, resilient service mesh for connecting applications running in Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.1.5]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=254190</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/06/07/datagrip-2022-1-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T14:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! Today we’ve got a new minor update for DataGrip 2022.1. Let’s see what’s been improved. Bug-fixes: DBE-14378: TiDB is now detected, and DataGrip only uses statements that are supported by the database. DBE-15553: [Exasol] The IMPERSONATE command is now supported. DBE-15322: [ClickHouse] Fixed type deduction for map literals. [Snowflake] Added the ability to skip […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | June 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=254193</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/06/07/net-annotated-monthly-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? The domain name www.youtube.com was registered on February 14, 2005. The first video was uploaded on April 23, 2005 titled Me at the zoo, which has over 230 million views as of June 2022. .NET news Announcing .NET 7 Preview 4 ASP.NET Core updates in .NET 7 Preview 4 Announcing Entity Framework […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the Webinar – 5 Approaches to Remote C++ Development With CLion]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=254181</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/06/join-the-webinar-5-approaches-to-remote-cpp-development-with-clion/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on Tuesday, July 26, 2022, 3:00 pm – 4:30 pm UTC (check other timezones) for our free live webinar, 5 Approaches to Remote C++ Development With CLion. REGISTER NOW and get a reminder, or join us on YouTube. In this webinar, JetBrains developer advocates Matt Ellis and Timur Doumler will show 5 different […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 7th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/07/this-week-in-spring-june-7th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/07/this-week-in-spring-june-7th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’ve just landed in tantalizing Toronto, Canada, for the SpringOne Tour Toronto show. I’m so excited to be here, at long last, after so long away from one of my favorite countries. I’ll be doing two talks - my usual, Kubernetes Native Java, and a talk on building Kubernetes Controllers (a.k.a. “Operators”) using the official Kubernetes Java client, Spring Boot, and Spring Native with my amazing friend and teammate Tiffany Jernigan, who you may recall was on the podcast not too long ago. 

After Toronto, I’m off to beautiful Berlin, Germany, for the We Are Developers show. 

If you’re at either show, don’t hesitate to say hi! 


  
Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (parts 1 and 2 of an ongoing series) Hi Spring …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.10 Achieves FIPS 140-2 Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-1-10-achieves-fips-140-2-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-1-10-achieves-fips-140-2-compliance"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault Enterprise 1.10 has been evaluated as conformant with the Federal Information Processing Standard (FIPS) 140-2 standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64349</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-lean-product-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T09:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 and Part 2 of the DevOps Dojo – Lean Product series, we covered the why, what, and how of the product-centric model and lean product model as outlined in the White & Orange Belts of the DevOps Dojo.
The post DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 3 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2 EAP #2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=252317</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/06/phpstorm-2022-2-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T09:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to the 2022.2 EAP series! If you’re new or unsure what our Early Access Program is, make sure to read the first post in this series. With that said, let’s take a look at what’s new in this week’s version! Download PhpStorm 2022.2 EAP New inspections You can expect new inspections with every […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – June 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=254035</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/06/java-annotated-monthly-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T09:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello in June! This month we will try to predict the future and say something about OpenJDK 19. We’ll read Kotlin books, recap recent conferences, and maybe even make a plan to go to one. Let’s start catching up with recent news and articles! Java News JEP 428: Structured Concurrency. What Can We Expect In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ida Bzowska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paying extra]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40085</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698681446/0/sethsblog~Paying-extra/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T08:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For six years, if you wanted an electric car, you’d need to pay extra. It cost more than the regular kind. Of course, if you decided to buy one, you weren’t paying extra. You were buying sustainability, community awareness, cachet, status, safety, quiet and the feeling of being an early adopter. People never pay extra. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic announces Elastic Security for Cloud, delivering new posture management and workload protection capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-your-cloud-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-your-cloud-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security for Cloud extends the capabilities of Elastic Security into the cloud with the addition of new capabilities for risk and posture management as well as threat monitoring and workload protection]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajiv Raghunarayan,Sneha Sachidananda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security Labs: Follow us for breaking news on security threat research]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-security-labs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-security-labs"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security Labs is now the official, one-stop domain for threat research, making it easier to find and share security threat research that will lead to a more secure workplace and a more protected industry overall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devon Kerr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic announces Elastic Security for Cloud, delivering new posture management and workload protection capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-your-cloud-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-your-cloud-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Security for Cloud is a new way to manage your cloud posture and ensure the security of cloud workloads. Elastic Security for Cloud expands the capabilities of the Elastic Security solution, extending visibility of the Elastic Security solution from endpoints to the cloud and building on the open and integrated approach and the rich security analytics capabilities already baked into Elastic.

With more than 85% of organizations moving to a cloud-first model and 95% of new digital workloads deployed on cloud-native platforms, according to Gartner, securing cloud environments is crucial to ensure sustained business innovation and growth. Whether it’s financial organizations moving to branchless banking or retailers improving customer experience via an omni-channel strategy, extendi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajiv Raghunarayan,Sneha Sachidananda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security Labs: Follow us for breaking news on security threat research]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-security-labs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-security-labs"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Security Labs is now the official, one-stop domain for threat research from a team of 40+ industry veterans. 

Elastic has been delivering timely and detailed security threat research for years — we’ve published more than 40 research articles and tools. We want to make it easier to find and share security threat research that will lead to a more secure workplace and a more protected industry overall.

“We feel that the availability of topical and timely security threat research has been traditionally inaccessible,” said Devon Kerr, Elastic Security Research Lead. “Elastic Security Labs intends to change this disparity and put in every security practitioner's hands the needed information and tools to protect their organizations.”

[Read more about CUBA and other malware here.]
Lev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devon Kerr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – June 6, 2022]]></title>
        <id>809e92b4a5a28eebe9aaedaedb0238c8547ff419</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-6-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I’ve just come back from a long (extended) holiday weekend here in the US and I’m still catching up on all the AWS launches that happened this past week. I’m […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KotlinDL 0.4 Is Out With Pose Detection API, EfficientDet for Object Detection, and EfficientNet for Image Recognition]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=253933</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/06/kotlindl-0-4-is-out-with-pose-detection-api-efficientdet-for-object-detection-and-efficientnet-for-image-recognition/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 0.4 of our deep learning library, KotlinDL, is out! KotlinDL 0.4 is now available on Maven Central with a variety of new features – check out all of the changes that are coming to the new release! We’re currently introducing new models in ModelHub (including the EfficientNet and EfficientDet model families), the experimental high-level […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Belov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Appsec at Netflix (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c9e0f1488bc5</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/scaling-appsec-at-netflix-part-2-c9e0f1488bc5?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Astha Singhal, Lakshmi Sudheer, Julia Knecht]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing GitHub Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-06-introducing-github-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-06-introducing-github-skills/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re announcing GitHub Skills, a new learning experience to help you throughout your GitHub journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Expect From the Kotlin Team in 2022–23: Key Projects and Productivity Features]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=253749</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/06/what-to-expect-from-the-kotlin-team-in-202223/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:44:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin is commonly used for writing server-side, multiplatform, and Android apps, but there are tons of lesser known use cases. Among them are Minecraft plugin development, writing software for robots, or even creating PowerPoint presentations using Compose for Desktop. The number of use cases to address and potential improvements to implement is huge, and it’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Egor Tolstoy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Busy Plugin Developers Newsletter – Spring 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=251481</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2022/06/busy-plugin-developers-newsletter-spring-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a while since the release of our most recent issue of the Busy Plugin Developers Newsletter, which means we’ve got a lot of work to do in this edition to fill you in on the major developments in plugin tooling and the latest news about JetBrains Marketplace. Marketplace news: ⭐️ Better visibility […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RiderFlow 2022.1.2 Bug-Fix Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=250401</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/06/06/riderflow-2022-1-2-bug-fix-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard about our new free plugin for Unity editor? RiderFlow helps manage the scenes, navigate and search through them, and even refactor them. You can download it from the Asset Store, use Unity package manager to install it, or get RiderFlow.unitypackage directly from our website. DOWNLOAD RIDERFLOW This new update brings a few […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Ansible Automation Platform's Automation Services Catalog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-ansible-automation-platforms-automation-services-catalog</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-ansible-automation-platforms-automation-services-catalog"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.2 introduces a technical preview of automation services catalog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.2 EAP3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=253199</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2022/06/rubymine-2022-2-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.2 EAP 3 is now available! Here are the build highlights: Code completion for Rails URLs in the HTTP client Support for URL searches in Rails applications Endpoints toolwindow Improved clickable links in Rails server logs Better completion for HTML tags in ERB files Other improvements Code completion for Rails URLs in the HTTP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Sarkisov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub brings supply chain security features to the Rust community]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-06-github-brings-supply-chain-security-features-to-the-rust-community/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-06-github-brings-supply-chain-security-features-to-the-rust-community/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T10:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust community can now discover, report, and prevent security vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are things like around here?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=31573</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698621914/0/sethsblog~What-are-things-like-around-here/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industries are often held together by unspoken hierarchies, signposts on the road to achievement. In the fancy parts of the book business, it’s not profit. Editors are often unaware of which books are truly profitable. They keep track of cultural impact, literary respect, the idea of a book being ‘well published’ and the hard-to-measure currency […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building secure and resilient telecom networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-secure-and-resilient-telecom-networks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-secure-and-resilient-telecom-networks"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using the NIST framework, ThoughtLab recently concluded a cybersecurity benchmark study that spanned across industries, including telecommunications. How well armed is the industry to protect critical network infrastructure?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building secure and resilient telecom networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-secure-and-resilient-telecom-networks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-secure-and-resilient-telecom-networks"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Using the NIST framework, ThoughtLab recently concluded a cybersecurity benchmark study that spanned across industries, including telecommunications. There is an urgent call to action for organizations to think and implement cybersecurity processes and technologies more strategically. The study shed some positive light for telecom companies as compared to peer industries. But, the MTTx (detect, respond, mitigate) and threat dwell time are high enough to raise serious concerns about how well armed the industry is to protect such critical network infrastructure.  

[Download the cybersecurity benchmark study here]
Synergies of 5G and cybersecurity challenges 
The study calls out eight mutually reinforcing megatrends that have pushed cybersecurity to an inflection point — and 5G is one of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Or Whatever]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2629/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2629/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/or_whatever.png" title="Oh yeah, I didn't even know they renamed it the Willis Tower in 2009, because I know a normal amount about skyscrapers." alt="Oh yeah, I didn't even know they renamed it the Willis Tower in 2009, because I know a normal amount about skyscrapers." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skepticism and Denial]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42114</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698569436/0/sethsblog~Skepticism-and-Denial/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Skepticism is a virtue. It requires a willingness to question conventional wisdom, and the guts to accept something after you discover that it’s actually true. Denialism, on the other hand, is a willful rejection of reality. It’s safe and easy, and unproductive. Because there’s no room to change your mind. To be a generous skeptic, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Java Annotated Monthly Webpage!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=250742</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/06/announcing-the-java-annotated-monthly-webpage/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-04T11:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAM started more than eight years ago with the publication of the first issue of the Java Annotated Monthly on May 5, 2014. In this time, an amazing group of authors – Trisha Gee, Dalia Abo Sheasha, Andrey Cheptsov, Helen Scott, and Irina Maryasova – has curated over 100 collections of JVM news. In January […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ida Bzowska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interested vs. interesting]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=31811</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698514950/0/sethsblog~Interested-vs-interesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-04T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of course you’re interesting. There’s something about what you’ve done, what you say, how you show up in the world that’s worthy of interest. But that doesn’t mean that people are interested. We each have a noise in our heads, an agenda and something urgent that’s grabbing our attention. And so, the amount of interest […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 04.06.2022]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64335</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-04-06-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-04T07:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Don’t Accept the Defaults’ -Abel Wang
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 04.06.2022 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A beginner’s guide to CI/CD and automation on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-03-a-beginners-guide-to-ci-cd-and-automation-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-03-a-beginners-guide-to-ci-cd-and-automation-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI/CD and workflow automation are native capabilities on GitHub platform. Here’s how to start using them and speed up your workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper and Rider 2022.1.2 Are Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=253389</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/06/03/resharper-rider-2022-1-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T16:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! The new bug-fix updates for ReSharper and Rider have just been released. Let’s go through the most important improvements. ReSharper We fixed the Ctrl+. hotkey for Visual Studio’s Show smart tag action, which had been affected by the previous version of ReSharper (RSRP-488222). We’re sorry for the inconvenience! We updated ReSharper’s initial event […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asia Rudenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making technical interviews better for everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-03-making-technical-interviews-better-for-everyone/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-03-making-technical-interviews-better-for-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T09:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to interview for skill, not spare time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The next train]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42110</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698438898/0/sethsblog~The-next-train/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T08:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not a luxury, it’s a choice. We can build slack into our lives. We can create cycles so that we don’t need to dance with a crisis around time on a regular basis. If there’s another train after this one, you don’t have to fret. If the deadline for the project is tomorrow, not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Too many fields! 3 ways to prevent mapping explosion in Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-ways-to-prevent-mapping-explosion-in-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-ways-to-prevent-mapping-explosion-in-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More often than not, we have customers indexing fields "just in case" they need to be used for search. Take a look at some techniques for cutting costs and focusing your cluster performance on what really matters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugo Sangiorgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Too many fields! 3 ways to prevent mapping explosion in Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-ways-to-prevent-mapping-explosion-in-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-ways-to-prevent-mapping-explosion-in-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
A system is said to be "observable" when it has three things: logs, metrics, and traces. While metrics and traces have predictable structures, logs (especially application logs) are usually unstructured data that need to be collected and parsed to be really useful. Therefore, getting your logs under control is arguably the hardest part of achieving Observability. 

In this article, we’ll dive into three effective strategies developers can use to manage logs with Elasticsearch.

[Related article: Leveraging Elastic to improve data management and observability in the cloud]

Putting Elasticsearch to work for your data
Sometimes we don't have control over what types of logs we receive in our cluster. Think of a log analytics provider that has a specific budget for storing its customers’ log…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugo Sangiorgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motion Blur]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2628/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2628/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/motion_blur.png" title="I can't speak for your other subjects, but MY motion was as smooth and natural as the framerate allowed." alt="I can't speak for your other subjects, but MY motion was as smooth and natural as the framerate allowed." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring I/O founder, Spring trainer and community legend Sergi Almar]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-i-o-founder-spring-trainer-and-community-legend-sergi-almar</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-i-o-founder-spring-trainer-and-community-legend-sergi-almar"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! At long last, against all odds, Josh Long (@starbuxman) finally gets to talk to Spring I/O founder and more-than-a-decade-long friend Sergi Almar (@sergialmar) about an edition of Spring I/O after 2019!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the newest AWS Heroes – June 2022]]></title>
        <id>c02650163773177062a3b118f232c97abe7eb4ae</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-newest-aws-heroes-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Heroes are some of the worlds most active and vocal leaders in AWS communities, recognized for their unwavering focus on sharing insights and technical knowledge with others. Heroes have a variety of contributions to community learning: they host events, meetups, and workshops, author blogs, contribute to open source projects, speak at conferences, and more. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022 Deprecation of Reporting Services]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64299</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-deprecation-of-reporting-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the Azure DevOps Server 2022 release, we wanted to reiterate the deprecation of the existing data warehouse reporting services. We previously announced this in the Azure DevOps Server 2020 release notes. The warehouse reporting service has been part of TFS and Azure DevOps for over a decade.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022 Deprecation of Reporting Services appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (parts 1 and 2 of an ongoing series)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-1-and-2-of-an-ongoing-series</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-1-and-2-of-an-ongoing-series"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In thi^^^ these installments, we begin a new series introducing the Spring for GraphQL project. 

In this first installment, GraphQL Java lead Andi Marek (@andimarek) and  I (@starbuxman) look at the basics of using the GraphQL Java engine that underpins Spring for GraphQL. 


In this second installment, Andi and I are joined by Spring for GraphQL lead Rossen Stoyanchev (@rstoya05) as we look at using the Spring for GraphQL component model by writing queries. 


I know it’s been more than a month since we last published a video, so I’m going to be releasing every episode of this series very quickly, over the next week or two. I’ve already recorded and mostly finished producing eight episodes. I’m working on producing a ninth, and that’ll be that! A complete introduction to all things Spring for GraphQL. These are of course part of the usual Spring Tips playlist on YouTube, but also part of the Learn Spring for GraphQL with Josh Long playlist. Follow that one to be notified of any new episodes!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Stream Applications 2021.1.2 GA Release now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/spring-cloud-stream-applications-2021-1-2-ga-release-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/spring-cloud-stream-applications-2021-1-2-ga-release-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Cloud Stream Applications 2021.1.2 has been released.

This release is based on Spring Boot 2.6.8 and Spring Cloud 2021.0.3 and contains many improvements and bug fixes - check out the release notes for more information.
Future plans


  
Switch apps to use Spring Boot 3.x

  
Move Spring Cloud Stream App Maven plugins to stream-application repository.

  
Align versioning of Stream Functions and Apps.


Stay in touch…

Please continue to engage with us by creating bug reports and feature requests on Github and asking questions on StackOverflow using the spring-cloud-stream or spring-cloud-dataflow tags.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What&#8217;s new in security and user management for GitHub Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-02-whats-new-in-security-and-user-management-for-github-enterprise/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-02-whats-new-in-security-and-user-management-for-github-enterprise/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can securely manage users with the latest ships for GitHub Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB Field Level Encryption with HashiCorp Vault KMIP Secrets Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mongodb-field-level-encryption-with-hashicorp-vault-kmip-secrets-engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mongodb-field-level-encryption-with-hashicorp-vault-kmip-secrets-engine"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how MongoDB’s field-level encryption capability pairs with Vault’s KMIP secrets engine to help organizations deliver strong privacy and security controls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub All In: Our first student cohort and what’s next]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-02-github-all-in-our-first-student-cohort-and-whats-next/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-02-github-all-in-our-first-student-cohort-and-whats-next/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on the GitHub All In journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Conversations: Jean Robert Alves, Agi]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56009</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/community-conversations-jean-robert-alves-agibank/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the latest installment of Community Conversations, we sat down with Jean Robert Alves, a Camunda Champion and software architect expert at Agi.
The post Community Conversations: Jean Robert Alves, Agi appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Work Item Revision Limits]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64125</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/work-item-revision-limits/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time a work item is updated, it creates an entry in the work item history. This is a great feature for users to track all the individual changes made to work items. However, we have seen organizations with automated tools that will generate tens of thousands of work item revisions.
The post Work Item Revision Limits appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failing in the trough]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43075</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698348784/0/sethsblog~Failing-in-the-trough/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T08:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a time gap. Marketers raise expectations in order to get someone to sign up and try a product and service. And (hopefully) there’s satisfaction, delight and remarkability once the organization actually delivers on what you promised. In between, the trough. You spend $400 per customer on rent and architecture and web design. Perhaps it’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Corey Williams explains what Come As You Are means to her]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-corey-williams-come-as-you-are</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-corey-williams-come-as-you-are"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We encourage people to come as they are. It’s written into our values, or, what we call our Source Code, which defines our entire culture. As you are made it easy for Corey Williams, Workplace Experience Lead, to seamlessly transition to Elastic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a search experience with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-a-search-experience-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-a-search-experience-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to share a new end-to-end demo to showcase how Elastic empowers developers to build rich search solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Corey Williams explains what Come As You Are means to her]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-corey-williams-come-as-you-are</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-corey-williams-come-as-you-are"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
At Elastic, we encourage people to come as they are. Not, come as you think you should, but come as you really are. It’s written into our Source Code, the values that define our entire culture. 

And that culture is what made it easy for Corey Williams, Workplace Experience Lead, to seamlessly transition to Elastic. She joined the company as part of an acquisition, but with the cultural alignment of both companies, it was an easy move, says Williams.

“Culturally, I was able to just fit in,” Williams said. “The Source Code paralleled my previous company’s culture.”

Identifying as LGBTQ+ wasn’t a factor for Williams either. “I was able to just jump in and be who I am,” she says. “It’s remarkable how unremarkable it is.” For example, Williams is open with her team about her relationship a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a search experience with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-a-search-experience-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-a-search-experience-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re excited to share an end-to-end demo that showcases how Elastic empowers developers to build rich search solutions. The demo provides mechanisms to run in your own environment, to ingest data into Elastic Enterprise Search using the Enterprise Search Python Libraries, and to create a modern UI in React, using the free and open source tool Search UI. 

Whether you are new to Elastic and need an example of putting together an interesting search application, or you have familiarity with Elastic and are looking for examples to show the whole experience, this sample can be used as a starting point for building a search experience of your own.

tldr; Go check out the GitHub repository and follow the steps to see the power of Elastic Enterprise Search in action!
Setting the scene: Elastifl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Team or Free? How to choose the right plan]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-01-github-team-or-free-how-to-choose-the-right-plan/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-01-github-team-or-free-how-to-choose-the-right-plan/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T21:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about all the features you may not have known come on the GitHub Free plan, and how to choose the right plan for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EMR Serverless Now Generally Available – Run Big Data Applications without Managing Servers]]></title>
        <id>230544885a857a26188de08fe94fb293329b5ed7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-emr-serverless-now-generally-available-run-big-data-applications-without-managing-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced three new serverless options for our data analytics services – Amazon EMR Serverless, Amazon Redshift Serverless, and Amazon MSK Serverless – that make it easier to analyze data at any scale without having to configure, scale, or manage the underlying infrastructure. Today we announce the general availability of Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security OAuth reaches End-of-Life]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/01/spring-security-oauth-reaches-end-of-life</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/01/spring-security-oauth-reaches-end-of-life"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spring Security OAuth and Spring Security OAuth Boot 2 auto-configuration projects have reached end of life.



The Spring Security OAuth project has been replaced by the Client and Resource Server support provided by Spring Security and the Authorization Server support provided by Spring Authorization Server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Support After Our Artifactory Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55942</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/improved-support-after-our-artifactory-migration/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently migrated our 10-year-old artifact storage to a new cloud-based setup. Here's a behind-the-scenes look at the migration and how you can help us continue to improve access and support. 
The post Improved Support After Our Artifactory Migration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Lange</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Released: Automation content navigator 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/released-automation-content-navigator-2.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/released-automation-content-navigator-2.0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation content navigator releases with Ansible Automation Platform 2.2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In search of hypocrites]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42763</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698234840/0/sethsblog~In-search-of-hypocrites/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T08:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would we want to wait until someone is perfect before we give them a chance to make things better? Each of us is part of a system, cogs in a process that rewards us for certain actions based on various inputs. When the system is broken, some of the most highly leveraged, aware and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability summary: Follina, CVE-2022-30190]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/vulnerability-summary-follina</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/vulnerability-summary-follina"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic is deploying a new malware signature to identify the use of the Follina vulnerability. Learn more in this post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devon Kerr,Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability summary: Follina, CVE-2022-30190]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/vulnerability-summary-follina</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/vulnerability-summary-follina"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
On May 27, 2022, the nao_sec independent security research group shared a VirusTotal link to a weaponized Microsoft Office document revealing a previously unknown vulnerability in the Microsoft Support Diagnostic Tool (MSDT). This vulnerability is most likely to be exploited via phishing lure attachments and is triggered when a document is opened. Readers should expect this vulnerability to be adopted by threats of all kinds and be aware that it enables arbitrary code to be executed as outlined in Microsoft’s disclosure.
Summary
Readers may recall that template injection is an established technique enabling an attacker to remotely load malicious content when a document is opened by a relevant application. This vulnerability — dubbed “Follina” — works in conjunction with template injectio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devon Kerr,Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types of Scopes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2627/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2627/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/types_of_scopes.png" title="An x-ray gyroscope is used to determine exactly which toppings they included in the pita." alt="An x-ray gyroscope is used to determine exactly which toppings they included in the pita." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 31st, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/31/this-week-in-spring-may-31st-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/31/this-week-in-spring-may-31st-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! And welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’ve just returned from three wonderful weeks overseas and now, I’m pleased as punch to convey, that I’m home! And hopefully, COVID-19 free! Who knows what sort of nonsense I caught on the flight home, anyway. Some things, I’ve always said, shouldn’t be open source! But knowledge isn’t one of them and I had a lot of fun with this week’s roundup, so let’s dive right into it! 


  
@RequestMapping Value in Properties File

  
A Bootiful Podcast: the good Dr. David Syer on the new and novel in Spring and Kubernetes

  
A Guide to Docker Logs

  
this is something I learned about at the recent Spring IO show: an open source ticket management system - Alf.io

  
Blog: Contextual Logging in Kubernetes 1.24

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.24: Maximum Unavailable Replicas for StatefulSet

  
Difference Between docker stop and docker kill Commands

  
Docker Registry API – Listing Images and Tags

  
Introduction to Spring Cloud Sidecar

  
Java HttpClient Timeout

  
Java Weekly, Issue 439

  
Setting Request Headers Using Feign

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.3.0 available now

  
Spring Boot and Liquibase

  
Spring Boot — Reactive Web

  
Spring Native 0.12.0 available now

  
Spring Shell 2.1.0-M4 is now available

  
Spring Vault 2.4.0-M1 and 3.0.0-M1 available

  
Spring Web Service Integration Tests with @WebServiceServerTest

  
Visual Page Design with Spring Boot - YouTube

  
JVM Parameters

  
Azure Spring Apps Enterprise is generally available. Ship faster. Leverage Spring experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Terraform with Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-terraform-with-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-terraform-with-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we will dive into the two available Terraform providers from
Elastic. Terraform allows you to define your infrastructure as a code and keep
that in repositories to easily make changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Reelsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Terraform with Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-terraform-with-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-terraform-with-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
TLDR; Today we will dive into the two available Terraform providers from Elastic. Terraform allows you to define your infrastructure as a code and keep that in repositories to easily make changes.
Getting Started
Infrastructure-as-code (IaC) means managing your IT infrastructure via files so that changes can be applied automatically without intervention and are properly documented all the time. Terraform has become kind of a standard with some competitors like CloudFormation or Pulumi. Today we will focus on Terraform in combination with Elastic Cloud, so you do not need to use the Cloud UI to spin up, change or remove clusters.
Creating a Cloud API Key
In order to use Terraform, you need a cloud API key. Make sure this is not an API key for a Elastic Cloud instance but for your Elastic …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Reelsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating multi-vendor network prefix-lists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-multi-vendor-network-prefix-lists</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-multi-vendor-network-prefix-lists"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To keep the networks healthy, cause connectivity matters
 
I love being a network engineer, even though I struggled to explain to non-networking people about the utmost relevance of network administration. However, during the last two years of the COVID-19 pandemic, the world could see the relevance of having connectivity. Networks are the highways of information. Data, applications, entertainment, and factories need the network connectivity roads to make the world run. It’s interesting that even network models to estimate traffic behavior use algorithms that are similar to the ones to estimate transportation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The delay]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42061</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698146152/0/sethsblog~The-delay/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T08:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes we’re not that good with time. If people got a hacking cough and a chronic disease an hour after smoking their first cigarette, it’s unlikely many people would smoke. If earthquakes happened a day after fracking for gas was tried, they would probably have stopped. And if entrepreneurs discovered freedom, satisfaction and customer delight […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Native 0.12.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/31/spring-native-0-12-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/31/spring-native-0-12-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Native 0.12.0 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release.

This release includes 12 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades to GraalVM 22.1, Spring Boot 2.7.0 and Spring Cloud 2021.0.3. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.0-M4 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/30/spring-shell-2-1-0-m4-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/30/spring-shell-2-1-0-m4-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T06:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.0-M4 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

Notable changes include:


  
Project has been updated to Boot 2.7.0

  
Command sub-system has been rewritten

  
Support registering commands dynamically

  
Execution target can now also be Function or Consumer

  
Build-in help command is rendered via a template


Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – May 30, 2022]]></title>
        <id>11f85bc4066ba75d8f5b71875bdaee4c76ef9d1a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-30-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T14:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the US observes Memorial Day. South Korea also has a national Memorial Day, celebrated next week on June 6. In both countries, the day is set aside to remember those who sacrificed in service to their country. This time provides an opportunity to recognize and show our appreciation for the armed services and the important […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Camunda in a Low-code Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55577</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/integrating-camunda-in-a-low-code-platform/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Apex Process Consultants integrated Camunda Platform 7 with their low-code platform to make it easier to build processes. 
The post Integrating Camunda in a Low-code Platform appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personal responsibility]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43053</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698069666/0/sethsblog~Personal-responsibility/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T08:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s complicated. Because we made it complicated. Our culture is built on the principle that people are responsible for what they do. And then we spend time and effort diffusing the responsibility. If you work for a company and are just doing your job, are you responsible? What if you founded the company? What if […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Vault 2.4.0-M1 and 3.0.0-M1 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-vault-2-4-0-m1-and-3-0-0-m1-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-vault-2-4-0-m1-and-3-0-0-m1-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T14:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Vault 2.4.0-M1 and 3.0.0-M1 milestones have been released and are now available from repo.spring.io.



Notable new features include:





Support for PEM-encoded certificates and private keys including Elliptic Curve ("EC")



Support for Vault Repositories using versioned Key/Value secrets engines



Support for Vault-based RevisionRepository using versioned Key/Value secrets engines





Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.



Additionally, Spring Vault 3.0.0-M1 ships with:





Upgrade to Java 17 baseline, Spring Framework 6



Upgrade to AWS SDK v2





Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.



Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.



How can you help?


If you’re interested in helping out, check out the "ideal for contribution" tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-vault tag.



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Release 2.4.0-M1 on GitHub | Documentation for 2.4.0-M1 | Release 3.0.0-M1 on GitHub | Documentation for 3.0.0-M1 | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.3 is available. Compatible with Spring Boot 2.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-cloud-2021-0-3-is-available-compatible-with-spring-boot-2-7-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-cloud-2021-0-3-is-available-compatible-with-spring-boot-2-7-0"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce the Spring Cloud 2021.0.3 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2021.0.3 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0.3 Release Train

This release is primarily for compatibility with Spring Boot 2.7.0 along with Spring Boot 2.6.x.

To see all the issues and pull requests in this release, please see here.
Spring Cloud Sleuth


  
Bug fixes and minor enhancements


Spring Cloud Contract


  
Bug fixes and JsonAssert upgrade


Spring Cloud Gateway


  
Bug fixes and path variable support for PrefixPath filter.


The following modules were updated as part of 2021.0.3:


  
    

      Module 
      Version 
      Issues
    

  
  
    
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M6id and C6id Instances with Up to 7.6 TB Local NVMe Storage]]></title>
        <id>dabb34f9d25282db77234ee28cb2826f74cfe7b3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-m6id-and-c6id-instances-with-up-to-7-6-tb-local-nvme-storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T21:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, we launched the Amazon EC2 M6i instances and C6i instances, our sixth-generation offerings that include 3rd generation Intel Xeon Scalable processors. Today we are expanding Amazon EC2 M6id and C6id instances, backed by NVMe-based SSD block-level instance storage physically connected to the host server. These instances are powered by the Intel Xeon Scalable […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTS 0.6 Adds New Terraform Cloud Agent and HCP Consul Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cts-0-6-new-terraform-cloud-agent-hcp-consul-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cts-0-6-new-terraform-cloud-agent-hcp-consul-support"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of HashiCorp Consul-Terraform-Sync (CTS) 0.6 represents a key step in the maturity of our Network Infrastructure Automation (NIA) solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: the good Dr. David Syer on the new and novel in Spring and Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/26/a-bootiful-podcast-the-good-dr-david-syer-on-the-new-and-novel-in-spring-and-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/26/a-bootiful-podcast-the-good-dr-david-syer-on-the-new-and-novel-in-spring-and-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long talks to Spring Boot and Spring Cloud luminary, the good Dr. @David_Syer, about the latest and greatest on Spring and Kubernetes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2.2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible product team at Red Hat is thrilled to announce the general availability of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.2, which includes numerous features and bug fixes that further solidify Ansible Automation Platform as the de facto enterprise IT automation solution for developers to operations teams in data centers, clouds, and at the edge. A few of the most noteworthy features in this release include:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andriusb@redhat.com (Andrius Benokraitis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 Webinar Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55344</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-platform-8-webinar-recap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out these answers to the questions we didn't get to answer during our recent Camunda Platform 8 Release Webinar.
The post Camunda Platform 8 Webinar Recap appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning with Label Differential Privacy]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/deep-learning-with-label-differential.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/deep-learning-with-label-differential.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T20:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by  Pasin Manurangsi and Chiyuan Zhang, Research Scientists, Google Research  
Over the last several years, there has been an increased focus on developing differential privacy (DP) machine learning (ML) algorithms. DP has been the basis of several practical deployments in industry — and has even been employed by the U.S. Census — because it enables the understanding of system and algorithm privacy guarantees. The underlying assumption of DP is that changing a single user’s contribution to an algorithm should not significantly change its output distribution. 
 In the standard supervised learning setting, a model is trained to make a prediction of the label for each input given a training set of example pairs {[input1,label1], …, [inputn, labeln]}. In the case of deep learning, previ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.3.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/25/spring-authorization-server-0-3-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/25/spring-authorization-server-0-3-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.3.0.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.3.0'




See the release notes for complete details.



With this release, you can view the initial version of the reference documentation and the new project page on spring.io.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.11 Introduces New Provider Command and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-terraform-0-11-introduces-new-provider-command</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-terraform-0-11-introduces-new-provider-command"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform (CDKTF) 0.11 introduces an easier way to add providers to your application and improvements to the debugging process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to do When You Can’t Quickly Migrate to Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55237</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/what-to-do-when-you-cant-quickly-migrate-to-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not ready to migrate to Camunda Platform 8 yet? Learn the alternative approaches you can take now to prepare for migrating later.
The post What to do When You Can’t Quickly Migrate to Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring New Possibilities with the AWS Cloud Control Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/exploring-new-possibilities-with-the-aws-cloud-control-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/exploring-new-possibilities-with-the-aws-cloud-control-collection"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently made available an experimental alpha Collection of generated modules using the AWS Cloud Control API for interacting with AWS Services. This content is not intended for production in its current state. We are making this work available because we thought it was important to share our research and get your feedback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Open is Camunda Platform 8?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55199</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/how-open-is-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the different components of Camunda Platform 8 and their licenses. Plus, explore the possible paths to production.
The post How Open is Camunda Platform 8? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for AWS DataSync – Move Data Between AWS and Other Public Locations]]></title>
        <id>905a367112dd04b244491567bac3a7266994c9f7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-aws-datasync-move-data-between-aws-and-google-cloud-storage-or-aws-and-microsoft-azure-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moving data to and from AWS Storage services can be automated and accelerated with AWS DataSync. For example, you can use DataSync to migrate data to AWS, replicate data for business continuity, and move data for analysis and processing in the cloud. You can use DataSync to transfer data to and from AWS Storage services, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image-Text Pre-training with Contrastive Captioners]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/image-text-pre-training-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/image-text-pre-training-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zirui Wang and Jiahui Yu, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Oftentimes, machine learning (ML) model developers begin their design using a generic backbone model that is trained at scale and with capabilities transferable to a wide range of downstream tasks. In natural language processing, a number of popular backbone models, including BERT, T5, GPT-3 (sometimes also referred to as “foundation models”), are pre-trained on web-scale data and have demonstrated generic multi-tasking capabilities through zero-shot, few-shot or transfer learning. Compared with training over-specialized individual models, pre-training backbone models for a large number of downstream tasks can amortize the training costs, allowing one to overcome resource limitations when building large s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing for Spring Boot 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/preparing-for-spring-boot-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/preparing-for-spring-boot-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.0 was the first release in the 2.x line and was published on Feburary 28th 2018.
We’ve just released Spring Boot 2.7 which means that, so far, we’ve been maintaining the 2.x line for just over 4 years.
In total we’ve published 95 distinct releases over that timeframe!



The entire Spring team, and many in our community of contributors, are now preparing for the next generation of Spring.
We are planning to release Spring Boot 3.0 in November 2022.
This next major revision will be based on Spring Framework 6.0 and will require Java 17 or above.
It will also be the first version of Spring Boot that makes use of Jakarta EE 9 APIs (jakarta.*)  instead of EE 8 (javax.*).



The next six months offer an ideal opportunity to prepare your own projects for this major relea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Spring Apps Enterprise is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/azure-spring-apps-enterprise-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/azure-spring-apps-enterprise-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! This is a guest post by Julia Liuson, President, Developer Division, Microsoft 
Azure Spring Cloud is now Azure Spring Apps

We launched Azure Spring Cloud with VMware in 2019 to solve common challenges developers, IT operators, and DevOps teams face when running Spring Boot applications at scale. Since then we’ve helped many customers adopt the service including Bosch, Digital Realty, FedEx, Kroger, Liantis, Morgan Stanley, National Life, Raley’s, and Swiss Re. They value the fully managed infrastructure of Azure Spring Cloud that lets them focus on their apps, while the service manages dynamic scaling, security patching, out-of-the-box instrumentation for monitoring, and more. Through customer feedback. we have expanded the capabilities of the service, including the Ent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 24th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/this-week-in-spring-may-24th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/this-week-in-spring-may-24th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! I’m in Spain for business and not just a little pleasure. Yesterday, my partner, her mother, and I went to Formentera, Spain, a little island off of Ibiza, Spain. It was amazing. We’re now in Ibiza, Spain, which is a little island not far from Barcelona, Spain, on the mainland of Spain. It feels a bit like that Inception movie. We traveled by boat to Formentera for a little vacation inside of another little vacation (Ibiza) and inside of another little vacation (Barcelona). Tomorrow I’ll return to Barcelona for the Spring IO event. Yes, technically, this is work. But it’s an oh-so-much pleasure, too. I can’t wait! It’ll be the first time I’ve seen a ton of these people in years! I hope to see y’all there or los vemos!


  
Happily, Spring for GraphQL 1.0 has been release…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 C7g Instances, Powered by AWS Graviton3 Processors]]></title>
        <id>85274dcdcd66e71abf62466cd5e084f9aca8df04</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c7g-instances-powered-by-aws-graviton3-processors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T21:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am excited to announce that Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) C7g instances powered by the latest AWS Graviton3 processors that have been available in preview since re:Invent last year are now available for all. Let’s decompose the name C7g: the “C” instance family is designed for compute-intensive workloads. This is the 7th generation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – May 23, 2022]]></title>
        <id>75cfd7cc41f56e72a28e830102fd6d20f55dbfb1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-27-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T19:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! This is the right place to quickly learn about recent AWS news from last week, in just about five minutes or less. This week, I have collected a couple of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the HCL Extension for Visual Studio Code 0.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcl-extension-for-visual-studio-code-0-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcl-extension-for-visual-studio-code-0-1"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp adopts the community-created HCL Extension for Visual Studio Code and adds HCL 2.0 support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uplevel your automation skills with Red Hat training for Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/uplevel-your-automation-skills-with-red-hat-training-for-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/uplevel-your-automation-skills-with-red-hat-training-for-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 includes major features that allow customers to onboard more easily with even more flexible automation architectures and use cases. Ansible Automation Platform enables IT professionals to automate at enterprise scale more easily and flexibly. This means that everything you know and love about writing Ansible Playbooks is largely unchanged, but what is evolving is the underlying implementation of how automation is developed, managed, and operated in large complex environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Bonneville</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheers to Our Newest Camunda Champions Cohort]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=54752</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/cheers-to-our-newest-camunda-champions-cohort/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please join us in welcoming our latest batch of Camunda Champions! Check out which community members will participate in our third cohort. 
The post Cheers to Our Newest Camunda Champions Cohort appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Buchholz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Survey of Causal Inference Applications at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b62d25175e6f</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/a-survey-of-causal-inference-applications-at-netflix-b62d25175e6f?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T15:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Netflix, we want to entertain the world through creating engaging content and helping members discover the titles they will love. Key to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auth0, Fortinet, and Vercel Among New Verified Terraform Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/auth0-fortinet-and-vercel-among-new-verified-terraform-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/auth0-fortinet-and-vercel-among-new-verified-terraform-providers"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the addition of 18 new verified providers to the growing HashiCorp Terraform ecosystem we hit a milestone with 200 verified Terraform providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Java Applications to Azure using Continuous Delivery]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64092</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploying-java-applications-to-azure-using-continuous-delivery/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T10:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 3 in our series DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions and continuous delivery!
April: [00:00:00] Tune in into this week’s episode of the DevOps lab,
The post Deploying Java Applications to Azure using Continuous Delivery appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a Java Application to Azure using Continuous Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64087</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-a-java-application-to-azure-using-continuous-integration/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T07:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 2 in our series for DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions and continuous integration.
April: We’re back this week with the dev ops lab and we’re continuing our series DevOps for Java shops.
The post Deploy a Java Application to Azure using Continuous Integration appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-M3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-3-0-0-m3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-3-0-0-m3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T20:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-M3 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 74 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Auto-configuration for Micrometer Observation, Tracing, and OtlpMeterRegistry

  
Reinstated Support for REST Assured and Pooled JMS


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power of Partners: How Camunda’s Partners are Making an Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=54712</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/the-power-of-partners-how-camundas-partners-are-making-an-impact/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard of our Camunda Connect program? Learn how it's enabling our partners to make process automation more accessible to our clients.
The post The Power of Partners: How Camunda’s Partners are Making an Impact appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation at the Edge - Summit 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-at-the-edge-summit-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-at-the-edge-summit-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As some of you may know, Red Hat Summit was back in person in Boston last week. For those who are not familiar, Red Hat Summit is the premier enterprise open source event for IT professionals to learn, collaborate, and innovate on technologies from the datacenter and public cloud to the edge and beyond. Red Hat made a lot of exciting announcements, with several that included Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. If you could not make the event or would like to revisit some of the content, you can access any session on demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Lathram)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Do Accessible Design and Engineering at HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-do-accessible-design-and-engineering-at-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-do-accessible-design-and-engineering-at-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two HashiCorp engineers discuss accessible design and engineering at HashiCorp, from overall principles to the tools we use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to Azure Pipelines Runtime Variables Settings [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63937</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/updates-to-azure-pipelines-runtime-variables-settings/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have gotten a lot of feedback on this change and after internal deliberation, we are now rolling back this change ASAP.
We have now fully rolled back the change that caused the issue.
The post Updates to Azure Pipelines Runtime Variables Settings [Updated] appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.8 Expands Health and Events Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-8-expands-health-and-events-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-8-expands-health-and-events-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.8 adds key observability features and improvements to identity-based secure remote access for dynamic infrastructure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-2-7-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-2-7-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T13:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the Spring Boot team and everyone that has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0 has been released and is available from Maven Central. 

This release adds a significant number of new features and improvements. For full upgrade instructions and new and noteworthy features please see the release notes.
What’s new in 2.7

The highlights of the 2.7 release include:


  
Auto-configuration and metrics for Spring for GraphQL; see related 1.0 release announcement

  
New @DataCouchbaseTest and @DataElasticsearchTest support

  
Podman can now be used when building images using Cloud Native Buildpacks

  
Support for Cache2k

  
Simplified registration of Jackson Mixins

  
Web server SSL configuration using PEM-encoded certs


Dependency upgrades

Spring Boot 2.7 moves to new versions of several Spring projects:


  
Spring Data 2021.2

  
Spring HATEOAS 1.5

  
Spring LDAP 2.4

  
Spring Security 5.7

  
Spring Session 2021.2


We’ve also upgraded to the latest stable releases of other third-party libraries wherever possible. Please see the release notes for details.
Other changes

There’s a whole host of other changes and improvements that are documented in the release notes. You can also find a list of deprecated classes and methods that we plan to remove in the next version.

Additionally, Spring Boot 2.5 has now reached the end of its OSS support period. More information on Spring Boot’s support dates can be found here.
Thank you

We want to take this opportunity to again thank all our users and contributors.

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask at stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Devoxx UK organizer and VoxxedDays cofounder Mark Hazell on running great conferences]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/a-bootiful-podcast-devoxx-uk-organizer-and-voxxeddays-cofounder-mark-hazell-on-running-great-conferences</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/a-bootiful-podcast-devoxx-uk-organizer-and-voxxeddays-cofounder-mark-hazell-on-running-great-conferences"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Devoxx UK organizer and Voxxed Days cofounder Mark Hazell (@mrhazell).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.8 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-2-6-8-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-2-6-8-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T11:19:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.8 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 35 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-for-graphql-1-0-release</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-for-graphql-1-0-release"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the Spring for GraphQL team and every contributor, it is my pleasure to announce the 1.0 GA release. It’s been 10 months since the project was announced and under 2 years since the first commit, unremarkably called “first commit”. The project began with the modest goal to replace the (now archived) minimal GraphQL Java Spring integration, but has since moved significantly beyond through community feedback and collaboration across Spring Boot, Spring Framework, Spring Data, and Spring Security. 

The following are highlights from the release:


  
Annotation-based programming model for data fetchers

  
Data binding from input arguments with validation

  
Field-level security through annotations on data @Controller methods

  
Server handlers and interception over HTTP, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64084</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-a-java-application-to-azure-app-service-using-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T07:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 1 in our series for DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions. Brian also covers off feature flags!
April: Welcome to this week’s episode of the dev ops lab.
The post Deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.2 Improves Exception Handling and Updates to the CLI-driven Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-2-improves-exception-handling-and-updates-to-the-cli-driven-workflow</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-2-improves-exception-handling-and-updates-to-the-cli-driven-workflow"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now generally available, HashiCorp Terraform 1.2 introduces exception handling with pre- and post-conditions, support for non-interactive Terraform Cloud operations in a CI/CD pipeline, and CLI support for Run Tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Artifacts introduces new Upstreaming capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64079</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-artifacts-introduces-new-upstreaming-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T22:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Artifacts is announcing the long-desired feature of supporting Upstreams for Universal Packages across different ADO organizations.
The post Azure Artifacts introduces new Upstreaming capabilities appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Backup Now Supports Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP]]></title>
        <id>4a4714ab05fe013a182547e67a8696dc9531dab4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-backup-now-supports-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T20:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a long-time reader of this blog, you know that I categorize some posts as “chocolate and peanut butter” in homage to an ancient (1970 or so) series of TV commercials for Reese’s Peanut Butter Cups. Today, I am happy to bring you the latest such post, combining AWS Backup and Amazon FSx […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector-Quantized Image Modeling with Improved VQGAN]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/vector-quantized-image-modeling-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/vector-quantized-image-modeling-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jiahui Yu, Senior Research Scientist, and Jing Yu Koh, Research Software Engineer, Google Research 
In recent years, natural language processing models have dramatically improved their ability to learn general-purpose representations, which has resulted in significant performance gains for a wide range of natural language generation and natural language understanding tasks. In large part, this has been accomplished through pre-training language models on extensive unlabeled text corpora.  
This pre-training formulation does not make assumptions about input signal modality, which can be language, vision, or audio, among others. Several recent papers have exploited this formulation to dramatically improve image generation results through pre-quantizing images into discrete integer …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contextual Rephrasing in Google Assistant]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/contextual-rephrasing-in-google.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/contextual-rephrasing-in-google.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T19:38:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Aurelien Boffy, Senior Staff Software Engineer, and Roberto Pieraccini, Engineering Director, Google Assistant 
When people converse with one another, context and references play a critical role in driving their conversation more efficiently. For instance, if one asks the question “Who wrote Romeo and Juliet?” and, after receiving an answer, asks “Where was he born?”, it is clear that ‘he’ is referring to William Shakespeare without the need to explicitly mention him. Or if someone mentions “python” in a sentence, one can use the context from the conversation to determine whether they are referring to a type of snake or a computer language. If a virtual assistant cannot robustly handle context and references, users would be required to adapt to the limitation of the technology by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Helm and Kubernetes to deploy Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=53853</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/using-helm-and-kubernetes-to-deploy-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know to install, configure, and run Camunda Platform 8 Helm charts. 
The post Using Helm and Kubernetes to deploy Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – May 16, 2022]]></title>
        <id>188f6fbb789cd4b216b2e97a6340bddf3499db79</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-16-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T19:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I had been on the road for the last five weeks and attended many of the AWS Summits in Europe. It was great to talk to so many of you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask me Anything Recap - April]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ask-me-anything-recap-april</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ask-me-anything-recap-april"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For this webinar, we had an awesome group of individuals with a diverse talent range across multiple skill sets from Product Management, Technical Marketing and Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenges in Multi-objective Optimization for Automatic Wireless Network Planning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/challenges-in-multi-objective.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/challenges-in-multi-objective.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Ahmadian and Matthew Fahrbach, Research Scientists, Google Research, Large-Scale Optimization Team 
Economics, combinatorics, physics, and signal processing conspire to make it difficult to design, build, and operate high-quality, cost-effective wireless networks. The radio transceivers that communicate with our mobile phones, the equipment that supports them (such as power and wired networking), and the physical space they occupy are all expensive, so it’s important to be judicious in choosing sites for new transceivers. Even when the set of available sites is limited, there are exponentially many possible networks that can be built. For example, given only 50 sites, there are 250 (over a million billion) possibilities!  
Further complicating things, for every location wher…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 Adds Native Service Discovery and Edge Workload Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 includes built-in service discovery, improved edge compute support, Container Storage Interface (CSI) general availability, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Language Models Perform Reasoning via Chain of Thought]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/language-models-perform-reasoning-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/language-models-perform-reasoning-via.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jason Wei and Denny Zhou, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain team 
In recent years, scaling up the size of language models has been shown to be a reliable way to improve performance on a range of natural language processing (NLP) tasks. Today’s language models at the scale of 100B or more parameters achieve strong performance on tasks like sentiment analysis and machine translation, even with little or no training examples. Even the largest language models, however, can still struggle with certain multi-step reasoning tasks, such as math word problems and commonsense reasoning. How might we enable language models to perform such reasoning tasks? 
In “Chain of Thought Prompting Elicits Reasoning in Large Language Models,” we explore a prompting method for improving the re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Zero-Resource Machine Translation to Support New Languages in Google Translate]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/24-new-languages-google-translate.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/24-new-languages-google-translate.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:07:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Isaac Caswell and Ankur Bapna, Research Scientists, Google Translate  
Machine translation (MT) technology has made significant advances in recent years, as deep learning has been integrated with natural language processing (NLP). Performance on research benchmarks like WMT have soared, and translation services have improved in quality and expanded to include new languages. Nevertheless, while existing translation services cover languages spoken by the majority of people world wide, they only include around 100 languages in total, just over 1% of those actively spoken globally. Moreover, the languages that are currently represented are overwhelmingly European, largely overlooking regions of high linguistic diversity, like Africa and the Americas. 
 There are two key bottlenecks t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 Now Supports NitroTPM and UEFI Secure Boot]]></title>
        <id>43dd6308bbff890b8b4acc020ae36428fe8fba36</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-now-supports-nitrotpm-and-uefi-secure-boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In computing, Trusted Platform Module (TPM) technology is designed to provide hardware-based, security-related functions. A TPM chip is a secure crypto-processor that is designed to carry out cryptographic operations. There are three key advantages of using TPM technology. First, you can generate, store, and control access to encryption keys outside of the operating system. Second, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第209話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270296674344129439</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270296674344129439"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe Is Back: Join Us in Amsterdam or Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years as a fully digital event, HashiConf Europe will once again return to Amsterdam on 20-22 June 2022. Here’s what you can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>