<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-03-12T01:10:56.910Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-03-12T01:10:56.910Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault, Boundary, and Zero Trust Videos from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-boundary-and-zero-trust-videos-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-boundary-and-zero-trust-videos-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several of this year’s HashiTalks showcased useful strategies and use cases for HashiCorp Vault and Boundary. Watch the videos here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and AWS: Get the most value from your data sets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-get-the-most-value-from-your-data-sets</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-get-the-most-value-from-your-data-sets"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic has achieved AWS Data and Analytics ISV Competency Partner status by working with AWS to build a performant Elastic Cloud platform that simplifies how you collect, analyze, secure, and scale data across your AWS data sets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uday Theepireddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and AWS: Get the most value from your data sets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-get-the-most-value-from-your-data-sets</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-get-the-most-value-from-your-data-sets"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic is excited to announce that we have achieved Amazon Web Services (AWS) Data and Analytics ISV Competency partner status. Elastic has worked with AWS to help customers to collect, store, govern, and analyze their AWS data at any scale. Leveraging the power of Elastic Enterprise Search, Observability, and Security solutions, Elastic delivers the resiliency, scalability, and cost-efficiency benefits required for data sets residing in your AWS environment. 
Elastic helps you accelerate results that matter by leveraging data across all your workloads on AWS — whether you are enhancing customer and employee search experiences, keeping mission-critical applications running smoothly, or protecting against cyber threats.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt70d04…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uday Theepireddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start with someone else’s work]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=32252</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/685797766/0/sethsblog~Start-with-someone-elses-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T09:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A simple approach to learning how to solicit and receive feedback: Begin by showing a well-meaning peer someone else’s novel, painting, design or business plan… You might discover that when you show it to a friend (“here’s a chapter from a novel I’m writing” or “Here’s the logo my firm is considering”) you get harsh, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[False Dichotomy]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2592/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2592/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/false_dichotomy.png" title="There are two types of dichotomy: False dichotomies, true dichotomies, and surprise trichotomies." alt="There are two types of dichotomy: False dichotomies, true dichotomies, and surprise trichotomies." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 X2idn and X2iedn Instances for Memory-Intensive Workloads with Higher Network Bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>f702f965974bf29a23cdde80bb0f3dacddcfcbc5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-x2idn-and-x2iedn-instances-for-memory-intensive-workloads-with-higher-network-bandwidth/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T21:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2016, we launched Amazon EC2 X1 instances designed for large-scale and in-memory applications in the cloud. The price per GiB of RAM for X1 instances is among the lowest. X1 instances are ideal for high performance computing (HPC) applications and running in-memory databases like SAP HANA and big data processing engines such as Apache […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved management for GitHub Enterprise owners]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-10-improved-management-github-enterprise-owners/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-10-improved-management-github-enterprise-owners/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T18:36:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've introduced several new features to help enterprise owners more easily manage their accounts, including two features now in public beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul and Chaos Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-and-chaos-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-and-chaos-engineering"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn more about how HashiCorp Consul can help improve application resiliency, and how to test whether it’s working with chaos engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft Azure Developer Advocate Mark Heckler]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/10/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-azure-developer-advocate-mark-heckler</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/10/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-azure-developer-advocate-mark-heckler"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to former fellow Spring Developer Advocate at Tanzu, and current Java Developer Advocate at Microsoft, friend, ally, and altogether amazing human being, Mark Heckler (@mkheck).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spell Checker for Code in IntelliJ IDEA]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=writerside&amp;p=230479</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/writerside/2022/03/spell-checker-for-code-in-intellij-idea/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T11:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One day you write some code, commit, push, and then receive a comment on the pull request: “Looks good. Oh, but you misspelled this word in a class name”. Now you have to change the pull request just because of the typo. Annoying and time-consuming, isn’t it? How IntelliJ IDEA spellchecks code IntelliJ IDEA understands […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Svetlana Novikova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the hook]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=39509</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/685612514/0/sethsblog~On-the-hook/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T09:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s scary. That’s the point. Pick a date certain. You’re on the hook. Describe a particular type of client, or even choose one by name. Be really clear about the change you seek to make. Put your name on it. Charge a fair price. Assert that you’ve got something to say. Know what you are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – March 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=233189</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/03/java-annotated-monthly-march-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T09:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the March edition of Java Annotated – our monthly collection of the latest JVM-related news and updates. Java News High-Performance Java Persistence Newsletter, Issue 36 – Vlad Mihalcea’s latest newsletter provides links to articles, videos, workshops, and Stack Overflow answers for Java developers interacting with a database system. JDK 18 and JDK 19: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ida Bzowska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Steps for automating Elastic workload migration from on-prem to Elastic on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/10-steps-for-automating-elastic-workload-migration-from-on-prem-to-elastic-on-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/10-steps-for-automating-elastic-workload-migration-from-on-prem-to-elastic-on-aws"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline your Elastic on-premises migration to AWS with a proven methodology and simple steps to success. Take advantage of everything that the cloud has to offer — scalability, affordability, and simplicity with Elastic on AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uday Theepireddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight On: Ankitaa Bhowmick | More Flexibility Means More Time for Family]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/spotlight-on-ankitaa-bhowmick-more-flexibility-means-more-time-for-family</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/spotlight-on-ankitaa-bhowmick-more-flexibility-means-more-time-for-family"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The distributed, flexible work environment is a favorite among Elasticians. Here, we talk with Ankitaa Bhowmick, a Solutions Architect in our EMEA region about Elastic’s culture and how being flexible at work has allowed her to be more present at home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Steps for automating Elastic workload migration from on-prem to Elastic on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/10-steps-for-automating-elastic-workload-migration-from-on-prem-to-elastic-on-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/10-steps-for-automating-elastic-workload-migration-from-on-prem-to-elastic-on-aws"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Are you ready to migrate your self-managed Elastic workloads to Elastic on Amazon Web Services (AWS) to leverage cost, time and scale efficiencies? Take advantage of the best practices and tools we developed with AWS to ensure your fast and smooth transition. Let’s run through your self-service migration path options, then go over the simple “how-to” steps to automate your migration.
Choose your path 
The three main options to add your on-premises data sets to Elastic in your AWS environment are data re-ingestion, snapshot and restore, and reindexing from a cluster.
1. If your data source (applications, databases and infrastructure) is also going to be migrated to AWS, then the data can then be re-ingested into Elastic from your source. Elastic provides integrations with popular AWS serv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uday Theepireddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight On: Ankitaa Bhowmick | More Flexibility Means More Time for Family]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/spotlight-on-ankitaa-bhowmick-more-flexibility-means-more-time-for-family</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/spotlight-on-ankitaa-bhowmick-more-flexibility-means-more-time-for-family"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Flexibility is more than just a buzzword. It’s now as much of a necessity for companies as it is for the people they employ. And while many companies have been trying to find ways to pivot policies to become more accommodating of the shift to remote work, here at Elastic, being flexible and distributed has been part of our source code from the start. 
For Ankitaa Bhowmick, a Solutions Architect in Elastic’s EMEA region, that flexibility means more time for family. 
We asked her about why she works for Elastic in this month’s employee spotlight. 
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt683421b99a8f63a4/622a0a1ab130ac22c454d53e/image1.jpg,image1.jpg,
What do you value most about Elastic’s culture?
Come As You Are, is a tenant of Elastic’s culture that motivates and n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better search can help government serve people when they need it most]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-government-citizens-nlp-elasticsearch-sled</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-government-citizens-nlp-elasticsearch-sled"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T23:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From enhancing website, workplace, and application search and data sharing to keeping websites performant, Elastic stands ready to support government leaders improve digital customer experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzzanna Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better search can help government serve people when they need it most]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-government-citizens-nlp-elasticsearch-sled</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-government-citizens-nlp-elasticsearch-sled"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T23:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As citizens, we interact with the government at various points in our lives. Many interactions serve as important rites of passage like obtaining a marriage or business license, claiming a new dependent on a tax return, or filing for retirement benefits. Other interactions serve as a safety net like obtaining financial assistance after a disaster or reporting a scam attempt. No matter the reason for transacting with the government, citizens want the interaction to be as frictionless as possible.
Deloitte characterizes frictionless as a way of accessing a service with little to no effort on the part of the consumer – there are no hoops to jump through, no demands for information, no frustrating barriers. The US federal government, for example, in its Executive Order on Transforming Federa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzzanna Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Community Summit 2022: Dedicated to Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45372</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/camunda-community-summit-2022-dedicated-to-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Expert Sessions agenda is now live for you to preview. Join us on April 26 - 28 for our virtual, interactive conference.
The post Camunda Community Summit 2022: Dedicated to Developers appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Thengvall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Airline Tail Assignments for Cleaner Skies]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/optimizing-airline-tail-assignments-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/optimizing-airline-tail-assignments-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T18:52:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Emily Masten, Software Engineer, Google Research, Operations Research Team  
Airlines around the world are exploring several tactics to meet aggressive CO2 commitments set by the International Civil Aviation Organization (ICAO). This effort has been emphasized in Europe, where aviation accounts for 13.9% of the transportation industry’s carbon emissions. The largest push comes from the European Green Deal, which aims to decrease carbon emissions from transportation by 90% by 2051. The Lufthansa Group has gone even further, committing to a 50% reduction in emissions compared to 2019 by the year 2030 and to reach net-zero emissions by 2050.  
 One unexpected approach that airlines can use to lower carbon emissions is through optimizing their tail assignment, i.e., how to assign air…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[User Story Videos from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/user-story-videos-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/user-story-videos-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insightful case-study sessions were plentiful at this year’s HashiTalks. Check them out in these user-story video highlights from the virtual conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Spring Cloud Alibaba 2021.0.1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/09/introducing-spring-cloud-alibaba-2021-0-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/09/introducing-spring-cloud-alibaba-2021-0-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T15:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Today, we are excited to announce the availability of Spring Cloud Alibaba 2021.0.1.0!
Spring Cloud Alibaba provides a one-stop solution for distributed application development. It contains all the components required to develop distributed applications, making it easy for you to develop your applications using Spring Cloud. With Spring Cloud Alibaba, you need only add some annotations and a small amount of configuration to connect Spring Cloud applications to the distributed solutions of Alibaba and build a distributed application system with Alibaba middleware.

NOTE: The Spring Cloud Alibaba project is a community project maintained by Alibaba.
​
Introducing Spring Cloud Alibaba 2021.0.1.0

Spring Cloud 2021.0.1 and Spring Boot 2.6.3. Major upgrades have been made to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第205話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496802660149</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496802660149"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible cookie: Magic in the middle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-ansible-cookie-magic-in-the-middle</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-ansible-cookie-magic-in-the-middle"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Ansible Automation Platform was compared to the crunchy goodness of a cookie, private automation hub would be the sweet center bringing it all together and making your mouth water!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Product Updates in February 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=233306</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2022/03/09/space-product-updates-in-february-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T09:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you miss any of the latest Space product updates?  To help you to catch up, we’ve compiled a list of the features released in Space in February 2022, along with explanations of how to use them. Read through this blog post to learn about what was added to Space last month.  Issues Sub-items in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgenia Verbina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calculating the last minute]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42439</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/685373859/0/sethsblog~Calculating-the-last-minute/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T09:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It probably doesn’t pay to buy your prom dress when you are 12 years old. You’re not sure of the size, not sure of what styles will be like and not even sure you want to go. On the other hand, filing your taxes an hour before the deadline is a risk that doesn’t really […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Hilla, an amazing new web framework from Vaadin]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/09/spring-tips-hilla-an-amazing-new-web-framework-from-vaadin</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/09/spring-tips-hilla-an-amazing-new-web-framework-from-vaadin"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of Spring Tips! In this installment we’ll look at the new frontend/backend web framework from the fine folks at Vaadin: Hilla! 

code is available at github.com/spring-tips/vaadin-hilla]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Elastic Cloud is the best way to use Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-use-elastic-cloud-work-free-computing-kubernetes-enterprise-storage-server-solutions-pricing</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-use-elastic-cloud-work-free-computing-kubernetes-enterprise-storage-server-solutions-pricing"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T01:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Elastic, we believe that the best way to use our products and solutions is on the cloud. Here's why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Elastic Cloud is the best way to use Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-use-elastic-cloud-work-free-computing-kubernetes-enterprise-storage-server-solutions-pricing</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-use-elastic-cloud-work-free-computing-kubernetes-enterprise-storage-server-solutions-pricing"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T01:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Welcome to Elastic’s cloud information and resource hub. Here you’ll find the latest and most important information about Elastic Cloud.
At Elastic, we believe that the best way to use our products and solutions is on the cloud. If you’re already convinced and can’t wait to get started, start your free trial on Elastic Cloud right now.
Before we dive in, if you’re trying to understand how cloud computing in general can help you unlock the potential of your business through data, start with this primer: The data-driven organization is within reach — if CIOs can tap the power of cloud.
What Elastic Cloud offers your organization
Fastest time to value

Elastic Cloud lets you get up and running in minutes, globally. Learn more about how our solutions work across our partners: Amazon Web Serv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qua]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2591/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2591/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/qua.png" title="Qua qua qua is the sine qua non of sine qua non qua sine qua non." alt="Qua qua qua is the sine qua non of sine qua non qua sine qua non." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate app development and defend against novel attacks with Elastic 8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With more data source integrations, new prebuilt detections, faster indexing speeds, reduced data storage requirements, and enhanced ad hoc analytics capabilities — Elastic 8.1 is here to help the world’s leading organizations search, solve, and succeed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Courcy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate app development and defend against novel attacks with Elastic 8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today, we are pleased to announce the latest iteration of the world’s leading platform for search-powered solutions with the general availability of Elastic 8.1.
Elastic 8.1 enables our customers and community to further accelerate software development lifecycles with deeper visibility into both serverless architectures and CI/CD pipelines. In addition, Elastic 8.1 includes new prebuilt detections, malicious behavior protections, and data source integrations to help organizations more efficiently stop advanced adversaries before they are able to cause harm.
And, across use cases, with each of Elastic’s search-powered solutions built on one stack — the Elastic Stack — users who upgrade to Elastic 8.1 will be able to enjoy 20% faster indexing speeds, 20% lower data storage requirements, an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Courcy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust Graph Neural Networks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/robust-graph-neural-networks.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/robust-graph-neural-networks.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T19:44:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bryan Perozzi, Research Scientist and Qi Zhu, Research Intern, Google Research 
Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) are powerful tools for leveraging graph-structured data in machine learning. Graphs are flexible data structures that can model many different kinds of relationships and have been used in diverse applications like traffic prediction, rumor and fake news detection, modeling disease spread, and understanding why molecules smell. 
 

Graphs can model the relationships between many different types of data, including web pages (left), social connections (center), or molecules (right).

        
As is standard in machine learning (ML), GNNs assume that training samples are selected uniformly at random (i.e., are an independent and identically distributed or “IID” sample). This i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - March 8th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/08/this-week-in-spring-march-8th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/08/this-week-in-spring-march-8th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How’re you doin’? 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Reactive Streams cofounder, former deputy CTO at Lightbend, and legend Viktor Klang

  
Announcing Spring Cloud Stream Applications 2021.1.1 GA Release

  
GraphQL with Spring Boot java

  
Hidden gems in Java 16 and Java 17, from Stream.mapMulti to HexFormat

  
Introducing Spring Native for JHipster: Serverless Full-Stack Made Easy | Okta Developer

  
Mar 10 - Getting Started with Spring Authorization Server

  
Spring Cloud Data Flow 2.10.0-M1 Released

  
Spring Cloud Gateway CVE reports published

  
Spring Cloud Square 0.4.1 has been released

  
Spring Tips: Reliable Database Migrations with Liquibase and Spring Boot

  
I’m proud to stand with Ukraine, and it’s nice to know my company is too: VMware Statement Regarding Ukraine ‑ VMware News and Stories]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.1: Visibility into AWS Lambda, CI/CD pipelines, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Elastic Observability 8.1, development teams can now get enhanced visibility into AWS Lambda and CI/CD build pipelines, and leverage open standards based instrumentation for unified data ingest and analysis across a wide variety of data types.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.1: Visibility into AWS Lambda, CI/CD pipelines, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Technologies such as serverless computing frameworks and CI/CD automation tools help accelerate software development lifecycles (SDLC) to give development teams a competitive edge in the marketplace. Armed with these technologies, teams can deploy and innovate faster and more frequently by automating repetitive tasks and eliminating the need to manage or provision servers.
With Elastic Observability 8.1, DevOps and SRE teams can now leverage even better support for these technologies with the ability to capture application traces from AWS Lambda, ingest OpenTelemetry logs, and collect detailed Jenkins build logs using the OpenTelemetry Collector. 
These new features allow customers to:

Accelerate release cycles with observability for AWS Lambda functions and CI/CD build pipelines
Standa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 70 – Intro to @Azure Stream Analytics with @fleid_bi]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63507</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-70-intro-to-azure-stream-analytics-with-fleid_bi/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T16:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 70 – Intro to @Azure Stream Analytics with @fleid_bi appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 8.1: Enhanced web crawling and SharePoint on-prem connectivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Elastic Enterprise Search 8.1, enhancements to the Elastic web crawler make website content ingestion faster and more flexible than ever with partial crawls and new debugging tools. Plus, a new addition to the Workplace Search prebuilt connector library with SharePoint Server on-prem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud 8.1: Faster indexing, less disk storage, and smarter analytics capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 8.1, Elasticsearch and Kibana help you search, solve, and succeed with 20% faster indexing, a 20% reduction in storage requirements, and new ad-hoc analytics capabilities. Search smarter with new visualizations, Geohexgrid, and more, on Elastic Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar,Adeline Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 8.1: Stop novel attacks in their tracks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of Elastic Security 8.1, enhance defenses against novel attacks like Log4Shell and prevent adversaries from compromising macOS systems. Achieve visibility into host-based network activity, leverage new sources of threat intelligence, collect data from across your enterprise, and more.
Let’s jump in.
Defend in depth against emerging exploits
Log4j protections
Just hours after an unprecedented Log4j vulnerability was publicly announced on December 10, Elastic threat researchers detailed how to defend enterprises with Elastic Security, sharing a Log4j research brief, complete with targeted searches and automated protections. We also buttressed existing attack-agnostic protections with threat-specific detections, streamlining investigation and preparing organizations for futur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 8.1: Enhanced web crawling and SharePoint on-prem connectivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The 8.1 release of Elastic Enterprise Search features faster and more efficient content ingestion with the latest enhancements to the Elastic web crawler, with additional troubleshooting capabilities as well. This release also features the addition of SharePoint Server to our library of prebuilt connectors to enable aggregation of on-premises SharePoint Server content into Elastic for seamless search.
Elastic Enterprise Search is available on Elastic Cloud — the only hosted Elasticsearch offering to include all of the new features in this latest release. Users can also download the Elastic Stack and our cloud orchestration products, Elastic Cloud Enterprise and Elastic Cloud for Kubernetes, for a self-managed experience.
Enhance your crawling experience
Since the general availability of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud 8.1: Faster indexing, less disk storage, and smarter analytics capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Welcome aboard the 8.x journey as we continue to usher in a new era of speed, scale, relevance, and simplicity.
Pack your bags and climb aboard with 8.1, where indexing data is 20% faster and consumes 20% less disk space with doc-value-only fields. Then, map the world in a whole new way with Geohexgrid aggregation and new Elastic Maps features. Plus, discover new perspectives for your data via ad-hoc analytics while experiencing a faster, smaller Elastic Stack. 
Ready to buckle up and get started? We have the links you need:

Try out the new features on Elastic Cloud 
Download the latest versions of Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes
Dig deeper in the release notes: Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud, Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes
See Elasticsearch breaking changes

A new…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar,Adeline Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 8.1: Stop novel attacks in their tracks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Elastic Security 8.1, stop novel attacks in their tracks. Thwart emerging exploits like Log4Shell with malicious behavior protections for every host and new detection rules for centralized alerting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the Bias – Women at AWS Developer Relations]]></title>
        <id>660bac839b3d1f53837ae0f822bfc533a449a9fc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/breaking-the-bias-women-at-aws-developer-relations/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T15:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today for International Women’s Day we’re joined by a special guest writer, Rashmi Nambiar. She’s here to share her conversations with a few other members of the AWS Developer Relations team, talking about their work and experience as women in tech. Enjoy! – The AWS News Blog Team When I was contemplating joining AWS, many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rashmi Nambiar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three problems of healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41569</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/685165698/0/sethsblog~Three-problems-of-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T10:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology/science Resources Information For a long time, we had no clue. We didn’t know about germs or viruses. We thought that ulcers were caused by pastrami sandwiches. We went to the barber for bloodletting and didn’t understand genes or evolution. Technology in medicine, the science of understanding and intervening, has made huge leaps. There are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International Women's Day: HashiCorp Leaders Share Their Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/international-women-s-day-hashicorp-leaders-share-their-stories</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/international-women-s-day-hashicorp-leaders-share-their-stories"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In honor of International Women’s Day, three HashiCorp leaders talk about their inspirations, their challenges, and their hopes for the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0-alpha5 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=44937</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/camunda-automation-platform-7-17-0-alpha5-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0. Check out the improvements featured in this release.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0-alpha5 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.8.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45305</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/camunda-optimize-3-8-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the new features we're introducing to expand on our existing functionality and make the interface more user-friendly.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.8.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.4.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45445</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/camunda-cloud-1-4-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Cloud 1.4.0-alpha2. You can sign up for a free trial now to get started right away.
The post Camunda Cloud 1.4.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.1 EAP4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=232874</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2022/03/rubymine-2022-1-eap4/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T02:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.1 EAP4 is available. Here are the most notable new features: Tests Navigation to shared contexts and examples in RSpec VCS Updated Annotate with Git Blame Git File History: new UI without index Updated Commit Details pane in Git tool window User Experience Run Current File More actions in the Markdown editor toolbar Hidden […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Kudanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Spring Cloud Stream Applications 2021.1.1 GA Release]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/07/announcing-spring-cloud-stream-applications-2021-1-1-ga-release</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/07/announcing-spring-cloud-stream-applications-2021-1-1-ga-release"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T23:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Cloud Stream Applications 2021.1.1 has been released.

This release is based on Spring Boot 2.6.3 and Spring Cloud 2021.0.1 and contains many improvements and bug fixes - check out the release notes for more information.
Stay in touch…

Please continue to engage with us by creating bug reports and feature requests on Github and asking questions on StackOverflow using the spring-cloud-stream or spring-cloud-dataflow tags.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.1 EAP #4 Is Available With Docker Improvements, Kubernetes Updates, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=233193</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/03/07/goland-2022-1-eap-4-is-available-with-docker-improvements-kubernetes-updates-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T22:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.1 EAP #4 is out. You can get the EAP build via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package (for Ubuntu), or from inside GoLand select Check IDE updates for Early Access Program in Preferences / Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System Settings | Updates. Download GoLand 2022.1 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 7, 2022]]></title>
        <id>333419a96f3de40ad13a5947d1445b7bfe0a3156</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-7-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T21:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Hello Again The AWS Week in Review is back! Many years ago, I tried to write a weekly post that captured the most significant AWS activity. This was easy […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer provides automation, collaboration, and security for managing images across multiple clouds. It includes image security and compliance workflows with Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning from Weakly-Labeled Videos via Sub-Concepts]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/learning-from-weakly-labeled-videos-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/learning-from-weakly-labeled-videos-via.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T18:08:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zizhao Zhang and Guanhang Wu, Software Engineers, Google Research, Cloud AI Team  
Video recognition is a core task in computer vision with applications from video content analysis to action recognition. However, training models for video recognition often requires untrimmed videos to be manually annotated, which can be prohibitively time consuming. In order to reduce the effort of collecting videos with annotations, learning visual knowledge from videos with weak labels, i.e., where the annotation is auto-generated without manual intervention, has attracted growing research interest, thanks to the large volume of easily accessible video data. Untrimmed videos, for example, are often acquired by querying with keywords for classes that the video recognition model aims to classify.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate your Ansible Playbooks to Support AWS boto3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-migrate-your-ansible-playbooks-to-support-aws-boto3</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-migrate-your-ansible-playbooks-to-support-aws-boto3"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform is known for automating Linux, Windows and networking infrastructure. While both the community version of Ansible and our enterprise offering, Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, are prominently known for configuration management, this is just a small piece of what you can really achieve with Ansible’s automation. There are many other use-cases that Ansible Automation Platform is great at automating, such as your AWS, Azure or Google public cloud]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Grow a Developer Champion Program]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=43528</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/how-to-build-and-grow-a-developer-champion-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover some of the most important lessons learned to establish and grow your own developer champion program. 
The post How to Build and Grow a Developer Champion Program appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Buchholz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The million-dollar gap]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40598</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/684966191/0/sethsblog~The-milliondollar-gap/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T09:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To make an album of music good enough to make it to the Top 40, it used to cost a million dollars. Now you can do it in your bedroom. To make a commercial for network TV, a minute of footage cost about a million dollars… And that same million was what it would cost […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Tencent Cloud Secrets Engine and Authentication Method in HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-tencent-cloud-secrets-engine-authentication-method-in-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-tencent-cloud-secrets-engine-authentication-method-in-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T05:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tencent Cloud has announced new HashiCorp Vault integrations. See how they are implemented in this guest post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Shouldn't Complain]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2590/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2590/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/i_shouldnt_complain.png" title="Bald-faced hornets are only a 2 on the Schmidt pain index, so I shouldn't complain. The tennis ball ejected from the dryer exhaust vent could have ricocheted off the nest of a much higher-scoring insect before knocking me off the ladder. Really, I'm lucky." alt="Bald-faced hornets are only a 2 on the Schmidt pain index, so I shouldn't complain. The tennis ball ejected from the dryer exhaust vent could have ricocheted off the nest of a much higher-scoring insect before knocking me off the ladder. Really, I'm lucky." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The leap]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41556</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/684844688/0/sethsblog~The-leap/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-06T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marketing makes change happen. And for humans, the change is rarely linear. There’s a moment before and a moment after the decision is made. Some people find the moment thrilling, others are unnerved by it. When a salesperson fails to open the door for the leap, the customer is ill-served. The status quo is powerful […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show us your work]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41560</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/684713343/0/sethsblog~Show-us-your-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-05T08:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a mythology around people with famous resumes. Folks who have worked for brands we’ve heard of and on projects that have been successful. We give the benefit of the doubt to someone who did “app development at Slack” or “sales at Google.” But what this generally means is that they were patient and pretty […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Data Flow 2.10.0-M1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/04/spring-cloud-data-flow-2-10-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/04/spring-cloud-data-flow-2-10-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-05T00:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.10.0-M1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This preview release contains many improvements and bug fixes - check out the release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in 2.10.0-M1


  
Update to Spring Boot 2.6.3 and Spring Cloud 2021.0.0

  
Provide a Carvel package for easy installation into k8s

  
Starting from 2.10, dropping support for mysql database in favour of MariaDB


Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on Stackoverflow or GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.1 EAP #4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=232868</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/03/phpstorm-2022-1-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T17:24:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth build of our Early Access Program for PhpStorm 2022.1 is now available! In this blog post, we’ll take a quick look at the enhanced New Project wizard, support for WebDAV deployment, some additional capabilities for Rsync, and a couple of new inspections. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Monakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Roadmap Q1-Q2 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=232987</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2022/03/04/space-roadmap-q1-q2-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T16:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2021 Retrospective First of all, let us admit that we were maybe a little too bold with our plans last year. Space is a huge platform, including more than ten modules that can each be considered as separate products. We wanted to bring in everything from your feedback and our vision, so you can fully […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerie Andrianova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1 EAP #4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=232722</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/03/webstorm-2022-1-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T14:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1 EAP build #4 is now available. To catch up on all the new features, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. You can also manually download the EAP builds from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Ryabukha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 EAP 4: Docker Improvements, Kubernetes Updates, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=232304</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/03/intellij-idea-2022-1-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T13:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 EAP build is available. This version brings a number of updates to Docker and Kubernetes functionality, along with an enhanced user experience when running and debugging code. You can get the latest build from our website, through the free Toolbox App, or as a snap if you use Ubuntu. Read […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Square 0.4.1 has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/04/spring-cloud-square-0-4-1-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/04/spring-cloud-square-0-4-1-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the 0.4.1 release of Spring Cloud Square is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 0.4.1 release notes for more information.

This is primarily a bug fix release.
Notable changes in 0.4.1:


  
Support for configuring custom WebClient.Builder beans for non-load-balanced scenarios (#44)


The documentation for this release can be found here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Interactive Reports to Datalore!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=232624</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2022/03/04/introducing-interactive-reports-to-datalore/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T11:06:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings from the Datalore team! We talk and write a lot about sharing in Datalore as we truly believe in the collaborative nature of data workflows.  When you get stuck on a piece of code, you can ask for help in real time by sharing your notebook with an Edit access link with your colleagues. When […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools Plugin v2022.2 Is Out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=232033</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/03/04/edutools-plugin-v2022-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T10:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools plugin v2022.2 introduces PHP support and customizable headers in multiple-choice tasks for course creators, the option to register for Codeforces contests from the IDE, and more. Install EduTools Plugin For course creators PHP support Now you can use the EduTools plugin to create PHP courses. To get started, install the EduTools plugin for PhpStorm, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wayfinding]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41576</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/684575988/0/sethsblog~Wayfinding/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T09:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The map might be correct, but that doesn’t mean it will work. The sign might be legal, but that doesn’t mean it’s going to be effective. We’re surrounded by instruction manuals, videos, announcements and all sorts of other forms of instruction. But a map only works if it helps. Finding our way, getting the job […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outlet Denier]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2589/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2589/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/outlet_denier.png" title="There are regularly placed bumps on the underside just the right size to press the rocker switch on the power strip." alt="There are regularly placed bumps on the underside just the right size to press the rocker switch on the power strip." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRILLsson: Small, Universal Speech Representations for Paralinguistic Tasks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/trillsson-small-universal-speech.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/trillsson-small-universal-speech.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T20:39:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Joel Shor, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research   
In recent years, we have seen dramatic improvements on lexical tasks such as automatic speech recognition (ASR). However, machine systems still struggle to understand paralinguistic aspects — such as tone, emotion, whether a speaker is wearing a mask, etc. Understanding these aspects represents one of the remaining difficult problems in machine hearing. In addition, state-of-the-art results often come from ultra-large models trained on private data, making them impractical to run on mobile devices or to release publicly.  
 In “Universal Paralinguistic Speech Representations Using Self-Supervised Conformers”, to appear in ICASSP 2022, we introduce CAP12— the 12th layer of a 600M parameter model trained on the YT-U training da…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Reactive Streams cofounder, former deputy CTO at Lightbend, and legend Viktor Klang]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/03/a-bootiful-podcast-reactive-streams-cofounder-former-deputy-cto-at-lightbend-and-legend-viktor-klang</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/03/a-bootiful-podcast-reactive-streams-cofounder-former-deputy-cto-at-lightbend-and-legend-viktor-klang"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to former Akka lead and deputy CTO at Lightbend, engineering director at Sinch, Reactive Streams cofounder, the one and only legendary Viktor Klang (@viktorklang)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outsourcing]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41554</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/684473448/0/sethsblog~Outsourcing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T10:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I’d like corn for dinner.” So, six months ago, you’ll need to plant the corn so you can harvest it today and cook it tonight. Or you can drive to the farmer’s market this morning, buy a few ears and have it tonight. Or you can walk over to the supermarket and get a can. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s New Vault Operations Pro Certification Is Lab-Based]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-s-new-vault-operations-pro-certification-is-lab-based</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-s-new-vault-operations-pro-certification-is-lab-based"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s first lab-based certification exam lets Vault professionals vet their knowledge of configuring, managing, and monitoring a production Vault environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: February 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-02-github-availability-report-february-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-02-github-availability-report-february-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T23:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In February, we experienced one incident resulting in significant impact to multiple GitHub services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon RDS for MySQL & PostgreSQL Multi-AZ Deployment Option: Improved Write Performance & Faster Failover]]></title>
        <id>1c237e54f743e5cabb1a58c19142452eba8836da</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-rds-multi-az-db-cluster/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T22:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing a new Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS) Multi-AZ deployment option with up to 2x faster transaction commit latency, automated failovers typically under 35 seconds, and readable standby instances. Amazon RDS offers two replication options to enhance availability and performance: Multi-AZ deployments gives high availability and automatic failover. Amazon RDS creates a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our response to the war in Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-02-our-response-to-the-war-in-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-02-our-response-to-the-war-in-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T21:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the global response to the tragedies in Ukraine and other impacted regions continues to evolve, I wanted to share with our community an expansion of the message that I shared earlier this week with our Hubbers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Deep Learning to Annotate the Protein Universe]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/using-deep-learning-to-annotate-protein.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/using-deep-learning-to-annotate-protein.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T20:16:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Maxwell Bileschi, Staff Software Engineer and Lucy Colwell, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team  
Proteins are essential molecules found in all living things. They play a central role in our bodies’ structure and function, and they are also featured in many products that we encounter every day, from medications to household items like laundry detergent. Each protein is a chain of amino acid building blocks, and just as an image may include multiple objects, like a dog and a cat, a protein may also have multiple components, which are called protein domains. Understanding the relationship between a protein’s amino acid sequence — for example, its domains — and its structure or function are long-standing challenges with far-reaching scientific implications. 

  
An examp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responding to the Russian Invasion of Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=44995</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/responding-to-the-russian-invasion-of-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are shocked and saddened by the Russian invasion of Ukraine. We join the many individuals and companies supporting them, with our own contributions.
The post Responding to the Russian Invasion of Ukraine appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forecasting and tracking the ROI of automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/forecast-track-measure-roi-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/forecast-track-measure-roi-automation"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great ideas start with coffee, but business innovation starts with automation. Just like that morning jolt of warm friendly caffeine, Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform has the ability to enhance, optimize and make your technology stack flow like the beloved beverage most of the world consumes on a daily basis.
 
It is easy to discuss all the technical benefits that Ansible Automation Platform can bring to organizations, but what about the business benefits? How can you observe the state of your automation and return on investment (ROI)? How can you explain the financial impact of automation to key stakeholders? The answer to all of these questions is Red Hat Insights for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform.
 
Red Hat Insights is an analytics platform to help you understand your automation efforts. It lets your data work for you by proactively identifying and correcting issues. Included as a hosted service offering with Ansible Automation Platform, Insights provides a visual dashboard to indicate automation performance, health notifications, organizational statistics, and more.
 
The most relevant features within Insights for IT business leaders and decision makers  who want to validate their automation strategy are Reports, Savings Planner and Automation Calculator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.1 EAP4: Debugger Enhancements, CUDA-GDB, and Valgrind with Docker Toolchain]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=232368</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/03/clion-2022-1-eap4-cuda-debugger/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T12:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CLion 2022.1 EAP build, 221.4906.7, is now available from our website, or via the Toolbox App. Please note that if you are on macOS, there is a separate build for Apple Silicon (M1 chip). Those of you already using EAP3 can apply a patch to update to EAP4. DOWNLOAD CLION 2022.1 EAP CUDA […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous incremental improvement]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42398</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/684328257/0/sethsblog~Continuous-incremental-improvement/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T09:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who invented the smartphone? Well, certainly Alexander Graham Bell, Antonio Meucci, Hedy Lamarr and Edison and Tesla had something to do with it. And the folks at Fairchild. And Palm and Cisco and General Magic and countless others. When we insist on waiting until it’s done before we share it, we walk away from the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Reliable Database Migrations with Liquibase and Spring Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/02/spring-tips-reliable-database-migrations-with-liquibase-and-spring-boot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/02/spring-tips-reliable-database-migrations-with-liquibase-and-spring-boot"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, we look at database migrations with the very popular Liquibase database migration library and how you can use it in the context of a Spring Boot application (and in a GraalVM native image)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Video Highlights from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-video-highlights-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-video-highlights-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were many popular Kubernetes sessions at this year’s HashiTalks. Watch the highlights from the virtual conference here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Co-training Transformer with Videos and Images Improves Action Recognition]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/co-training-transformer-with-videos-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/co-training-transformer-with-videos-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bowen Zhang, Student Researcher and Jiahui Yu, Senior Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team   
Action recognition has become a major focus area for the research community because many applications can benefit from improved modeling, such as video retrieval, video captioning, video question-answering, etc. Transformer-based approaches have recently demonstrated state-of-the-art performance on several benchmarks. While Transformer models require data to learn better visual priors compared to ConvNets, action recognition datasets are relatively small in scale. Large Transformer models are typically first trained on image datasets and later fine-tuned on a target action recognition dataset. 
 While the current pre-training and fine-tuning action recognition paradigm is stra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - March 1st, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/01/this-week-in-spring-march-1st-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/01/this-week-in-spring-march-1st-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We’ve got a lot to cover this week so let’s get right into it!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: InfoQ editor and Java Champion, Dr. Alex Blewitt

  
Advanced Spring: Spring Boot Actuator Online Class

  
GraphQL with Spring Boot java

  
Leverage Java 17 New Features to Create Your Wordle Checker - JEP Café #10

  
We’ve just released Micrometer 1.7.9, 1.8.3, 1.9.0-M3, 2.0.0-M2, Micrometer Tracing 1.0.0-M2, and Micrometer Docs Generator 1.0.0-M1 

  
Spring Boot 2.5.10 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.6.4 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.7.0-M2 available now

  
Spring Cloud Gateway CVE reports published

  
Spring Native 0.11.3 available now

  
Spring Session 2021.0.5 and 2021.1.2 released

  
Spring Shell 2.1.0-M3 is now available

  
Spring Tips: easy IOT integration with HiveMQ, Spring Integration MQTT, and Spring Native

  
toedter/spring-hateoas-jsonapi: A JSON:API media type implementation for Spring HATEOAS has a new release!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Gateway CVE reports published]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/01/spring-cloud-gateway-cve-reports-published</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/01/spring-cloud-gateway-cve-reports-published"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T17:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two vulnerabilities in Spring Cloud Gateway have been identified and fixed. Versions 3.1.1 and 3.0.7 were released to address the vulnerabilities. Please see the CVE reports below for specific upgrade and mitigation instructions:


  
CVE-2022-22947: Spring Cloud Gateway Code Injection Vulnerability

  
CVE-2022-22946: Spring Cloud Gateway HTTP2 Insecure TrustManager


Spring Cloud users should upgrade to 2021.0.1 (which includes 3.1.1) or for 2020.0.x users should upgrade Spring Cloud Gateway to 3.0.7.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 69 – What’s New In @AzureStaticApps with @simona_cotin and @nthonyChu]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63503</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-69-whats-new-in-azurestaticapps-with-simona_cotin-and-nthonychu/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T16:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 69 – What’s New In @AzureStaticApps with @simona_cotin and @nthonyChu appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Customer Carbon Footprint Tool]]></title>
        <id>d83dde763cc072586117e0edc83562050f1ab1a2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-customer-carbon-footprint-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T08:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carbon is the fourth-most abundant element in the universe, and is also a primary component of all known life on Earth. When combined with oxygen it creates carbon dioxide (CO2). Many industrial activities, including the burning of fossil fuels such as coal and oil, release CO2 into the atmosphere and cause climate change. As part […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Native 0.11.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/01/spring-native-0-11-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/01/spring-native-0-11-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Native 0.11.3 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release.

This release includes 25 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades with GraalVM 22.0, Spring Boot 2.6.4 and Spring Cloud 2021.0.1. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a New Modeler for Camunda Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=44946</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/introducing-a-new-modeler-for-camunda-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn all that's featured in the release of Camunda Web Modeler, a new modeling tool that's part of Camunda Cloud.  
The post Introducing a New Modeler for Camunda Cloud appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annie Talvasto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Developers and Operators, All Paths Lead to Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/for-developers-and-operators-all-paths-lead-to-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/for-developers-and-operators-all-paths-lead-to-consul"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how Consul can help you achieve the right DevOps workflow whether you’re a developer or an operator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federated Learning with Formal Differential Privacy Guarantees]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/federated-learning-with-formal.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/federated-learning-with-formal.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T21:55:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brendan McMahan and Abhradeep Thakurta, Research Scientists, Google Research 
In 2017, Google introduced federated learning (FL), an approach that enables mobile devices to collaboratively train machine learning (ML) models while keeping the raw training data on each user's device, decoupling the ability to do ML from the need to store the data in the cloud. Since its introduction, Google has continued to actively engage in FL research and deployed FL to power many features in Gboard, including next word prediction, emoji suggestion and out-of-vocabulary word discovery. Federated learning is improving the “Hey Google” detection models in Assistant, suggesting replies in Google Messages, predicting text selections, and more. 
While FL allows ML without raw data collection, differe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let Your IPv6-only Workloads Connect to IPv4 Services]]></title>
        <id>e1b359af295167726a228a6bd6d6b6af7809afec</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/let-your-ipv6-only-workloads-connect-to-ipv4-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T21:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing two new capabilities for Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) NAT gateway and Amazon Route 53, allowing your IPv6-only workloads to transparently communicate with IPV4-only services. Curious? Read on; I have details for you. Some of you are running very large workloads involving tens of thousands of virtual machines, containers, or micro-services. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constrained Reweighting for Training Deep Neural Nets with Noisy Labels]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/constrained-reweighting-for-training.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/constrained-reweighting-for-training.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Abhishek Kumar and Ehsan Amid, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Over the past several years, deep neural networks (DNNs) have been quite successful in driving impressive performance gains in several real-world applications, from image recognition to genomics. However, modern DNNs often have far more trainable model parameters than the number of training examples and the resulting overparameterized networks can easily overfit to noisy or corrupted labels (i.e., examples that are assigned a wrong class label). As a consequence, training with noisy labels often leads to degradation in accuracy of the trained model on clean test data. Unfortunately, noisy labels can appear in several real-world scenarios due to multiple factors, such as errors and inconsistencies in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Improvements in Automation Controller 4.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/performance-improvements-in-automation-controller-4.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/performance-improvements-in-automation-controller-4.1"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 is the next generation automation platform from Red Hat’s trusted enterprise technology experts. With the release of Ansible Automation Platform 2.1, users now have access to the latest control plane – automation controller 4.1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving Consistency without Transaction Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=44607</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/achieving-consistency-without-transaction-managers/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to learn how to integrate multiple components without the help of ACID transaction managers? We'll teach you.
The post Achieving Consistency without Transaction Managers appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observability, CTS & Nomad Video Highlights from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/observability-cts-nomad-video-highlights-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/observability-cts-nomad-video-highlights-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Observability, Consul-Terraform-Sync use cases, and deep-level Nomad explorations were popular at this year’s HashiTalks. Watch our highlighted videos from the virtual event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul-Terraform-Sync 0.5 Adds New APIs and UX Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-terraform-sync-0-5-adds-new-apis-and-ux-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-terraform-sync-0-5-adds-new-apis-and-ux-improvements"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul-Terraform-Sync (CTS) 0.5 adds improvements to task lifecycle management and new ecosystem integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Voices: How the Blacksmiths ERG Supports the Community]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-voices-how-the-blacksmiths-erg-supports-the-community</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-voices-how-the-blacksmiths-erg-supports-the-community"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three members of HashiCorp’s Blacksmiths ERG talk about the outside projects they’re working on to support their communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Additional Checksum Algorithms for Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>c087e4b8f683c9847a7242660d3729c6a4fb3a22</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-additional-checksum-algorithms-for-amazon-s3/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T16:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) is designed to provide 99.999999999% (11 9s) of durability for your objects and for the metadata associated with your objects. You can rest assured that S3 stores exactly what you PUT, and returns exactly what is stored when you GET. In order to make sure that the object is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.0-M3 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/25/spring-shell-2-1-0-m3-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/25/spring-shell-2-1-0-m3-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T14:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.0-M3 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

Notable changes include:


  
Usual small fixes

  
UI Component model




Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.25.02 are here!]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63512</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-azuredevops-community-for-2022-25-02/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T13:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! I am April Edwards and every week I try to bring you the latest updates from around the DevOps on Azure community. If you have a post you’d like to have me include, I am always listening. You can reach out on Twitter or LinkedIn and I will be sure to share your latest post with the community.
The post Top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.25.02 are here! appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: InfoQ editor and Java Champion, Dr. Alex Blewitt]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/a-bootiful-podcast-infoq-editor-and-java-champion-dr-alex-blewitt</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/a-bootiful-podcast-infoq-editor-and-java-champion-dr-alex-blewitt"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to InfoQ editor and contributor, fellow Java Champion, and an all-around amazing human being Dr. Alex Blewitt.


  
the creator of bash, readline, etc.: Brian Fox

  
Reload4j is the version which has Log4j 1.x compatibility with CVEs fixed 

  
Alex’s blog  and speaker deck

  
Magic number (programming) - Wikipedia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-7-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-7-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T21:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0-M2 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 137 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Test slices for Couchbase and Elasticsearch

  
Enhancements to auto-configuration registration and ordering

  
Support for OkHttp4


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests. 
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Consul API Gateway has now reached its first GA release, adding TCPRoute support, Helm chart support, and a new HashiCorp Learn tutorial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce Provider for HashiCorp Terraform Now in Tech Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/salesforce-provider-for-hashicorp-terraform-now-in-tech-preview</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/salesforce-provider-for-hashicorp-terraform-now-in-tech-preview"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Salesforce users, roles, and profiles with HashiCorp Terraform using the new Salesforce provider — now in tech preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s in Your Hyperautomation Tech Stack?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=41879</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/whats-in-your-hyperautomation-tech-stack/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As much as we’d all like to operate at the automation levels of an organization like Amazon, most organizations are relatively early in their process automation maturity journey. That’s where a universal process orchestrator like the Camunda Platform comes in.
The post What’s in Your Hyperautomation Tech Stack? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.4 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-6-4-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-6-4-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.4 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 61 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.10 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-5-10-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-5-10-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T11:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.10 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 52 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 4.3.5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-batch-4-3-5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-batch-4-3-5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T21:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 4.3.5 has been released to Maven Central repository. This patch release comes with a number of bug fixes, enhancements and dependency updates. You can find the complete change logs here: 4.3.5.

I would like to thank all contributors who had a role in this release!

Spring Batch Home | Source on Github | Reference Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4D-Net: Learning Multi-Modal Alignment for 3D and Image Inputs in Time]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/4d-net-learning-multi-modal-alignment.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/4d-net-learning-multi-modal-alignment.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T20:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by AJ Piergiovanni and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research 
While not immediately obvious, all of us experience the world in four dimensions (4D). For example, when walking or driving down the street we observe a stream of visual inputs, snapshots of the 3D world, which, when taken together in time, creates a 4D visual input. Today’s autonomous vehicles and robots are able to capture much of this information through various onboard sensing mechanisms, such as LiDAR and cameras. 
 LiDAR is a ubiquitous sensor that uses light pulses to reliably measure the 3D coordinates of objects in a scene, however, it is also sparse and has a limited range — the farther one is from a sensor, the fewer points will be returned. This means that far-away objects might only get a hand…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new way to understand your GitHub-hosted runner capacity]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-23-new-way-understand-github-hosted-runner-capacity/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-23-new-way-understand-github-hosted-runner-capacity/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T19:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore and understand your overall GitHub-hosted Actions runner capacity with the new runner view.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codespaces for the largest repositories just got faster]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-23-codespaces-largest-repositories-faster/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-23-codespaces-largest-repositories-faster/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T18:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ability to prebuild codespaces is entering public beta. Enable fast environment creation times, regardless of the size and complexity of your repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 68 – Progressive Delivery with @SplitSoftware and @AzureDevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63499</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-68-progressive-delivery-with-splitsoftware-and-azuredevops/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T16:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 68 – Progressive Delivery with @SplitSoftware and @AzureDevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第204話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496777629727</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496777629727"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge Automation with NetGitOps on Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/edge-automation-with-netgitops-on-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/edge-automation-with-netgitops-on-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network edge automation challenges 
 
As organizations grow and expand geographi cally, they start extending their IT infrastructure into the distributed and far edge layers through opening new branch offices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paulo Seguel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Session 2021.0.5 and 2021.1.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-session-2021-0-5-and-2021-1-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-session-2021-0-5-and-2021-1-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Session 2021.0.5 and 2021.1.2. These releases deliver bug fixes and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot will pick up these artifacts with its upcoming releases.

The following modules were updated as part of 2021.0.5:


  
Spring Session Core 2.5.5 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 2.5.5 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 2.5.5 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 2.5.5 - release notes


The following modules were updated as part of 2021.1.2:


  
Spring Session Core 2.6.2 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 2.6.2 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 2.6.2 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 2.6.2 - release notes

  
Spring Session MongoDB 2.6.2 - release notes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: easy IOT integration with HiveMQ, Spring Integration MQTT, and Spring Native]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-tips-easy-iot-integration-with-hivemq-spring-integration-mqtt-and-spring-native</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-tips-easy-iot-integration-with-hivemq-spring-integration-mqtt-and-spring-native"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment I’m joined by my friend, fellow Java Champion, and Developer Advocate at HiveMQ, Mary Grygleski (@mgrygles), and we look at easy Internet of Things (IOT) integration with HiveMQ, Spring Integration MQTT, Spring Boot, and Spring Native]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Region Replication Now Available with HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multi-region-replication-now-available-with-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multi-region-replication-now-available-with-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New HCP Vault Plus Clusters adds high availability replication of secrets and policies across cloud regions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with ease using security workflows!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-22-get-started-using-security-workflows/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-22-get-started-using-security-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T17:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions workflows in the Security category will now appear among the workflow recommendations based on a repository's content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Glue Code without Java Delegates in Camunda Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=43978</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/how-to-write-glue-code-without-java-delegates-in-camunda-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T17:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the benefits of external tasks in Camunda Cloud and how you can still call your service endpoints via any protocol.
The post How to Write Glue Code without Java Delegates in Camunda Cloud appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Advisory Database now open to community contributions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-22-github-advisory-database-now-open-to-community-contributions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-22-github-advisory-database-now-open-to-community-contributions/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T17:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone can now provide additional information to further the community’s understanding and awareness of security advisories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five ways to get started with network automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/five-ways-to-get-started-with-network-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/five-ways-to-get-started-with-network-automation"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many of you know, Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform is a highly flexible IT automation platform that can automate your Linux and Windows instances, your VMware private cloud, your AWS, Azure or Google public cloud, and even your security infrastructure.  Today I want to write about one of my favorite use-cases; using Ansible Automation Platform for network automation. It provides easy, highly customizable automation for your routers and switches so you can automate them just like any other IT infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 10th Birthday, DynamoDB! 🎉🎂🎁]]></title>
        <id>6a6363a6fd2f05ad00504fbee779ecb0f06a2c82</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-birthday-dynamodb/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T23:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 18th 2012, Jeff and Werner announced the general availability of Amazon DynamoDB, a fully managed flexible NoSQL database service for single-digit millisecond performance at any scale. During the last 10 years, hundreds of thousands of customers have adopted DynamoDB. It regularly reaches new peaks of performance and scalability. For example, during the last […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Security Automation using Cisco Secure Firewall and HashiCorp Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/network-security-automation-using-cisco-secure-firewall-and-hashicorp-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/network-security-automation-using-cisco-secure-firewall-and-hashicorp-consul"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how  Consul-Terraform-Sync can be used to auto-update values of objects in Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust Routing Using Electrical Flows]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/robust-routing-using-electrical-flows.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/robust-routing-using-electrical-flows.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T19:58:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ali Kemal Sinop and Kostas Kollias, Research Scientists, Google Research 
In the world of networks, there are models that can explain observations across a diverse collection of applications. These include simple tasks such as computing the shortest path, which has obvious applications to routing networks but also applies in biology, e.g., where the slime mold Physarum is able to find shortest paths in mazes. Another example is Braess’s paradox — the observation that adding resources to a network can have an effect opposite to the one expected — which manifests not only in road networks but also in mechanical and electrical systems. For instance, constructing a new road can increase traffic congestion or adding a new link in an electrical circuit can increase voltage. Such connec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid Event Notification System at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6deb1d2b57d1</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/rapid-event-notification-system-at-netflix-6deb1d2b57d1?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T15:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post gives an overview of the Rapid Event Notification System at Netflix and shares some of the learnings gained while building it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.02.18]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63477</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-02-18/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T09:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.02.18 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.02.18 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning for Mechanical Ventilation Control]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/machine-learning-for-mechanical.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/machine-learning-for-mechanical.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Daniel Suo, Software Engineer and Elad Hazan, Research Scientist, Google Research, on behalf of the Google AI Princeton Team 
  Mechanical ventilators provide critical support for patients who have difficulty breathing or are unable to breathe on their own. They see frequent use in scenarios ranging from routine anesthesia, to neonatal intensive care and life support during the COVID-19 pandemic. A typical ventilator consists of a compressed air source, valves to control the flow of air into and out of the lungs, and a "respiratory circuit" that connects the ventilator to the patient. In some cases, a sedated patient may be connected to the ventilator via a tube inserted through the trachea to their lungs, a process called invasive ventilation. 


A mechanical ventilator takes br…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HPE, ServiceNow, JFrog Among New Verified Terraform Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hpe-servicenow-jfrog-among-new-verified-terraform-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hpe-servicenow-jfrog-among-new-verified-terraform-providers"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We welcome 15 new verified providers to the growing HashiCorp Terraform ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Balloon Learning Environment]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/the-balloon-learning-environment.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/the-balloon-learning-environment.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T18:11:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Joshua Greaves, Software Engineer and Pablo Samuel Castro, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
Benchmark challenges have been a driving force in the advancement of machine learning (ML). In particular, difficult benchmark environments for reinforcement learning (RL) have been crucial for the rapid progress of the field by challenging researchers to overcome increasingly difficult tasks. The Arcade Learning Environment, Mujoco, and others have been used to push the envelope in RL algorithms, representation learning, exploration, and more.  
 In “Autonomous Navigation of Stratospheric Balloons Using Reinforcement Learning”, published in Nature two years ago, we demonstrated how deep RL can be used to create a high-performing flight agent that can control stratosph…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning finds more vulnerabilities using machine learning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-17-code-scanning-finds-vulnerabilities-using-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-17-code-scanning-finds-vulnerabilities-using-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T18:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we launched new code scanning analysis features powered by machine learning. The experimental analysis finds more of the most common types of vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging machine learning to find security vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-17-leveraging-machine-learning-find-security-vulnerabilities/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-17-leveraging-machine-learning-find-security-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T17:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A behind-the-scenes peek into the machine learning framework powering new code scanning security alerts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make the most out of a mentoring relationship]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-16-how-to-make-the-most-out-of-a-mentoring-relationship/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-16-how-to-make-the-most-out-of-a-mentoring-relationship/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T18:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tips from our developer advocates on how and why to find a mentor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from Python virtual environments to automation execution environments in Ansible Automation Platform 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/migrating-from-python-virtual-environments-to-automation-execution-environments-in-ansible-automation-platform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/migrating-from-python-virtual-environments-to-automation-execution-environments-in-ansible-automation-platform-2"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Tower (included in Ansible Automation Platform 1.x) used Python virtual environments to manage dependencies and implement consistent automation execution across multiple Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform instances. This method of managing dependencies came with its own set of limitations:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good News About the Carbon Footprint of Machine Learning Training]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/good-news-about-carbon-footprint-of.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/good-news-about-carbon-footprint-of.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T20:36:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by David Patterson, Distinguished Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team  
Machine learning (ML) has become prominent in information technology, which has led some to raise concerns about the associated rise in the costs of computation, primarily the carbon footprint, i.e., total greenhouse gas emissions. While these assertions rightfully elevated the discussion around carbon emissions in ML, they also highlight the need for accurate data to assess true carbon footprint, which can help identify strategies to mitigate carbon emission in ML.
 
In “The Carbon Footprint of Machine Learning Training Will Plateau, Then Shrink”, accepted for publication in IEEE Computer, we focus on operational carbon emissions — i.e., the energy cost of operating ML hardware, including data center overhead…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for Amazon CodeGuru Reviewer – Detector Library and Security Detectors for Log-Injection Flaws]]></title>
        <id>4431491871a4ee3d928576163daaa289ff9714db</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-amazon-codeguru-reviewer-detector-library-and-security-detectors-for-log-injection-flaws/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T16:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeGuru Reviewer is a developer tool that detects security vulnerabilities in your code and provides intelligent recommendations to improve code quality. For example, CodeGuru Reviewer introduced Security Detectors for Java and Python code to identify security risks from the top ten Open Web Application Security Project (OWASP) categories and follow security best practices for AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic File System Update – Sub-Millisecond Read Latency]]></title>
        <id>9453612a47b3048c109c3b2d7b4e5054b089e439</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-elastic-file-system-update-sub-millisecond-read-latency/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T22:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) was announced in early 2015 and became generally available in 2016. We launched EFS in order to make it easier for you to build applications that need shared access to file data. EFS is (and always has been) simple and serverless: you simply create a file system, attach it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 C6a Instances Powered By 3rd Gen AMD EPYC Processors for Compute-Intensive Workloads]]></title>
        <id>d0be7f91366e127f0cb3c4144bb5a5b8910d05be</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c6a-instances-powered-by-3rd-gen-amd-epyc-processors-for-compute-intensive-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T21:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2021, we launched Amazon EC2 M6a instances powered by the 3rd Gen AMD EPYC processors, running at frequencies up to 3.6 GHz, which offer customers up to 35 percent improvement in price-performance compared to M5a instances. Many customers are looking for ways to optimize their cloud utilization, and they are taking advantage […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Automation Platform - A video tour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-a-video-tour</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-a-video-tour"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people are familiar with the community version of Ansible, the command line automation tool, but I wanted to elaborate on how our enterprise offering, Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, and how it expands the possibilities of Ansible for our customers in Red Hat's most recent release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An International Scientific Challenge for the Diagnosis and Gleason Grading of Prostate Cancer]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/an-international-scientific-challenge.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/an-international-scientific-challenge.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Po-Hsuan Cameron Chen, Software Engineer, Google Health and Maggie Demkin, Program Manager, Kaggle 
In recent years, machine learning (ML) competitions in health have attracted ML scientists to work together to solve challenging clinical problems. These competitions provide access to relevant data and well-defined problems where experienced data scientists come to compete for solutions and learn new methods. However, a fundamental difficulty in organizing such challenges is obtaining and curating high quality datasets for model development and independent datasets for model evaluation. Importantly, to reduce the risk of bias and to ensure broad applicability of the algorithm, evaluation of the generalisability of resulting algorithms should ideally be performed on multiple indepe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Azure AD Identity with HashiCorp Vault — Part 3: Azure Managed Identity Auth via Azure Auth Method]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/integrating-azure-ad-identity-vault-part-3-azure-managed-identity-via-azure-auth-method</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/integrating-azure-ad-identity-vault-part-3-azure-managed-identity-via-azure-auth-method"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to achieve machine authentication to HashiCorp Vault with the Azure auth method using Microsoft Azure managed identity — and set it up with Terraform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Into Azure Using Pulumi and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63458</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-into-azure-using-pulumi-and-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T14:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week’s episode of The DevOps Lab we have Kat Cosgrove and Matty Stratton from Pulumi joining us!
02:45 –
The post Deploy Into Azure Using Pulumi and GitHub Actions appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.02.11]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63450</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-02-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T10:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.02.11 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.02.11 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guiding Frozen Language Models with Learned Soft Prompts]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/guiding-frozen-language-models-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/guiding-frozen-language-models-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-10T23:22:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brian Lester, AI Resident and Noah Constant, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research 
Large pre-trained language models, which are continuing to grow in size, achieve state-of-art results on many natural language processing (NLP) benchmarks. Since the development of GPT and BERT, standard practice has been to fine-tune models on downstream tasks, which involves adjusting every weight in the network (i.e., model tuning). However, as models become larger, storing and serving a tuned copy of the model for each downstream task becomes impractical. 
 An appealing alternative is to share across all downstream tasks a single frozen pre-trained language model, in which all weights are fixed. In an exciting development, GPT-3 showed convincingly that a frozen model can be conditio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AWS Provider 4.0 Refactors S3 Bucket Resource]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-aws-provider-4-0-refactors-s3-bucket-resource</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-aws-provider-4-0-refactors-s3-bucket-resource"/>
        <updated>2022-02-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.0 of the HashiCorp Terraform AWS provider brings usability improvements to data sources and attribute validations along with a refactored S3 bucket resource.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>