<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-16T00:19:23.860Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-16T00:19:23.860Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advancements in machine learning for machine learning]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/advancements-in-machine-learning-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/advancements-in-machine-learning-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Phitchaya Mangpo Phothilimthana, Staff Research Scientist, Google DeepMind, and Bryan Perozzi, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Research





With the recent and accelerated advances in machine learning (ML), machines can understand natural language, engage in conversations, draw images, create videos and more. Modern ML models are programmed and trained using ML programming frameworks, such as TensorFlow, JAX, PyTorch, among many others. These libraries provide high-level instructions to ML practitioners, such as linear algebra operations (e.g., matrix multiplication, convolution, etc.) and neural network layers (e.g., 2D convolution layers, transformer layers). Importantly, practitioners need not worry about how to make their models run efficiently on hardware because an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[StyleDrop: Text-to-image generation in any style]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/styledrop-text-to-image-generation-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/styledrop-text-to-image-generation-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kihyuk Sohn and Dilip Krishnan, Research Scientists, Google Research




Text-to-image models trained on large volumes of image-text pairs have enabled the creation of rich and diverse images encompassing many genres and themes. Moreover, popular styles such as “anime” or “steampunk”, when added to the input text prompt, may translate to specific visual outputs. While many efforts have been put into prompt engineering, a wide range of styles are simply hard to describe in text form due to the nuances of color schemes, illumination, and other characteristics. As an example, “watercolor painting” may refer to various styles, and using a text prompt that simply says “watercolor painting style” may either result in one specific style or an unpredictable mix of several.
 




When we …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2023.11.1 Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=420077</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/12/teamcity-2023-11-1-is-here/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T14:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first bug-fix update for TeamCity On-Premises 2023.11 is out and available for download. Version 2023.11.1 addresses multiple issues (including limited LDAP synchronization and artifact domain isolation problems) and includes a few security and performance updates. Please refer to our release notes for the complete change list. As with other minor updates, TeamCity 2023.11.1 shares […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitrii Korovin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Portrait of the Average Data Scientist of 2023 in 3 Facts]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=418835</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2023/12/15/a-portrait-of-the-average-data-scientist-of-2023-in-3-facts/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider the average data scientist of 2023: They spend a significant chunk of their time visualizing data, with line and bar plots as their go-to tools. They’ve mastered their craft through independent study and use Jupyter notebooks for in-depth data analysis. Version control is not their strong suit, and when presenting findings, they tend to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signal and noise]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46030</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/851619875/0/sethsblog~Signal-and-noise/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T09:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the signal is very weak and the noise is large, it’s easy to imagine that there’s no signal at all. AI and computers can be used as lenses now, which means we can strip away the noise and see things that we certainly didn’t expect. Dina Katabi at MIT can point a radio antenna […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2023.1.1 and 2023.0.7 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/15/spring-data-2023-1-1-and-2023-0-7-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/15/spring-data-2023-1-1-and-2023-0-7-available"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decemberfest is here! How we celebrate the holidays at Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-decemberfest-elastic-holiday-celebration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-decemberfest-elastic-holiday-celebration"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a peek at how Elasticians around the world are celebrating the holiday season during Decemberfest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decemberfest is here! How we celebrate the holidays at Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-decemberfest-elastic-holiday-celebration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-decemberfest-elastic-holiday-celebration"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
December is here and that means holiday celebrations. At Elastic, we call the season’s celebration Decemberfest. It’s a time for all Elasticians to connect — either at an in-person event or from home. 
We’ve always been distributed by design. To uphold that ethos and to allow everyone to join the festivities, we have many ways for our Elasticians to celebrate the season. 

Decemberfest started in 2020 when the world had to be 100% virtual and has evolved into our flagship holiday celebration running from the end of November to mid-December.
This year, Elasticians have multiple opportunities to join in on the fun. 
In-person events are organized in 48 cities around the world. Our workplace experience team has events planned in cities with Elastic offices. For those who don’t live near an …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Label the States]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2868/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2868/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/label_the_states.png" title="Even with a blank map, a lot of people can only name 45-50 of the 64 states." alt="Even with a blank map, a lot of people can only name 45-50 of the 64 states." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.29: CSI Storage Resizing Authenticated and Generally Available in v1.29]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/csi-node-expand-secret-support-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/csi-node-expand-secret-support-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Humble Chirammal (Vmware), Louis Koo (deeproute.ai)
Kubernetes version v1.29 brings generally available support for authentication
during CSI (Container Storage Interface) storage resize operations.
Let's embark on the evolution of this feature, initially introduced in alpha in
Kubernetes v1.25, and unravel the changes accompanying its transition to GA.
Authenticated CSI storage resizing unveiled
Kubernetes harnesses the capabilities of CSI to seamlessly integrate with third-party
storage systems, empowering your cluster to seamlessly expand storage volumes
managed by the CSI driver. The recent elevation of authentication secret support
for resizes from Beta to GA ushers in new horizons, enabling volume expansion in
scenarios where the underlying storage operation demands credenti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.29: VolumeAttributesClass for Volume Modification]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/kubernetes-1-29-volume-attributes-class/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/kubernetes-1-29-volume-attributes-class/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sunny Song (Google)
The v1.29 release of Kubernetes introduced an alpha feature to support modifying a volume
by changing the volumeAttributesClassName that was specified for a PersistentVolumeClaim (PVC).
With the feature enabled, Kubernetes can handle updates of volume attributes other than capacity.
Allowing volume attributes to be changed without managing it through different
provider's APIs directly simplifies the current flow.
You can read about VolumeAttributesClass usage details in the Kubernetes documentation
or you can read on to learn about why the Kubernetes project is supporting this feature.
VolumeAttributesClass
The new storage.k8s.io/v1alpha1 API group provides two new types:
VolumeAttributesClass
Represents a specification of mutable volume attributes defined by th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitchell reflects as he departs HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mitchell-reflects-as-he-departs-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mitchell-reflects-as-he-departs-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After more than 11 years, HashiCorp Co-Founder Mitchell Hashimoto pens a heartfelt goodbye letter to the company he helped create.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-42793 Vulnerability in TeamCity: December 14, 2023 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=419495</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/12/cve-2023-42793-vulnerability-in-teamcity-december-14-2023-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background On September 6, 2023, a critical TeamCity On-Premises vulnerability issue (CVE identifier CVE-2023-42793) was discovered by the Sonar team. TeamCity Cloud was not affected by this. We subsequently investigated and fixed the issue, providing mitigation steps to our customers on September 18, 2023. Customers could either upgrade to a new version which contained the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yegor Naumov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.29: Cloud Provider Integrations Are Now Separate Components]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/14/cloud-provider-integration-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/14/cloud-provider-integration-changes/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Michael McCune (Red Hat), Andrew Sy Kim (Google)
For Kubernetes v1.29, you need to use additional components to integrate your
Kubernetes cluster with a cloud infrastructure provider. By default, Kubernetes
v1.29 components abort if you try to specify integration with any cloud provider using
one of the legacy compiled-in cloud provider integrations. If you want to use a legacy
integration, you have to opt back in - and a future release will remove even that option.
In 2018, the Kubernetes community agreed to form the Cloud Provider Special
Interest Group (SIG), with a mission to externalize all cloud provider
integrations and remove all the existing in-tree cloud provider integrations.
In January 2019, the Kubernetes community approved the initial draft of
KEP-2395: Removing In-T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to Azure DevOps Demo Generator and Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67966</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/updates-to-azure-devops-demo-generator-and-labs/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that we have published new content to the Azure DevOps Demo Generator and Azure DevOps Labs!
The Azure DevOps Labs is a great tool to help you learn about the integrated features offered in Azure DevOps.
The post Updates to Azure DevOps Demo Generator and Labs appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our First Netflix Data Engineering Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f326b0589102</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/our-first-netflix-data-engineering-summit-f326b0589102?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holden Karau Elizabeth Stone Pedro Duarte Chris Stephens Pallavi Phadnis Lee Woodridge Mark Cho Guil Pires Sujay Jain Tristan Reid…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds on-demand policy evaluation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-on-demand-policy-evaluation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-on-demand-policy-evaluation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-demand policy evaluation improves visibility and control by letting users evaluate the effects of policy changes in Terraform Cloud before they are enforced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kandy: the new Kotlin plotting library by JetBrains]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=418364</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/12/kandy-the-new-kotlin-plotting-library-by-jetbrains/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T15:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to introduce Kandy, a new Kotlin plotting library by JetBrains. It provides a new, powerful DSL for creating charts of various kinds. The first public preview version is ready for you to try, and we welcome any feedback and comments you may have. Kandy Documentation How does it look and feel? Why […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavel Gorgulov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MPS 2022.2.2 Is Ready]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=mps&amp;p=416259</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/mps/2023/12/mps-2022-2-2-has-been-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T15:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For MPS users who are still using version 2022.2, we’ve prepared a bug-fix release with several fixes and updates. It also includes additional features, some new and some that have already been published in other MPS versions. Back-ported from master Ability to copy messages from Model Checker The Model Checker tool window allows you to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaclav Pech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Common Rust Compiler Errors as Encountered in RustRover: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rust&amp;p=418715</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rust/2023/12/14/the-most-common-rust-compiler-errors-as-encountered-in-rustrover-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T15:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust compiler is a picky creature. If it’s unhappy with the source code it’s fed, it can emit more than 400 different errors (with more being added every month!). Some of the errors are extremely rare, while others complicate the lives of Rust developers on a daily basis. In this blog post series, we’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vitaly Bragilevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling vulnerability management across thousands of services and more than 150 million findings]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-14-scaling-vulnerability-management-across-thousands-of-services-and-more-than-150-million-findings/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-14-scaling-vulnerability-management-across-thousands-of-services-and-more-than-150-million-findings/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn about how we run a scalable vulnerability management program built on top of GitHub. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-14-scaling-vulnerability-management-across-thousands-of-services-and-more-than-150-million-findings/">Scaling vulnerability management across thousands of services and more than 150 million findings</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar – Chris Woodruff – Mastering OData: An In-Depth Developer’s Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=406320</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/12/14/webinar-chris-woodruff-mastering-odata-an-in-depth-developers-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T10:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us Tuesday, January 9th, 2024, 3:00 – 4:00 PM UTC (check other timezones) for our free live webinar, Mastering OData: An In-Depth Developer’s Guide, with Software Architect at Real Time Technologies, Chris Woodruff. Register now and get a reminder, or join on YouTube Are you tired of struggling with complex data exchange methods and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight marketing maxims]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48022</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/851485229/0/sethsblog~Eight-marketing-maxims/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trust is worth more than attention. Helping people get to where they seek to go is more effective than hustling people to persuade them to go where you’re going. Choose your customers, choose…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Microcks.io contributors Laurent Broudoux and Yacine-Kheddache]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/14/a-bootiful-podcast-microcks-io-contributors-laurent-broudoux-and-yacine</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/14/a-bootiful-podcast-microcks-io-contributors-laurent-broudoux-and-yacine"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.15 and 6.1.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/14/spring-framework-6-0-15-and-6-1-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/14/spring-framework-6-0-15-and-6-1-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: November 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-13-github-availability-report-november-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-github-availability-report-november-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T20:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In November, we experienced one incident that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-github-availability-report-november-2023/">GitHub Availability Report: November 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buy PyCharm. Support Data Science.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=418559</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/12/support-data-science/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm is joining forces with NumFOCUS to support their year-end fundraising Here at PyCharm, we acknowledge the profound impact of data science in the realm of Python and the importance of projects backed by NumFOCUS for the future of data science and the Python ecosystem. PyCharm Professional stands out with robust support for data science […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roberto Pesce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing our home labs: Frigate code review]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-13-securing-our-home-labs-frigate-code-review/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-securing-our-home-labs-frigate-code-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This blog post describes two linked vulnerabilities found in Frigate, an AI-powered security camera manager, that could have enabled an attacker to silently gain remote code execution.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-securing-our-home-labs-frigate-code-review/">Securing our home labs: Frigate code review</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PKI certificate issuance flexibility with Vault CIEPS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pki-certificate-issuance-flexibility-with-vault-cieps</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pki-certificate-issuance-flexibility-with-vault-cieps"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault Enterprise 1.15 adds an external policy service for issuing PKI certificates. Learn about its benefits and how it compares to existing policies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine: How To Accelerate Project Indexing?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=418307</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2023/12/rubymine-how-to-accelerate-project-indexing/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T16:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! We’re excited to share more tips and tricks to enhance your RubyMine experience. In September, our team attended the Euruko 2023 conference, where RubyMine developer Maxat Mansurov delivered a fascinating talk on project indexing. Indexing is a process that involves forming indexes to enable the quick retrieval of information. Although beneficial, this procedure […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Zykova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Default setup now includes scheduled scans and supports all languages covered by CodeQL]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-13-default-setup-now-includes-scheduled-scans-and-supports-all-languages-covered-by-codeql/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-default-setup-now-includes-scheduled-scans-and-supports-all-languages-covered-by-codeql/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T16:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We’ve added new improvements to default setup, including automatically scheduling scans on repositories and support for all CodeQL covered languages.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-default-setup-now-includes-scheduled-scans-and-supports-all-languages-covered-by-codeql/">Default setup now includes scheduled scans and supports all languages covered by CodeQL</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering AWS with amazon.aws 7.0: A Dive into New Modules for Enhanced Security and Seamless Migrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/mastering-aws-with-amazon.aws-7.0-a-dive-into-new-modules-for-enhanced-security-and-seamless-migrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/mastering-aws-with-amazon.aws-7.0-a-dive-into-new-modules-for-enhanced-security-and-seamless-migrations"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the technology landscape continues to evolve, the latest release of the Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for amazon.aws introduces a suite of powerful modules that redefine the boundaries of automation within Amazon Web Services (AWS) while redefining how organizations approach security deployments and seamless migrations within the AWS ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the Power of JetBrains AI in YouTrack for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=youtrack&amp;p=407450</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/youtrack/2023/12/discover-the-power-of-jetbrains-ai-in-youtrack-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T15:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The power of generative AI is now freely available to teams using YouTrack! AI Assistant, powered by JetBrains AI, is available in YouTrack 2023.3. It helps you generate summaries for content in tasks, articles, and support tickets, provides a localized summary of content in any language, and composes replies and comments for you. You can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Pishkova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第243話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755564103990</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755564103990"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valuable contributions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48015</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/850872368/0/sethsblog~Valuable-contributions/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T09:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We actually don’t really know. Netflix just released their first-ever detailed analysis of how many hours of engagement the top 15,000+ most watched shows on the network received over a six month period. Here’s the file. Who won? That question is actually the lesson here. The fact is, most organizations are pretty clueless about where […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The First Set of Bug-fixes for ReSharper and Rider 2023.3 Are Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=418078</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/12/13/rsrp-rd-2023-3-1-bug-fix/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T08:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, The ReSharper and Rider 2023.3.1 bug-fix updates have just been released! If you haven’t upgraded to the 2023.3 versions of our products, we highly recommend that you check out these blog posts: And now, let’s go over the most important fixes in 2023.3.1. Rider Here are the fixes included in this update: This […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DateTime]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2867/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2867/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/datetime.png" title="It's not just time zones and leap seconds. SI seconds on Earth are slower because of relativity, so there are time standards for space stuff (TCB, TGC) that use faster SI seconds than UTC/Unix time. T2 - T1 = [God doesn't know and the Devil isn't telling.]" alt="It's not just time zones and leap seconds. SI seconds on Earth are slower because of relativity, so there are time standards for space stuff (TCB, TGC) that use faster SI seconds than UTC/Unix time. T2 - T1 = [God doesn't know and the Devil isn't telling.]" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.29: Mandala]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/13/kubernetes-v1-29-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/13/kubernetes-v1-29-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes v1.29 Release Team
Editors: Carol Valencia, Kristin Martin, Abigail McCarthy, James Quigley
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.29: Mandala (The Universe), the last release of 2023!
Similar to previous releases, the release of Kubernetes v1.29 introduces new stable, beta, and alpha features. The consistent delivery of top-notch releases underscores the strength of our development cycle and the vibrant support from our community.
This release consists of 49 enhancements. Of those enhancements, 11 have graduated to Stable, 19 are entering Beta and 19 have graduated to Alpha.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes v1.29: Mandala (The Universe) ✨🌌
Join us on a cosmic journey with Kubernetes v1.29!
This release is inspired by the beautiful art form that is Mandala—a symbol o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68208</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/december-patches-for-azure-devops-server-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T19:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 Patch 1
The post December patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3.1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=417987</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/12/intellij-idea-2023-3-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T18:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first bug-fix update for v2023.3 has arrived!  You can update to this version from inside the IDE, using the Toolbox App, or via snaps, if you’re using Ubuntu. You can also download it directly from our website. This hotfix addresses the following issues: You can find detailed instructions on how to troubleshoot other common […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for AWS Amplify – Query MySQL and PostgreSQL database for AWS CDK]]></title>
        <id>32014208559319f447ba9286e5c9d009e392d2ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-aws-amplify-query-mysql-and-postgresql-database-for-aws-cdk/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T18:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the general availability to connect and query your existing MySQL and PostgreSQL databases with support for AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK), a new feature to create a real-time, secure GraphQL API for your relational database within or outside Amazon Web Services (AWS). You can now generate the entire API for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Cloud Automation with amazon.aws 7.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-7.0.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-7.0.0"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to Amazon Web Services (AWS) infrastructure automation, the latest release of the certified amazon.aws Ansible Content Collection for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform brings a number of enhancements to improve the overall user experience and speed up the process from development to production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital stocking stuffers (and the other kind)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47970</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/850431992/0/sethsblog~Digital-stocking-stuffers-and-the-other-kind/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since O. Henry wrote about the Magi, it’s been pretty clear that gifts aren’t about the stuff as much as they are the intent. Holidays where gifts are expected undermine this, because it’s hard to tell where obligation begins and intent fades away. One lightweight and quick alternative to traditional items are digital ones. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 12th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/12/this-week-in-spring-december-12th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/12/this-week-in-spring-december-12th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-3-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.16 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-16-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-16-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Buttner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That's a wrap! Looking back on the Elastic and AWS collaboration in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-elastic-aws-partnership-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-elastic-aws-partnership-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens in Vegas stays in Vegas, except when it’s Elastic recapping AWS re:Invent 2023! As a Diamond sponsor, we enjoyed supporting our partner AWS at this flagship event. We’ve also compiled an Elastic + AWS 2023 year in review.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm,Austin Jones,Jennifer Jarrad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-3-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 8.11.3 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.11.3 over 8.11.2 and 8.10.x releases.
The 8.11.3 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security advisory for more details.

For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.

The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.16 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-16-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-16-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 7.17.16 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.16 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
The 7.17.16 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security advisory for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Buttner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That's a wrap! Looking back on the Elastic and AWS collaboration in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-elastic-aws-partnership-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-elastic-aws-partnership-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
What a fantastic week at Amazon Web Services (AWS) re:Invent 2023! As a Diamond sponsor, we thoroughly enjoyed supporting our partner AWS at this flagship event and conversing with so many individuals from around the world who are interested in Elastic®.

On the heels of the event and with the holiday season upon us, we thought now would be a great time to share a blog post covering our highlights at AWS re:Invent and our extensive collaboration with AWS over the past year.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltbfd79ed3edce8588/657877cec7b407f848ad7f04/blog-elastic-aws-reinvent-jam.png,blog-elastic-aws-reinvent-jam.pngPresenting innovations at breakout sessions,
We held two Breakout Sessions covering pioneering technologies.

Elastic Distinguished Architect Micha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm,Austin Jones,Jennifer Jarrad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Podman and HashiCorp Nomad integration matures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/red-hat-podman-and-hashicorp-nomad-integration-matures</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/red-hat-podman-and-hashicorp-nomad-integration-matures"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improvements in the integration of Red Hat Podman and HashiCorp Nomad make it suitable for high-value applications and workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elegant and classy]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44600</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/850070624/0/sethsblog~Elegant-and-classy/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you announce that something is elegant or classy, it probably isn’t. There’s a humility to hospitality and sophistication that evaporates when we name it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forging a path to tech through economics — Data Scientist Susan Chang on how curiosity propelled her machine learning career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-susan-chang-machine-learning</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-susan-chang-machine-learning"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Susan Chang got into machine learning through mentoring. Now she’s returning the favor. Read her story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forging a path to tech through economics — Data Scientist Susan Chang on how curiosity propelled her machine learning career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-susan-chang-machine-learning</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-susan-chang-machine-learning"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Economics and machine learning might not seem like they have a lot in common, but Susan Chang found a common thread.
“Economics uses data and statistics to generate insights, which is the foundation of machine learning, too,” she says. “Machine learning is very broad. You’re using data and algorithms to analyze and predict things that are happening in the world.”
Susan, a Principal Data Scientist on Elastic®’s Security Machine Learning team, has worked in machine learning for a few years now but didn’t have the most straightforward path to get here.
She graduated with a master’s degree in economics and, during her studies, taught herself to program with the help of one university course and a lot of self-study.
“Because of the way the [economics] curriculum was taught, it wouldn’t have b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snow]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2866/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2866/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/snow.png" title="For someone who has ostensibly outgrown staying up late waiting for Santa, I do spend an awful lot of time refreshing websites to see if packages are here yet." alt="For someone who has ostensibly outgrown staying up late waiting for Santa, I do spend an awful lot of time refreshing websites to see if packages are here yet." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at NeurIPS 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/google-at-neurips-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/google-at-neurips-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T14:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Catherine Armato, Program Manager, Google




This week the 37th annual Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS 2023), the biggest machine learning conference of the year, kicks off in New Orleans, LA. Google is proud to be a Diamond Level sponsor of NeurIPS this year and will have a strong presence with >170 accepted papers, two keynote talks, and additional contributions to the broader research community through organizational support and involvement in >20 workshops and tutorials. Google is also proud to be a Platinum Sponsor for both the Women in Machine Learning and LatinX in AI workshops. We look forward to sharing some of our extensive ML research and expanding our partnership with the broader ML research community.



Attending for NeurIPS 2023 in per…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walking the city, walking the world]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46310</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/849720461/0/sethsblog~Walking-the-city-walking-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T09:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I passed 800 people as I walked my way through New York. I decided to look at the folks I was walking near. Of those 800 people, not one was as conventionally attractive as a movie star. Few looked like the images I saw on the billboards I passed. Most wouldn’t be cast […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrestling, fighting or dancing?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46308</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/849019229/0/sethsblog~Wrestling-fighting-or-dancing/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T09:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can wrestle with a challenge or a problem and find energy and possibility while doing it. And we can dance with someone else as we seek a mutual way forward. Fighting tends to be more brutal, final and hurtful than is often productive. You don’t want to spend your days fighting. The words matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sparsity-preserving differentially private training]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/sparsity-preserving-differentially.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/sparsity-preserving-differentially.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yangsibo Huang, Research Intern, Google Research; Chiyuan Zhang, Research Scientist, Google Research





Large embedding models have emerged as a fundamental tool for various applications in recommendation systems [1, 2] and natural language processing [3, 4, 5]. Such models enable the integration of non-numerical data into deep learning models by mapping categorical or string-valued input attributes with large vocabularies to fixed-length representation vectors using embedding layers. These models are widely deployed in personalized recommendation systems and achieve state-of-the-art performance in language tasks, such as  language modeling, sentiment analysis, and question answering. In many such scenarios, privacy is an equally important feature when deploying those models. A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All species are invasive species]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44588</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/848107322/0/sethsblog~All-species-are-invasive-species/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T09:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Human beings as we know them have only been around for 70,000 years or so. Honeybees got to North America around the time Columbus did. And the same is true for technologies and companies. Western Union was an interloper, telegrams were the scary new tech that was going to change everything for the worse. It’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wrong Stuff]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2865/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2865/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/the_wrong_stuff.png" title="The phantom found Edward Everett Hale a century too early; by the time we invented satellites, the specifics of his 'brick moon' proposal were dismissed as science fiction." alt="The phantom found Edward Everett Hale a century too early; by the time we invented satellites, the specifics of his 'brick moon' proposal were dismissed as science fiction." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrading GitHub.com to MySQL 8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-07-upgrading-github-com-to-mysql-8-0/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-upgrading-github-com-to-mysql-8-0/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub uses MySQL to store vast amounts of relational data. This is the story of how we seamlessly upgraded our production fleet to MySQL 8.0.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-upgrading-github-com-to-mysql-8-0/">Upgrading GitHub.com to MySQL 8.0</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From macOS runners to secure deployments, what’s new from GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-07-from-macos-runners-to-secure-deployments-whats-new-from-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-from-macos-runners-to-secure-deployments-whats-new-from-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Read a roundup of the exciting, new innovation coming from GitHub Actions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-from-macos-runners-to-secure-deployments-whats-new-from-github-actions/">From macOS runners to secure deployments, what’s new from GitHub Actions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.7 improves Vault and Consul integrations, adds NUMA support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.7 — now generally available — introduces improved workload identity, improved Vault and Consul integrations, NUMA support, Nomad actions, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[While you sleep, Automate resolving Dynatrace problem alerts and report them to ServiceNow!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/while-you-sleep-automate-resolving-dynatrace-problem-alerts-and-report-them-to-servicenow</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/while-you-sleep-automate-resolving-dynatrace-problem-alerts-and-report-them-to-servicenow"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating observability tools with automation is paramount in the realm of modern IT operations, as it fosters a symbiotic relationship between visibility and efficiency. Observability tools provide deep insights into the performance, health, and behavior of complex systems, enabling organizations to proactively identify and rectify issues before they escalate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bforrest@redhat.com (Ben Forrester)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VALID: A perceptually validated virtual avatar library for inclusion and diversity]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/valid-perceptually-validated-virtual.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/valid-perceptually-validated-virtual.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mar Gonzalez-Franco, Research Scientist, Google AR & VR


In the last decade, interdisciplinary scientists have dedicated a significant amount of effort to better understand the use of avatars, and have made many interesting observations, including the capacity of the users to embody their avatar (i.e., the illusion that the avatar body is their own) and the self-avatar follower effect, which creates a binding between the actions of the avatar and the user strong enough that the avatar can actually affect user behavior. 



The use of avatars in experiments isn’t just about how users will interact and behave in VR spaces, but also about discovering the limits of human perception and neuroscience. In fact, some VR social experiments often rely on recreating scenarios that can’t be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Innovation Graph Q2 2023 Data Release]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-07-github-innovation-graph-q2-2023-data-release/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-github-innovation-graph-q2-2023-data-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T16:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover the latest trends and insights on public software development activity on GitHub with the release of Q2 2023 data for the Innovation Graph.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-github-innovation-graph-q2-2023-data-release/">GitHub Innovation Graph Q2 2023 Data Release</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abundance and ideas]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47944</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/846275930/0/sethsblog~Abundance-and-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T09:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A colleague got an angry note. It concluded with, “you should know better.” The transgression? The sender was offended that my friend had written a post about a concept she’s been developing for nearly a decade. Of course, no idea is unique, and the posted idea sort of rhymed with one that the professor had […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring creator Rod Johnson and Oracle vice president Heather VanCura]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/07/spring-creator-rod-johnson-and-oracle-vice-president-heather-vancura</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/07/spring-creator-rod-johnson-and-oracle-vice-president-heather-vancura"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enrico Zimuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from self-managed Elastic Stack to Elastic Cloud using snapshot and restore with Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-cloud-snapshot-and-restore-amazon-s3</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-cloud-snapshot-and-restore-amazon-s3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow this step-by-step process to set up and run a self-managed Elastic stack. Then, migrate the Elastic stack content to an Elastic Cloud deployment using the snapshot and restore migration approach of storing and accessing snapshots in Amazon S3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 8.11.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.11.2 over 8.11.1 and 8.10.x releases.
The 8.11.2 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security advisory for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enrico Zimuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from self-managed Elastic Stack to Elastic Cloud using snapshot and restore with Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-cloud-snapshot-and-restore-amazon-s3</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-cloud-snapshot-and-restore-amazon-s3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
I had the pleasure of talking with many interesting people at AWS re:Invent 2023 in Las Vegas while I was helping out at Elastic®’s booth in the Expo hall. I spoke to many SREs, developers, solution architects, and other professionals who were running a self-managed Elastic Stack and had questions about the process of migrating their Elastic stack to Elastic Cloud. 

To help provide guidance on questions about Elastic Cloud migration, this blog post provides a walkthrough of how to set up a self-managed Elastic stack and then migrate that Elastic stack’s contents to Elastic Cloud using a snapshot and restore migration method. For the storage location of the snapshot, we’ll use Amazon S3, which is a perfect service for saving and accessing files with fine grain control provided by AWS Ide…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cueing up a calculator: an introduction to exploit development on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-06-cueing-up-a-calculator-an-introduction-to-exploit-development-on-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-06-cueing-up-a-calculator-an-introduction-to-exploit-development-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T17:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Using CVE-2023-43641 as an example, I’ll explain how to develop an exploit for a memory corruption vulnerability on Linux. The exploit has to bypass several mitigations to achieve code execution.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-06-cueing-up-a-calculator-an-introduction-to-exploit-development-on-linux/">Cueing up a calculator: an introduction to exploit development on Linux</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we’re experimenting with LLMs to evolve GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-06-how-were-experimenting-with-llms-to-evolve-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-06-how-were-experimenting-with-llms-to-evolve-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T16:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how we’re experimenting with generative AI models to extend GitHub Copilot across the developer lifecycle.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-06-how-were-experimenting-with-llms-to-evolve-github-copilot/">How we’re experimenting with LLMs to evolve GitHub Copilot</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women in Tech podcast: Transforming tech education]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/women-in-tech-podcast-transforming-tech-education</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/women-in-tech-podcast-transforming-tech-education"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Episode 2 of the HashiCast: Women in Tech podcast features Deborah Carter, a catalyst for change working to reshape technology education while advocating for diversity and inclusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hope and expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46254</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/845072033/0/sethsblog~Hope-and-expectations/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T10:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They’re not the same thing. Hope can fuel us. Hope can be refilled. Hope opens the door to possibility. Expectations, on the other hand, are a trap. They make us brittle and lead to disappointment. When we raise our hopes and lower our expectations, we establish a resilient way forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at EMNLP 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/google-at-emnlp-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/google-at-emnlp-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T01:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Malaya Jules, Program Manager, Google





Google is proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of Empirical Methods in Natural Language Processing (EMNLP 2023), a premier annual conference, which is being held this week in Sentosa, Singapore. Google has a strong presence at this year’s conference with over 65 accepted papers and active involvement in 11 workshops and tutorials. Google is also happy to be a Major Sponsor for the Widening NLP workshop (WiNLP), which aims to highlight global representations of people, perspectives, and cultures in AI and ML. We look forward to sharing some of our extensive NLP research and expanding our partnership with the broader research community.



We hope you’ll visit the Google booth to chat with researchers who are actively pursuing the latest innovati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2023.0.0 (aka Leyton) Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/06/spring-cloud-2023-0-0-aka-leyton-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/06/spring-cloud-2023-0-0-aka-leyton-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Gibb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.21.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/06/spring-tools-4-21-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/06/spring-tools-4-21-0-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lippert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.11 is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-05-github-enterprise-server-3-11-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-05-github-enterprise-server-3-11-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T23:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Customers using GitHub Enterprise Server can gain more insight and understanding into the security of their code.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-05-github-enterprise-server-3-11-is-now-generally-available/">GitHub Enterprise Server 3.11 is now generally available</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 5th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/05/this-week-in-spring-december-5th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/05/this-week-in-spring-december-5th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Lisa Jones-Huff reveals how she thrives in a startup atmosphere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lisa-jones-huff-thrives-startup-atmosphere</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lisa-jones-huff-thrives-startup-atmosphere"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Lisa Jones-Huff, senior director of global security specialists at Elastic and a startup enthusiast. From her first startup experience in 2003 to leading a growing team of security experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Elastigrads share the wellness benefits they’re most excited about in their first job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-wellness-benefits</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-wellness-benefits"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We asked new Elasticians and recent grads — who all joined the company through Elastigrad — what benefits and programs they were most excited about when they joined Elastic and which ones they use the most.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Lisa Jones-Huff reveals how she thrives in a startup atmosphere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lisa-jones-huff-thrives-startup-atmosphere</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lisa-jones-huff-thrives-startup-atmosphere"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Meet Lisa Jones-Huff, the senior director of global security specialists at Elastic and a startup enthusiast. From her first startup experience in 2003 to now leading a growing team of security experts, Lisa thrives on being self-motivated, innovative, and collaborative.
“I prefer not to come into an environment where you're farming the land after someone else has done the work. Part of the energy of a startup is that you get an opportunity to build something. You have an opportunity to see it grow and create processes that have never been in place,” Lisa says. “The thing that gives me energy is creating.”
We caught up with Lisa to hear more about how she thrives in a startup atmosphere, including her top tips for how you can do the same.
Dipping her toes in the startup world
Lisa was ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Elastigrads share the wellness benefits they’re most excited about in their first job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-wellness-benefits</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-wellness-benefits"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
One of the best benefits of landing a full-time position, besides the opportunity to grow your career and use your skill set, is the, well, the benefits themselves.
While navigating the ins and outs of programs offered by a company, especially if you’ve never done it before, can be overwhelming, it’s worth the effort to understand what is provided so you can take full advantage.
Elastic® has a variety of programs and resources designed with our Elasticians in mind that stretch beyond the standard health insurance and retirement plans. These programs, encompassed under one umbrella called Be.Well@Elastic, provide support when and where you need it. Plus, they all support our Source Code values.
We asked new Elasticians and recent grads — who all joined the company through Elastigrad — wha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new quantum algorithm for classical mechanics with an exponential speedup]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/a-new-quantum-algorithm-for-classical.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/a-new-quantum-algorithm-for-classical.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T22:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Robin Kothari and Rolando Somma, Research Scientists, Google Research, Quantum AI Team




Quantum computers promise to solve some problems exponentially faster than classical computers, but there are only a handful of examples with such a dramatic speedup, such as Shor’s factoring algorithm and quantum simulation. Of those few examples, the majority of them involve simulating physical systems that are inherently quantum mechanical — a natural application for quantum computers. But what about simulating systems that are not inherently quantum? Can quantum computers offer an exponential advantage for this?

 

In “Exponential quantum speedup in simulating coupled classical oscillators”, published in Physical Review X (PRX) and presented at the Symposium on Foundations of Computer …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary report optimization in the Privacy Sandbox Attribution Reporting API]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/summary-report-optimization-in-privacy.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/summary-report-optimization-in-privacy.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hidayet Aksu, Software Engineer, and Adam Sealfon, Research Scientist, Google





In recent years, the Privacy Sandbox initiative was launched to explore responsible ways for advertisers to measure the effectiveness of their campaigns, by aiming to deprecate third-party cookies (subject to resolving any competition concerns with the UK’s Competition and Markets Authority). Cookies are small pieces of data containing user preferences that websites store on a user’s device; they can be used to provide a better browsing experience (e.g., allowing users to automatically sign in) and to serve relevant content or ads. The Privacy Sandbox attempts to address concerns around the use of cookies for tracking browsing data across the web by providing a privacy-preserving alternative.



Ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp wins the Palo Alto Networks 2023 Global Technology Partner of the Year award]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-the-palo-alto-networks-2023-global-technology-partner-of-the-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-the-palo-alto-networks-2023-global-technology-partner-of-the-year"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp and Palo Alto Networks celebrate our ongoing partnership protecting customers with infrastructure security automation for the second year in a row.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDS with Spring Framework 6.1]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/04/cds-with-spring-framework-6-1</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/04/cds-with-spring-framework-6-1"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Deleuze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From trial to production: 5 key components of an optimal Elastic Cloud production deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-key-components-optimal-elastic-cloud-production-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-key-components-optimal-elastic-cloud-production-deployment"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ready to move beyond your Elastic Cloud trial and set yourself up for success in your Elastic Cloud journey? Learn the important factors to consider as you begin building out your production deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemendra Singh Lodhi,Tamara Rosini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From trial to production: 5 key components of an optimal Elastic Cloud production deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-key-components-optimal-elastic-cloud-production-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-key-components-optimal-elastic-cloud-production-deployment"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In our previous blog, How to get the most from your Elastic Cloud Trial, we showed how customers can benefit from using Elastic® Cloud trials and available resources to test and implement business use cases.

In this blog, we will discuss the critical factors that govern success in Elastic Cloud production deployment. After successful testing, customers should consider these factors to reliably launch an efficient and performant production deployment.
Next steps: Moving beyond the trial,
After successful completion of testing or proof of concept, customers can move on to the next phase, which is getting ready for production launch. There are a number of things to consider to ensure ongoing success in the Elastic Cloud journey.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemendra Singh Lodhi,Tamara Rosini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsupervised speech-to-speech translation from monolingual data]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/unsupervised-speech-to-speech.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/unsupervised-speech-to-speech.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eliya Nachmani, Research Scientist, and Michelle Tadmor Ramanovich, Software Engineer, Google Research






Speech-to-speech translation (S2ST) is a type of machine translation that converts spoken language from one language to another. This technology has the potential to break down language barriers and facilitate communication between people from different cultures and backgrounds. 




Previously, we introduced Translatotron 1 and Translatotron 2, the first ever models that were able to directly translate speech between two languages. However they were trained in supervised settings with parallel speech data. The scarcity of parallel speech data is a major challenge in this field, so much that most public datasets are semi- or fully-synthesized from text. This adds additiona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Work Items in Visual Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68130</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/work-items-in-visual-studio/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T14:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several years ago, with the introduction of Visual Studio 2019, we launched a completely revamped work item experience. This updated view operates entirely on REST, replacing the deprecated SOAP APIs utilized in the legacy version. Although Visual Studio 2022 still includes the option to revert to the legacy view,
The post Work Items in Visual Studio appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use AWS Fault Injection Service to demonstrate multi-region and multi-AZ application resilience]]></title>
        <id>b5f470ba74c346ed6f525a2a5e92522dc46cd4d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-aws-fault-injection-service-to-demonstrate-multi-region-and-multi-az-application-resilience/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Fault Injection Service (FIS) helps you to put chaos engineering into practice at scale. Today we are launching new scenarios that will let you demonstrate that your applications perform as intended if an AWS Availability Zone experiences a full power interruption or connectivity from one AWS region to another is lost. You can use […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zonal autoshift – Automatically shift your traffic away from Availability Zones when we detect potential issues]]></title>
        <id>f677c6705f71814fd999f39b325af14c6e9289e9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/zonal-autoshift-automatically-shift-your-traffic-away-from-availability-zones-when-we-detect-potential-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re launching zonal autoshift, a new capability of Amazon Route 53 Application Recovery Controller that you can enable to automatically and safely shift your workload’s traffic away from an Availability Zone when AWS identifies a potential failure affecting that Availability Zone and shift it back once the failure is resolved. When deploying resilient applications, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IDE extension for AWS Application Composer enhances visual modern applications development with AI-generated IaC]]></title>
        <id>66dd6400ac1e7d9ba598572e5cd829f82e8b6c05</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/ide-extension-for-aws-application-composer-enhances-visual-modern-applications-development-with-ai-generated-iac/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to share the integrated development environment (IDE) extension for AWS Application Composer. Now you can use AWS Application Composer directly in your IDE to visually build modern applications and iteratively develop your infrastructure as code templates with Amazon CodeWhisperer. Announced as preview at AWS re:Invent 2022 and generally available in March 2023, Application Composer is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Studio adds web-based interface, Code Editor, flexible workspaces, and streamlines user onboarding]]></title>
        <id>8202e0701d0edec7189fd74a2684035983c2a23f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-studio-adds-web-based-interface-code-editor-flexible-workspaces-and-streamlines-user-onboarding/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing an improved Amazon SageMaker Studio experience! The new SageMaker Studio web-based interface loads faster and provides consistent access to your preferred integrated development environment (IDE) and SageMaker resources and tooling, irrespective of your IDE choice. In addition to JupyterLab and RStudio, SageMaker Studio now includes a fully managed Code Editor based […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three new capabilities for Amazon Inspector broaden the realm of vulnerability scanning for workloads]]></title>
        <id>dbd84d0e15dc49a513d11dc8814a2ace24c64aef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/three-new-capabilities-for-amazon-inspector-broaden-the-realm-of-vulnerability-scanning-for-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon Inspector adds three new capabilities to increase the realm of possibilities when scanning your workloads for software vulnerabilities: Amazon Inspector introduces a new set of open source plugins and an API allowing you to assess your container images for software vulnerabilities at build time directly from your continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudWatch Application Signals for automatic instrumentation of your applications (preview)]]></title>
        <id>1d6092ef569153d497e5ee163eee98821d30bf12</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-cloudwatch-application-signals-for-automatic-instrumentation-of-your-applications-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the challenges with distributed systems is that they are made up of many interdependent services, which add a degree of complexity when you are trying to monitor their performance. Determining which services and APIs are experiencing high latencies or degraded availability requires manually putting together telemetry signals. This can result in time and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New myApplications in the AWS Management Console simplifies managing your application resources]]></title>
        <id>ec4fc257d1c6efc31dbdad1cfa3fa78ebe223b5a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-myapplications-in-the-aws-management-console-simplifies-managing-your-application-resources/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the general availability of myApplications supporting application operations, a new set of capabilities that help you get started with your applications on AWS, operate them with less effort, and move faster at scale. With myApplications in the AWS Management Console, you can more easily manage and monitor the cost, health, security […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily deploy SaaS products with new Quick Launch in AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>165f32cc180f9fa0cf1f36aff4e46a246fa890b6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/easily-deploy-saas-products-with-new-quick-launch-in-aws-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are excited to announce the general availability of SaaS Quick Launch, a new feature in AWS Marketplace that makes it easy and secure to deploy SaaS products. Before SaaS Quick Launch, configuring and launching third-party SaaS products could be time-consuming and costly, especially in certain categories like security and monitoring. Some products require […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Security legend Laura Spilca joins us to talk Spring Authorization Server and upgrading to Spring Boot 3]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-legend-laura-spilca-joins-us-to-talk</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-legend-laura-spilca-joins-us-to-talk"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All of Netflix’s HDR video streaming is now dynamically optimized]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e9e0cb15f2ba</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/all-of-netflixs-hdr-video-streaming-is-now-dynamically-optimized-e9e0cb15f2ba?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by  Aditya Mavlankar, Zhi Li, Lukáš Krasula and Christos Bampis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Package and deploy models faster with new tools and guided workflows in Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>9dfa4013fdeb3ce3b8c9cd5ded8657c6f07139cc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/package-and-deploy-models-faster-with-new-tools-and-guided-workflows-in-amazon-sagemaker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that Amazon SageMaker now comes with an improved model deployment experience to help you deploy traditional machine learning (ML) models and foundation models (FMs) faster. As a data scientist or ML practitioner, you can now use the new ModelBuilder class in the SageMaker Python SDK to package models, perform local inference […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use natural language to explore and prepare data with a new capability of Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>52022c89be15e7efe7a0e5d886a1b76e6bb36028</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-natural-language-to-explore-and-prepare-data-with-a-new-capability-of-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to introduce the ability to use natural language instructions in Amazon SageMaker Canvas to explore, visualize, and transform data for machine learning (ML). SageMaker Canvas now supports using foundation model-(FM) powered natural language instructions to complement its comprehensive data preparation capabilities for data exploration, analysis, visualization, and transformation. Using natural language instructions, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker adds new inference capabilities to help reduce foundation model deployment costs and latency]]></title>
        <id>070abf1c19c0afcc710d7953b53d84a40e4e4b82</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-adds-new-inference-capabilities-to-help-reduce-foundation-model-deployment-costs-and-latency/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing new Amazon SageMaker inference capabilities that can help you optimize deployment costs and reduce latency. With the new inference capabilities, you can deploy one or more foundation models (FMs) on the same SageMaker endpoint and control how many accelerators and how much memory is reserved for each FM. This helps to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage foundation models for business analysis at scale with Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>286f7dd53aa2b49a2bbca8dcddcd42842c920920</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/leverage-foundation-models-for-business-analysis-at-scale-with-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m excited to introduce a new capability in Amazon SageMaker Canvas to use foundation models (FMs) from Amazon Bedrock and Amazon SageMaker Jumpstart through a no-code experience. This new capability makes it easier for you to evaluate and generate responses from FMs for your specific use case with high accuracy. Every business has its […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing highly durable Amazon OpenSearch Service clusters with 30% price/performance improvement]]></title>
        <id>9254592bff3a8ff942fbbd9434437e0a80455403</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-highly-durable-amazon-opensearch-service-clusters-with-30-price-performance-improvement/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the new OR1 instances to create Amazon OpenSearch Service clusters that use Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) for primary storage. You can ingest, store, index, and access just about any imaginable amount of data, while also enjoying a 30% price/performance improvement over existing instance types, eleven nines of data durability, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Clarify makes it easier to evaluate and select foundation models (preview)]]></title>
        <id>8eb45aec03e2c9174185648ea2e15d148920732c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-clarify-makes-it-easier-to-evaluate-and-select-foundation-models-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that Amazon SageMaker Clarify now supports foundation model (FM) evaluation (preview). As a data scientist or machine learning (ML) engineer, you can now use SageMaker Clarify to evaluate, compare, and select FMs in minutes based on metrics such as accuracy, robustness, creativity, factual knowledge, bias, and toxicity. This new capability adds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluate, compare, and select the best foundation models for your use case in Amazon Bedrock (preview)]]></title>
        <id>d609890b177381df2b101da3ee61fcba234993e4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/evaluate-compare-and-select-the-best-foundation-models-for-your-use-case-in-amazon-bedrock-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that you can now evaluate, compare, and select the best foundation models (FMs) for your use case in Amazon Bedrock. Model Evaluation on Amazon Bedrock is available today in preview. Amazon Bedrock offers a choice of automatic evaluation and human evaluation. You can use automatic evaluation with predefined metrics such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift adds new AI capabilities, including Amazon Q, to boost efficiency and productivity]]></title>
        <id>d33d7b803e5c2060a28968285e9fa1f2403b84ce</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-redshift-adds-new-ai-capabilities-to-boost-efficiency-and-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift puts artificial intelligence (AI) at your service to optimize efficiencies and make you more productive with two new capabilities that we are launching in preview today. First, Amazon Redshift Serverless becomes smarter. It scales capacity proactively and automatically along dimensions such as the complexity of your queries, their frequency, the size of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Clean Rooms Differential Privacy enhances privacy protection of your users’ data (preview)]]></title>
        <id>046eaa3e0b7d8591180c049c34b977499c294c70</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-clean-rooms-differential-privacy-enhances-privacy-protection-of-your-users-data-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can use AWS Clean Rooms Diﬀerential Privacy (preview) to help protect the privacy of your users with mathematically backed and intuitive controls in a few steps. As a fully managed capability of AWS Clean Rooms, no prior differential privacy experience is needed to help you prevent the reidentification of your users. AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Clean Rooms ML helps customers and partners apply ML models without sharing raw data (preview)]]></title>
        <id>30344b64e2852c44c41aaa3fee6ef1070e91cf3a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-clean-rooms-ml-helps-customers-and-partners-apply-ml-models-without-sharing-raw-data-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re introducing AWS Clean Rooms ML (preview), a new capability of AWS Clean Rooms that helps you and your partners apply machine learning (ML) models on your collective data without copying or sharing raw data with each other. With this new capability, you can generate predictive insights using ML models while continuing to protect your sensitive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon OpenSearch Service zero-ETL integration with Amazon S3 (preview)]]></title>
        <id>eda84244f81c1f8800d261452c3a2b4a004d3ae9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-opensearch-service-zero-etl-integration-with-amazon-s3-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing a preview of Amazon OpenSearch Service zero-ETL integration with Amazon S3, a new way to query operational logs in Amazon S3 and S3-based data lakes without needing to switch between services. You can now analyze infrequently queried data in cloud object stores and simultaneously use the operational analytics and visualization capabilities […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your Terraform development with Amazon CodeWhisperer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerate-your-terraform-development-with-amazon-codewhisperer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerate-your-terraform-development-with-amazon-codewhisperer"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improve the developer experience writing Terraform code with the help of generative AI powered by Amazon CodeWhisperer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第242話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755511181824</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755511181824"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform delivers launch-day support for Amazon S3 Express]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-delivers-launch-day-support-for-amazon-s3-express</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-delivers-launch-day-support-for-amazon-s3-express"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s Terraform provider for AWS now enables users to manage their S3 Express buckets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updated: Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68117</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-1-rtw-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[12/5 Update: There is a known issue where the Agent version does not update after upgrading to Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 and using Update Agent in Agent Pool configuration. We are currently working on a patch to resolve this issue and will share updates in the Developer Community as we make progress.
The post Updated: Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: New Experimental Features in Gateway API v1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/28/gateway-api-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/28/gateway-api-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Candace Holman (Red Hat), Dave Protasowski (VMware), Gaurav K Ghildiyal (Google), John Howard (Google), Simone Rodigari (IBM)
Recently, the Gateway API announced its v1.0 GA release, marking a huge milestone for the project.
Along with stabilizing some of the core functionality in the API, a number of exciting new experimental features have been added.
Backend TLS Policy
BackendTLSPolicy is a new Gateway API type used for specifying the TLS configuration of the connection from the Gateway to backend Pods via the Service API object.
It is specified as a Direct PolicyAttachment without defaults or overrides, applied to a Service that accesses a backend, where the BackendTLSPolicy resides in the same namespace as the Service to which it is applied.
All Gateway API Routes that point t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform extension for VS Code adds Terraform Cloud view]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-extension-for-vs-code-adds-terraform-cloud-view</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-extension-for-vs-code-adds-terraform-cloud-view"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new view in the HashiCorp Terraform extension for Visual Studio Code shows your Terraform Cloud workspaces and runs, reducing context-switching.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at re:Invent 2023: A year of collaboration with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-re-invent-2023-a-year-of-collaboration-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-re-invent-2023-a-year-of-collaboration-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recap of HashiCorp infrastructure and security news and developments on AWS from the past year, from self-service provisioning to fighting secrets sprawl and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault benchmark testing tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-benchmark-testing-tool</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-benchmark-testing-tool"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault benchmark is an open source tool that tests the performance of HashiCorp Vault auth methods and secrets engines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Original Research: MIT CODE 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9340b879176a</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/netflix-original-research-mit-code-2023-9340b879176a?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix was thrilled to be the premier sponsor for the 2nd year in a row at the 2023 Conference on Digital Experimentation (CODE@MIT).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gain operator confidence with HCP Consul Central observability features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/gain-operator-confidence-with-hcp-consul-central-observability-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/gain-operator-confidence-with-hcp-consul-central-observability-features"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul Central’s new observability features were recently used by a customer to help troubleshoot an issue with assistance from HashiCorp engineers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform stacks, explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-stacks-explained</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-stacks-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform stacks simplify provisioning and managing resources at scale, reducing the time and overhead of managing infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing resources with the Terraform AWS Cloud Control provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Cloud Control provider — built around the AWS Cloud Control API — is designed to bring new services to HashiCorp Terraform faster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Causal Machine Learning for Creative Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4b0ce22a8a96</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/causal-machine-learning-for-creative-insights-4b0ce22a8a96?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T01:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A framework to identify the causal impact of successful visual components.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/24/sig-testing-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/24/sig-testing-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sandipan Panda
Welcome to another edition of the SIG spotlight blog series, where we
highlight the incredible work being done by various Special Interest
Groups (SIGs) within the Kubernetes project. In this edition, we turn
our attention to SIG Testing,
a group interested in effective testing of Kubernetes and automating
away project toil. SIG Testing focus on creating and running tools and
infrastructure that make it easier for the community to write and run
tests, and to contribute, analyze and act upon test results.
To gain some insights into SIG Testing, Sandipan
Panda spoke with Michelle Shepardson,
a senior software engineer at Google and a chair of SIG Testing, and
Patrick Ohly, a software engineer and architect at
Intel and a SIG Testing Tech Lead.
Meet the contributors
San…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closing the skills and talent divide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/closing-the-skills-and-talent-divide</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/closing-the-skills-and-talent-divide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the HashiCast: Navigating the Cloud for C-Suites podcast addresses how to close the skills gap. Guest James Footman, Head of Talent for EMEA at HashiCorp, highlights the key takeaways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving simulations of clouds and their effects on climate]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/improving-simulations-of-clouds-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/improving-simulations-of-clouds-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tapio Schneider, Visiting Researcher, and Yi-fan Chen, Engineering Lead, Google Research




Today’s climate models successfully capture broad global warming trends. However, because of uncertainties about processes that are small in scale yet globally important, such as clouds and ocean turbulence, these models’ predictions of upcoming climate changes are not very accurate in detail. For example, predictions of the time by which the global mean surface temperature of Earth will have warmed 2℃, relative to preindustrial times, vary by 40–50 years (a full human generation) among today’s models. As a result, we do not have the accurate and geographically granular predictions we need to plan resilient infrastructure, adapt supply chains to climate disruption, and assess the risks of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open sourcing Project Guideline: A platform for computer vision accessibility technology]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/open-sourcing-project-guideline.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/open-sourcing-project-guideline.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dave Hawkey, Software Engineer, Google Research




Two years ago we announced Project Guideline, a collaboration between Google Research and Guiding Eyes for the Blind that enabled people with visual impairments (e.g., blindness and low-vision) to walk, jog, and run independently. Using only a Google Pixel phone and headphones, Project Guideline leverages on-device machine learning (ML) to navigate users along outdoor paths marked with a painted line. The technology has been tested all over the world and even demonstrated during the opening ceremony at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games.



Since the original announcement, we set out to improve Project Guideline by embedding new features, such as obstacle detection and advanced path planning, to safely and reliably navigate users t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at AWS re:Invent: Your blueprint for cloud success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-your-blueprint-for-cloud-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-your-blueprint-for-cloud-success"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re attending AWS re:Invent in Las Vegas, Nov. 27 - Dec. 1, visit us for breakout sessions, expert talks, and product demos to learn how to accelerate your adoption of a cloud operating model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Fall Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68016</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-fall-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T16:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have been following these posts, then you are more than familiar with our New Boards Hub initiative. We have been doing our best to keep our community informed of the new features and our rollout plans. Now is a good time to provide an update on where things are at with a couple of our new preview features,
The post New Boards Hub, Fall Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Processing using Netflix Maestro and Apache Iceberg]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b8ba072ddeeb</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/incremental-processing-using-netflix-maestro-and-apache-iceberg-b8ba072ddeeb?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T05:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Jun He, Yingyi Zhang, and Pawan Dixit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault integrations with Intel, Pure Storage, Red Hat, and more continue to strengthen customer security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-intel-pure-storage-red-hat-and-more-continue-to-strengthe</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-intel-pure-storage-red-hat-and-more-continue-to-strengthe"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10 new HashiCorp Vault ecosystem integrations extend security use cases for customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging practices for Society-Centered AI]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/emerging-practices-for-society-centered.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/emerging-practices-for-society-centered.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Anoop Sinha, Research Director, Technology & Society, and Yossi Matias, Vice President, Google Research




The first of Google’s AI Principles is to “Be socially beneficial.” As AI practitioners, we’re inspired by the transformative potential of AI technologies to benefit society and our shared environment at a scale and swiftness that wasn’t possible before. From helping address the climate crisis to helping transform healthcare, to making the digital world more accessible, our goal is to apply AI responsibly to be helpful to more people around the globe. Achieving global scale requires researchers and communities to think ahead — and act — collectively across the AI ecosystem.



We call this approach Society-Centered AI. It is both an extension and an expansion of Human-Cente…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps’ First Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68002</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-first-consensus-assessment-initiative-questionnaire-caiq-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am thrilled to announce that we have now published, for the first time, a Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) specific to Azure DevOps. The Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) is a tool developed by the Cloud Security Alliance (CSA). It serves as a standard set of questions aimed at helping potential cloud customers evaluate the security capabilities of cloud service providers.
The post Azure DevOps’ First Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) Now Available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benibo Ajumogobia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Adversarial testing for generative AI safety]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research_16.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research_16.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kathy Meier-Hellstern, Building Responsible AI & Data Systems, Director, Google Research




The Responsible AI and Human-Centered Technology (RAI-HCT) team within Google Research is committed to advancing the theory and practice of responsible human-centered AI through a lens of culturally-aware research, to meet the needs of billions of users today, and blaze the path forward for a better AI future. The BRAIDS (Building Responsible AI Data and Solutions) team within RAI-HCT aims to simplify the adoption of RAI practices through the utilization of scalable tools, high-quality data, streamlined processes, and novel research with a current emphasis on addressing the unique challenges posed by generative AI (GenAI).





GenAI models have enabled unprecedented capabilities leading …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>