<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-10-21T00:45:56.610Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-10-21T00:45:56.610Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce data transfer and storage (DTS) costs in Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/reduce-data-transfer-and-storage-dts-costs-in-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/reduce-data-transfer-and-storage-dts-costs-in-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New features in Elastic Cloud — data relocation and recovery via snapshots and compression on indexing data — reduce data transfer and storage (DTS) costs, potentially resulting in lower or more predictable Elastic Cloud bills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leaf Lin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized in first Forrester XDR report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/forrester-evaluation-limitless-xdr</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/forrester-evaluation-limitless-xdr"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forrester has recognized Elastic as a Contender in the industry's first analysis of XDR vendors, recognizing our strong customizable SIEM offering.
Forrester Research is helping to increase end-user understanding of the emerging XDR space with the release of The Forrester New WaveTM: Extended Detection and Response (XDR) Providers, Q4 2021. While the XDR market is still being defined, we believe this report is important third-party validation to guide users in understanding which vendors they should spend time evaluating.
“…[This] is your official notice: XDR is real. This market matters; practitioners like you are using XDR today,” writes Allie Mellen, Forrester’s lead analyst in this market.
Forrester evaluated the “14 most significant providers in the category” that met their definition…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Vision at the Edge with AWS Panorama]]></title>
        <id>bb64b081a33e0e139a0be82e2486b897d168e908</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/JoLbC_gpGfQ/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T17:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the AWS Panorama Appliance is generally available to all of you. The AWS Panorama Appliance is a computer vision (CV) appliance designed to be deployed on your network to analyze images provided by your on-premises cameras. Every week, I read about new and innovative use cases for computer vision. Some customers are using CV […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diversity, inclusion, and belonging at GitHub in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-10-20-diversity-inclusion-belonging-github-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-10-20-diversity-inclusion-belonging-github-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T16:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past two years, GitHub has doubled in size, welcoming more than 760 new Hubbers in 2021 alone. This past year we particularly focused on our goal of making GitHub more equitable. We saw growth in our diversity representation, whose population increased at a higher rate than the company itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Consul API Gateway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-consul-api-gateway</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-consul-api-gateway"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Consul API Gateway is a dedicated ingress solution for intelligently routing traffic to applications running on the HashiCorp Consul service mesh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Consul 1.11 Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-consul-1-11</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-consul-1-11"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul 1.11 adds important new features: multi-tenancy with administrative partitions and a new installation-and-management Consul Kubernetes CLI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Square 0.4.0-M2 is available.]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/20/spring-cloud-square-0-4-0-m2-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/20/spring-cloud-square-0-4-0-m2-is-available"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T15:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Milestone 2 (M2) of the Spring Cloud Square 0.4.0 is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 0.4.0-M2 release notes for more information.

See all issues included in this release here.
Notable Changes in 0.4.0-M2


  
Spring Native support adjustments for non-load-balanced use-cases (PR)

  
Support for configuring different WebClient.Builder beans (not shared) for each @RetrofitClient instance (PR)


The documentation for this milestone can be found here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS Data Exchange for Amazon Redshift]]></title>
        <id>c4673307b7ed8b0999036138fd06f046349261cb</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/e4hxlIIKsqk/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T21:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2019 I told you about AWS Data Exchange and showed you how to Find, Subscribe To, and Use Data Products. Today, you can choose from over 3600 data products in ten categories: In my introductory post I showed you how could subscribe to data products and then download the data sets into an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new from GitHub Changelog? September 2021 recap]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-10-19-whats-new-from-github-changelog-september-2021-recap/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-10-19-whats-new-from-github-changelog-september-2021-recap/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T19:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on 44 ships, including a colorblind-accessible theme, a public README.md for organizations, and customization of code review settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - October 19th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/19/this-week-in-spring-october-19th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/19/this-week-in-spring-october-19th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How’re you doing? Good? Keepin’ busy? Good. I’m doing alright, too. 


  
Last week, I did a sort of smörgåsbord episode of Tanzu Code on twitch.tv/vmwaretanzu. It was super fun! I stream on VMWare Tanzu as well as on my own Twitch channel, twitch.tv/JavaJoshLong about all things Spring, Java, and more.

  
In last week’s super short-and-to-the-point installment of Spring Tips, I looked at the Spring Plugin project

  
I also put out This Month in Spring - a newsletter digest version of this very weekly roundup that comes out every… month. Naturally.

  
Did you see this? Twitter is now using graphql-java, the very same project that underpins the Spring GraphQL project, for their APIs and they’re reporting incredible performance gains! twitter + graphql-java · Discussion #2591 · graphql-java/graphql-java

  
In last week’s A Bootiful Podcast, I talked to .NET legend Layla Porter on Azure Spring Cloud, Steeltoe.NET, and more

  
Announcing: Knative 1.0 

  
Harden Performance of REST calls using Spring WebFlux

  
How to upload/download file using Spring MVC and Spring Boot ? Example Tutorial

  
 Matt Raible and I did a talk for the SF JUG about Spring Native and GraalVM with Spring Boot and JHipster. It was a ton of fun and I hope you’ll enjoy it.

  
Multiple Hierarchical Contexts in Spring Boot - DEV Community

  
Did you get your tickets for the Reactive Summit ? There are going to be some amazing talks this year!

  
Release 1.16.1 · testcontainers/testcontainers-java

  
Release Europium-SR12 (2020.0.12) · reactor/reactor

  
Spring Data 2021.0.6 and 2020.0.14 released

  
Spring Data 2021.1 enters RC phase

  
Spring Data JDBC - How do I implement caching?

  
Spring Framework 5.3.11 and 5.2.18 available now

  
The State of Java 2021]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Share Your Nomad Packs for a Pack Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/share-your-nomad-packs-for-a-pack-contest</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/share-your-nomad-packs-for-a-pack-contest"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a HashiCorp backpack! Contributors who share their open source templates in the Nomad Pack Registry can win a variety of Nomad-themed prizes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Public Beta of HCP Packer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-public-beta-of-hcp-packer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-public-beta-of-hcp-packer"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The free public beta of HCP Packer lets DevOps teams track and automate build updates across their HashiCorp Packer and Terraform workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A single platform for US Government security and logging compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-single-platform-for-us-government-security-and-logging-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-single-platform-for-us-government-security-and-logging-compliance"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With event logging and endpoint security unified on a single platform, Elastic is helping the US Federal Government meet and exceed requirements of the Executive Order on Improving the Nation’s Cybersecurity with a more affordable business model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Harmon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximus Modernizing and Maximizing Their Potential]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=32773</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/maximus-modernizing-and-maximizing-their-potential/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is less really more? Maximus embraced microservices orchestration to gain reduced software license, implementation and infrastructure costs.
The post Maximus Modernizing and Maximizing Their Potential appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Garth Knudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the GitHub Universe hosts, and start building your schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-10-18-meet-github-universe-hosts-start-building-schedule/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-10-18-meet-github-universe-hosts-start-building-schedule/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T16:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We sat down with Universe hosts Lorena Mesa and Jarryd McCree for a quick Q&#038;A to help you make the most out of your conference experience this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault Surpasses 100 Integrations with 75 Partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-surpasses-100-integrations-with-75-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-surpasses-100-integrations-with-75-partners"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault now supports more than 100 integrations with 75 partners, including Cisco, Datadog, F5, MongoDB, Palo Alto Networks, Red Hat, ServiceNow, and Snowflake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.1 enters RC phase]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/18/spring-data-2021-1-enters-rc-phase</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/18/spring-data-2021-1-enters-rc-phase"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T14:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring community,

On behalf of the Spring Data team and everyone who contributed, it is my pleasure to announce that Spring Data 2021.1.0 has entered its release candidate phase by releasing RC1 today. It is available from the milestone repository. This release ships with several tickets fixed. The most notable changes are:


  
Deprecate support for RxJava 2 in preparation for removal of RxJava 2 support with Spring Data 3.0.

  
Fluent Query API for Querydsl and Query-by-Example, allowing for projections, pagination, and consuming results as a Stream.

  
Spring Data JDBC ships with a refined SQL DSL, accepting complex JOIN conditions and subselects.

  
Support for exists and not empty keywords in Elasticsearch repository query methods and support for field exclusion in sour…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data JDBC - How do I implement caching?]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/18/spring-data-jdbc-how-do-i-implement-caching</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/18/spring-data-jdbc-how-do-i-implement-caching"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the third article of a series about how to tackle various challenges you might encounter when using Spring Data JDBC.



The series consists of





Spring Data JDBC - How to use custom ID generation.



Spring Data JDBC - How do I make bidirectional relationships?



Spring Data JDBC - How do I implement caching? (this article).





If you are new to Spring Data JDBC, you should start by reading its introduction and this article, which explains the relevance of aggregates in the context of Spring Data JDBC. Trust me, it is important.



This article is based on part of a talk I did at Spring One 2021.



Why does Spring Data not cache?



One important design decision for Spring Data JDBC was to NOT include caching.
The reason for this was as with so …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.0.6 and 2020.0.14 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/18/spring-data-2021-0-6-and-2020-0-14-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/18/spring-data-2021-0-6-and-2020-0-14-released"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T09:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data 2021.0.6 and 2020.0.14 service releases.

Both releases are built on top of Spring Framework 5.3.11. For your convenience, you can consume Spring Data 2021.0.6 and 2020.0.14 through the upcoming Spring Boot releases 2.5.6 and 2.4.12, respectively. 

Both service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.

To round things off, here are the links to the artifacts, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.0.6


  
Spring Data Commons 2.5.6 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.2.6 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.5.6 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data for Apache Geode 2.5.6 - Artifacts -…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clinical Trials]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2530/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2530/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/clinical_trials.png" title="We don't need to do a clinical trial of this change because the standard of care is to adopt new ideas without doing clinical trials." alt="We don't need to do a clinical trial of this change because the standard of care is to adopt new ideas without doing clinical trials." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[💾 Save the date for GitHub Game Off 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-10-15-save-the-date-for-github-game-off-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-10-15-save-the-date-for-github-game-off-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T14:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game Off is an annual game jam (or “hackathon for building games”) that’s a little different from most—it lasts for the entire month of November—not just a weekend or a few days. It’s the perfect]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master the Elastic Stack with trainings featured at ElasticON Global]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/master-the-elastic-stack-with-trainings-featured-at-elasticon-global</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/master-the-elastic-stack-with-trainings-featured-at-elasticon-global"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Training has certified Analysts and Engineers across more than 37 countries, and set out to certify many more as a result of industry leading live training sessions held at this year's ElasticOn Global event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikki Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and HashiCorp Collaborate on New Terraform Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-hashicorp-collaborate-new-terraform-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-hashicorp-collaborate-new-terraform-modules"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and HashiCorp are collaborating to develop Terraform modules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsolved Math Problems]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2529/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2529/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/unsolved_math_problems.png" title="After decades of studying the curve and the procedure that generates it, the consensus explanation is &quot;it's just like that.&quot;" alt="After decades of studying the curve and the procedure that generates it, the consensus explanation is &quot;it's just like that.&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: .NET legend LaylaCodesIT on Azure Spring Cloud, Steeltoe.NET, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/14/a-bootiful-podcast-net-legend-laylacodesit-on-azure-spring-cloud-steeltoe-net-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/14/a-bootiful-podcast-net-legend-laylacodesit-on-azure-spring-cloud-steeltoe-net-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment  Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to teammate, .NET ecosystem legend and awesome human being Layla (@LaylaCodesIt).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Optimyze join forces to deliver "always on" continuous profiling of infrastructure, applications, and services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-optimyze-join-forces-to-deliver-always-on-continuous-profiling-of-infrastructure-applications-and-services</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-optimyze-join-forces-to-deliver-always-on-continuous-profiling-of-infrastructure-applications-and-services"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that Elastic is joining forces with Optimyze, to accelerate our vision for unified, actionable observability and enhance the ability to detect and find root cause faster in complex distributed environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Waypoint 0.6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-waypoint-0-6</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-waypoint-0-6"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint 0.6 focuses on Kubernetes by integrating Helm, showing Kubernetes resources in the UI, adding pod auto-scaling, and supporting Ingresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Nomad 1.2 Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-nomad-1-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-nomad-1-2"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.2 and Nomad Pack deliver exciting new features, workflows, and tools to the HashiCorp Nomad ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Student developer resources you won’t find in the classroom]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-10-14-student-developer-resources-wont-find-classroom/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-10-14-student-developer-resources-wont-find-classroom/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T15:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heading back to school? Did you just graduate? The GitHub Education Stream Team (GEST) is sharing resources, tools, and more to help emerging developers land a job. Student leaders from around the world are creating and hosting shows to grow the tech community and share information you won’t find in the classroom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Consul-Terraform-Sync 0.4 for Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-consul-terraform-sync-0-4-for-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-consul-terraform-sync-0-4-for-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compliance-driven network infrastructure automation with Consul-Terraform-Sync 0.4 is now generally available for HashiCorp Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic traced a formatting bug in Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-elastic-traced-a-formatting-bug-in-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-elastic-traced-a-formatting-bug-in-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently had a tricky date formatting bug. This is the story of how we traced it back to an error in the JDK date formatting library (now fixed for Java 17 & 18).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Tozzi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 6.8.20 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-6-8-20-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-6-8-20-released"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 6.8.20 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Kibana, Elasticsearch, Beats, Logstash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quin Hoxie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.15.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-15-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-15-1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.15.1 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Logstash, Beats, APM, Enterprise Search, Elastic Security, and ECK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quin Hoxie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide to Solving Bottlenecks with Camunda: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=32691</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/the-ultimate-guide-to-solving-bottlenecks-with-camunda-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use Camunda Optimize to find and solve your bottlenecks with business processes, and apply best practices from the manufacturing industry. 
The post The Ultimate Guide to Solving Bottlenecks with Camunda: Part 1 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.11 and 5.2.18 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/14/spring-framework-5-3-11-and-5-2-18-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/14/spring-framework-5-3-11-and-5-2-18-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T12:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.11 and 5.2.18 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.11 includes 32 fixes and improvements. Spring Framework 5.2.18 includes 10 selected fixes and improvements.

Stay tuned for follow-up Spring Boot releases next week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate actions on anomaly detection jobs with the Kibana alerting framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/accelerate-actions-on-anomaly-detection-jobs-with-the-kibana-alerting-framework</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/accelerate-actions-on-anomaly-detection-jobs-with-the-kibana-alerting-framework"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration with the new Kibana Alerting framework allows users to define custom logic and provides an easy and flexible way of setting up conditions. And users don’t have to worry about keeping the actual implementation up-to-date, as the framework will handle all the hard work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitrii Arnautov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Search Platform: Maximizing data utility in public sector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-elastic-search-platform-maximizing-data-utility-in-public-sector</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-elastic-search-platform-maximizing-data-utility-in-public-sector"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Elastic, we believe the best way to extract the full value of data is to put that data to work.  See how the Search Platform for Public Sector helps maximize data utility for enhanced mission delivery, citizen services, and education.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzzanna Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Spring Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/13/spring-tips-spring-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/13/spring-tips-spring-plugin"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) looks at the little-known, often-used Spring Plugin project, which supports the strategy pattern]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flag Map Sabotage]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2528/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2528/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/flag_map_sabotage.png" title="Delaware hopes to explore the western edge of areas marked with the Belgian flag, once the tornadoes die down." alt="Delaware hopes to explore the western edge of areas marked with the Belgian flag, once the tornadoes die down." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 59 – Remote Possibilities with @burkeholland]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62536</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-59-remote-possibilities-with-burkeholland/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T20:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 59 – Remote Possibilities with @burkeholland appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apply now for GitHub Universe 2021 micro-mentoring]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-10-12-apply-github-universe-2021-micro-mentoring/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-10-12-apply-github-universe-2021-micro-mentoring/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T16:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of our ongoing commitment to ensure GitHub’s conferences are accessible and inclusive to people from all walks of life, we’re offering 30-minute, 1:1 micro-mentoring sessions with GitHub employees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - October 12th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/12/this-week-in-spring-october-12th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/12/this-week-in-spring-october-12th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to yet another installment of This Week in Spring where we recap - with apologies to The Times - all the news that’s fit to reprint in the Spring and Spring-adjacent ecosystems. First: it’s almost Halloween! Can you believe it?? This year has absolutely flown by! I need to dust off my PHP costume for Halloween. Maybe I’ll even start using this particularly ghastly VS Code theme on the day… 

Anyway, it’s been a busy week for me already and we’re only at the very beginning of Tuesday! I’ve been attending Kubecon (virtually), I spoke at the online I Code Java event at midnight and then this morning at 8am I was on the SnykLive discussion on the State of Java in 2021. Fun! 

This week’s roundup also looks to be a fun one, so let’s get to it! 


  
I looked at the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform in Production: Learning from Pocket]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-in-production-learning-from-pocket</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-in-production-learning-from-pocket"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a live demo, two engineers from Mozilla’s Pocket show how they use CDK for Terraform to define and provision infrastructure in a TypeScript application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2: Migration strategy considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-2-migration-strategy-considerations</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-2-migration-strategy-considerations"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 introduces an updated architecture, new tools and an improved but familiar experience to automation teams. However, there are multiple considerations for your planning and strategy to migrate your current deployment to Ansible Automation Platform 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Align Human Workflows and Automation with Camunda Platform 7.16]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=32203</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/align-human-workflows-and-automation-with-camunda-platform-716/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Platform 7.16.0. Join our webinar on Oct. 19, as Camunda experts discuss the advantages.
The post Align Human Workflows and Automation with Camunda Platform 7.16 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.6.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=32166</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/camunda-optimize-360-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.6.0 and that Optimize is now available as part of Camunda Cloud.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.6.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cawemo Enterprise (On-Premises) 1.8.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=32224</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/cawemo-enterprise-on-premises-1-8-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re happy to announce our Cawemo Enterprise On-Premises 1.8.0 release. Sign up for a free trial of Camunda Enterprise Platform to learn more.
The post Cawemo Enterprise (On-Premises) 1.8.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cawemo Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.16.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=29676</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/camunda-platform-7-16-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to announce that Camunda Automation Platform 7.16.0 is now available, including many new features. Explore our latest release.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.16.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.2.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=32235</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/camunda-cloud-1-2-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Camunda Cloud 1.2 release brings enhanced enterprise capabilities, open architecture and real-time monitoring for an exceptional user experience. 
The post Camunda Cloud 1.2.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Response to GitKraken SSH Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62519</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-response-to-gitkraken-ssh-bug/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T17:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 28, 2021, Azure DevOps was notified by Axosoft of a vulnerability in a dependency of their popular git GUI client – GitKraken. This vulnerability led to the GitKraken client generating insecure SSH keys.
The post Azure DevOps Response to GitKraken SSH Bug appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub security update: revoking weakly-generated SSH keys]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-10-11-github-security-update-revoking-weakly-generated-ssh-keys/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-10-11-github-security-update-revoking-weakly-generated-ssh-keys/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T17:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 28, 2021, we received notice from the developer Axosoft regarding a vulnerability in a dependency of their popular git GUI client - GitKraken. An underlying issue with a dependency, called `keypair`, resulted in the GitKraken client generating weak SSH keys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Learning Resources Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-learning-resources-reference-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-learning-resources-reference-guide"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read this curated list of HashiCorp learning resources to help practitioners and organizations better understand the cloud operating model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Nobel Prizes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2527/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2527/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/new_nobel_prizes.png" title="They've endowed a separate prize in Physiology or Medicine or Stopping Dr. Adams." alt="They've endowed a separate prize in Physiology or Medicine or Stopping Dr. Adams." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · September 2021 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-10-08-release-radar-aug-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-10-08-release-radar-aug-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T18:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Northern Hemisphere has hit fall, and the southern is starting to warm into summer. September has been a busy time for our community. Maintainers have been getting their repositories ready for Hacktoberfest, joining us]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to HashiCorp at KubeCon North America 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-guide-to-hashicorp-at-kubecon-north-america-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-guide-to-hashicorp-at-kubecon-north-america-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about HashiCorp’s plans for the KubeCon North America 2021 conference and get updates on CNCF integrations with our tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第195話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496539355756</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496539355756"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Transformation: Evolution or Revolution?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=32011</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/digital-transformation-evolution-or-revolution/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow how our product vision has evolved to help our customers achieve their business objectives with automation and orchestration.
The post Digital Transformation: Evolution or Revolution? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware resource MOID lookup filter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/vmware-resource-moid-lookup-filter</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/vmware-resource-moid-lookup-filter"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you trying to manage private clouds easily and efficiently using Ansible Automation Platform? When it comes to VMware infrastructure automation, the latest release of the vmware.vmware_rest Collection and new lookup plugins bring a set of fresh features to build, manage and govern various VMware use cases and accelerate the process from development to production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.10.08]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62507</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-10-08/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T09:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.10.08 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.10.08 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Heiko Scherrer on OpenWMS, Spring, Spring Boot, Spring Data, workflow with Activiti and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/07/a-bootiful-podcast-heiko-scherrer-on-openwms-spring-spring-boot-spring-data-workflow-with-activiti-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/07/a-bootiful-podcast-heiko-scherrer-on-openwms-spring-spring-boot-spring-data-workflow-with-activiti-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to OpenWMS founder Heiko Scherrer (@openwms) about OpenWMS, Spring, Spring Boot, Spring Data, workflow with Activiti and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub&#8217;s guide to Hacktoberfest 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-10-07-githubs-guide-hacktoberfest-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-10-07-githubs-guide-hacktoberfest-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T18:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giving back to open source projects is a great way to practice skills you don’t get to use in your day job. Check out ways to get involved!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Advisory Database now powers npm audit]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-10-07-github-advisory-database-now-powers-npm-audit/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-10-07-github-advisory-database-now-powers-npm-audit/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T16:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re adding a proxy on top of the GitHub Advisory Database that speaks the `npm audit` protocol.  This means that every version of the npm CLI that supports security audits is now talking directly to the GitHub Advisory Database.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s Early Career Program: A Year in Review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-s-early-career-program-a-year-in-review</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-s-early-career-program-a-year-in-review"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s inaugural summer internship program is complete, here’s how it went and how you can apply for next year!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falling in Love with Camunda Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=31839</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/falling-in-love-with-camunda-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get motivated to overcome your initial challenges and doubts. Plus, discover how Camunda Cloud does a great job at lowering the barrier to get started.
The post Falling in Love with Camunda Cloud appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Ihme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2: automation content navigator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2-automation-content-navigator</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2-automation-content-navigator"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the introduction of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2, several new key components are being introduced as a part of the overall developer experience. This includes automation execution environments, introduced to provide predictable environments during automation runtime. All collection dependencies are contained within the execution environment to make sure that automation created in development environments runs the same as in production environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault Integrates with ServiceNow for Credential Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-integrates-with-servicenow-for-credential-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-integrates-with-servicenow-for-credential-management"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault can now integrate with ServiceNow for credential management with the Vault Credential Resolver integration now available in the ServiceNow App Store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Need a Chief Automation Officer?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=32003</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/do-you-need-a-chief-automation-officer/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T14:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the impact of having a chief automation officer or CoE team to spearhead end-to-end process automation efforts across the enterprise. 
The post Do You Need a Chief Automation Officer? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2: private automation hub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2-private-automation-hub</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2-private-automation-hub"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that the Ansible Automation Platform 2 release includes private automation hub 4.3. Private automation hub provides automation developers the ability to collaborate and publish their own automation content and streamline delivery of Ansible code within their organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Spring GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/06/spring-tips-spring-graphql</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/06/spring-tips-spring-graphql"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment we look at the new Spring GraphQL project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Boards Fall Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62483</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-boards-fall-update/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T17:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Boards Fall Update
The post Azure Boards Fall Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Global Preview: Sessions for Cloud Platform Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-preview-sessions-for-cloud-platform-teams</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-preview-sessions-for-cloud-platform-teams"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a list of the 10 most interesting HashiConf Global sessions for enterprise cloud platform teams. Join us October 19 - 20, 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 58 – Improve your Open Source Security with @WhiteSourceSoft]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62492</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-58-improve-your-open-source-security-with-whitesourcesoft/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T13:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 58 – Improve your Open Source Security with @WhiteSourceSoft appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2: automation controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2-automation-controller</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2-automation-controller"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 is the next generation automation platform from Red Hat’s trusted enterprise technology experts. We are excited to announce that the Ansible Automation Platform 2 release includes automation controller 4.0, the improved and renamed Red Hat Ansible Tower.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Cloud on AWS Outposts Brings VMware SDDC as a Fully Managed Service on Premises]]></title>
        <id>cc1604636a9a5bddcd177cc87efad781d3c4393a</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/a_jxBRgCfjg/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T12:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2017, AWS and VMware brought VMware Cloud on AWS, the VMware enterprise-class Software-Defined Data Center (SDDC) software for all vSphere-based workloads, to the AWS Cloud with optimized access to native AWS services. VMware Cloud on AWS provides dedicated, single-tenant cloud infrastructure, delivered on the next-generation bare-metal AWS infrastructure based on the latest Amazon EC2 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - October 5th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/05/this-week-in-spring-october-5th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/05/this-week-in-spring-october-5th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! Life’s been busy but fun this last week. I’ve been knee-deep in video production! I’ve got a lot of fun Spring Tips installments lined up or in production at the moment, and I can’t wait for you to see ’em! 

I also spent much of last week with my buddy Matt Raible and we made JHipster work with Spring Native, and I’m still giddy as can be about the newly opened possibilities. (More on that below) 

How are you doin’, otherwise? I hope you’re doing well! 

Now then, we’ve got a lot to cover and oh-so little time in which to do it. Let’s goo! 


  
In this installment of Spring Tips, I look at “Bootiful Edge Services” with Spring GraphQL, Spring Cloud Gateway, and Reactive Programming.

  
In this installment of a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.0-M2 (codename Jubilee) is Available.]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/04/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-m2-codename-jubilee-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/10/04/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-m2-codename-jubilee-is-available"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T16:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Milestone 2 (M2) of the Spring Cloud 2021.0 Release Train (codename Jubilee) is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2021.0.0-M2 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0.0-M2 Release Train

Milestone 2 is compatible with Spring Boot 2.6.0-M3.

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.
Spring Cloud Commons

Adjusts NamedContextFactory API for Sleuth.
Spring Cloud Config

Allow types in JDBC Environment repository besides String issue 1952
Spring Cloud Contract

UUID v4 and case insnsitivity issue 1688. Allow custom build.gradle when using standalone docker image issue 1672.
Spring Cloud Gateway

Supp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2: automation execution environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2-automation-execution-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2-automation-execution-environments"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 is now available to customers. This release expands the possibilities of automation across your organization, with a more secure, flexible foundation to build and deploy automation with greater acceleration, orchestration and innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.10.01]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62461</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-10-01/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T12:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.10.01 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.10.01 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Terraform AWS Cloud Control Provider Tech Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider-tech-preview</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider-tech-preview"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new provider for HashiCorp Terraform — built around the AWS Cloud Control API — is designed to bring new services to Terraform faster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Cloud Control API, a Uniform API to Access AWS & Third-Party Services]]></title>
        <id>72cc28524eba802679698e51dfda034efdf3809e</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/rJ7y1-dBxPk/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T19:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am happy to announce the availability of AWS Cloud Control API a set of common application programming interfaces (APIs) that are designed to make it easy for developers to manage their AWS and third-party services. AWS delivers the broadest and deepest portfolio of cloud services. Builders leverage these to build any type of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Data engineer Christoph Strobl on MongoDB, Redis, GraphQL and Spring Native`]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-data-engineer-christoph-strobl-on-mongodb-redis-graphql-and-spring-native</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-data-engineer-christoph-strobl-on-mongodb-redis-graphql-and-spring-native"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring Data engineer Christoph Strobl (@stroblchristoph) about GraphQL, MongoDB, and Spring Native, among other things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now — AWS Step Functions Supports 200 AWS Services To Enable Easier Workflow Automation]]></title>
        <id>cee8bd4b535d73803cbea8d752906218175bc530</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/VCHFtkeO7Q8/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T17:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today AWS Step Functions expands the number of supported AWS services from 17 to over 200 and AWS API Actions from 46 to over 9,000 with its new capability AWS SDK Service Integrations. When developers build distributed architectures, one of the patterns they use is the workflow-based orchestration pattern. This pattern is helpful for workflow […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing academic papers: lessons learned from Elasticsearch and Lucene]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/implementing-academic-papers-lessons-learned-from-elasticsearch-and-lucene</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/implementing-academic-papers-lessons-learned-from-elasticsearch-and-lucene"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While developing Elasticsearch, we occasionally come across an important problem with no simple or established approach to solving it. It's natural to ask “hmm, is there an academic paper that addresses this?” Other times, academic work is a source of inspiration. We'll encounter a paper proposing a new algorithm or data structure and think “this would be so useful!” Here are just a few examples of how Elasticsearch and Apache Lucene incorporate academic work:

HyperLogLog++ for cardinality aggregations
C3 algorithm for adaptive replica selection
Hierarchical Navigable Small World Graphs (HNSW) for nearest vector search in Lucene
MIC statistic to improve machine learning classification
Block-max WAND for faster top-hits retrieval in Lucene
... and many more
Academic papers are an invaluabl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julie Tibshirani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda Functions Powered by AWS Graviton2 Processor – Run Your Functions on Arm and Get Up to 34% Better Price Performance]]></title>
        <id>0cae1763504c1bb73a2607ef87d1be87390daeb6</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/TymIJew6a4s/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T21:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of our customers (such as Formula One, Honeycomb, Intuit, SmugMug, and Snap Inc.) use the Arm-based AWS Graviton2 processor for their workloads and enjoy better price performance. Starting today, you can get the same benefits for your AWS Lambda functions. You can now configure new and existing functions to run on x86 or Arm/Graviton2 processors. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Managed Service for Prometheus Is Now Generally Available with Alert Manager and Ruler]]></title>
        <id>650ab218c81385c93b055ed2e0e247ffe471c1a9</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/pTITSdH8m6E/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T20:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2020, we introduced the preview of Amazon Managed Service for Prometheus, an open source Prometheus-compatible monitoring service that makes it easy to monitor containerized applications at scale. With Amazon Managed Service for Prometheus, you can use the Prometheus query language (PromQL) to monitor the performance of containerized workloads without having to manage […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Cloud in Context: Comparing Cloud Survey Results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multi-cloud-in-context-comparing-cloud-survey-results</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multi-cloud-in-context-comparing-cloud-survey-results"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From multi-cloud to COVID-19, we look at 5 key results of the HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy survey, and how they stack up to other industry research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Beta Release of Consul Service Mesh for Amazon ECS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-beta-release-of-consul-service-mesh-for-amazon-ecs</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-beta-release-of-consul-service-mesh-for-amazon-ecs"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul now provides a reliable and secure service mesh on Amazon ECS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon Redshift Query Editor V2, a Free Web-based Query Authoring Tool for Data Analysts]]></title>
        <id>dfcf4b0d01f5728e795d8a0a6dab20e326c8d56a</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/PcK079sK_5M/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T15:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to manipulating and analyzing relational data, Structured Query Language (SQL) has been an international standard since 1986, a couple of years before I was born. And yet, it sometimes takes hours to get access to a new database or data warehouse, configure credentials or single sign-on, download and install multiple desktop libraries […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Casalboni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Ansible Automation Platform 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-ansible-automation-platform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-ansible-automation-platform-2"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the last two years, the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform product team has been hard at work developing the next major release. We are incredibly excited to introduce Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2, which was just announced at AnsibleFest 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andriusb@redhat.com (Andrius Benokraitis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Bootiful Edge Services]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/29/spring-tips-bootiful-edge-services</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/29/spring-tips-bootiful-edge-services"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long looks at how to build bootiful Edge Services with Spring Cloud Gateway, Spring GraphQL, and Reactive Programming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 28th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/28/this-week-in-spring-september-28th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/28/this-week-in-spring-september-28th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! This week I’m with my buddy Matt Raible preparing for what I’m hoping will be an awesome San Francisco JUG joint appearance on Wednesday this week! 

I’ve got to get back to that! But I did want to get through this roundup because it’s enormous! So, without further ado:


  
Spring Initializr 0.11.0 available now

  
In last week’s A Bootiful Podcast, I talked to Spring web legend Rossen Stoyanchev on RSocket, GraphQL and more

  
Reassessing TestNG vs. Junit

  
Spring Boot 2.4.11 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.5.5 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.6.0-M3 available now

  
Spring Data JDBC - How do I make Bidirectional Relationships?

  
Spring Native in Action with the Okta Spring Boot Starter

  
TodoMVC with Spring Boot and Thymeleaf (Part 1) - Wim Deblauwe

  
TodoMVC with Spring Boot and Thymeleaf (Part 2) - Wim Deblauwe

  
TodoMVC with Spring Boot and Thymeleaf (Part 3) - Wim Deblauwe

  
Neat article on InfoQ.com: VMware Overhauls Spring 6 & Spring Boot 3 for Another Decade

  
Check this resource on the Spring Security Authorization Server:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic on Elastic: Configuring the Security app to use Cross Cluster Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-on-elastic-configuring-the-security-app-to-use-cross-cluster-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-on-elastic-configuring-the-security-app-to-use-cross-cluster-search"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Infosec Detections and Analytics team is responsible for building, tuning, and maintaining the security detections used to protect all Elastic systems. Within Elastic we call ourselves Customer Zero and we strive to always use the newest versions of our products. 

In the previous blog posts we gave an overview of our architecture and what data we send to our clusters. In this blog post we will provide instructions on how we use Cross Cluster Search (CCS) with the Security and Machine Learning (ML) applications

Configuring CCS

Getting the Security app to work with CCS only requires a few minor changes. The first step is to configure the Security app so that it knows to look for the CCS index patterns instead of local index patterns. To do this open the Kibana ‘Advanced Settin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Jewitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 57 – Securing @Azure with @shehackspurple]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62413</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-57-securing-azure-with-shehackspurple/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T11:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 57 – Securing @Azure with @shehackspurple appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon Genomics CLI Is Now Open Source and Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>6ba6437e1f536de9e1efe66deb59b74940f5bd37</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/wE9aGkClpdg/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T17:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (October 2021) – Added more information about the workflows developed by the Broad Institute. Less than 70 years separate us from one of the greatest discoveries of all time: the double helix structure of DNA. We now know that DNA is a sort of a twisted ladder composed of four types of compounds, called […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ingest data directly from Google Pub/Sub into Elastic using Google Dataflow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ingest-data-directly-from-google-pub-sub-into-elastic-using-google-dataflow</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ingest-data-directly-from-google-pub-sub-into-elastic-using-google-dataflow"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re excited to announce the latest development in our ongoing partnership with Google Cloud. Now developers, site reliability engineers (SREs), and security analysts can ingest data from Google Pub/Sub to the Elastic Stack with just a few clicks in the Google Cloud Console. By leveraging Google Dataflow templates, Elastic makes it easy to stream events and logs from Google Cloud services like Google Cloud Audit, VPC Flow, or firewall into the Elastic Stack. This allows customers to simplify their data pipeline architecture, eliminate operational overhead, and reduce the time required for troubleshooting.

Many developers, SREs, and security analysts who use Google Cloud to develop applications and set up their infrastructure also use the Elastic Stack to troubleshoot, monitor, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Yang,Suyog Rao,Adam Quan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Initializr 0.11.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/27/spring-initializr-0-11-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/27/spring-initializr-0-11-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T16:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Initializr 0.11.0 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 15 fixes, improvements and dependency upgrades.
Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

For full upgrade instructions and new and noteworthy features please see the release notes.

GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for Amazon Connect: Voice ID, Wisdom, and Outbound Communications]]></title>
        <id>2ffd0d8fddb47ee86afdbcfa8ab33909870bf899</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/J94TeS2u8O4/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T12:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the AWS re:Invent conference last year, I wrote about new capabilities added to Amazon Connect. Today, I am happy to announce the general availability of two of these capabilities, Voice ID and Wisdom, and the launch of a new one. High-volume outbound communications allows, as the name implies, the initiation and management of outbound […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.09.24]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62431</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-09-24/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T12:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.09.24 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.09.24 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon QuickSight Q – Business Intelligence Using Natural Language Questions]]></title>
        <id>701147b345634ef37f028239c154531da9dae71e</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/y5xKtRfDeRo/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T23:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making sense of business data so that you can get value out of it is worthwhile yet still challenging. Even though the term Business Intelligence (BI) has been around since the mid-1800s (according to Wikipedia) adoption of contemporary BI tools within enterprises is still fairly low. Amazon QuickSight was designed to make it easier for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring web legend Rossen Stoyanchev on RSocket, GraphQL and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/23/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-web-legend-rossen-stoyanchev-on-rsocket-graphql-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/23/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-web-legend-rossen-stoyanchev-on-rsocket-graphql-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Rossen Stoyanchev (@rstoya05) about Spring, RSocket, GraphQL, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.0-M3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/23/spring-boot-2-6-0-m3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/23/spring-boot-2-6-0-m3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.0-M3 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

Highlights of this release include:


  
The PathPattern based path matching strategy is now used by default for Spring MVC applications.

  
Elasticsearch properties for the different client implementations have have been consolidation and rationalized.

  
Sanitization rules are now pluggable and can be based on the backing PropertySource.

  
Spring Integration PollerMetadata properties are now provided.


For more details please take a look at the release notes wiki page and the changelog. Spring Boot 2.6.0-RC1 will be released October 21st with the GA due on November 18th.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic APM iOS agent technical preview released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-apm-ios-agent-technical-preview-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-apm-ios-agent-technical-preview-released"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are proud to announce the preview release of the Elastic APM iOS agent! This release is intended to elicit feedback from the community, while providing some initial functionality within the Elastic Observability stack and is not intended for production use. Now is your chance to influence the direction of this new iOS agent and let us know what you think on our discussion forum. If you find an issue, or would like to contribute yourself, visit the GitHub repository. 
 Elastic APM is an Application Performance Monitoring solution from Elastic and alongside the iOS agent, there are official agents available for Java, Node.js, Python, Ruby, JavaScript/RUM, .NET, PHP, and Go. Elastic APM helps you to gain insight into the performance of your application, track errors, and gauge the end-user…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryce Buchanan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Automated Provisioning Tools Pave the Way to Multi-Cloud Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-automated-provisioning-tools-pave-the-way-to-multi-cloud-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-automated-provisioning-tools-pave-the-way-to-multi-cloud-adoption"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey reveals that infrastructure as code and provisioning tools are at the forefront of the movement to multi-cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Cloud Builders – Career Transformation & Personal Growth]]></title>
        <id>aaa9610a6d30f30168b9fb5803d4aaed4815e991</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/aC43vDdnvCM/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T16:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long-time readers of this blog know that I firmly believe in the power of education to improve lives. AWS Training and Certification equips people and organizations around the world with cloud computing education to build and validate cloud computing skills. With demand for cloud skills and experience at an all-time high, there’s never been a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for AWS Distro for OpenTelemetry – Tracing Support is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>71d9597f69dcd0af2b228f6aa58d647adbeb261c</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/Z6UVy7uC4qo/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T15:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year before re:Invent, we introduced the public preview of AWS Distro for OpenTelemetry, a secure distribution of the OpenTelemetry project supported by AWS. OpenTelemetry provides tools, APIs, and SDKs to instrument, generate, collect, and export telemetry data to better understand the behavior and the performance of your applications. Yesterday, upstream OpenTelemetry announced tracing stability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the French Ministry of Agriculture deploys Elastic to monitor the commercial fishing industry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-the-french-ministry-of-agriculture-deploys-elastic-to-monitor-the-commercial-fishing-industry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-the-french-ministry-of-agriculture-deploys-elastic-to-monitor-the-commercial-fishing-industry"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the French Ministry of Agriculture and Food (the Ministry), our team of architects in the Methods, Support and Quality office (BMSQ) evaluate and supply software solutions to resolve issues encountered by project teams that affect various disciplines.

As data specialists, one area we’ve been involved in includes reconfiguring the traceability of activities for the commercial fishing industry. The aim is to improve the quality, speed and precision of how we collect and analyze large volumes of data connected to the industry — from declared fish hauls, harbor exit manifests, to GPS data tracking vessel locations.

The challenge we have is to provide up-to-date information that is verified, complete, dynamic and can be viewed in various formats depending on the target audience, and El…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Arnaud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What you can expect: AnsibleFest 2021 for IT Leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/what-you-can-expect-ansiblefest-2021-for-it-leaders</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/what-you-can-expect-ansiblefest-2021-for-it-leaders"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, we are adapting our signature automation event, AnsibleFest, into a free virtual experience. Seasoned pros and new Ansible enthusiasts alike can find answers and learn more about Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, the platform for building and operating automation at scale and creating an enterprise automation strategy. We are excited to offer a track designed specifically for IT leaders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michele Null</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/23/spring-boot-2-5-5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/23/spring-boot-2-5-5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T10:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.5 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 41 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Works – AWS Region in New Zealand]]></title>
        <id>e444816ed2574dbf8497e030161de6a7e0995fe1</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/u12rqAu3KlQ/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T22:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are currently working on regions in Australia, India, Indonesia, Israel, Spain , Switzerland, and the United Arab Emirates. Auckland, New Zealand in the Works Today I am happy to announce that the new AWS Asia Pacific (Auckland) Region is in the works and will open in 2024. This region will have three Availability Zones […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Ad Verification with Machine Learning and AWS Inferentia]]></title>
        <id>1abe9f34421eb828051ee4010e67c4f61a85225c</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/XcJMU3nysi8/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T17:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Advertising helps companies build their brand and connect with shoppers, through ads shown both within and beyond Amazon’s store, including websites, apps, and streaming TV content in more than 15 countries. Businesses or brands of all sizes including registered sellers, vendors, book vendors, Kindle Direct Publishing (KDP) authors, app developers, and agencies on Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 7.15: Create powerful, personalized search experiences in seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-15-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-15-0"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T16:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the general availability of Elastic 7.15, a release that brings a broad set of new capabilities to the Elastic Search Platform (including Elasticsearch and Kibana) and its three built-in solutions — Elastic Enterprise Search, Elastic Observability, and Elastic Security.

With Elastic 7.15 comes the general availability of the Elastic App Search web crawler and tighter integrations with Google Cloud — enabling our customers and community to more quickly create powerful new web search experiences, to ingest data more quickly and securely, and to more easily put their data to work with the power of search.

In addition, with Elastic Observability’s new APM correlations feature, DevOps teams can accelerate root cause analysis and reduce mean time to resolution (MTTR)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Courcy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Elastic Enterprise Search 7.15: Web crawler GA and personalized Workplace Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-15-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-15-0"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 7.15 introduces general availability for App Search’s web crawler making it quick and effortless to spin up powerful, new search experiences for every use case.

We’re also adding countless ways to personalize Workplace Search to meet the unique needs of your organization with the ability to add custom branding, schedule sync frequency, and configure automatic filter detection.

These updates help teams launch search faster and tailor the search experiences they create:

Take the headache out of data ingestion and make your website content instantly searchable with a sophisticated, easy-to-use web crawler
Apply your organization’s branding across all your mission-critical productivity tools
Schedule sync frequency in line with infrastructure demands
Define custom …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elasticsearch, Kibana, and Elastic Cloud for 7.15]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-7-15-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-7-15-0"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T16:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud customers can now ingest data more simply, quickly, and securely, and the latest updates to the core Elastic Stack provide users with new tools for maximizing performance and exploring their data.

The 7.15 release of Elastic Cloud brings new integrations with Google Cloud that allow customers to ingest Google Cloud services data directly into their Elastic Cloud deployments and take advantage of additional network security with Google Cloud Private Service Connect. Plus, the Elastic Stack brings enhancements to Elasticsearch and Kibana including improved data transfer, better resiliency, and more flexible data ingest and analysis. 

Ready to roll up your sleeves and get started? We have the links you need:

Try out the new features on Elastic Cloud 
Download the latest versi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fermi Fang,George Kobar,Adeline Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 7.15: Automated correlations, frictionless log ingestion from Google Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-15-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-15-0"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 7.15 introduces the general availability of automated correlations, unified views across application service logs and dependencies, and agentless log ingestion from Google Cloud Platform (GCP), accelerating troubleshooting of root causes of application issues and making it even easier to ingest telemetry from cloud services. 

These new features allow customers to:

Automatically surface attributes of the APM data set that are correlated with high-latency or erroneous transactions
Effortlessly troubleshoot application issues by viewing all associated application or service logs from within the APM user interface 
Seamlessly ingest log data into Elastic from within the Google Cloud console and extend monitoring to native Google Cloud services
Elastic Observability 7.15…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Security 7.15: End threats at the endpoint…and beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-15-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-15-0"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 7.15 further arms the SOC to achieve extended detection and response (XDR). 
Malicious behavior protection applies behavior analytics to prevent attack techniques often leveraged by named threats by performing dynamic, stateful correlation of on-host events, and then reacting instantly to disrupt attacks before they cause damage.
Memory threat protection now safeguards Windows hosts, stopping attacks designed to evade most other defenses.
To accelerate response and prevent damage and loss, 7.15 adds host isolation for cloud-native Linux systems, making the capability now available on every OS protected by Elastic Agent. 
Let’s dive in.
End threats at the endpoint
Malicious behavior protection for Linux, Windows, and macOS
Malicious behavior protection, new in 7.15, buttres…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New at HashiConf Global: Hands-on Labs, HashiCorp Zone, a Contest, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-at-hashiconf-global-hands-on-labs-hashicorp-zone-a-contest-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-at-hashiconf-global-hands-on-labs-hashicorp-zone-a-contest-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Global takes place Tuesday–Thursday, October 19-21, 2021, and we are excited to introduce several new elements to the program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 56 – Secretless Applications with @ChristosMatskas]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62379</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-56-secretless-applications-with-christosmatskas/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T15:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 56 – Secretless Applications with @ChristosMatskas appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>