<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-08-29T02:25:28.468Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-08-29T02:25:28.468Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: CSI Inline Volumes have graduated to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/29/csi-inline-volumes-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/29/csi-inline-volumes-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jonathan Dobson (Red Hat)
CSI Inline Volumes were introduced as an alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.15 and have been beta since 1.16. We are happy to announce that this feature has graduated to General Availability (GA) status in Kubernetes 1.25.
CSI Inline Volumes are similar to other ephemeral volume types, such as configMap, downwardAPI and secret. The important difference is that the storage is provided by a CSI driver, which allows the use of ephemeral storage provided by third-party vendors. The volume is defined as part of the pod spec and follows the lifecycle of the pod, meaning the volume is created once the pod is scheduled and destroyed when the pod is destroyed.
What's new in 1.25?
There are a couple of new bug fixes related to this feature in 1.25, and the CSIInlineVolum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unprepared, as always]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43632</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/708284394/0/sethsblog~Unprepared-as-always/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technological leaps always take us by surprise. What happens when every visual image ever created can be remixed and expanded? Van Gogh, Superman, or Moses. These link to an open search engine, so your mileage may vary. New software allows anyone to create images simply by typing in a dozen or so words. And software […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisionism]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40856</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/708162724/0/sethsblog~Revisionism/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T08:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two marketing problems when it comes to creating interventions for the public good. The first marketing problem is that when it works we take the intervention for granted. The world doesn’t fall apart, and we don’t notice, because our expectation was that the world (whatever world matters to you) should stay on course. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a custom Spring Cloud Gateway Filter]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/26/creating-a-custom-spring-cloud-gateway-filter</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/26/creating-a-custom-spring-cloud-gateway-filter"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we look into writing a custom extension for Spring Cloud Gateway. Before we get started, let’s go over how Spring Cloud Gateway works:




  
First, a client makes a network request to the Gateway

  
The Gateway is defined with a number of routes, each with Predicates to match the request to the route. For example, you can match on the path segment of the URL or the HTTP method of the request.

  
Once matched, the Gateway executes pre-request logic on each of the filters applied to the route. For example, you might want to add query parameters to your request

  
A proxy filter routes the request to the proxied service

  
The service executes and returns a response

  
The gateway receives the response and executes post-request logic on each filter before return…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways every company can get started with an open-source software strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-26-3-ways-every-company-can-get-started-with-an-open-source-software-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-26-3-ways-every-company-can-get-started-with-an-open-source-software-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T16:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of software development does not exist without open source. However, to maintain today’s software and create the software of the future, the largest organizations and beneficiaries of open source need to expand their collaboration with the community and help it grow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways to involve your community to improve your programs]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60542</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/3-ways-to-involve-your-community-to-improve-your-programs/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a DevRel project manager, program manager, community manager, etc. you might be a team of one, and there’s only so much one person can do. Getting a community program off the ground is hard enough, but how can you find ways to improve it when you are flying solo? I am my team’s program manager and I’m lucky enough to have colleagues who oversee our various programs such as our Champion Program, Camunda meet-ups, Educational Licenses Program, and more. I collaborate with my coworkers on these programs but I also “own” our Camunda for Common Good program, which is dedicated to assisting nonprofit organizations who could benefit from having free access to our enterprise products. As this is the...
The post 3 ways to involve your community to improve your programs appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danielle Andrist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“A good study”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41717</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/708029102/0/sethsblog~A-good-study/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T08:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gatekeepers keep disappearing. When it cost $500,000 to produce a record album, you could assume that it was going to reach some people and not be completely amateurish. Today, many songs in the iTunes store have had exactly one listen. When it cost $5,000,000 to make a video or a film, there was a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webhook for Case Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/webhook-for-case-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/webhook-for-case-management"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 8.4, a new Webhook - Case Management connector was introduced. Learn how to connect the Webhook - Case Management connector with a demo instance of Jira (a third-party case management system) and use it with the Kibana Cases feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steph Milovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webhook for Case Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/webhook-for-case-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/webhook-for-case-management"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In 8.4, a new Webhook - Case Management connector was introduced. The Webhook - Case Management connector uses axios to send POST, PUT, and GET requests to a case management RESTful API web service and integrates with the Kibana Cases feature.


In this blog post, we will demonstrate how to connect the Webhook - Case Management connector with a demo instance of Jira (a third-party case management system) and use it with the Kibana Cases feature. We will refer to the Jira API documentation in order to configure the connector.


Note: If you want to connect with Jira quickly, we recommend using the preconfigured Jira connector.
Step 1. Set up connector
In the Webhook - Case Management connector create flyout, begin by entering a connector Name — for example, Jira Test Connector. Basic auth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steph Milovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Swirls]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2664/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2664/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/cloud_swirls.png" title="'Why did you get into fluid dynamics?' 'Well, SOME planet has to have the coolest clouds, odds are it's not ours, and rockets are slow.'" alt="'Why did you get into fluid dynamics?' 'Well, SOME planet has to have the coolest clouds, odds are it's not ours, and rockets are slow.'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the latest AWS Heroes – August 2022]]></title>
        <id>f94b7ec2837a44f904bb188f134e48c449671094</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-latest-aws-heroes-august-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T18:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global AWS community is filled with passionate builders, eager to learn and explore ways to build better and faster on AWS. Within the AWS community, a select few individuals truly go above and beyond to share their knowledge and inspire others through content creation, event organization, open source contributions, and more. These community leaders […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping your skillset fresh as a developer]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-25-keeping-your-skillset-fresh-as-a-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-25-keeping-your-skillset-fresh-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T17:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’re committing 30 minutes or 3 hours a day to learning, consistency is key. Klint Finley asks 3 tech professionals at different stages in their career for more advice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-Definition Segmentation in Google Meet]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/high-definition-segmentation-in-google.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/high-definition-segmentation-in-google.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tingbo Hou and Juhyun Lee, Software Engineers, Google 
In recent years video conferencing has played an increasingly important role in both work and personal communication for many users. Over the past two years, we have enhanced this experience in Google Meet by introducing privacy-preserving machine learning (ML) powered background features, also known as “virtual green screen”, which allows users to blur their backgrounds or replace them with other images. What is unique about this solution is that it runs directly in the browser without the need to install additional software.  
So far, these ML-powered features have relied on CPU inference made possible by leveraging neural network sparsity, a common solution that works across devices, from entry level computers to high-end …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Fine-Grained Visual Embedding Powered by Amazon QuickSight]]></title>
        <id>a1501b50fea420ead40fcf160e7a0bea82b5b85f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-fine-grained-visual-embedding-powered-by-amazon-quicksight/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T16:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing a new feature, Fine-Grained Visual Embedding Powered by Amazon QuickSight. With this feature, individual visualizations from Amazon QuickSight dashboards can now be embedded in high-traffic webpages and applications. Additionally, this feature enables you to provide rich insights for your end-users where they need them the most, without server or software setup […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Trilogy: a new database adapter for Ruby on Rails]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-25-introducing-trilogy-a-new-database-adapter-for-ruby-on-rails/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-25-introducing-trilogy-a-new-database-adapter-for-ruby-on-rails/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've open sourced Trilogy, the database adapter we use to connect Ruby on Rails to MySQL-compatible database servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Monthly: August 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-25-open-source-monthly-august-2022-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-25-open-source-monthly-august-2022-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T13:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month's featured open source project, Open Sauced, connects contributors and maintainers through analytical insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools Plugin 2022.8 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=275401</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/08/25/edutools-plugin-2022-8-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T11:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools 2022.8 is here with the ability for course creators to specify the input for output tasks. With a predefined set of inputs and outputs, no extra tests are required to check a learner’s solution. We also improved plugin quality by fixing bugs. You can install the EduTool plugin or update it to the latest […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Git With Jupyter Notebooks in DataSpell]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=274407</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2022/08/how-to-use-git-with-jupyter-notebooks/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T08:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re like me and many other data scientists, you’re more of a casual user of Git and mostly use it to keep track of changes to your notebooks and share them with others. As I tend to work on the same project for months, I am always forgetting Git basics such as how to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jodie Burchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And when we disagree…]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41701</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/707898072/0/sethsblog~And-when-we-disagree/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hallmark of a resilient, productive and sustainable culture is that disagreements aren’t risky. When someone cares enough to make an assertion and show their work, a healthy organization or society takes a look. The alternative is the brittle, closed culture of talking points, loyalty oaths and unquestioned status quo. It might be a neighborhood […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-fellow-java-champion-and-timescaledb-developer-advocate-christoph-engelbert</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-fellow-java-champion-and-timescaledb-developer-advocate-christoph-engelbert"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert (@noctarius2k) about PostgreSQL, Java, time series databases, observability, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Run Tasks Ecosystem Continues to Grow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-run-tasks-ecosystem-continues-to-grow</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-run-tasks-ecosystem-continues-to-grow"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teams can now integrate oak9 and Torq into the Terraform Cloud workflow via run tasks. Plus: A list of integrations now validated to work with Terraform Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Console improvements in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-console-improvements-in-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-console-improvements-in-kibana"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how recent improvements in Kibana Console can boost your productivity in versions 8.1 through 8.4 of the Elastic Stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CJ Cenizal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How personalization pays off for online retailers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-personalization-pays-off-for-online-retailers</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-personalization-pays-off-for-online-retailers"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting data back to customers is key to reaping rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Console improvements in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-console-improvements-in-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-console-improvements-in-kibana"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For the past nine months, one of our engineers, Muhammad Ibragimov, has been quietly building new features, fixing bugs, and generally polishing the heck out of Kibana Console. From performance improvements to the ability to leave comments inside request bodies, he and the team have done some incredible work on this app that’s used and loved by so many. Read on to learn how these and other improvements can boost your productivity in versions 8.1 through 8.4 of the Elastic Stack.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt3dc4ca4570bbef66/6304fb60e8e6887097a15861/blog-elastic-kibanaconsole-1.png,blog-elastic-kibanaconsole-1.png,
Major features
There are five sweet new features I’d like to share with you.
1. Send requests to Kibana APIs
In 8.3, we shipped the ability to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CJ Cenizal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How personalization pays off for online retailers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-personalization-pays-off-for-online-retailers</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-personalization-pays-off-for-online-retailers"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The concept of 'know your customer' has been the gold standard in the retail world for decades. The more you understand your customers' needs and desires, and the better you're able to connect with them on a one-to-one basis, the more you can ensure their loyalty.



Thanks to ecommerce, stores can know more about their customers than ever before. Online retailers are awash in data detailing how often shoppers visited their stores, what products they searched for, what they considered, and what they ended up buying.



But making that data connect back to information about customers — through demographics, intent, and browsing history — is still a significant challenge. Stores that master this challenge reap much greater rewards. A June 2022 study by Wakefield Research (sponsored by Elas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.25: Pod Security Admission Controller in Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/25/pod-security-admission-stable/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/25/pod-security-admission-stable/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Tim Allclair (Google), Sam Stoelinga (Google)
The release of Kubernetes v1.25 marks a major milestone for Kubernetes out-of-the-box pod security
controls: Pod Security admission (PSA) graduated to stable, and Pod Security Policy (PSP) has been
removed.
PSP was deprecated in Kubernetes v1.21,
and no longer functions in Kubernetes v1.25 and later.
The Pod Security admission controller replaces PodSecurityPolicy, making it easier to enforce predefined
Pod Security Standards by
simply adding a label to a namespace. The Pod Security Standards are maintained by the K8s
community, which means you automatically get updated security policies whenever new
security-impacting Kubernetes features are introduced.
What’s new since Beta?
Pod Security Admission hasn’t changed much since the Beta i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using ML to Boost Engagement with a Maternal and Child Health Program in India]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/using-ml-to-boost-engagement-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/using-ml-to-boost-engagement-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Aparna Taneja, Software Engineer, and Milind Tambe, Principal Scientist, Google Research, India Research Lab 
The widespread availability of mobile phones has enabled non-profits to deliver critical health information to their beneficiaries in a timely manner. While advanced applications on smartphones allow for richer multimedia content and two-way communication between beneficiaries and health coaches, simpler text and voice messaging services can be effective in disseminating information to large communities, particularly those that are underserved with limited access to information and smartphones. ARMMAN1, one non-profit doing just this, is based in India with the mission of improving maternal and child health outcomes in underserved communities. 
    


Overview of ARMMAN

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning for Budget Constrained Recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6cbc5263a32a</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/reinforcement-learning-for-budget-constrained-recommendations-6cbc5263a32a?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Ehtsham Elahi
with James McInerney, Nathan Kallus, Dario Garcia Garcia and Justin Basilico]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS Support App in Slack to Manage Support Cases]]></title>
        <id>7987abd39e83187889bce5fb0aa7f7f73557375e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-support-app-in-slack-to-manage-support-cases/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatOps speeds up software development and operations by enabling DevOps teams to use chat clients and chatbots to communicate and run tasks. DevOps engineers have increasingly moved their monitoring, system management, continuous integration (CI), and continuous delivery (CD) workflows to chat applications in order to streamline activities in a single place and enable better collaboration […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is available now!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/24/spring-batch-5-0-0-m5-is-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/24/spring-batch-5-0-0-m5-is-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is now available from our milestone repository. The main theme of this milestone is improving testing support in Spring Batch. This post walks through the major changes in this area as well as other changes introduced in this milestone release. For the complete list of changes, see the release notes.
Test utilities configuration updates

Up to version 4.3, the JobLauncherTestUtils used to autowire the job under test with the goal of facilitating the test setup. But what if multiple jobs are defined in the test context? And what if no Job beans are defined at all? So while this autowiring was convenient for most cases, it turned out to cause several issues in the aforementioned situations. In this release, and based on community feedback,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps and CI/CD with automation controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/devops-and-ci/cd-with-automation-controller</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/devops-and-ci/cd-with-automation-controller"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog shares practical examples of using Ansible Automation Platform to accelerate your DevOps journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entity Framework Core and Multiple Database Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=267202</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/08/24/entity-framework-core-and-multiple-database-providers/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T12:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While many software developers would prefer to sell software as a service (SaaS), there’s a market for offering your customers a self-hosted solution tailored to their infrastructure choices. Of course, one essential element of any modern software solution is the database, but in 2022 there are hundreds of battle-tested storage solutions. For example, the Entity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Annotated – August 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=275620</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/08/php-annotated-august-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T10:11:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings everyone! Welcome to the August installment of PHP Annotated, where we’ll catch up on the most interesting things that have happened in the PHP world over the last month, including curated news, articles, tools, and videos. News PHP 8.2 Beta 3 has been released The final beta has been delivered according to schedule. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Association]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43598</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/707772720/0/sethsblog~The-Association/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T08:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have competition, but you might be wrong about who they are. The freelance wedding photographer can easily imagine that the other professional photographers in town are the ones to beat. The romance author might imagine that the other romance authors are competing for shelf space and sales. I could give the cold shoulder to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The results of turning your data into intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-results-of-turning-your-data-into-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-results-of-turning-your-data-into-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent third-party survey, over 600 technology and telecom companies shared their Elastic experiences. Learn how these companies are using Elastic to deliver the next-gen technologies that are reshaping customer journeys and improving lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 8.4: Supercharged relevance for Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-4-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-4-0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 8.4 delivers enhanced vector-based querying for searching and analyzing datasets large and small, with little to no implementation overhead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Chow,Serena Chou,Jonas Lavoie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 8.4 introduces SOAR for modern security operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-4-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-4-0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 8.4 delivers SOAR to accelerate response via built-in automation and customizable orchestration capabilities. Elastic further expands the set of third-party SOAR vendors through partnerships with D3 and Torq.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud 8.4: Reduce size for metric data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-4-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-4-0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce metrics storage with Elasticsearch’s synthetic _source, implement similarity search with KNN in _search API. Explain log rate spikes, schedule alert snoozes. Fleet logstash output is GA and customizable integration ingest pipelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Platform team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search, solve, and succeed with Elastic 8.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-4-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-4-0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With enhancements to native vector search capabilities, smarter alert and incident management for AIOps, and an ever-expanding ecosystem of SOAR partnerships —  Elastic 8.4 is helping the world’s leading organizations to search, solve, and succeed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Courcy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-6-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-6-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.17.6 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.6 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
The 7.17.6 patch release includes a JDK update that pertains to a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security statement for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes:
7.17.6 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ioana Tagirta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The results of turning your data into intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-results-of-turning-your-data-into-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-results-of-turning-your-data-into-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Technology and telecom companies have been at the helm of some of the most advanced technologies, such as 5G, AI, and IoT — pushing the boundaries of what’s possible in a connected world. They use data as the linchpin in building innovative applications that leverage these core technologies. In the fiercely competitive technology and telecom markets, these companies need to find relevant information faster, accelerate decision-making, and avoid data blind spots that can risk business growth and continuity.

Elastic is a search-powered data platform that can help them unlock insights from seemingly disparate data, empower teams to collaborate and solve problems faster, generate trust among customers, and build confidence within the ecosystem.

In a recent third-party survey managed and an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 8.4: Supercharged relevance for Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-4-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-4-0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In Enterprise Search 8.4, hybrid ranking for vector similarity is now available from the main querying endpoint, commonly known as the _search Elasticsearch endpoint.

Introduced as a standalone query endpoint in 8.0, vector querying functionality (specifically, kNN vector similarity) greatly simplifies and accelerates the process of crafting and issuing queries that leverage the native vector querying capabilities of Elasticsearch along with the tried-and-tested traditional scoring algorithms.

With this approach, a new hybrid retrieval method now combines vector similarity with query scoring, so you can integrate vector search with your existing Elasticsearch scoring functions. Now, there is no need to use a separate endpoint and manual rescore documents across multiple query types — i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Chow,Serena Chou,Jonas Lavoie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 8.4 introduces SOAR for modern security operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-4-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-4-0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
New in Elastic Security 8.4, Elastic introduces SOAR capabilities to empower modern security operation centers (SOCs) to streamline analyst operations. 

Modern SOCs are running headlong into numerous challenges. While the visibility and impact of security operations has become a board-level issue, the resources available to those security teams are still limited. Data is exploding, and correspondingly, the responsibility of the security team has been increasing. Teams are tasked with protecting a perimeter-less, distributed environment while also assessing the risk of SaaS providers and shared services.

To address these challenges, many organizations have begun unifying teams with similar goals in order to share best practices and reduce the skills gap. The walls between observability …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud 8.4: Reduce size for metric data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-4-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-4-0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are pleased to announce the release of Elastic 8.4. 

In Elasticsearch, synthetic _source is the first of many future innovations designed to reduce storage for machine generated data. An impressive reduction in index size by tens of percentage points will help you store more metric data at the same cost. Elasticsearch also welcomes KNN to the _search API endpoint. You can now implement similarity search on vector embeddings directly from the _search syntax you are familiar with.

Analyze and reduce MTTR of production problems or security threats with the “explain log rate spikes” functionality. Using explain log rate spikes, you can easily identify the root cause of significant deviations in your log message rates.


Finally in 8.4, Kibana introduces a new option for scheduling snooz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Platform team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search, solve, and succeed with Elastic 8.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-4-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-4-0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today, we are pleased to announce the latest iteration of the world’s leading platform for search-powered solutions with the general availability of Elastic 8.4.

Elastic 8.4 introduces a broad set of new capabilities to the Elastic Search Platform and its three built-in solutions — Elastic Enterprise Search, Elastic Observability, and Elastic Security.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltbc40559ca61d0e9c/62fbd55a7ca59e6977e5e0de/8-4-announcement.png,8-4-announcement.png,
What’s new?
Elastic Enterprise Search is the gold standard for implementing powerful, modern search and discovery experiences with Elasticsearch — enabling you to search everything, anywhere.

With Elastic 8.4, Elastic Enterprise Search delivers both increasingly flexible data ingestion option…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Courcy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-6-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-6-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ioana Tagirta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tetherball Configurations]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2663/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2663/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/tetherball_configurations.png" title="Ground-pole-ball-pole can be fun if you shake the first pole to get the second one whipping around dangerously, but the ball at the joint gets torn apart pretty fast." alt="Ground-pole-ball-pole can be fun if you shake the first pole to get the second one whipping around dangerously, but the ball at the joint gets torn apart pretty fast." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: PodSecurityPolicy: The Historical Context]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/podsecuritypolicy-the-historical-context/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/podsecuritypolicy-the-historical-context/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mahé Tardy (Quarkslab)
The PodSecurityPolicy (PSP) admission controller has been removed, as of
Kubernetes v1.25. Its deprecation was announced and detailed in the blog post
PodSecurityPolicy Deprecation: Past, Present, and Future,
published for the Kubernetes v1.21 release.
This article aims to provide historical context on the birth and evolution of
PSP, explain why the feature never made it to stable, and show why it was
removed and replaced by Pod Security admission control.
PodSecurityPolicy, like other specialized admission control plugins, provided
fine-grained permissions on specific fields concerning the pod security settings
as a built-in policy API. It acknowledged that cluster administrators and
cluster users are usually not the same people, and that creating workloads …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UVQ: Measuring YouTube's Perceptual Video Quality]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/uvq-measuring-youtubes-perceptual-video.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/uvq-measuring-youtubes-perceptual-video.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T17:02:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yilin Wang, Staff Software Engineer, YouTube and Feng Yang, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research 
Online video sharing platforms, like YouTube, need to understand perceptual video quality (i.e., a user's subjective perception of video quality) in order to better optimize and improve user experience. Video quality assessment (VQA) attempts to build a bridge between video signals and perceptual quality by using objective mathematical models to approximate the subjective opinions of users. Traditional video quality metrics, like peak signal-to-noise ratio (PSNR) and Video Multi-Method Assessment Fusion (VMAF), are reference-based and focus on the relative difference between the target and reference videos. Such metrics, which work best on professionally generated content …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.2.2 Improves the Modify Object UI]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=274735</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/08/23/datagrip-2022-2-2-improves-the-modify-object-ui/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T15:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This bug-fix update is focused on enhancing the new Modify Object UI. Before listing what we’ve improved, let us give you a bit more background info about how the new UI came about. Why the new UI? At some point it became clear that the whole Modify Object UI had to be rewritten from scratch. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maksim Sobolevskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA Meetup. Free Onsite Event in Munich]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=275372</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/08/intellij-idea-meetup-free-onsite-event-in-munich/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T13:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At JetBrains we like to say that we build our software so you can enjoy building yours. It gives us a lot of satisfaction to know that people worldwide use our IDEs, plugins, languages, and other tools at work, school, or when developing their pet projects. We’re developers too, and we learn many new things […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ida Bzowska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The full lineup for Git Merge 2022 revealed]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-23-the-full-lineup-for-git-merge-2022-revealed/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-23-the-full-lineup-for-git-merge-2022-revealed/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T13:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the full lineup of talks and workshops for this year’s Git Merge conference in Chicago. 17 talks, 3 workshops, 1 panel, and some great company!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in Datalore: BigQuery Support, SSH tunneling, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=234602</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2022/08/23/new-in-datalore-bigquery-support-ssh-tunneling-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T12:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In today’s newsletter we’ll mostly talk about the recent improvements for data connections in Datalore, but first… Meet us at BigDataLDN! On September 21st, our team will be attending BigDataLDN and it’ll be a great chance to meet in person! If you are going, drop us a line on Twitter and swing by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why hyperautomation can help developers grow]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60513</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/why-hyperautomation-can-help-developers-grow/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technological advances of the last decade have caused consumer and user expectations to skyrocket. Digital-first companies used this to their advantage early on by delivering a better experience and improving it over time. As a result, disruptive companies were able to widen the gap between their products and their competitors more quickly. Innovative technology like Internet-of-Things, augmented reality, blockchain, or artificial intelligence are just some of the tools opening up new possibilities for both corporations and the developers they rely on. The growing variety of emerging solutions provide developers a chance to solve complex problems in new ways. Learning the skills to harness new technologies increases your employability and gives you a leg up to secure a better job and...
The post Why hyperautomation can help developers grow appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Next: WebStorm 2022.3 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=274738</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/08/webstorm-2022-3-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T11:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We rolled out WebStorm 2022.2, our second major update of 2022, in July. Today we want to tell you about our plans for the next release, which is coming this November. We’ll continue improving the overall quality of WebStorm and fix some long-standing bugs. Here are the biggest things we’ve planned for WebStorm 2022.3: Further […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Ryabukha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet Below Deck, Part V – The Story of Code Completion]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=fleet&amp;p=274314</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/fleet/2022/08/fleet-below-deck-part-v-the-story-of-code-completion/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T11:09:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a multipart series on building Fleet, a next-generation IDE by JetBrains. Part I – Architecture Overview Part II – Breaking Down the Editor Part III – State Management Part IV – Distributed Transactions Part V – The Story of Code Completion In Parts III and IV of this series, we discussed the complicated […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vitaly Bragilevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2022.2.1 Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=274808</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2022/08/2022-2-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T09:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first minor update to DataSpell 2022.2 brings the ability to copy-paste directories between your local machine and remote Jupyter servers, as well as better rendering for Markdown and HTML tables in the Jupyter editor. Let’s take a closer look! You can download the new version from our website, update directly from the IDE, update […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup costs]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42576</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/707648728/0/sethsblog~Startup-costs/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s typical to include machines, rent, stationery, all that stuff. But the real startup costs are the missteps, errors and learnings that every new project goes through on the way to success. They’re not mistakes. They’re part of the deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Next: PhpStorm 2022.3 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=274819</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/08/what-s-next-phpstorm-2022-3-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T09:11:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm has been around for more than 10 years. From the beginning, our task tracker has been open, allowing anyone to send us bug reports or suggest new features. We always strive to be more transparent and collect feedback from you, our users, as early as possible. So this time, we want to share with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Access Program for MPS 2022.2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=mps&amp;p=274924</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/mps/2022/08/early-access-program-for-mps-2022-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T07:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As previously mentioned, we decided to skip MPS 2022.1 as we were too busy fixing issues from the last release and didn’t have enough time to prepare the new functionality. Now we have new features to present to give you a glimpse of what’s to come in MPS 2022.2. DOWNLOAD MPS 2022.2 EAP Annotations in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oscar Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 23rd, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/23/this-week-in-spring-august-23rd-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/23/this-week-in-spring-august-23rd-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We’ve got a ton to cover, so let’s dive right into it!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Flowable founder Joram Barrez on a Bootiful Podcast on workflow, business process management, and more

  
Building IoT Applications Using Fauna and Spring

  
Cosmos DB for Spring Developers, Part I: Using Cosmos DB as a SQL Database

  
How to Build Web Servers with Paketo Buildpacks - Paketo Buildpacks

  
Introducing Experimental Spring Support for Apache Pulsar

  
Propagating Exceptions With OpenFeign and Spring

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M1 available now

  
Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M1 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.6.11 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.7.3 available now

  
Spring Boot Actuator

  
Spring Boot Native image builds with 22.2.0 are failing · Issue #176 paketo-buildpacks/native-image - this is in regards to an issue related to Buildpacks that just appeared last week. There’s a workaround that’s been recently deployed.

  
Spring Boot and Spring Security with JWT including Access and Refresh Tokens 🔑

  
Spring JDBC Batch Inserts

  
Spring Security 5.8.0-M2 is released

  
Spring Shell 2.1.1 is now available

  
Spring for GraphQL with Querydsl.

  
Testcontainers and Spring Boot for local development and integration testing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You don't need to be perfect at work. Here’s how to adopt a different mindset.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-you-dont-have-to-be-perfect</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-you-dont-have-to-be-perfect"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being perfect, at work or at home, sounds like a great goal. It can motivate you and engage you, but it can also lead to working longer hours and the inability to disengage. Here are a few ways to get out of the “I need to be perfect” mindset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You don't need to be perfect at work. Here’s how to adopt a different mindset.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-you-dont-have-to-be-perfect</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-you-dont-have-to-be-perfect"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Being perfect, at work or at home, sounds like a great goal. It can motivate you and engage you, but it can also lead to working longer hours and the inability to disengage. In a study that looked at the relationship between perfectionism and employees’ effectiveness, the need to be perfect is strongly and consistently related with burnout, anxiety, and depression. 
But if you strive to be perfect at work, you’re not alone. Another study found the need to be perfect has increased over time, citing the comparisons with each other on social media and the competitive environments in colleges and employers as the main culprits.
It’s easy to compare yourself to coworkers, other people in your industry, your manager, and a whole host of other people you interact with. If you find yourself havi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.25: Combiner]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/kubernetes-v1-25-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/kubernetes-v1-25-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes 1.25 Release Team
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.25!
This release includes a total of 40 enhancements. Fifteen of those enhancements are entering Alpha, ten are graduating to Beta, and thirteen are graduating to Stable. We also have two features being deprecated or removed.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes 1.25: Combiner
The theme for Kubernetes v1.25 is Combiner.
The Kubernetes project itself is made up of many, many individual components that, when combined, take the form of the project you see today. It is also built and maintained by many individuals, all of them with different skills, experiences, histories, and interests, who join forces not just as the release team but as the many SIGs that support the project and the community year-round.
With this rel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 22, 2022]]></title>
        <id>cd57561ca684dacfdb5a73e1204fff6a6bfa1214</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-22-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T18:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I’m back from my summer holidays and ready to get up to date with the latest AWS news from last week! Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Cloud Skills Shortage Is Affecting Multi-Cloud Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-a-cloud-skills-shortage-is-affecting-multi-cloud-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-a-cloud-skills-shortage-is-affecting-multi-cloud-adoption"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 State of Cloud Strategy survey reveals that IT organizations are turning to platform teams and automated tools to bridge a growing skills shortage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 10th Anniversary, Amazon S3 Glacier – A Decade of Cold Storage in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>2d8c2df87af9a66f78fc7d7776db8517bedf54f4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-10th-anniversary-amazon-s3-glacier-a-decade-of-cold-storage-in-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T15:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten years ago, on August 20, 2012, AWS announced the general availability of Amazon Glacier, secure, reliable, and extremely low-cost storage designed for data archiving and backup. At the time, I was working as an AWS customer and it felt like an April Fools’ joke, offering long-term, secure, and durable cloud storage that allowed me […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing a VMware Template Lifecycle with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/managing-a-vmware-template-lifecycle-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/managing-a-vmware-template-lifecycle-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we manage a large number of virtual machines (VMs), we want to reduce the differences between them and create a standard template. By using a standard template, it becomes easier to manage and propagate the same operation on the different nodes. When using VMware vSphere, it is a common practice to share a standardized VM template and use it to create new VMs. This template is often called a golden image. Its creation involves a series of steps that can be automated with Ansible. In this blog, we will see how one can create and use a new golden image.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gonéri Le Bouder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five true statements we don’t hear very often]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43545</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/707520306/0/sethsblog~Five-true-statements-we-dont-hear-very-often/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T08:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a shame, because it would help us do a much better job of bringing ideas to people: “I don’t care enough to do what you’re asking.” “I don’t trust you enough to hear you out.” “I don’t believe it’s worth what it will cost in time, money or risk.” “I’m afraid of the changes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad Service Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-service-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-service-discovery"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad’s addition of native service discovery offers a new option for simple service registration, plus integration with Consul for more complex service mesh use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physics Safety Tip]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2662/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2662/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/physics_safety_tip.png" title="In general, avoid exposure to any temperatures, pressures, particle energies, or states of matter that physicists think are neat." alt="In general, avoid exposure to any temperatures, pressures, particle energies, or states of matter that physicists think are neat." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/22/sig-storage-spotlight/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/22/sig-storage-spotlight/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS)
Since the very beginning of Kubernetes, the topic of persistent data and how to address the requirement of stateful applications has been an important topic. Support for stateless deployments was natural, present from the start, and garnered attention, becoming very well-known. Work on better support for stateful applications was also present from early on, with each release increasing the scope of what could be run on Kubernetes.
Message queues, databases, clustered filesystems: these are some examples of the solutions that have different storage requirements and that are, today, increasingly deployed in Kubernetes. Dealing with ephemeral and persistent storage, local or remote, file or block, from many different vendors, while considering how to provide the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opportunity is now disorganized]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42562</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/707414524/0/sethsblog~Opportunity-is-now-disorganized/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-21T08:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It used to be well lit. Apply to a famous institution, get picked. Get the agent of an agent or A&R person. Get picked. Get good grades… get picked. Now, many of the “pickers” have little influence or power. Instead of the reassurance that comes from someone else telling us what to do and then […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just that one scarce resource]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43578</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/707252996/0/sethsblog~Just-that-one-scarce-resource/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-20T09:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing our impact or profit usually involves maximizing something that’s valuable. And things that are valuable are often scarce. Finding the one thing that is at the heart of your value/scarcity matrix makes it much easier to focus your energy on strategic decisions. If you own a single store, you need to maximize the profit […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/19/spring-shell-2-1-1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/19/spring-shell-2-1-1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T13:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release and Maven Central.

Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clues that you might not be trying hard enough]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42555</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/707040474/0/sethsblog~Clues-that-you-might-not-be-trying-hard-enough/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T07:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You usually succeed You rarely feel like an imposter You already know what you need to know You’re confident it’s going to work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Age Milestone Privileges]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2661/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2661/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/age_milestone_privileges.png" title="If you reach 122, you get complete unrevertible editorial control over Jeanne Calment's Wikipedia article." alt="If you reach 122, you get complete unrevertible editorial control over Jeanne Calment's Wikipedia article." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OptFormer: Towards Universal Hyperparameter Optimization with Transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/optformer-towards-universal.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/optformer-towards-universal.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T19:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yutian Chen, Staff Research Scientist, DeepMind, and Xingyou (Richard) Song, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team 
One of the most important aspects in machine learning is hyperparameter optimization, as finding the right hyperparameters for a machine learning task can make or break a model’s performance. Internally, we regularly use Google Vizier as the default platform for hyperparameter optimization. Throughout its deployment over the last 5 years, Google Vizier has been used more than 10 million times, over a vast class of applications, including machine learning applications from vision, reinforcement learning, and language but also scientific applications such as protein discovery and hardware acceleration. As Google Vizier is able to keep track of use patterns i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.4 Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-4-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-4-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.4 introduces support for the new beta version of the Kubernetes Gateway API and HTTP path rewrites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary 0.10 Expands Credential Management and Admin UI IAM Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-10-expands-credential-management-and-admin-ui-iam-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-10-expands-credential-management-and-admin-ui-iam-workflows"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary 0.10 adds support for credential management of SSH keys and enhanced IAM workflows in the admin UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Flowable founder Joram Barrez on a Bootiful Podcast on workflow, business process management, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/a-bootiful-podcast-flowable-founder-joram-barrez-on-a-bootiful-podcast-on-workflow-business-process-management-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/a-bootiful-podcast-flowable-founder-joram-barrez-on-a-bootiful-podcast-on-workflow-business-process-management-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Flowable founder Joram Barrez (@jbarrez) about workflow, business process management (BPM), decision management, rules, and so much more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/spring-boot-2-7-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/spring-boot-2-7-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T07:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.3 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 48 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.11 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-boot-2-6-11-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-boot-2-6-11-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T06:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.11 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 40 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第215話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270375685435178676</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270375685435178676"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Stargazing, solutions and staycations: the Kubernetes 1.24 release interview]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/18/stargazing-solutions-and-staycations-the-kubernetes-1.24-release-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/18/stargazing-solutions-and-staycations-the-kubernetes-1.24-release-interview/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Craig Box (Google)
The Kubernetes project has participants from all around the globe. Some are friends, some are colleagues, and some are strangers. The one thing that unifies them, no matter their differences, are that they all have an interesting story. It is my pleasure to be the documentarian for the stories of the Kubernetes community in the weekly Kubernetes Podcast from Google. With every new Kubernetes release comes an interview with the release team lead, telling the story of that release, but also their own personal story.
With 1.25 around the corner, the tradition continues with a look back at the story of 1.24. That release was led by James Laverack of Jetstack. James was on the podcast in May, and while you can read his story below, if you can, please do listen to it i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrialized Workflows - Using Microsoft CAF Patterns and Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/industrialized-workflows-using-microsoft-caf-patterns-and-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/industrialized-workflows-using-microsoft-caf-patterns-and-terraform"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how even non-technical operators can use HashiCorp Terraform Cloud to deploy Azure resources based on Microsoft's Cloud Adoption Framework (CAF) templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Trusted Advisor – New Priority Capability]]></title>
        <id>b0c7ecebd1612af876be081dc850f50a0a0ebf98</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-trusted-advisor-new-priority-capability/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T17:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Trusted Advisor is a service that continuously analyzes your AWS accounts and provides recommendations to help you to follow AWS best practices and AWS Well-Architected guidelines. Trusted Advisor implements a series of checks. These checks identify ways to optimize your AWS infrastructure, improve security and performance, reduce costs, and monitor service quotas. Today, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Discussions is now available on GitHub Enterprise Server]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-17-github-discussions-is-now-available-on-github-enterprise-server/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-17-github-discussions-is-now-available-on-github-enterprise-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T16:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of GitHub Enterprise Server 3.6, enterprise customers will now be able to use GitHub Discussions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Survey Shows Broad Cloud Waste — HashiCorp Terraform Can Help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-survey-shows-broad-cloud-waste-hashicorp-terraform-can-help</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-survey-shows-broad-cloud-waste-hashicorp-terraform-can-help"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to our 2022 State of Cloud Strategy Survey, 94% of organizations have avoidable cloud spending. See where the money’s going and how Terraform can help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.6 is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-17-github-enterprise-server-3-6-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-17-github-enterprise-server-3-6-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T13:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Discussions and Audit Log Streaming, new automation features, and security enhancements are available now in GitHub Enterprise Server 3.6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating automation execution environments using ansible-builder and Shipwright]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-automation-execution-environments-using-ansible-builder-and-shipwright</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-automation-execution-environments-using-ansible-builder-and-shipwright"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reproducibility and consistency are two key traits that are the driving forces behind the popularity of containers. Consistency is also a principle found within Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. With only a few lines of YAML-formatted manifests, thousands of instances can be set up and configured uniformly. While the management of target instances is simple, it is the control node, or where the Ansible execution is initiated, that can  be the most challenging aspect. As Ansible is written in Python, does the machine have the correct version of Python installed?  Are the necessary Python modules installed? Are there any operating system dependencies needed? The list goes on and on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ablock@redhat.com (Andrew Block)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-1-0-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-1-0-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M1.



You can download it from repo.spring.io milestone repository by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:1.0.0-M1'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-0-4-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-0-4-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M1.



You can download it from repo.spring.io milestone repository by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.4.0-M1'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Transparency Report: January to June]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-16-2022-transparency-report-january-to-june/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-16-2022-transparency-report-january-to-june/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re reporting on a six-month period rather than annually to increase our level of transparency. For this report, we’ve continued with the more granular reporting we began in our 2021 reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Grillo Built a Low-Cost Earthquake Early Warning System on AWS]]></title>
        <id>13b116ed4d0b61d043f96e454e4cc6a616f9f183</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-grillo-built-a-low-cost-earthquake-early-warning-system-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T18:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is estimated that 50 percent of the injuries caused when a high magnitude earthquake affects an area are because of falls or falling hazards. This means that most of these injuries could have been prevented if the population had a few seconds of warning to take cover. Grillo, a social impact enterprise focused on seismology, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.8.0-M2 is released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/spring-security-5-8-0-m2-is-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/spring-security-5-8-0-m2-is-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.8.0-M2 is available now.



This release includes dependency upgrades, bug fixes, and enhancements. Here are a few noteworthy changes:





Hash-based Content-Security-Policy for SAML post pages



Customization of redirect strategy





See the 5.8.0-M2 release notes for more details.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards Helpful Robots: Grounding Language in Robotic Affordances]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/towards-helpful-robots-grounding.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/towards-helpful-robots-grounding.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T14:02:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brian Ichter and Karol Hausman, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Over the last several years, we have seen significant progress in applying machine learning to robotics. However, robotic systems today are capable of executing only very short, hard-coded commands, such as “Pick up an apple,” because they tend to perform best with clear tasks and rewards. They struggle with learning to perform long-horizon tasks and reasoning about abstract goals, such as a user prompt like “I just worked out, can you get me a healthy snack?” 
Meanwhile, recent progress in training language models (LMs) has led to systems that can perform a wide range of language understanding and generation tasks with impressive results. However, these language models are inherently not grounded i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Experimental Spring Support for Apache Pulsar]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/introducing-experimental-spring-support-for-apache-pulsar</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/introducing-experimental-spring-support-for-apache-pulsar"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce that we are incubating a new experimental Spring project for Apache Pulsar. This project aims to provide Spring-friendly APIs, building blocks, and programming models for writing Java applications that interact with Apache Pulsar. 

Apache Pulsar is a popular messaging system with a growing ecosystem of developers in the enterprise messaging and streaming space. Here are some main features and advantages of using Apache Pulsar for messaging-based software applications:


  
Apache Pulsar provides both the traditional queuing semantics of RabbitMQ, ActiveMQ, and others and the log-based structure of Apache Kafka through various subscription models.

  
The broker in Apache Pulsar is stateless, and the storage is not part of the broker. Instead, it uses another A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 16th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/this-week-in-spring-august-16th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/this-week-in-spring-august-16th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another wonder-filled installment of This Week in Spring! It’s been a week! Sometimes I can scarcely believe it myself. And can you believe it’s August 16th already?? My daughter’s starting school this week! We’re in the northern hemisphere, and Summer break is already over and done with for her. There’s still another month and some change of summer, officially, though. So, I hope you all are doing whatever you can to maximize your enjoyment of it before the darker and colder months arrive. 

Twitter helps me pass the time. I’ve been working on some code and wanted to use Twitter’s OAuth 2 and PKCE support in the application but couldn’t quite make it work. So I pinged my pal (everybody’s pal, really!) and Spring Security lead Rob Winch (@rob_winch) for some cl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.3 and 5.6.7 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/15/spring-security-5-7-3-and-5-6-7-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/15/spring-security-5-7-3-and-5-6-7-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.7.3 and 5.6.7 are available now. In both cases the releases are largely composed of dependency upgrades and minor fixes.



To learn more, please visit the 5.7.3 and
 5.6.7 release summaries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Decade of Ever-Increasing Provisioned IOPS for Amazon EBS]]></title>
        <id>62b434c84905bf2a24ca8943b82a7e2149abf628</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/a-decade-of-ever-increasing-provisioned-iops-for-amazon-ebs/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T22:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress is often best appreciated in retrospect. It is often the case that a steady stream of incremental improvements over a long period of time ultimately adds up to a significant level of change. Today, ten years after we first launched the Provisioned IOPS feature for Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS), I strongly believe that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – HTTP/3 Support for Amazon CloudFront]]></title>
        <id>a4970c24e76d5efa333710d9e50da964387520ea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-http-3-support-for-amazon-cloudfront/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T22:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudFront is a content delivery network (CDN) service, a network of interconnected servers that is geographically closer to the users and reaches their computers much faster. Amazon CloudFront reduces latency by delivering data through 410+ globally dispersed Points of Presence (PoPs) with automated network mapping and intelligent routing. With Amazon CloudFront, content, API requests […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 15, 2022]]></title>
        <id>ec58e447970e428041f23a062ac4b1e7cf8bc433</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-15-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love the AWS Twitch channel for watching interesting online live shows such as AWS On Air, Containers from the Couch, and Serverless Office Hours. Last week, AWS Storage Day 2022 was hosted virtually on the AWS Twitch channel and covered recent announcements and insights that address customers’ needs to reduce and optimize storage costs and build data resiliency […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.13 Introduces Cluster Peering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-introduces-cluster-peering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-introduces-cluster-peering"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This release enhances a number of features in Consul while adding such new features as a Consul on Kubernetes CNI plugin and a beta version of cluster peering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The next step for LGTM.com: GitHub code scanning!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-15-the-next-step-for-lgtm-com-github-code-scanning/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-15-the-next-step-for-lgtm-com-github-code-scanning/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, GitHub code scanning has all of LGTM.com’s key features—and more! The time has therefore come to announce the plan for the gradual deprecation of LGTM.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.9.5 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/15/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-9-5-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/15/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-9-5-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.9.5 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release contains an update of the Spring Boot version (2.5.14) and numerous bug fixes. See the release notes for more information.
Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on Stackoverflow or GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Meet Our Contributors - APAC (China region)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/15/meet-our-contributors-china-ep-03/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/15/meet-our-contributors-china-ep-03/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors & Interviewers: Avinesh Tripathi, Debabrata Panigrahi, Jayesh Srivastava, Priyanka Saggu, Purneswar Prasad, Vedant Kakde
Hello, everyone 👋
Welcome back to the third edition of the "Meet Our Contributors" blog post series for APAC.
This post features four outstanding contributors from China, who have played diverse leadership and community roles in the upstream Kubernetes project.
So, without further ado, let's get straight to the article.
Andy Zhang
Andy Zhang currently works for Microsoft China at the Shanghai site. His main focus is on Kubernetes storage drivers. Andy started contributing to Kubernetes about 5 years ago.
He states that as he is working in Azure Kubernetes Service team and spends most of his time contributing to the Kubernetes community project. Now he is the mai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.15.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/12/spring-tools-4-15-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/12/spring-tools-4-15-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.15.3 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: Spring Boot Tools slow down code complete (#808)

  
(Language Server) fixed: Copied files should retain copyright ownership (#807)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-08-11-4153-release-incl-language-servers-version-1380

Spring Tools 4.16.0 is scheduled to be released in mid September 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS Private 5G – Build Your Own Private Mobile Network]]></title>
        <id>8f6fde13422a7d6f709abd13a6bff48a21025568</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-private-5g-build-your-own-private-mobile-network/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T22:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the mid-1990’s, I had a young family and 5 or 6 PCs in the basement. One day my son Stephen and I bought a single box that contained a bunch of 3COM network cards, a hub, some drivers, and some cables, and spent a pleasant weekend setting up our first home LAN. Introducing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rax: Composable Learning-to-Rank Using JAX]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/rax-composable-learning-to-rank-using.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/rax-composable-learning-to-rank-using.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T18:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rolf Jagerman and Honglei Zhuang, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Ranking is a core problem across a variety of domains, such as search engines, recommendation systems, or question answering. As such, researchers often utilize learning-to-rank (LTR), a set of supervised machine learning techniques that optimize for the utility of an entire list of items (rather than a single item at a time). A noticeable recent focus is on combining LTR with deep learning. Existing libraries, most notably TF-Ranking, offer researchers and practitioners the necessary tools to use LTR in their work. However, none of the existing LTR libraries work natively with JAX, a new machine learning framework that provides an extensible system of function transformations that compose: automatic different…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Sentinel Policies to the Terraform Registry (Beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-sentinel-policies-to-the-terraform-registry</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-sentinel-policies-to-the-terraform-registry"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Sentinel policies are now available in the Terraform Registry so you can publish policies you want to share and search the Registry for policies you need.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Successful Multi-Cloud Adoption Requires Automated Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/successful-multi-cloud-adoption-requires-automated-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/successful-multi-cloud-adoption-requires-automated-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HashiCorp’s new State of Cloud Strategy survey, 89% of respondents said that security is the key driver of their cloud success — here’s how to best secure your multi-cloud environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: the good Dr. Venkat Subramaniam]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/11/a-bootiful-podcast-the-good-dr-venkat-subramaniam</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/11/a-bootiful-podcast-the-good-dr-venkat-subramaniam"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to the good Dr. Venkat Subramaniam (@venkat_s) about the art of writing software, his latest projects, and more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Enhancing Kubernetes one KEP at a Time]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/11/enhancing-kubernetes-one-kep-at-a-time/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/11/enhancing-kubernetes-one-kep-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ryler Hockenbury (Mastercard)
Did you know that Kubernetes v1.24 has 46 enhancements? That's a lot of new functionality packed into a 4-month release cycle. The Kubernetes release team coordinates the logistics of the release, from remediating test flakes to publishing updated docs. It's a ton of work, but they always deliver.
The release team comprises around 30 people across six subteams - Bug Triage, CI Signal, Enhancements, Release Notes, Communications, and Docs.  Each of these subteams manages a component of the release. This post will focus on the role of the enhancements subteam and how you can get involved.
What's the enhancements subteam?
Great question. We'll get to that in a second but first, let's talk about how features are managed in Kubernetes.
Each new feature requ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to AWS Storage Day 2022]]></title>
        <id>895c8f94e7763a3e32f7029ecb7f0e5aefa364af</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/welcome-to-aws-storage-day-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are on the fourth year of our annual AWS Storage Day! Do you remember our first Storage Day 2019 and the subsequent Storage Day 2020? I watched Storage Day 2021, which was streamed live from downtown Seattle. We continue to hear from our customers about how powerful the Storage Day announcements and educational sessions […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Pages now uses Actions by default]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-10-github-pages-now-uses-actions-by-default/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-10-github-pages-now-uses-actions-by-default/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As GitHub Pages, home to 16 million websites, approaches its 15th anniversary, we’re excited to announce that all sites now build and deploy with GitHub Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Web Flow 3.0 M1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/10/spring-web-flow-3-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/10/spring-web-flow-3-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:26:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been almost 4 years since the last set of Spring Web Flow releases. Nevertheless, the project continues to serve a specific need particularly well, arguably better than alternatives, and remains in active use. While there hasn’t been a strong driver for new releases, the upcoming Spring Framework 6 brings a Java 17 baseline and makes the shift to Jakarta EE, which creates the need for such a release in order to enable applications to migrate to this new baseline.

Today I’m pleased to announce the availability of Spring Web Flow 3.0 M1 in the Spring milestone repository. This release focuses mainly on compatibility with Spring Framework 6 and Jakarta EE. The Travel booking-mvc sample on spring-projects/spring-webflow-samples has been updated and the commit history provides example changes. One significant change is the need to remove Tiles which has not migrated to Jakarta EE. In the sample, Thymeleaf Layouts is used instead.

Note that Spring Faces is not included in the release due to its deep integration with JSF and the additional time and effort required to migrate. Please, reach out if you have experience with Web Flow and JSF and are interested to help out with the migration of Spring Faces to Spring Framework 6 and Jakarta EE.

If you have a Web Flow application and you plan to migrate to Spring Framework 6, please give this milestone a try and provide feedback through the project issue tracker. Special thanks to Ian Young and Scott Cantor for their substantial contributions to this release!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual Production — A Validation Framework For Unreal Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/aab780b2f8c8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/virtual-production-a-validation-framework-for-unreal-engine-aab780b2f8c8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T14:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The use of virtual production and real time technologies in film & tv has accelerated in recent years. Game engines, such as Unreal Engine, have been a major part driving the democratization of advanced in-camera visual effects (ICVFX). But with infinite configuration and setting combinations, how can a production get it right?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Kubernetes Dynamic Inventories with kubernetes.core Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-kubernetes-dynamic-inventories-with-kubernetes.core-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-kubernetes-dynamic-inventories-with-kubernetes.core-modules"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When managing infrastructure, there are times when a dynamic inventory is essential. Kubernetes is a perfect example of this where you may create multiple applications within a namespace but you will not be able to create a static inventory due to Kubernetes appending a systems-generated string to uniquely identify objects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why R-KOM Chose Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60009</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/why-r-kom-chose-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog series, we highlight the customers who have chosen to utilize Camunda Platform 8 and explore the challenges those companies are attempting to overcome using process orchestration. For the latest installment of Why Camunda 8, we spoke with R-KOM, a telecommunications company based in Regensburg, Germany. When R-KOM was founded in 1997, its shareholders pooled their telecommunications infrastructure, which had evolved over decades with utility networks for water, electricity, and gas. Initially, R-KOM’s services were limited to business and the public sector, but now it has developed further in line with demand. Over the years, the company’s high-performance infrastructure and a broad range of products have grown. Today, R-KOM has a number of city networks in Eastern Bavaria...
The post Why R-KOM Chose Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Schroth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trust Security for Kubernetes with a Service Mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/zero-trust-security-for-kubernetes-with-a-service-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/zero-trust-security-for-kubernetes-with-a-service-mesh"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A service mesh like HashiCorp Consul can be an essential part of applying zero trust security principles to modern, complex, Kubernetes deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Azure DevOps Server 2022 RC1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65570</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-azure-devops-server-2022-rc1/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T18:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re very excited to announce the first release candidate (RC) of Azure DevOps Server 2022!
Delivery Plans
There are many more features with this release and you can read all about those features in our release notes.
The post Introducing Azure DevOps Server 2022 RC1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Video-Text Learning with Iterative Co-tokenization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/efficient-video-text-learning-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/efficient-video-text-learning-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T17:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by AJ Piergiovanni and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Video is an ubiquitous source of media content that touches on many aspects of people’s day-to-day lives. Increasingly, real-world video applications, such as video captioning, video content analysis, and video question-answering (VideoQA), rely on models that can connect video content with text or natural language. VideoQA is particularly challenging, however, as it requires grasping both semantic information, such as objects in a scene, as well as temporal information, e.g., how things move and interact, both of which must be taken in the context of a natural-language question that holds specific intent. In addition, because videos have many frames, processing all of them to learn spatio-temp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[August patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65582</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/august-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T16:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Fix identity value error while assigning a work item to an identity which appears in different domains.
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2 Patch 2
The post August patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha4 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=59448</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/camunda-automation-platform-7180-alpha4-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.18. This release features the following improvements: Support for H2 2.1 Traditional Chinese translations are available Improved status monitoring of batch jobs Improved safety of executing a batch operation on the Batch Operation page 8 Bug Fixes You can download Camunda for free or run it with Docker. For a complete list of all improvements, take a look at the release notes. Please also see the list of known issues. If you want to dig in deeper, you can find the source code on GitHub. Support for H2 2.1 This release adds support for the H2 database in version 2.1, which provides fixes for vulnerabilities. Enterprise customers...
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha4 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0 alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=59822</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce a new release of Camunda Optimize. Camunda Optimize provides business activity monitoring for workflows, supporting continuous process improvement by providing transparency into your automated workflows and decisions. Business-friendly reports, dashboards, and alerts make it possible to identify process bottlenecks, improve end-to-end processes, and evaluate the success of your process automation initiative. In the rest of this post, we’ll highlight some of the new capabilities introduced in Optimize 3.9.0 alpha3. What’s new? Ease of adding new reports to dashboard Reports are added to dashboards to design an individual overview of the performance of your processes. Adding reports to dashboards was already possible with previous versions of Optimize, but now we’ve reduced the number of steps to do...
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0 alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 9th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/09/this-week-in-spring-august-9th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/09/this-week-in-spring-august-9th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you this fine Tuesday? I’m in Kansas City for the Kansas City Developer Conference. It’s a crazy fun show, and I’m glad to be here. I only wish the rest of you were here, too! We’ve got a packed This Week in Spring, however, so let’s dive right into it.


  
snicoll/demo-aot-native: Demo of a basic webapp using Ahead-Of-Time compilation

  
A Bootiful Podcast: Observability guru Jonatan Ivanov on the future of observability in Spring Boot

  
Blog: Kubernetes Removals and Major Changes In 1.25

  
Building a Topic Exchange with RabbitMQ and .NET 6

  
Display Logged-in User’s Information in Thymeleaf

  
Dockerizing a Java Application

  
Get Started with Spring Boot and SAML

  
Resilient Kafka Consumers With Reactor Kafka - DZone Java

  
Spring Batch + Karp Rabin = How CRISPR CAS9 Works

  
Spring Tools 4.15.2 released

  
Upload Image With Spring Boot and Thymeleaf]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 8, 2022]]></title>
        <id>5368b5f3eeaf1b269292cf7fe2e8e38eb5b9e360</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-8-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T20:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an ex-.NET developer, and now Developer Advocate for .NET at AWS, I’m excited to bring you this week’s Week in Review post, for reasons that will quickly become apparent! There are several updates, customer stories, and events I want to bring to your attention, so let’s dive straight in! Last Week’s launches .NET developers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Platform Teams Are Everywhere — Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cloud-platform-teams-are-everywhere-heres-why</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cloud-platform-teams-are-everywhere-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HashiCorp’s new State of Cloud Strategy survey, 86% of respondents said they rely on cloud platform teams — for a wide variety of very good reasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Mother of Four Claims Her Seat at the Tech Table]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/claiming-her-seat-at-the-tech-table</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/claiming-her-seat-at-the-tech-table"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zoraya Sanchez De La Vega Cayero makes a mid-career transition to tech via the HashiCorp Early Careers program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Google Universal Image Embedding Challenge]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/introducing-google-universal-image.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/introducing-google-universal-image.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T17:47:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bingyi Cao, Software Engineer, Google Research, and Mário Lipovský, Software Engineer, Google Lens 
Computer vision models see daily application for a wide variety of tasks, ranging from object recognition to image-based 3D object reconstruction. One challenging type of computer vision problem is instance-level recognition (ILR) — given an image of an object, the task is to not only determine the generic category of an object (e.g., an arch), but also the specific instance of the object (”Arc de Triomphe de l'Étoile, Paris, France”).  
Previously, ILR was tackled using deep learning approaches. First, a large set of images was collected. Then a deep model was trained to embed each image into a high-dimensional space where similar images have similar representations. Finally, the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey 2022: Multi-Cloud Is Working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2022-multi-cloud-is-working</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2022-multi-cloud-is-working"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-cloud approaches — and platform teams — are helping 90% of respondents achieve their goals. But watch out for challenges around security, skills, and spending.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Observability guru Jonatan Ivanov on the future of observability in Spring Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/04/a-bootiful-podcast-observability-guru-jonatan-ivanov-on-the-future-of-observability-in-spring-boot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/04/a-bootiful-podcast-observability-guru-jonatan-ivanov-on-the-future-of-observability-in-spring-boot"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring observability guru Jonatan Ivanov (@jonatan_ivanov)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Removals and Major Changes In 1.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/04/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-1-25/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/04/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-1-25/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kat Cosgrove, Frederico Muñoz, Debabrata Panigrahi
As Kubernetes grows and matures, features may be deprecated, removed, or replaced with improvements for the health of the project. Kubernetes v1.25 includes several major changes and one major removal.
The Kubernetes API Removal and Deprecation process
The Kubernetes project has a well-documented deprecation policy for features. This policy states that stable APIs may only be deprecated when a newer, stable version of that same API is available and that APIs have a minimum lifetime for each stability level. A deprecated API is one that has been marked for removal in a future Kubernetes release; it will continue to function until removal (at least one year from the deprecation), but usage will result in a warning being displayed. R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graviton Fast Start – A New Program to Help Move Your Workloads to AWS Graviton]]></title>
        <id>d6058242a768258e28607ce3481412188bae9244</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/graviton-fast-start-a-new-program-to-help-move-your-workloads-to-aws-graviton/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T20:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the Graviton Challenge last year, we helped customers migrate to Graviton-based EC2 instances and get up to 40 percent price performance benefit in as little as 4 days. Tens of thousands of customers, including 48 of the top 50 Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) customers, use AWS Graviton processors for their workloads. In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Efficient Multiple Visual Domain Models with Multi-path Neural Architecture Search]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/building-efficient-multiple-visual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/building-efficient-multiple-visual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T19:57:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Qifei Wang, Senior Software Engineer, and Feng Yang, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research 
Deep learning models for visual tasks (e.g., image classification) are usually trained end-to-end with data from a single visual domain (e.g., natural images or computer generated images). Typically, an application that completes visual tasks for multiple domains would need to build multiple models for each individual domain, train them independently (meaning no data is shared between domains), and then at inference time each model would process domain-specific input data. However, early layers between these models generate similar features, even for different domains, so it can be more efficient — decreasing latency and power consumption, lower memory overhead to store parameter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Sequence Modeling for On-Device ML]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/efficient-sequence-modeling-for-on.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/efficient-sequence-modeling-for-on.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Arun Kandoor, Software Engineer, Google Research  
The increasing demand for machine learning (ML) model inference on-device (for mobile devices, tablets, etc.) is driven by the rise of compute-intensive applications, the need to keep certain data on device for privacy and security reasons, and the desire to provide services when a network connection may not be available. However, on-device inference introduces a myriad of challenges, ranging from modeling to platform support requirements. These challenges relate to how different architectures are designed to optimize memory and computation, while still trying to maintain the quality of the model. From a platform perspective, the issue is identifying operations and building on top of them in a way that can generalize well across …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Surprising Things Consul Service Mesh Can Do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/3-surprising-things-consul-service-mesh-can-do</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/3-surprising-things-consul-service-mesh-can-do"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul has evolved into a comprehensive networking platform that bolsters zero trust networking, works well with Kubernetes, and is remarkably easy to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第214話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270375685396151729</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270375685396151729"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Run Visual Studio Software on Amazon EC2 with User-Based License Model]]></title>
        <id>c9b4d0c62bc0acd424a612d9281c227e53c86a7c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-run-visual-studio-software-on-amazon-ec2-with-user-based-license-model/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T23:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the general availability of license-included Visual Studio software on Amazon Elastic Cloud Compute (Amazon EC2) instances. You can now purchase fully compliant AWS-provided licenses of Visual Studio with a per-user subscription fee. Amazon EC2 provides preconfigured Amazon Machine Images (AMIs) of Visual Studio Enterprise 2022 and Visual Studio Professional 2022. You […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 208 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65387</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-208-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T17:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the March announcement of the New Boards Hub, our team has collected a lot of your feedback. Thank you! We have been hard at work addressing the issues. Every week the experience gets better and better. The issues backlog is getting smaller,
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 208 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS Skill Builder Subscriptions]]></title>
        <id>aff220b67001fae8fec9dc52e8fe845d58be9d9e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-skill-builder-subscriptions/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T10:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am excited to announce AWS Skill Builder Individual and Team subscriptions. This is a new way for you to learn about cloud technologies and get practical experience with hands-on training. Between 2013 and 2016, I spent three years delivering AWS Training classes to customers in Europe, North America, and Asia. At the time, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/02/sig-docs-spotlight-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/02/sig-docs-spotlight-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Purneswar Prasad
Introduction
The official documentation is the go-to source for any open source project. For Kubernetes,
it's an ever-evolving Special Interest Group (SIG) with people constantly putting in their efforts
to make details about the project easier to consume for new contributors and users. SIG Docs publishes
the official documentation on kubernetes.io which includes,
but is not limited to, documentation of the core APIs, core architectural details, and CLI tools
shipped with the Kubernetes release.
To learn more about the work of SIG Docs and its future ahead in shaping the community, I have summarised
my conversation with the co-chairs, Divya Mohan (DM),
Rey Lejano (RL) and Natali Vlatko (NV), who ran through the
SIG's goals and how fellow contributors can help.
A su…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 1, 2022]]></title>
        <id>0f24a0fdd5f7ab793f757ad334ae2cdb84629c3b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-1-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T19:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS re:Inforce returned to Boston last week, kicking off with a keynote from Amazon Chief Security Officer Steve Schmidt and AWS Chief Information Security officer C.J. Moses: Be sure to take some time to watch this video and the other leadership sessions, and to use what you learn to take some proactive steps to improve […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Mesh — A Data Movement and Processing Platform @ Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1288bcab2873</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/data-mesh-a-data-movement-and-processing-platform-netflix-1288bcab2873?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T18:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Bo Lei, Guilherme Pires, James Shao, Kasturi Chatterjee, Sujay Jain, Vlad Sydorenko]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform (CDKTF) has reached its first GA release, adding full support for Go and providing a GitHub action to use with Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peeling back the layers and understanding automation mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/peeling-back-the-layers-and-understanding-automation-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/peeling-back-the-layers-and-understanding-automation-mesh"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 features an awesome new way to scale out your automation workloads: automation mesh.  If you are unfamiliar with automation mesh, I highly recommend reading Craig Brandt’s blog post What's new: an introduction to automation mesh which outlines how automation mesh can simplify your operations and scale your automation globally.  For this blog post, I want to focus on the technical implementation of automation mesh, what network ports it is using and how you can secure it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>