<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-04-23T01:41:37.947Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-23T01:41:37.947Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pix2Seq: A New Language Interface for Object Detection]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pix2seq-new-language-interface-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pix2seq-new-language-interface-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T20:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ting Chen and David Fleet, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Object detection is a long-standing computer vision task that attempts to recognize and localize all objects of interest in an image. The complexity arises when trying to identify or localize all object instances while also avoiding duplication. Existing approaches, like Faster R-CNN and DETR, are carefully designed and highly customized in the choice of architecture and loss function. This specialization of existing systems has created two major barriers: (1) it adds complexity in tuning and training the different parts of the system (e.g., region proposal network, graph matching with GIOU loss, etc.), and (2), it can reduce the ability of a model to generalize, necessitating a redesign of the model for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss Re’s Journey Toward a Cloud-Native Orchestration Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51662</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/swiss-res-journey-toward-a-cloud-native-orchestration-solution/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ready for a digital transformation? Learn why Swiss Re selected Camunda Platform 8 as its cloud-native process orchestration solution.
The post Swiss Re’s Journey Toward a Cloud-Native Orchestration Solution appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing the stigma of a CVE]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-22-removing-the-stigma-of-a-cve/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-22-removing-the-stigma-of-a-cve/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you worry that a CVE will hurt the reputation of your project? In reality, CVEs are a tracking number, and nothing more. Here's how we think of them at GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.12 Hardens Security on Kubernetes with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-12-hardens-security-on-kubernetes-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-12-hardens-security-on-kubernetes-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This release strengthens zero trust security architecture by leveraging HashiCorp Vault to reduce secrets sprawl and automate server TLS certificate rotation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 simple things every developer can do to ship more secure code]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-22-5-simple-things-every-developer-can-do-to-ship-more-secure-code/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-22-5-simple-things-every-developer-can-do-to-ship-more-secure-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T14:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From plug-and-play automations to protected branches, here are simple ways any developer can build more secure software on GitHub—all with a free account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The traffic metaphors]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41890</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/692313834/0/sethsblog~The-traffic-metaphors/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your mileage may vary. Speeding up to get to a red light faster just wastes energy. Honking doesn’t make traffic go away. Doesn’t matter how fancy your car is, it’s not worth very much if they close the road. One of the worst ways to get to where you’re going is to always drive in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud legend Glenn Renfro about batch processing, tasks, stream processing, data flow, and t-shirts]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-legend-glenn-renfro-about-batch-processing-tasks-stream-processing-data-flow-and-t-shirts</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-legend-glenn-renfro-about-batch-processing-tasks-stream-processing-data-flow-and-t-shirts"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of A Bootiful Podcast! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring Cloud luminary and all around lovable guy Glenn Renfro (@cppwfs) about batch processing, tasks, messaging, integration, data flow, and a million other things. Also: t-shirts!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assigning Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2610/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2610/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/assigning_numbers.png" title="Gödel should do an article on which branches of math have the lowest average theorem number." alt="Gödel should do an article on which branches of math have the lowest average theorem number." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing My Fire Service Notification System with Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51389</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/implementing-my-fire-service-notification-system-with-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever struggled to notify the right people during an emergency? Learn how a fire service notification system was built with BPMN and Camunda Platform 8.
The post Implementing My Fire Service Notification System with Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0-RC1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-7-0-rc1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-7-0-rc1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T22:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0-RC1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes more than a 100 bug fixes, enhancements, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Auto-configuration for Kafka Retry Topics

  
Auto-configuration for RSocket support in GraphQL


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your guide to GitHub InFocus: Improving the way software development teams work in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-21-guide-to-github-infocus-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-21-guide-to-github-infocus-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T21:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re kicking off InFocus, a global virtual event focused on accelerating, securing, and improving the way software development teams work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden Interfaces for Ambient Computing]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/hidden-interfaces-for-ambient-computing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/hidden-interfaces-for-ambient-computing.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T19:59:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alex Olwal, Research Scientist, Google Augmented Reality and Artem Dementyev, Hardware Engineer, Google Research 
As consumer electronics and internet-connected appliances are becoming more common, homes are beginning to embrace various types of connected devices that offer functionality like music control, voice assistance, and home automation. A graceful integration of devices requires adaptation to existing aesthetics and user styles rather than simply adding screens, which can easily disrupt a visual space, especially when they become monolithic surfaces or black screens when powered down or not actively used. Thus there is an increasing desire to create connected ambient computing devices and appliances that can preserve the aesthetics of everyday materials, while providing …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Serverless Inference – Machine Learning Inference without Worrying about Servers]]></title>
        <id>3f2dde001172ce44e72138f038da17f0191c2c33</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-serverless-inference-machine-learning-inference-without-worrying-about-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T17:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December 2021, we introduced Amazon SageMaker Serverless Inference (in preview) as a new option in Amazon SageMaker to deploy machine learning (ML) models for inference without having to configure or manage the underlying infrastructure. Today, I’m happy to announce that Amazon SageMaker Serverless Inference is now generally available (GA). Different ML inference use cases […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Aurora Serverless v2 is Generally Available: Instant Scaling for Demanding Workloads]]></title>
        <id>94931a6d5038a338992ac375a270cfd3a1a2c213</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-aurora-serverless-v2-is-generally-available-instant-scaling-for-demanding-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are very excited to announce that Amazon Aurora Serverless v2 is generally available for both Aurora PostgreSQL and MySQL. Aurora Serverless is an on-demand, auto-scaling configuration for Amazon Aurora that allows your database to scale capacity up or down based on your application’s needs. Amazon Aurora is a MySQL- and PostgreSQL-compatible relational database […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the General Availability of AWS Amplify Studio]]></title>
        <id>a646396f947ba813c8558c3ba67d16b8e63ee6bd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-general-availability-of-aws-amplify-studio/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amplify Studio is a visual interface that simplifies front- and backend development for web and mobile applications. We released it as a preview during AWS re:Invent 2021, and today, I’m happy to announce that it is now generally available (GA). A key feature of Amplify Studio is integration with Figma, helping designers and front-end developers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IoT TwinMaker Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>0bc74371fc1afc6c01a04e5c726c01a6a266613e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-iot-twinmaker-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year at AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced the preview of AWS IoT TwinMaker, a new AWS IoT service that makes it faster and easier to create digital twins of real-world systems and use them to monitor and optimize industrial operations. A digital twin is a living digital representation of an individual physical system that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Git push times through faster server side hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-21-improving-git-push-times-through-faster-server-side-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-21-improving-git-push-times-through-faster-server-side-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The history of pre-receive hooks, how we discovered that the performance was problematic, and how we went about safely replacing them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Count Downloads in the Public Terraform Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-count-downloads-in-the-public-terraform-registry</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-count-downloads-in-the-public-terraform-registry"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how download metrics are calculated in the HashiCorp Terraform Registry, and how that count has evolved over time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Detect Operational Issues in Lambda Functions with Amazon DevOps Guru for Serverless]]></title>
        <id>8268d306374a02f09df77e136e38f9dbf78c0766</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/automatically-detect-operational-issues-in-lambda-functions-with-amazon-devops-guru-for-serverless/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T15:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing Amazon DevOps Guru for Serverless, a new capability for Amazon DevOps Guru. It allows developers to improve the operational performance and availability of serverless applications. AWS pioneered the serverless computing space with the launch of AWS Lambda in 2014. Today, hundreds of thousands of customers are using AWS Lambda. Lambda allows […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create PHP Courses Inside PhpStorm With EduTools]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=241750</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/04/21/create-php-courses-inside-phpstorm-with-edutools/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T13:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point in your professional career, you may want to share your programming knowledge with your co-workers or students. You may even want to start your own blog, YouTube channel, or account on social media to share your experience with a larger audience. If any of this is something you are interested in, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ACCU 2022 Trip Report]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=241696</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/04/accu-2022-trip-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T12:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From April 6-9, 2022, I attended ACCU 2022, the 25th edition of the ACCU conference, in Bristol, UK. It was only my third in-person conference post-COVID (after CppCon’21 and ADC’21). It felt very special to be back in Bristol after a three-year break, and it felt as good as ever to be among real people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timur Doumler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote Development 2022.1 is here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=241709</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/blog/2022/04/21/remote-development-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T11:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week we released new builds of Remote Development and JetBrains Gateway. In this release cycle, our team has focused on the overall solution quality and bug fixes. In addition to the quality improvements, the latest version has several noticeable new features, which we’ll highlight in this blog post. Remote Development with Gateway is a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Kalinina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.7 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-6-7-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-6-7-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T11:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.7 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 38 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE report published for Spring Security OAuth]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/cve-report-published-for-spring-security-oauth</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/cve-report-published-for-spring-security-oauth"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Spring Security OAuth 2.5.2 to address the following CVE report.


  
CVE-2022-22969: Denial-of-Service (DoS) in spring-security-oauth2


This vulnerability exposes OAuth 2.0 Client applications only.

Please review the information in the CVE report and upgrade immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.13 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-5-13-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-5-13-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T08:51:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.13 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 31 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Words that matter]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41866</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/692175900/0/sethsblog~Words-that-matter/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T08:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any word that’s really important is also confusing. Words like trust, love, friend, fair, honest, lead, connect, authentic, justice, dignity–they have dozens of different meanings. Perhaps that’s because they’re important. It’s worth spending a moment to understand what we mean when we say something that might mean something else.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing the future of search relevance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/embracing-the-future-of-search-relevance</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/embracing-the-future-of-search-relevance"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an effort to provide the most relevant, accurate search possible, developers must learn how to integrate machine learning into thier solutions. Starting in Elastic 8.0, the story around machine learning and how to embrace it is more clear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing the future of search relevance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/embracing-the-future-of-search-relevance</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/embracing-the-future-of-search-relevance"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
When looking for new opportunities to innovate and compete, companies today need to look no further than search, which has come a long way from the search bar of old. Whether you’re enabling search across integrations your business relies on or building a state-of-the-art website experience, search is on the critical path to research and discovery. 
The canonical search bar in mobile apps and websites is only the first step in the journey though. Additional value gets added when intelligent, robust solutions come together to build visually engaging customer experiences.

With the release of Elastic 8.0, we lowered the barrier of entry for teams to build intelligent, relevant search. This release brings more machine learning (ML) capabilities into the core of the Elastic Search Platform, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Session 2021.2.0-RC1, 2021.1.3 and 2021.0.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/20/spring-session-2021-2-0-rc1-2021-1-3-and-2021-0-6-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/20/spring-session-2021-2-0-rc1-2021-1-3-and-2021-0-6-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T23:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Session 2021.2.0-RC1, 2021.1.3 and 2021.0.6.
The 2021.2.0 release train is entering the RC phase. If you haven’t done so yet, please give it a try!
The 2021.1.3 and 2021.0.6 releases deliver bug fixes and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot will pick up these artifacts with its upcoming releases.

The following modules were updated as part of 2021.2.0-RC1:


  
Spring Session Core 2.7.0-RC1 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 2.7.0-RC1 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 2.7.0-RC1 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 2.7.0-RC1 - release notes

  
Spring Session MongoDB 2.7.0-RC1 - release notes

  
Spring Session for Apache Geode 2.7.0-RC1


The following modules were updated as part of 2021.1.3:


  
Spring Session Core 2.6.3 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 2.6.3 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 2.6.3 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 2.6.3 - release notes

  
Spring Session MongoDB 2.6.3 - release notes

  
Spring Session for Apache Geode 2.6.1


The following modules were updated as part of 2021.0.6:


  
Spring Session Core 2.5.6 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 2.5.6 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 2.5.6 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 2.5.6 - release notes

  
Spring Session for Apache Geode 2.5.6]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FormNet: Beyond Sequential Modeling for Form-Based Document Understanding]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/formnet-beyond-sequential-modeling-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/formnet-beyond-sequential-modeling-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T20:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Chen-Yu Lee and Chun-Liang Li, Research Scientists, Google Research, Cloud AI Team 
Form-based document understanding is a growing research topic because of its practical potential for automatically converting unstructured text data into structured information to gain insight about a document’s contents. Recent sequence modeling, which is a self-attention mechanism that directly models relationships between all words in a selection of text, has demonstrated state-of-the-art performance on natural language tasks. A natural approach to handle form document understanding tasks is to first serialize the form documents (usually in a left-to-right, top-to-bottom fashion) and then apply state-of-the-art sequence models to them.  
 However, form documents often have more complex layouts …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode 2022.1 Release Candidate Is Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=238803</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/04/appcode-2022-1-rc/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T19:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, The release of AppCode 2022.1 is approaching, and the Release Candidate is now available for download on our site. You need to have an active subscription or start a free trial to use this build. Here are the main highlights: We included PackagePlugin module into the prebuilt caches. We fixed the broken support […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#CamundaSummit: Unconference Agenda Announced]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51431</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/camundasummit-unconference-agenda-announced/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T19:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Unconference agenda is now live! Check out the lineup of peer-led sessions we have in store for you on April 27.
The post #CamundaSummit: Unconference Agenda Announced appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organization profiles leading the way]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-20-organization-profiles-leading-the-way/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-20-organization-profiles-leading-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T18:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organization profiles can now display custom content visible only to members of the organization. A new Member view can be tailored to show an alternative README and pinned private repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp and AWS Make it Easier to Secure Workloads in EKS with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-and-aws-partner-to-enhance-kubernetes-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-and-aws-partner-to-enhance-kubernetes-security"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp has partnered with AWS to enhance security on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service with Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opt-in to Auditing on Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63895</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/opt-in-to-auditing-on-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T17:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Auditing has now been made an opt-in feature on Azure DevOps. In our last blog post about Auditing, we discussed the exciting changes coming to the Auditing feature on Azure DevOps, as we work on bringing the feature to general availability.
The post Opt-in to Auditing on Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Migration Hub Orchestrator – New Migration Orchestration Capability with Customizable Workflow Templates]]></title>
        <id>0f99199a54f5eb036f2cc7d2f96cd7faee3329da</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-migration-hub-orchestrator-new-migration-orchestration-capability-with-customizable-workflow-templates/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T16:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can migrate any workload from an on-premises environment to AWS. The key to a successful migration to AWS is a well-thought-out plan, informative tools, prior migration experience, and a quality implementation. Every step along the way, you can use AWS’s years of experience to build your organizational, operational, and technical capabilities so that you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codespaces for multi-repository and monorepo scenarios]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-20-codespaces-multi-repository-monorepo-scenarios/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-20-codespaces-multi-repository-monorepo-scenarios/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T16:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re releasing exciting improvements that will streamline your Codespaces experience when working with multi-repository projects and monorepos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New reference architecture: Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 1.2 to 2 Migration Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-1.2-to-2-migration-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-1.2-to-2-migration-guide"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[we created a simple reference architecture to help guide you migrate from Ansible Automation Platform 1.2 to Ansible Automation Platform 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0 RC1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/20/spring-for-graphql-1-0-rc1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/20/spring-for-graphql-1-0-rc1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of everyone involved, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the first and final release candidate of Spring for GraphQL 1.0. We’re finally going to release a 1.0 version on May 17, the reference version for Spring Boot 2.7.0. We’ve shipped a few noteworthy changes and one important new feature in this release.

Note: The Spring for GraphqL Boot starter is up-to-date with the changes discussed in this post and Spring Boot 2.7.0-RC1 is scheduled to be released on Thursday this week.
GraphQL over RSocket

Spring for GraphQL started out with the HTTP and WebSocket transports - must haves in the GraphQL world. Our programming model allows adding others too, and our existing infrastructure pointed at another clear candidate: the RSocket protocol. In RC1 we’ve added client and s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defender of the brand]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41863</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/692016614/0/sethsblog~Defender-of-the-brand/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T08:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some CMOs and marketing types simply do ads and promo. Give them average products for average people and some money, and they’ll do the ad thing. And some are actually marketers. Marketing involves making a promise and keeping it. Marketers understand that your logo isn’t a brand, it’s simply a flag. The brand is the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022.1 Versions of All JetBrains IDEs and .NET Tools Have Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=241495</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/blog/2022/04/20/2022-1-versions-ides-and-dotnet-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T08:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post offers an overview of the major updates you will find in the 2022.1 releases of all JetBrains IDEs and .NET tools. Check out the summary below, and follow the links to dive deeper and learn more about your favorite tools. You can update at any time via the Toolbox App or from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Kovaleva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.17.3 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.3 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
The 7.17.3 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security announcement for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
7.17.3 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia Mitter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.1.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.1.3 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
The 8.1.3 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security announcement for more details.
This release addresses some notable issues in our Observability and Security solutions:
A bug where the APM Server might run out of memory when overloaded by too many incoming requests. Users running APM Server versions 8.0.0 up to 8.1.2 are advised to upgrade immediately.
Multiple issues that impacted Elastic Security UI performance in environments with a high number of field mappings.
A bug where the binary verification will fail when upgrading the Elastic Agent through the upgrade cli command or through the Fleet UI upgrade feature. The bug was impacting 8.1.1 and 8.1.2 releases.
This 8.1.3 patch release contains other fixes and small enhancements for the stack. For more details and a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
8.1.3 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia Mitter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.3 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Logstash, Beats, APM, Enterprise Search, Elastic Security, and ECK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia Mitter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.1.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.1.3 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Logstash, Beats, APM, Enterprise Search, Elastic Security, and ECK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia Mitter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entwives]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2609/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2609/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/entwives.png" title="No, we actually do have a woman who's basically part of our fellowship. She lives in Rivendell, you wouldn't know her." alt="No, we actually do have a woman who's basically part of our fellowship. She lives in Rivendell, you wouldn't know her." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic announces TISAX certification, enhancing security in connected vehicles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-tisax-certification-security-connected-vehicles</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-tisax-certification-security-connected-vehicles"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T21:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, connected vehicles are proliferating, smart cities are translating from vision to reality, and cloud-based connectivity services are increasing. Advanced connectivity solutions like 5G, cloud-based services and automations, and personalization are redefining in-vehicle experiences. In addition, the growth of an intelligent Edge, smart infrastructure, and the Internet of Things are pushing the boundaries of the connected car. 
Automakers worldwide have slowly but steadily come to terms with what is commonly known as the “software-defined vehicle.” It will not be an exaggeration to say that the car of the future will be primarily software-driven, and the digital chassis will control every element within the car from autonomy to driver assistance to cockpit and telematics. 
“Security b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic announces TISAX certification, enhancing security in connected vehicles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-tisax-certification-security-connected-vehicles</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-tisax-certification-security-connected-vehicles"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T21:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic is excited to add TISAX certification to the list of several key information security standards and regulations that it has acquired.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 19th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/19/this-week-in-spring-april-19th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/19/this-week-in-spring-april-19th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! It’s been quite the week since we last talked! I flew to Atlanta, GA, for my first in-person show since the pandemic - Devnexus 2022. I loved the experience! Hopefully, the only souvenirs I’ll have are the amazing memories and not COVID. I loved to see so many smiling faces. Thanks so much for having me, Devnexus, and for running an amazing show. It was a privilege to return. 

And now, without further ado, let’s dive right into the roundup. 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Cloud guru Tiffany Jernigan

  
Jacky Chan on Twitter: “My new open source tool httpx, CLI and IDE plugins to test REST API, GraphQL, gRPC, RSocket, Kafka etc services with HTTP DSL https://t.co/jkvJG2syff JetBrains/Neovim plugins are all ready. Support by @java and @graalvm” / Twitter

  
Ngrok Spring Boot Starter - Tunneling The Easy Way

  
Spring Boot with Drools Engine. In this blog we would see how Spring integrates with Drools Engine. | CodeX

  
Spring Data 2021.2.0-RC1, 2021.1.4, and 2021.0.11 released

  
Spring Framework 5.3.19 and 5.2.21 available now

  
Spring Framework Data Binding Rules Vulnerability (CVE-2022-22968)

  
Spring Security 5.6.3 and 5.5.6 available now

  
Spring Security 5.7.0-RC1 released

  
Build or migrate great applications that deliver great value to your customers. Register now]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing security expertise through CodeQL packs (Part I)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-19-sharing-security-expertise-through-codeql-packs-part-i/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-19-sharing-security-expertise-through-codeql-packs-part-i/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T17:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CodeQL packs to help you codify and share your knowledge of vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Prompt for Continual Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/learning-to-prompt-for-continual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/learning-to-prompt-for-continual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T17:00:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zifeng Wang, Student Researcher, and Zizhao Zhang, Software Engineer, Google Research
Supervised learning is a common approach to machine learning (ML) in which the model is trained using data that is labeled appropriately for the task at hand. Ordinary supervised learning trains on independent and identically distributed (IID) data, where all training examples are sampled from a fixed set of classes, and the model has access to these examples throughout the entire training phase. In contrast, continual learning tackles the problem of training a single model on changing data distributions where different classification tasks are presented sequentially. This is particularly important, for example, to enable autonomous agents to process and interpret continuous streams of informati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.2.0-RC1, 2021.1.4, and 2021.0.11 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/19/spring-data-2021-2-0-rc1-2021-1-4-and-2021-0-11-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/19/spring-data-2021-2-0-rc1-2021-1-4-and-2021-0-11-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2021.2.0 release train is entering the RC phase. If you haven’t done so yet, please give it a try! The 2021.1.4 and 2021.0.11 service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades. For your convenience those will be picked up by Spring Boot in the upcoming days.

To round things off, here are the links to the individual modules, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.2.0-RC1


  
Spring Data Commons 2.7 RC1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.4 RC1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.7 RC1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data for Apache Geode 2.7 RC1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data for Apache Cassandra 3.4 RC1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kubernetes to Nomad Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-kubernetes-to-nomad-cheat-sheet</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-kubernetes-to-nomad-cheat-sheet"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Kubernetes users looking to learn HashiCorp Nomad concepts and commands  — or vice versa — we’ve designed a cheat sheet for quick reference and a fast onramp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2022.1 Comes With Full Unreal Engine Support and Remote Development]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=240608</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/04/19/rider-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T12:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, Our first release of the year, Rider 2022.1 is now available. You can download it from the JetBrains website, install it via the Toolbox App, or use this snap package from the SnapCraft store (if you are using a compatible Linux distro). We initially dubbed Rider 2022.1 a quality release with a focus […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Kolesova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing RiderFlow, a Free Unity Editor Plugin for Scene Management]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=240621</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/04/19/introducing-riderflow-a-free-unity-editor-plugin-for-scene-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T12:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple of weeks ago, at GDC, we got a great reaction showing people RiderFlow, a new Unity editor plugin for scene management, navigation and searching your Unity assets.  Today, we’re pleased to announce that RiderFlow is generally available to everyone, and can be downloaded from the Asset Store, JetBrains website, or installed as a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify your Elastic on AWS deployment with the Elastic Cloud Quick Start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/simplify-your-elastic-on-aws-deployment-with-the-elastic-cloud-quick-start</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/simplify-your-elastic-on-aws-deployment-with-the-elastic-cloud-quick-start"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline your Elastic on AWS deployment with the Elastic Cloud Quick Start — an automated reference deployment — with just a few steps. And easily migrate your on-prem Elastic workloads into Elastic on AWS after your deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy,Antony Prasad Thevaraj, AWS,Battulga Purevragchaa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify your Elastic on AWS deployment with the Elastic Cloud Quick Start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/simplify-your-elastic-on-aws-deployment-with-the-elastic-cloud-quick-start</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/simplify-your-elastic-on-aws-deployment-with-the-elastic-cloud-quick-start"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Now it is even easier to deploy, ingest, and migrate data into Elastic within your Amazon Web Services (AWS) environment,  so you can quickly capture, store, and search your data. Quickly build and start your environment by leveraging the Elastic Cloud Quick Start — an automated reference deployment — that significantly reduces prior manual procedures to just a few steps. 

In this blog we will go over the details of the deployment environment, benefits of Elastic on AWS, and resources available if you require migration.
Deploy Elastic on AWS with ease
Streamline your deployment with the Elastic Cloud Quick Start. If you have on-prem Elastic workloads, you can easily migrate them into Elastic on AWS after your deployment. 
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blte6…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy,Antony Prasad Thevaraj, AWS,Battulga Purevragchaa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022.1 Release of dotTrace, dotMemory, dotCover, and dotPeek!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=240747</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/04/19/dottrace-dotmemory-dotcover-dotpeek-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T12:08:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released the 2022.1 versions of dotTrace, dotMemory, dotCover, and dotPeek. Take a look at what you can expect.  dotTrace 2022.1 The dotTrace command-line tool and dotTrace in Rider now support Alpine versions 3.13–3.15. You can now open NetTrace files collected with dotnet-trace collect. dotTrace supports SQL Server events from the Microsoft.Data.SqlClient provider. You […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Kurakin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ 2022.1: Updates for Unit Testing and Unreal Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rscpp&amp;p=241532</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rscpp/2022/04/19/resharper-cpp-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T12:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ 2022.1 is now available! It mainly addresses quality and performance issues but also brings a lot of updates for unit testing and Unreal Engine and improves the handling of implicit constructor calls. The brand new build is available on our website, and all of our tools for Visual Studio can be downloaded via […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elvira Mustafina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2022.1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=241332</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/04/19/resharper-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T12:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, ReSharper 2022.1 is now available! As promised during the first EAP, we have focused on quality, bug fixes, and diagnostics improvements in this version. We will still need to concentrate some of our efforts on C# support but, in general, this release cycle will be about fixing bugs. Let’s go through the most […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asia Rudenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Performance of Parallel Tasks in Camunda Platform 8 is so Good]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51170</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/why-performance-of-parallel-tasks-in-camunda-platform-8-is-so-good/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the fundamental redesigns we've made to Camunda Platform 8 to avoid some challenges present in Camunda Platform 7. 
The post Why Performance of Parallel Tasks in Camunda Platform 8 is so Good appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperative enthusiasm]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41861</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/691900840/0/sethsblog~Cooperative-enthusiasm/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When someone shares a new idea, or makes a pitch, or describes a dream, what would happen if you were enthusiastic? Perhaps positive thinking is contagious. Perhaps egging on the other person will help them explore the edges. And perhaps it will help them overcome their fear and share the very best version of what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Data Tools 1.5: Amazon EMR Support, Alibaba OSS Integration, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=big-data-tools&amp;p=240255</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/big-data-tools/2022/04/19/big-data-tools-1-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T07:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new release of Big Data Tools, we’ve added support for more instruments for data engineers, including Amazon EMR data processing platform and Alibaba Cloud Object Storage Service. Now you can work with them directly from your IDE. Read on to learn about these and other enhancements introduced in this release. Amazon EMR Support […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QA Tools Updates in 2022.1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=qa&amp;p=241080</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/qa/2022/04/qa-tools-updates-in-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T05:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most JetBrains tools have had their first major release of the year and QA Tools are no exception. In addition to the cosmetic updates, we made big improvements and enhancements to the Page Object Editor in the Selenium UI Testing plugin, which is part of the JetBrains Test Automation Kit. Let’s take a look at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Pavlu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic's response to the the Spring4Shell vulnerability (CVE-2022-22965)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-response-to-the-the-spring4shell-vulnerability-cve-2022-22965</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-response-to-the-the-spring4shell-vulnerability-cve-2022-22965"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T01:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On March 29, 2022 a vulnerability in the Spring framework was disclosed to the public by VMware. This vulnerability had several prerequisites affecting impact:
Spring framework versions 5.3.0-5.3.17, 5.2.0-5.2.19, potentially software versions prior to 5.2.x
An application running as a Spring MVX or WebFlux object
Apache Tomcat as the container for that application
The application packaged as a Web Application Resource (WAR)
Specifically, this vulnerability targets the ClassLoader() class, though similar undiscovered vulnerabilities in other classes are likely. A URI parameter can be passed to Tomcat as part of a standard web request to exploit this vulnerability. 
What is the threat?
CVE-2022-22965 is a vulnerability that may affect systems on which the Spring Framework has been installed…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ellard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic's response to the the Spring4Shell vulnerability (CVE-2022-22965)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-response-to-the-the-spring4shell-vulnerability-cve-2022-22965</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-response-to-the-the-spring4shell-vulnerability-cve-2022-22965"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T01:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Provide executive-level details about CVE-2022-22965, a recently-disclosed remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability also known as “Spring4Shell”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ellard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Elastic to improve data management and observability in the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/nucleus-research-elastic-data-management-observability-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/nucleus-research-elastic-data-management-observability-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T01:18:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two recent studies conducted by Nucleus Research, focused on how a global telecommunications provider, and multi-line insurance company realized quantified business value through Elastic.
The companies that were studied saw great levels of satisfaction from deploying Elastic Cloud. Through their adoption they were able to increase the maturity of their tech stack and circumvent prior limitations in scalability. The delivery of a full-stack observability platform with the capacity to detect incidents, avoid service disruptions, run root cause analytics, and deliver real-time metrics, helped deliver several key benefits, including:
Enhancing IT productivity and new revenue
After implementing Elastic Cloud, IT staff noted faster problem identification, reduced MTTR, greater platform stability…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Ben Pruden,Julie Leverenz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Elastic to improve data management and observability in the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/nucleus-research-elastic-data-management-observability-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/nucleus-research-elastic-data-management-observability-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T01:18:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In two recent studies conducted by Nucleus Research, the companies that were studied saw great levels of satisfaction from deploying Elastic Cloud]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Ben Pruden,Julie Leverenz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shut It Down days help Elasticians regroup, recharge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-shut-it-down-days-help-elasticians-regroup-recharge</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-shut-it-down-days-help-elasticians-regroup-recharge"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shut It Down days are extra paid days off where Elasticians can take the time and space they need to do…whatever they need to do, without the burden of coming back to an overflowing inbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shut It Down days help Elasticians regroup, recharge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-shut-it-down-days-help-elasticians-regroup-recharge</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-shut-it-down-days-help-elasticians-regroup-recharge"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As we enter the third year of the pandemic we continue to hear how Elasticians are juggling work, home, families, friends, and not to mention the other stressors that occur in everyday life. It is our goal to always support our employees where we can. That’s why Shut It Down days mean so much to Elasticians. 

The purpose of our Shut It Down days is to create extra space for our employees—it’s an evolution of our culture. Space, Time is a tenet of our Source Code. Instead of getting stuck in the day-to-day work pattern, we prioritize allowing for the space and time to breathe, recalibrate, and come back recharged. 
Shut It Down days, explained
Shut It Down days are paid days off that allow Elasticians to get some breathing room. They apply to employees worldwide, which means we take into…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.0-RC1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/18/spring-security-5-7-0-rc1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/18/spring-security-5-7-0-rc1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T20:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Security 5.7.0-RC1!



In addition to dependency upgrades, bug fixes, and minor enhancements, the release candidate contains a few noteworthy changes:





Introduced SecurityContextHolderFilter - Ability to require explicit saving of the SecurityContext



Added DSL support for Cross Origin Policies headers



Allow configuring PKCE for confidential clients



Added SAML 2.0 Login & Single Logout XML support





This release candidate is a good opportunity to give feedback before the actual GA release in mid-May. We look forward to hearing from you.



You can find the complete details in the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.6.3 and 5.5.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/18/spring-security-5-6-3-and-5-5-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/18/spring-security-5-6-3-and-5-5-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T20:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.6.3 and 5.5.6 are available now.



You can find more details about the respective releases here and
 here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 18, 2022]]></title>
        <id>ef7b946d35336128b5b4045b8988427e735ae9f3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-18-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T18:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Here we are with another roundup of the most significant AWS launches from the previous week. Among the news, we have a new deployment option for Amazon FSx for NetApp […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux process and session model as part of security alerting and monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/linux-process-and-session-model-as-part-of-security-alerting-and-monitoring</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/linux-process-and-session-model-as-part-of-security-alerting-and-monitoring"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux process model, available within Elastic, allows users to write very target alerting rules and gain deeper insight into exactly what is happening on their Linux servers and desktops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Sample</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux process and session model as part of security alerting and monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/linux-process-and-session-model-as-part-of-security-alerting-and-monitoring</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/linux-process-and-session-model-as-part-of-security-alerting-and-monitoring"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The Linux process model, available within Elastic, allows users to write very targeted alerting rules and gain deeper insight into exactly what is happening on their Linux servers and desktops.
In this blog, we will provide background on the Linux process model, a key aspect of how Linux workloads are represented.
Linux follows the Unix process model from the 1970's that was augmented with the concept sessions in the 1980's judging from when the setsid() system call was introduced by early POSIX documents.
The Linux process model is a good abstraction for recording computer workloads (which programs are run) and for writing rules to react to these events. It offers a clear representation of who did what when on which server for alerting, compliance and threat hunting.
Capturing process c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Sample</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from Git 2.36]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-18-highlights-from-git-2-36/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-18-highlights-from-git-2-36/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T16:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another new release of Git is here! Take a look at some of our highlights on what's new in Git 2.36.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Partner Network (APN) – 10 Years and Going Strong]]></title>
        <id>8ef86720707ad81177cef1eb9b0d2fe43d2e7cc6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-partner-network-apn-10-years-and-going-strong/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T15:27:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten years ago we launched AWS Partner Network (APN) in beta form for our partners and our customers. In his post for the beta launch, my then-colleague Jinesh Varia noted that: Partners are an integral part of the AWS ecosystem as they enable customers and help them scale their business globally. Some of our greatest […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep dive on Ansible VScode extension]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/deep-dive-on-ansible-vscode-extension</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/deep-dive-on-ansible-vscode-extension"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible as part of the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform continues to grow and mature. Recent enhancements include Ansible Content Collections, automation execution environments, and an increasing list of integrations using plugins and modules. It is more important than ever that both new and experienced content creators have access to tools that help them write better content faster. The newly created Ansible Devtools initiative focuses on developing and enhancing tools like ansible-navigator, Ansible VScode extension, ansible-lint and so on to help ease the Ansible automation content creator experience. In this blog, we will do a deep dive into the Ansible VSCode extension, giving an overview of how it works and the initial setup required to get it working after installation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coiling ropes]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42569</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/691781478/0/sethsblog~Coiling-ropes/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T08:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Professionals put things away slowly so that they’ll be ready quickly when needed. Investing time now for time later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Family Reunion]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2608/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2608/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/family_reunion.png" title="Grandma says that because of differences in primate and feline lifespans, the cat is actually my 17,000,000th cousin 14,000,000 times removed." alt="Grandma says that because of differences in primate and feline lifespans, the cat is actually my 17,000,000th cousin 14,000,000 times removed." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asking and daring]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41855</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/691688510/0/sethsblog~Asking-and-daring/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-17T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Noon is a cornerstone of American cinema, a sobering and memorable look at heroism and community. In the movie, the sheriff is facing near-certain death at the hands of a killer freed from prison. He has about an hour to gather a posse of deputies, because together they’ll be able to repel the avenging […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The resolution of communication]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41859</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/691534446/0/sethsblog~The-resolution-of-communication/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-16T09:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s better, a phone call or a zoom call? Which creates more intimacy, a meeting in person or a hand-written letter? The only answer is: it depends. It’s tempting to believe that being in a store, surrounded by sights, smells, packaging, crowds and helpful salespeople delivers more interaction and sales than a catalog. But a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security alert: Attack campaign involving stolen OAuth user tokens issued to two third-party integrators]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-15-security-alert-stolen-oauth-user-tokens/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-15-security-alert-stolen-oauth-user-tokens/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T22:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 12, GitHub Security began an investigation that uncovered evidence that an attacker abused stolen OAuth user tokens issued to two third-party OAuth integrators, Heroku and Travis-CI, to download data from dozens of organizations, including npm. Read on to learn more about the impact to GitHub, npm, and our users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Studio: A Hands-on Guided Tour of Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=50634</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/code-studio-a-hands-on-guided-tour-of-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready for our first Code Studio based on Camunda Platform 8 with breakout rooms and a collaborative design. 
The post Code Studio: A Hands-on Guided Tour of Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things to feel bad about]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42726</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/691411296/0/sethsblog~Things-to-feel-bad-about/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T08:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might have a list of them. In fact, many of us do, and consult it quite often. The list is defective for a number of reasons: It’s not accurate. There are things that aren’t right in our world that don’t appear on the list. Our personal list tends to be organized around things that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Cloud guru Tiffany Jernigan]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/14/a-bootiful-podcast-cloud-guru-tiffany-jernigan</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/14/a-bootiful-podcast-cloud-guru-tiffany-jernigan"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talk about his first in-person conference since the pandemic descended upon us -the fabulous Devnexus 2022 show - and talks to colleague, teacher, friend, and Kubernetes legend Tiffany Jernigan (@tiffanyfayj).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Spring Boot with Elastic App Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-spring-boot-with-elastic-app-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-spring-boot-with-elastic-app-search"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we will go from nothing to a fully running Spring Boot application querying Elastic App Search, which has crawled the contents of a website. We will start up the cluster and configure the application step by step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Reelsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Spring Boot with Elastic App Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-spring-boot-with-elastic-app-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-spring-boot-with-elastic-app-search"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In this article we will go from nothing to a fully running Spring Boot application querying Elastic App Search, which has crawled the contents of a website. We will start up the cluster and configure the application step by step.
git clone https://github.com/spinscale/spring-boot-app-search,
In order to have an example up and running, we have to create an API key in Elastic Cloud as described in the terraform provider setup.
Once that is done, run
terraform init
terraform validate
terraform apply,
and grab a coffee before the serious work begins. After a few minutes you should see your instance in the Elastic Cloud UI up and running like this
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt59d116a581c56493/625748c11c67524fc6889299/screenshot-springboot-with-elasticsearch-s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Reelsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geiger Counter]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2607/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2607/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/geiger_counter.png" title="At first I didn't get why they were warning me about all those birds sitting on the wire, but then I understood." alt="At first I didn't get why they were warning me about all those birds sitting on the wire, but then I understood." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Locked-Image Tuning: Adding Language Understanding to Image Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/locked-image-tuning-adding-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/locked-image-tuning-adding-language.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T21:41:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Andreas Steiner and Basil Mustafa, Research Software Engineers at Google Research, Brain team 
The ability to classify images into categories has been transformed by deep learning. It has also been significantly accelerated by transfer learning, whereby models are first pre-trained on large datasets, like ImageNet, to learn visual representations that are then transferred via fine-tuning to a new task with less data (e.g., classifying animals). Previous works such as BiT and ViT employed these methods to achieve state-of-the-art performance on a wide range of classification tasks, such as the VTAB benchmark. 
However, fine-tuning has some downsides: though pre-training is done only once, fine-tuning is necessary on every new dataset for which task-specific data is needed. Multimo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Achieves AWS DevOps Competency Status]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-achieves-aws-devops-competency-status</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-achieves-aws-devops-competency-status"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The all-new AWS DevSecOps Competency includes HashiCorp as a Day 1 launch partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot alerts now surface if your code is calling a vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-14-dependabot-alerts-now-surface-if-code-is-calling-vulnerability/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-14-dependabot-alerts-now-surface-if-code-is-calling-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T16:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we're shipping a new feature for Dependabot alerts which helps you better understand how you're affected by a vulnerability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 – A 10-Year Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=50440</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/camunda-platform-8-a-10-year-journey/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how a bold idea with ten years of research, development, and hardening it in practice has resulted in the launch of Camunda Platform 8. 
The post Camunda Platform 8 – A 10-Year Journey appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two things we say to kids]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40762</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/691246778/0/sethsblog~Two-things-we-say-to-kids/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overhead recently: To a 10-year-old on his way to a baseball game, “Come home with a win.” To a 9-year-old at the supermarket, “I don’t think you’ll like that.” It’s pretty clear what lessons are being taught.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP Update – New Single-AZ Deployment Type]]></title>
        <id>6c44f453a20a0ebed0a4e44b2abe9e79c0c320de</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap-update-new-single-az-deployment-type/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T19:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year I told you about Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP and showed you how you can create a file system in minutes with just a couple of clicks. You can use these high-performance, scalable (up to 176 PiB) file systems to migrate your on-premises applications to the cloud and to build new, cloud-native applications. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple and Effective Zero-Shot Task-Oriented Dialogue]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/simple-and-effective-zero-shot-task.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/simple-and-effective-zero-shot-task.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T17:06:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeffrey Zhao and Raghav Gupta, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Modern conversational agents need to integrate with an ever-increasing number of services to perform a wide variety of tasks, from booking flights and finding restaurants, to playing music and telling jokes. Adding this functionality can be difficult — for each new task, one needs to collect new data and retrain the models that power the conversational agent. This is because most task-oriented dialogue (TOD) models are trained on a single task-specific ontology. An ontology is generally represented as a list of possible user intents (e.g., if the user wants to book a flight, if the user wants to play some music, etc.) and possible parameter slots to extract from the conversation (e.g., the date of the flight, the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco, Datadog, Fortinet, VMware & Others Add Consul Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cisco-datadog-fortinet-vmware-others-add-consul-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cisco-datadog-fortinet-vmware-others-add-consul-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Consul ecosystem has experienced rapid growth in the past six months, recording a total of 10 new integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#CamundaSummit Unconference: Cast Your Vote]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=50343</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/camunda-summit-unconference-cast-your-vote/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for your submissions! From now until April 16, cast your vote for the discussion topics you want on the Unconference agenda.
The post #CamundaSummit Unconference: Cast Your Vote appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework Data Binding Rules Vulnerability (CVE-2022-22968)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/13/spring-framework-data-binding-rules-vulnerability-cve-2022-22968</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/13/spring-framework-data-binding-rules-vulnerability-cve-2022-22968"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table of Contents


  
Overview

  
Does This Affect My Application?

  
Reassessing Your Data Binding Approach


Overview

While investigating the Spring Framework RCE vulnerability CVE-2022-22965 and the suggested workaround, we realized that the disallowedFields configuration setting on WebDataBinder is not intuitive and is not clearly documented. We have fixed that but also decided to be on the safe side and announce a follow-up CVE, in order to ensure application developers are alerted and have a chance to review their configuration.


  
CVE-2022-22968: Spring Framework Data Binding Rules Vulnerability


We have released Spring Framework 5.3.19 and 5.2.21 which contain the fix. Spring Boot 2.6.7 and 2.5.13 are scheduled to be released on April 21, 2022.


  
Until Spring …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Insights for Ansible Automation Platform New Report : Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-insights-for-ansible-automation-platform-new-report-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-insights-for-ansible-automation-platform-new-report-modules"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Insights is a suite of cloud services available on the Red Hat Hybrid Cloud Console, powered by an expert system that is built upon years of data collected from across Red Hat’s worldwide customer base. For Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform customers, it provides predictive analytical reporting of your Ansible automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.19 and 5.2.21 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/13/spring-framework-5-3-19-and-5-2-21-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/13/spring-framework-5-3-19-and-5-2-21-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T11:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.19 and 5.2.21 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.19 includes 12 fixes and improvements. Spring Framework 5.2.21 includes 5 selected fixes and improvements.

In addition, Spring Framework 5.3.19 and 5.2.21 include a fix for CVE-2022-22968: Spring Framework Data Binding Rules Vulnerability and are recommended upgrades for all Spring production scenarios.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking categories of media]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42708</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/691088161/0/sethsblog~Rethinking-categories-of-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T08:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is found or it arrives. It is hosted many places or it has a single home. It earns and delivers on permission, or it’s spam. It changes over time or it’s static. It’s the work of an individual or the production of a community. It’s valuable because of network effects, or in spite of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 12th, 2022 (Devnexus 2022 Edition!!)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/12/this-week-in-spring-april-12th-2022-devnexus-2022-edition</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/12/this-week-in-spring-april-12th-2022-devnexus-2022-edition"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - Devnexus Edition

Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring - I’m at my first in-person event since the virus: Devnexus! WOOHOOO!! Well, technically I’m still in San Francisco as I write this, but I’ll be in Atlanta, GA tomorrow for… Devnexus! I hope if you’re there that you’ll reach out! 

Friends, colleagues, and community members from the Spring, Tanzu, and adjoining communities will also be there! Here are some of the people I hope to nab a selfie with and whose talks I hope to see! 


  
Glenn Renfro

  
Adib Saikali

  
Joe Grandja

  
Whitney Lee

  
Hillmer Chona

  
Jonatan Ivanov

  
Josh Cummings

  
Alberto C. Rios

  
Simon Brown


And of course I’ll be doing two talks, as well, (one on GraalVm and another on edge services) and I hope you’ll come see those, too! 

And with that out of the way, let’s get on with our regularly scheduled roundup!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: GraphQL Java founder Andi Marek

  
Asir V Selvasingh on Twitter

  
Blog: Kubernetes Removals and Deprecations In 1.24

  
Congrats to the Hibernate team for reaching Hibernate 6.0

  
SivaLabs has a nice post called, “My attempt to understand why people perceive Java as complex.”  What do you think?

  
Spring Cloud Data Flow 2.9.4 Released

  
 Spring Cloud Azure 4.0 integrations are generally available.  Congrats to the teams at Microsoft and the community on such an epic release!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lidar-Camera Deep Fusion for Multi-Modal 3D Detection]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/lidar-camera-deep-fusion-for-multi.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/lidar-camera-deep-fusion-for-multi.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T19:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yingwei Li, Student Researcher, Google Cloud and Adams Wei Yu, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team  
LiDAR and visual cameras are two types of complementary sensors used for 3D object detection in autonomous vehicles and robots. LiDAR, which is a remote sensing technique that uses light in the form of a pulsed laser to measure ranges, provides low-resolution shape and depth information, while cameras provide high-resolution shape and texture information. While the features captured by LiDAR and cameras should be merged together to provide optimal 3D object detection, it turns out that most state-of-the-art 3D object detectors use LiDAR as the only input. The main reason is that to develop robust 3D object detection models, most methods need to augment and transform th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Netflix Content Engineering makes a federated graph searchable]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5c0c1c7d7eaf</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/how-netflix-content-engineering-makes-a-federated-graph-searchable-5c0c1c7d7eaf?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T17:16:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Alex Hutter, Falguni Jhaveri and Senthil Sayeebaba]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul on Amazon ECS 0.4 Now Supports Multi-Tenancy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-4-now-supports-multi-tenancy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-4-now-supports-multi-tenancy"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest version of HashiCorp Consul on Amazon ECS adds support for multi-tenancy with administrative partitions and namespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 – Orchestrate All the Things]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=48495</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/camunda-platform-8-orchestrate-all-the-things/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 is here! Find out why we built Camunda Platform 8, what problems it solves, and why it’s a universal process orchestrator. 
The post Camunda Platform 8 – Orchestrate All the Things appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8.0 Released – What’s New]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=48464</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/camunda-platform-8-0-released-whats-new/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 brings what you love about Camunda with added performance, scalability, availability, connectivity, and collaboration.
The post Camunda Platform 8.0 Released – What’s New appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 for Camunda Platform 7 Users – What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=48483</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/camunda-platform-8-for-camunda-platform-7-users-what-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 is here! Let's look at what this new product launch means for our large Camunda Platform 7 community. 
The post Camunda Platform 8 for Camunda Platform 7 Users – What You Need to Know appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 11, 2022]]></title>
        <id>6021dc6654c0552b04372a3d6090b690a95a121e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-11-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T18:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! As spring arrives in the Northern Hemisphere, tulips, sunshine, and cherry blossoms finally appear to be in bloom—surely signs of warmer days to come in North America, Asia, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate Your Application with Vault: Static Secrets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-integrate-your-application-with-vault-static-secrets</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-integrate-your-application-with-vault-static-secrets"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to retrieve static secrets from HashiCorp Vault in a real-world setting using a new sample application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large-Scale Matrix Factorization on TPUs]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/large-scale-matrix-factorization-on-tpus.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/large-scale-matrix-factorization-on-tpus.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T17:52:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Harsh Mehta, Software Engineer, Google Research 
Matrix factorization is one of the oldest, yet still widely used, techniques for learning how to recommend items such as songs or movies from user ratings. In its basic form, it approximates a large, sparse (i.e., mostly empty) matrix of user-item interactions with a product of two smaller, denser matrices representing learned item and user features. These dense matrices, in turn, can be used to recommend items to a user with which they haven't interacted before. 
Despite its algorithmic simplicity, matrix factorization can still achieve competitive performance in recommender benchmarks. Alternating least squares (ALS), and especially its implicit variation, is a fundamental algorithm to learn the parameters of matrix factorization…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.08.04]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63867</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-08-04/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back for another top stories from the #AzureDevOps #Community! After last weeks’ ‘catch-up’ from the last month, this week feels so much quieter, but there is some awesome content for you!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.08.04 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VDTTS: Visually-Driven Text-To-Speech]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/vdtts-visually-driven-text-to-speech.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/vdtts-visually-driven-text-to-speech.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T20:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tal Remez, Software Engineer, Google Research and Micheal Hassid, Software Engineer Intern, Google Research   
Recent years have seen a tremendous increase in the creation and serving of video content to users across the world in a variety of languages and over numerous platforms. The process of creating high quality content can include several stages from video capturing and captioning to  video and audio editing. In some cases dialogue is re-recorded (referred to as dialog replacement, post-sync or dubbing) in a studio in order to achieve high quality and replace original audio that might have been recorded in noisy conditions. However, the dialog replacement process can be difficult and tedious because the newly recorded audio needs to be well synced with the video, requiring …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: GraphQL Java founder Andi Marek]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/07/a-bootiful-podcast-graphql-java-founder-andi-marek</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/07/a-bootiful-podcast-graphql-java-founder-andi-marek"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment of a Bootiful Podcast, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to the GraphQL Java project founder and lead, Atlassian engineer, and Spring GraphQL cofounder Andi Marek (@andimarek).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.8 Adds Secret Values for Input Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-8-adds-secret-values-for-input-variables</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-8-adds-secret-values-for-input-variables"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint 0.8 introduces targetable runners, secret values for input variables, and a new command line tool that adds new insight to Waypoint operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 Beta Adds Native Service Discovery and Edge Workload Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 includes built-in service discovery, improved edge compute support, Container Storage Interface (CSI) general availability, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Login MFA Support Added to Vault Open Source and HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/login-mfa-support-added-to-vault-open-source-and-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/login-mfa-support-added-to-vault-open-source-and-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp expands MFA support across open source and all HCP Vault tiers, previously available only through Vault Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing AWS Lambda Function URLs: Built-in HTTPS Endpoints for Single-Function Microservices]]></title>
        <id>b2c24ddd82a7e2defa1973b188f7be843a16b154</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-aws-lambda-function-urls-built-in-https-endpoints-for-single-function-microservices/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are adopting microservices architectures to build resilient and scalable applications using AWS Lambda. These applications are composed of multiple serverless functions that implement the business logic. Each function is mapped to API endpoints, methods, and resources using services such as Amazon API Gateway and Application Load Balancer. But sometimes all you need is a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Casalboni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第207話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496856368973</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496856368973"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficiently Initializing Reinforcement Learning With Prior Policies]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/efficiently-initializing-reinforcement.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/efficiently-initializing-reinforcement.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T14:38:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ikechukwu Uchendu, AI Resident and Ted Xiao, Software Engineer, Robotics at Google 
Reinforcement learning (RL) can be used to train a policy to perform a task via trial and error, but a major challenge in RL is learning policies from scratch in environments with hard exploration challenges. For example, consider the setting depicted in the door-binary-v0 environment from the adroit manipulation suite, where an RL agent must control a hand in 3D space to open a door placed in front of it. 
   


An RL agent must control a hand in 3D space to open a door placed in front of it. The agent receives a reward signal only when the door is completely open.

   
Since the agent receives no intermediary rewards, it cannot measure how close it is to completing the task, and so must explore …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Data Flow 2.9.4 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/05/spring-cloud-data-flow-2-9-4-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/05/spring-cloud-data-flow-2-9-4-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.9.4 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release contains an update of the Spring Boot version and addresses a couple of CVEs. See the release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in 2.9.4


  
Update to Spring Boot 2.5.12

  
Resolves CVE-2022-22965

  
Resolves CVE-2021-29425


Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on Stackoverflow or GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M2 (codename Kilburn) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/05/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m2-codename-kilburn-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/05/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m2-codename-kilburn-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T19:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Milestone 2 (M2) of the Spring Cloud 2022.0.0 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2022.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2022.0.0-M2 Release Train

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.

Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M2 is compatible with Spring Boot 3.0.0-M2.
Spring Cloud Stream


  
Both Kafka and RabbitMQ binders for Spring Cloud Stream have been migrated as part of the core Spring Cloud Stream repository. With this change, Spring Cloud Stream now follows a mono-repo approach where all the framework-related codebase for Spring Cloud Stream is now part of a single repository. See mor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 5th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/05/this-week-in-spring-april-5th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/05/this-week-in-spring-april-5th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’m back home from the Hawaiin islands. It’s so good to be home. 

First thing’s first: there’s a security vulnerability. We’ve already released guidance on how to mitigate as well as new releases of Spring Framework and Spring Boot that include the mitigation by deault. See the links below for more.


  
Spring Framework RCE, Early Announcement

  
Spring Framework RCE, Mitigation Alternative

  
CVE report published for Spring Cloud Function


Now, back to your regularly scheduled installment of This Week in Spring: 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Kubernetes cofounder and vice president of R&D at VMware, Craig McLuckie

  
Blog: Is Your Cluster Ready for v1.24?
native-java-framework-comparison)

  
Clean Architecture in a Spring Application

  
JHipster Native Blueprint Supports GraalVM Native Image

  
JobRunr & JobRunr Pro v5.0.0

  
Major migrations made easy with OpenRewrite

  
Spring Boot 2.5.12 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.6.6 available now

  
Spring Cloud Azure 4.0 is Now Generally Available

  
Happy April Fools! :D Spring I/O on Twitter

  
In last week’s installment of Spring Tips, I looked at the Brave, Bold, and Boring YugabyteDB

  
 I haven’t watched this yet, but it’s a ten hour long tutorial on Spring Boot - there’s bound to be some good stuff in there! 

  
https://twitter.com/JavaAtMicrosoft/status/1511138560321142793 @JavaAtMicrosoft #Java has played a critical role in democratizing cross-platform development. With #Microsoft’s recent JEP 388 contribution to #OpenJDK, Java apps can now run on a wider range

  
The differences between Docker, containerd, CRI-O and runc - Tutorial Works]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reproducibility in Deep Learning and Smooth Activations]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/reproducibility-in-deep-learning-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/reproducibility-in-deep-learning-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T17:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Gil Shamir and Dong Lin, Research Software Engineers, Google Research 
Ever queried a recommender system and found that the same search only a few moments later or on a different device yields very different results? This is not uncommon and can be frustrating if a person is looking for something specific. As a designer of such a system, it is also not uncommon for the metrics measured to change from design and testing to deployment, bringing into question the utility of the experimental testing phase. Some level of such irreproducibility can be expected as the world changes and new models are deployed. However, this also happens regularly as requests hit duplicates of the same model or models are being refreshed.  
Lack of replicability, where researchers are unable to reproduce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 4, 2022]]></title>
        <id>6e8469ff0f01ab8c8b1e0c9ad99babde49d94aea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-4-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T20:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Welcome to the April 4 edition of the AWS Week in Review. This week, alongside the main launches, I also captured a couple of new capabilities, such as a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63769</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-lean-product-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T18:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product has three parts; this is Part 2. In this blog, we discuss why lean product, what is lean product, how to approach lean product, and then we demonstrate How we apply lean product to build our own lean product in Dojo.  Finally, we ask a question if we should scale process or scale leaders. 
The post DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 2 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pathways Language Model (PaLM): Scaling to 540 Billion Parameters for Breakthrough Performance]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pathways-language-model-palm-scaling-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pathways-language-model-palm-scaling-to.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T16:01:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sharan Narang and Aakanksha Chowdhery, Software Engineers, Google Research 
In recent years, large neural networks trained for language understanding and generation have achieved impressive results across a wide range of tasks. GPT-3 first showed that large language models (LLMs) can be used for few-shot learning and can achieve impressive results without large-scale task-specific data collection or model parameter updating. More recent LLMs, such as GLaM, LaMDA, Gopher, and Megatron-Turing NLG, achieved state-of-the-art few-shot results on many tasks by scaling model size, using sparsely activated modules, and training on larger datasets from more diverse sources. Yet much work remains in understanding the capabilities that emerge with few-shot learning as we push the limits of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Kubernetes Secrets for Flux with HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/manage-kubernetes-secrets-for-flux-with-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/manage-kubernetes-secrets-for-flux-with-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure the Secrets Store CSI driver with HashiCorp Vault to securely inject secrets into Flux or other GitOps tools on Kubernetes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.04]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63811</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-01-04/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T18:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s April in April! It’s no joke, the top stories from the #AzureDevOps #Community are back this week! We have been on a short hiatus in support of the people in Ukraine. We do hope that everyone out there is safe and healthy.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.04 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CVSS: A Massively Multilingual Speech-to-Speech Translation Corpus]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/introducing-cvss-massively-multilingual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/introducing-cvss-massively-multilingual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T16:06:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ye Jia and Michelle Tadmor Ramanovich, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Automatic translation of speech from one language to speech in another language, called speech-to-speech translation (S2ST), is important for breaking down the communication barriers between people speaking different languages. Conventionally, automatic S2ST systems are built with a cascade of automatic speech recognition (ASR), text-to-text machine translation (MT), and text-to-speech (TTS) synthesis sub-systems, so that the system overall is text-centric. Recently, work on S2ST that doesn’t rely on intermediate text representation is emerging, such as end-to-end direct S2ST (e.g., Translatotron) and cascade S2ST based on learned discrete representations of speech (e.g., Tjandra et al.). While early vers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat, Datadog, and More Partners Add Vault Ecosystem Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/red-hat-datadog-and-more-partners-add-vault-ecosystem-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/red-hat-datadog-and-more-partners-add-vault-ecosystem-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We welcome six new HCP Vault verified integrations from Datadog, Grafana Labs, Redis, Red Hat, Splunk, and Ui Path, plus four new self-managed HashiCorp Vault integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63764</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-lean-product-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T14:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product has three parts; this is Part 1. In this blog, we provide some historical info about Lean Product in DevOps Dojo; then we explain why use a product-centric model, compare project vs. product, deep dive various roles and transition strategy, finally discuss product-centric model at services. 
The post DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework RCE, Mitigation Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/01/spring-framework-rce-mitigation-alternative</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/01/spring-framework-rce-mitigation-alternative"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T11:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday we announced a Spring Framework RCE vulnerability CVE-2022-22965, listing Apache Tomcat as one of several preconditions. The Apache Tomcat team has since released versions 10.0.20, 9.0.62, and 8.5.78 all of which close the attack vector on Tomcat’s side. While the vulnerability is not in Tomcat itself, in real world situations, it is important to be able to choose among multiple upgrade paths that in turn provides flexibility and layered protection. 

Upgrading to Spring Framework 5.3.18+ or 5.2.20+ continues to be our main recommendation not only because it addresses the root cause and prevents other possible attack vectors, but also because it adds protection for other CVEs addressed since the current version in use. 

For older, unsupported versions of the Spring Framework, the Tomcat releases provide an adequate solution for the reported attack vector. Nevertheless, we must stress that this should only be seen as a tactical solution, while the main goal should still be to upgrade to a currently supported Spring Framework version as soon as possible.

Last but not least, it’s worth mentioning that downgrading to Java 8 provides another viable workaround, which may be another tactical solution option.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Provider Support Comes to the Terraform Private Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/provider-support-comes-to-the-terraform-private-registry</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/provider-support-comes-to-the-terraform-private-registry"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now publish and distribute providers from the private registry in Terraform Cloud and Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.10 Adds Multi-Stack Deployments and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-10-adds-multi-stack-deployments-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-10-adds-multi-stack-deployments-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform 0.10 (CDKTF) enables multi-stack deployments and improves the CLI experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring an AWS dynamic inventory with Automation controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/configuring-an-aws-dynamic-inventory-with-automation-controller</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/configuring-an-aws-dynamic-inventory-with-automation-controller"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the core components of Ansible is inventories. In its most basic form, an inventory provides host information to Ansible so it can trigger the tasks on the right host or system. In most environments, the static inventory is sufficient for the Ansible control node to work from, however as we expand our use of automation, we need to transition to more effective methods of gathering ever-changing environment details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Cloud NGFW for AWS]]></title>
        <id>5419ef265e15cd23d7d20fc3aafb456bd449eedb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-cloud-ngfw-for-aws/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T12:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2018 I wrote about AWS Firewall Manager (Central Management for Your Web Application Portfolio) and showed you how you could host multiple applications, perhaps spanning multiple AWS accounts and regions, while maintaining centralized control over your organization’s security settings and profile. In the same way that Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS) supports multiple database […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Simplifies Reusable Variable Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-simplifies-reusable-variable-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-simplifies-reusable-variable-management"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud variable sets let you simplify the management of reusable variables across an entire organization — the feature is now generally available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New and Updated Vault Tutorials for 1.10 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-and-updated-vault-tutorials-for-1-10-release</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-and-updated-vault-tutorials-for-1-10-release"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try out the new and enhanced features introduced in Vault 1.10 with step-by-step tutorials on HashiCorp Learn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“New Boards Hub” Public Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63721</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T19:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to officially announce the public preview for the "New Boards Hub". We look forward to having you try it and sending us your feedback.
The post “New Boards Hub” Public Preview appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 28, 2022]]></title>
        <id>36fca099d51da2eb5217d3b6cd96385675ea994c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-28-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T19:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Welcome to another round up of the most significant AWS launches from the previous week. Among the most relevant news, we have improvements done in AWS Lambda, a new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the newest features in the Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for ServiceNow ITSM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-the-newest-features-in-the-red-hat-ansible-certified-content-collection-for-servicenow-itsm</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-the-newest-features-in-the-red-hat-ansible-certified-content-collection-for-servicenow-itsm"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for ServiceNow helps you create automated workflows targeting IT service management (ITSM) tasks faster while establishing and maintaining a single source of truth in the ServiceNow configuration management database (CMDB). In this blog, I’ll share the latest features we’ve added to the Collection, and you can find additional resources about existing features at the end of this blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Four HashiCorp Women Got Into Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-women-leaders-got-into-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-women-leaders-got-into-tech"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four women at HashiCorp talk about their journey to a career in tech and offer lessons, inspiration, and advice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda Now Supports Up to 10 GB Ephemeral Storage]]></title>
        <id>57c25c20e6d01488a25def63e79d1c56dd2638df</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-lambda-now-supports-up-to-10-gb-ephemeral-storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T20:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless applications are event-driven, using ephemeral compute functions ranging from web APIs, mobile backends, and streaming analytics to data processing stages in machine learning (ML) and high-performance applications. While AWS Lambda includes a 512 MB temporary file system (/tmp) for your code, this is an ephemeral scratch resource not intended for durable storage such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Signs of Disease from External Images of the Eye]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/detecting-signs-of-disease-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/detecting-signs-of-disease-from.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T17:10:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Boris Babenko, Software Engineer and Naama Hammel, Clinical Research Scientist, Google Health 
Three years ago we wrote about our work on predicting a number of cardiovascular risk factors from fundus photos (i.e., photos of the back of the eye)1 using deep learning. That such risk factors could be extracted from fundus photos was a novel discovery and thus a surprising outcome to clinicians and laypersons alike. Since then, we and other researchers have discovered additional novel biomarkers from fundus photos, such as markers for chronic kidney disease and diabetes, and hemoglobin levels to detect anemia.  
A unifying goal of work like this is to develop new disease detection or monitoring approaches that are less invasive, more accurate, cheaper and more readily available. How…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AzureRM 3.0 Brings Enhanced Azure Function Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-azurerm-3-0-brings-enhanced-azure-function-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-azurerm-3-0-brings-enhanced-azure-function-support"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureRM 3.0 brings significant parity between the Azure provider for Terraform and Azure services currently available. Review the breaking changes as you prepare to upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>