<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-09T00:19:26.332Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-09T00:19:26.332Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sparsity-preserving differentially private training]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/sparsity-preserving-differentially.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/sparsity-preserving-differentially.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yangsibo Huang, Research Intern, Google Research; Chiyuan Zhang, Research Scientist, Google Research





Large embedding models have emerged as a fundamental tool for various applications in recommendation systems [1, 2] and natural language processing [3, 4, 5]. Such models enable the integration of non-numerical data into deep learning models by mapping categorical or string-valued input attributes with large vocabularies to fixed-length representation vectors using embedding layers. These models are widely deployed in personalized recommendation systems and achieve state-of-the-art performance in language tasks, such as  language modeling, sentiment analysis, and question answering. In many such scenarios, privacy is an equally important feature when deploying those models. A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All species are invasive species]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44588</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/848107322/0/sethsblog~All-species-are-invasive-species/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T09:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Human beings as we know them have only been around for 70,000 years or so. Honeybees got to North America around the time Columbus did. And the same is true for technologies and companies. Western Union was an interloper, telegrams were the scary new tech that was going to change everything for the worse. It’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the Wrong Stuff]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2865/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2865/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/the_wrong_stuff.png" title="The phantom found Edward Everett Hale a century too early; by the time we invented satellites, the specifics of his 'brick moon' proposal were dismissed as science fiction." alt="The phantom found Edward Everett Hale a century too early; by the time we invented satellites, the specifics of his 'brick moon' proposal were dismissed as science fiction." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrading GitHub.com to MySQL 8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-07-upgrading-github-com-to-mysql-8-0/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-upgrading-github-com-to-mysql-8-0/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub uses MySQL to store vast amounts of relational data. This is the story of how we seamlessly upgraded our production fleet to MySQL 8.0.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-upgrading-github-com-to-mysql-8-0/">Upgrading GitHub.com to MySQL 8.0</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From macOS runners to secure deployments, what’s new from GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-07-from-macos-runners-to-secure-deployments-whats-new-from-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-from-macos-runners-to-secure-deployments-whats-new-from-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Read a roundup of the exciting, new innovation coming from GitHub Actions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-from-macos-runners-to-secure-deployments-whats-new-from-github-actions/">From macOS runners to secure deployments, what’s new from GitHub Actions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.7 improves Vault and Consul integrations, adds NUMA support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.7 — now generally available — introduces improved workload identity, improved Vault and Consul integrations, NUMA support, Nomad actions, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[While you sleep, Automate resolving Dynatrace problem alerts and report them to ServiceNow!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/while-you-sleep-automate-resolving-dynatrace-problem-alerts-and-report-them-to-servicenow</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/while-you-sleep-automate-resolving-dynatrace-problem-alerts-and-report-them-to-servicenow"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating observability tools with automation is paramount in the realm of modern IT operations, as it fosters a symbiotic relationship between visibility and efficiency. Observability tools provide deep insights into the performance, health, and behavior of complex systems, enabling organizations to proactively identify and rectify issues before they escalate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bforrest@redhat.com (Ben Forrester)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VALID: A perceptually validated virtual avatar library for inclusion and diversity]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/valid-perceptually-validated-virtual.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/valid-perceptually-validated-virtual.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mar Gonzalez-Franco, Research Scientist, Google AR & VR


In the last decade, interdisciplinary scientists have dedicated a significant amount of effort to better understand the use of avatars, and have made many interesting observations, including the capacity of the users to embody their avatar (i.e., the illusion that the avatar body is their own) and the self-avatar follower effect, which creates a binding between the actions of the avatar and the user strong enough that the avatar can actually affect user behavior. 



The use of avatars in experiments isn’t just about how users will interact and behave in VR spaces, but also about discovering the limits of human perception and neuroscience. In fact, some VR social experiments often rely on recreating scenarios that can’t be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Innovation Graph Q2 2023 Data Release]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-07-github-innovation-graph-q2-2023-data-release/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-github-innovation-graph-q2-2023-data-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T16:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover the latest trends and insights on public software development activity on GitHub with the release of Q2 2023 data for the Innovation Graph.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-github-innovation-graph-q2-2023-data-release/">GitHub Innovation Graph Q2 2023 Data Release</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple Fork-Join Framework With Matrix Builds]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=416702</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/12/simple-fork-join-framework-with-matrix-builds/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T16:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recently released TeamCity 2023.11 comes with the long-awaited matrix build feature. Matrix build is a build that executes the same set of steps on different combinations of input parameters, producing a matrix with the result of every execution. This is a classic approach to testing code changes on different architectures and operating systems. Matrix […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavel Sher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy: New Projects and Topics in December]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=416447</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/12/07/jetbrains-academy-new-projects-and-topics-in-december-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T15:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready for a jolly coding ride this December at JetBrains Academy!  We’ve got three new projects and more than 80 topics coming your way. One great way to feel the festivities is to immerse yourself in our fun projects, like the X-mas Tree project, now released from Beta. You’ll be learning Python and spreading […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Regina Muradova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=412897</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/12/intellij-idea-2023-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T15:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 is here, and it comes packed with an array of new features and enhancements to elevate your coding experience. You can get the latest build from our website, through the free Toolbox App, or via snaps for Ubuntu. Download IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 The IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 release signifies the continued evolution of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ 2023.3: Updated AI Assistant and Better Support for Cross-Platform Code]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rscpp&amp;p=414594</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rscpp/2023/12/07/resharper-cpp-2023-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T15:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get the most out of your developer experience with the latest ReSharper C++ update! ReSharper C++ 2023.3 brings a major update to JetBrains AI Assistant; a new built-in grammar and spelling checker; updates for C, C++, and HLSL support; code completion and Find Usages for inactive code inside conditional preprocessor branches; and more. Read on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elvira Mustafina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion Classic 2023.3 Released With AI Assistant, Meson and Bazel Support, Enhancements for Embedded Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=415070</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/12/clion-classic-2023-3-released-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T14:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.3 features JetBrains AI Assistant, which has now moved beyond the technical preview stage, bringing more context-aware actions to benefit your everyday C++ development workflows. The new release also expands the variety of supported projects by adding Meson and improving Bazel support. New abilities like the Assembly view and enhanced code analysis with memory […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dotCover, dotMemory, dotPeek, and dotTrace 2023.3 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=415759</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/12/07/dotcover-dotmemory-dotpeek-and-dottrace-2023-3-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T14:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dotCover 2023.3, dotMemory 2023.3, dotPeek 2023.3, and dotTrace 2023.3 have been released and are ready for download!  Let’s take a look at what’s new with these .NET tools. dotMemory 2023.3 dotTrace 2023.3 dotPeek 2023.3 dotCover 2023.3 If you’re also interested in learning more about ReSharper 2023.3 or Rider 2023.3, please visit:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.3 Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=407837</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/12/phpstorm-2023-3-is-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T14:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the latest version of PhpStorm with power-boosting enhancements that include the new capabilities of JetBrains AI Assistant, improvements for the Symfony framework, Pest updates, and much more. Learn how to become even more productive with PhpStorm 2023.3 from this blog post. Download PhpStorm 2023.3 For a quick video overview, check out this roundup of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tania Goral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2023.3: Support For C# 12, Performance Enhancements, and More AI-Powered Features]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=415573</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/12/07/resharper-2023-3-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T14:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2023.3 and new versions of other JetBrains .NET tools have just been released. This version brings support for the latest C# 12 features, optimized background code analysis, and the ability to control the amount of resources allocated to solution-wide code analysis. AI Assistant has also received important enhancements. In this article, we’ll cover the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2023.3: Support for .NET 8 SDK, the Latest From C# 12, Performance Enhancements, Predictive Debugging, and More AI-powered Features.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=415219</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/12/07/rider-2023-3-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T14:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A major update for Rider has just been published! Rider 2023.3 offers support for the .NET 8 SDK, including the latest features from C# 12. Other enhancements include an improved experience when running multiple projects, a predictive debugging mode, and the ability to easily create and navigate through unit tests. The release of Rider 2023.3 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ Scala Plugin 2023.3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=scala&amp;p=402141</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/scala/2023/12/07/intellij-scala-plugin-2023-3-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scala 3 As usual, the new release focused much on improving the Scala 3 support. Especially enums received much attention. The Scala plugin now recognizes that enums cannot be extended and highlights such attempts; annotations and modifiers are now propagated correctly to generated symbols; type widening of apply methods is fixed to take only direct […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maciej Gorywoda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin for WebAssembly Goes Alpha]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=416264</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/12/kotlin-for-webassembly-goes-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T12:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin/Wasm, the newest Kotlin Multiplatform target platform, has reached Alpha status! Here’s what you need to know about this change at a glance: Get started with Kotlin/Wasm WebAssembly: The newest Kotlin Multiplatform target WebAssembly is establishing itself as the standard compilation target for languages targeting the browser – and beyond! With Kotlin/Wasm, we’re giving you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Aigner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abundance and ideas]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47944</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/846275930/0/sethsblog~Abundance-and-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T09:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A colleague got an angry note. It concluded with, “you should know better.” The transgression? The sender was offended that my friend had written a post about a concept she’s been developing for nearly a decade. Of course, no idea is unique, and the posted idea sort of rhymed with one that the professor had […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2023.3: Generally Available AI Assistant, Improved Project Indexing, New Supported Libraries and Technologies]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=412220</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2023/12/rubymine-2023-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T08:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2023.3 is now available! As we announced in our previous blog post, the latest version of our popular Ruby and Rails IDE comes complete with RubyMine’s improved project indexing.  We also identified and resolved several problems that had been causing low memory performance and freezes when running larger test suites with the profiler in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iryna Pisklyarova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring creator Rod Johnson and Oracle vice president Heather VanCura]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/07/spring-creator-rod-johnson-and-oracle-vice-president-heather-vancura</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/07/spring-creator-rod-johnson-and-oracle-vice-president-heather-vancura"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from self-managed Elastic Stack to Elastic Cloud using snapshot and restore with Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-cloud-snapshot-and-restore-amazon-s3</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-cloud-snapshot-and-restore-amazon-s3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow this step-by-step process to set up and run a self-managed Elastic stack. Then, migrate the Elastic stack content to an Elastic Cloud deployment using the snapshot and restore migration approach of storing and accessing snapshots in Amazon S3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enrico Zimuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from self-managed Elastic Stack to Elastic Cloud using snapshot and restore with Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-cloud-snapshot-and-restore-amazon-s3</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-cloud-snapshot-and-restore-amazon-s3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
I had the pleasure of talking with many interesting people at AWS re:Invent 2023 in Las Vegas while I was helping out at Elastic®’s booth in the Expo hall. I spoke to many SREs, developers, solution architects, and other professionals who were running a self-managed Elastic Stack and had questions about the process of migrating their Elastic stack to Elastic Cloud. 

To help provide guidance on questions about Elastic Cloud migration, this blog post provides a walkthrough of how to set up a self-managed Elastic stack and then migrate that Elastic stack’s contents to Elastic Cloud using a snapshot and restore migration method. For the storage location of the snapshot, we’ll use Amazon S3, which is a perfect service for saving and accessing files with fine grain control provided by AWS Ide…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 8.11.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.11.2 over 8.11.1 and 8.10.x releases.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enrico Zimuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cueing up a calculator: an introduction to exploit development on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-06-cueing-up-a-calculator-an-introduction-to-exploit-development-on-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-06-cueing-up-a-calculator-an-introduction-to-exploit-development-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T17:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Using CVE-2023-43641 as an example, I’ll explain how to develop an exploit for a memory corruption vulnerability on Linux. The exploit has to bypass several mitigations to achieve code execution.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-06-cueing-up-a-calculator-an-introduction-to-exploit-development-on-linux/">Cueing up a calculator: an introduction to exploit development on Linux</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we’re experimenting with LLMs to evolve GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-06-how-were-experimenting-with-llms-to-evolve-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-06-how-were-experimenting-with-llms-to-evolve-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T16:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how we’re experimenting with generative AI models to extend GitHub Copilot across the developer lifecycle.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-06-how-were-experimenting-with-llms-to-evolve-github-copilot/">How we’re experimenting with LLMs to evolve GitHub Copilot</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women in Tech podcast: Transforming tech education]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/women-in-tech-podcast-transforming-tech-education</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/women-in-tech-podcast-transforming-tech-education"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Episode 2 of the HashiCast: Women in Tech podcast features Deborah Carter, a catalyst for change working to reshape technology education while advocating for diversity and inclusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hope and expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46254</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/845072033/0/sethsblog~Hope-and-expectations/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T10:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They’re not the same thing. Hope can fuel us. Hope can be refilled. Hope opens the door to possibility. Expectations, on the other hand, are a trap. They make us brittle and lead to disappointment. When we raise our hopes and lower our expectations, we establish a resilient way forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at EMNLP 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/google-at-emnlp-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/google-at-emnlp-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T01:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Malaya Jules, Program Manager, Google





Google is proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of Empirical Methods in Natural Language Processing (EMNLP 2023), a premier annual conference, which is being held this week in Sentosa, Singapore. Google has a strong presence at this year’s conference with over 65 accepted papers and active involvement in 11 workshops and tutorials. Google is also happy to be a Major Sponsor for the Widening NLP workshop (WiNLP), which aims to highlight global representations of people, perspectives, and cultures in AI and ML. We look forward to sharing some of our extensive NLP research and expanding our partnership with the broader research community.



We hope you’ll visit the Google booth to chat with researchers who are actively pursuing the latest innovati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2023.0.0 (aka Leyton) Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/06/spring-cloud-2023-0-0-aka-leyton-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/06/spring-cloud-2023-0-0-aka-leyton-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Gibb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.21.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/06/spring-tools-4-21-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/06/spring-tools-4-21-0-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lippert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compact Graphs]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2864/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2864/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/compact_graphs.png" title="People may complain about readability, but even with jpeg compression, extracting the data points is usually computationally feasible if there aren't too many of them." alt="People may complain about readability, but even with jpeg compression, extracting the data points is usually computationally feasible if there aren't too many of them." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.11 is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-05-github-enterprise-server-3-11-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-05-github-enterprise-server-3-11-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T23:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Customers using GitHub Enterprise Server can gain more insight and understanding into the security of their code.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-05-github-enterprise-server-3-11-is-now-generally-available/">GitHub Enterprise Server 3.11 is now generally available</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing post-quantum cryptography with CodeQL]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-05-addressing-post-quantum-cryptography-with-codeql/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-05-addressing-post-quantum-cryptography-with-codeql/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T22:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how researchers and security experts at GitHub, Microsoft, and Santander came together to address the challenges presented by the post-quantum cryptography world.  </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-05-addressing-post-quantum-cryptography-with-codeql/">Addressing post-quantum cryptography with CodeQL</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The head of marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47918</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/844165718/0/sethsblog~The-head-of-marketing/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T09:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to be confused about this job, because it’s not one job, it’s at least three. This is why it’s a difficult job to fill, and why turnover is so high–we’re not allocating resources or setting expectations in a way that matches the work to be done. Marketing strategy: This is the work of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 5th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/05/this-week-in-spring-december-5th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/05/this-week-in-spring-december-5th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Elastigrads share the wellness benefits they’re most excited about in their first job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-wellness-benefits</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-wellness-benefits"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We asked new Elasticians and recent grads — who all joined the company through Elastigrad — what benefits and programs they were most excited about when they joined Elastic and which ones they use the most.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Lisa Jones-Huff reveals how she thrives in a startup atmosphere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lisa-jones-huff-thrives-startup-atmosphere</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lisa-jones-huff-thrives-startup-atmosphere"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Lisa Jones-Huff, senior director of global security specialists at Elastic and a startup enthusiast. From her first startup experience in 2003 to leading a growing team of security experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Elastigrads share the wellness benefits they’re most excited about in their first job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-wellness-benefits</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-wellness-benefits"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
One of the best benefits of landing a full-time position, besides the opportunity to grow your career and use your skill set, is the, well, the benefits themselves.
While navigating the ins and outs of programs offered by a company, especially if you’ve never done it before, can be overwhelming, it’s worth the effort to understand what is provided so you can take full advantage.
Elastic® has a variety of programs and resources designed with our Elasticians in mind that stretch beyond the standard health insurance and retirement plans. These programs, encompassed under one umbrella called Be.Well@Elastic, provide support when and where you need it. Plus, they all support our Source Code values.
We asked new Elasticians and recent grads — who all joined the company through Elastigrad — wha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Lisa Jones-Huff reveals how she thrives in a startup atmosphere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lisa-jones-huff-thrives-startup-atmosphere</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lisa-jones-huff-thrives-startup-atmosphere"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Meet Lisa Jones-Huff, the senior director of global security specialists at Elastic and a startup enthusiast. From her first startup experience in 2003 to now leading a growing team of security experts, Lisa thrives on being self-motivated, innovative, and collaborative.
“I prefer not to come into an environment where you're farming the land after someone else has done the work. Part of the energy of a startup is that you get an opportunity to build something. You have an opportunity to see it grow and create processes that have never been in place,” Lisa says. “The thing that gives me energy is creating.”
We caught up with Lisa to hear more about how she thrives in a startup atmosphere, including her top tips for how you can do the same.
Dipping her toes in the startup world
Lisa was ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new quantum algorithm for classical mechanics with an exponential speedup]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/a-new-quantum-algorithm-for-classical.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/a-new-quantum-algorithm-for-classical.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T22:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Robin Kothari and Rolando Somma, Research Scientists, Google Research, Quantum AI Team




Quantum computers promise to solve some problems exponentially faster than classical computers, but there are only a handful of examples with such a dramatic speedup, such as Shor’s factoring algorithm and quantum simulation. Of those few examples, the majority of them involve simulating physical systems that are inherently quantum mechanical — a natural application for quantum computers. But what about simulating systems that are not inherently quantum? Can quantum computers offer an exponential advantage for this?

 

In “Exponential quantum speedup in simulating coupled classical oscillators”, published in Physical Review X (PRX) and presented at the Symposium on Foundations of Computer …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wild Hope Now: The power of books for causes]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47960</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/843944042/0/sethsblog~Wild-Hope-Now-The-power-of-books-for-causes/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T20:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-profits and charities depend on the emotional and financial support of their backers. And that support is always based on a story. A story of possibility, of justice, of community. They serve to right wrongs, to fix problems, to shine a light and to make things better. I’ve discovered that a book is a powerful […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary report optimization in the Privacy Sandbox Attribution Reporting API]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/summary-report-optimization-in-privacy.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/summary-report-optimization-in-privacy.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hidayet Aksu, Software Engineer, and Adam Sealfon, Research Scientist, Google





In recent years, the Privacy Sandbox initiative was launched to explore responsible ways for advertisers to measure the effectiveness of their campaigns, by aiming to deprecate third-party cookies (subject to resolving any competition concerns with the UK’s Competition and Markets Authority). Cookies are small pieces of data containing user preferences that websites store on a user’s device; they can be used to provide a better browsing experience (e.g., allowing users to automatically sign in) and to serve relevant content or ads. The Privacy Sandbox attempts to address concerns around the use of cookies for tracking browsing data across the web by providing a privacy-preserving alternative.



Ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp wins the Palo Alto Networks 2023 Global Technology Partner of the Year award]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-the-palo-alto-networks-2023-global-technology-partner-of-the-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-the-palo-alto-networks-2023-global-technology-partner-of-the-year"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp and Palo Alto Networks celebrate our ongoing partnership protecting customers with infrastructure security automation for the second year in a row.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ultimate gifts for the developer in your life this holiday season]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-04-the-ultimate-gifts-for-the-developer-in-your-life-this-holiday-season/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-04-the-ultimate-gifts-for-the-developer-in-your-life-this-holiday-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T16:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If you're on the hunt for the perfect holiday gifts for the developer who has it all, look no further. We’ve curated a list of 10 must-have items (plus a few more) that strike the perfect balance between practicality and style.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-04-the-ultimate-gifts-for-the-developer-in-your-life-this-holiday-season/">The ultimate gifts for the developer in your life this holiday season</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The sixty-day staircase]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46240</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/843839549/0/sethsblog~The-sixtyday-staircase/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T09:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the moment, it’s really difficult. l’esprit de l’escalier means, “the spirit of the staircase.” That thing you wished you had a said just a moment ago, the bon mot or the clever riposte. It only comes to us as we’re walking away. But this sort of quick comment is good for the movies, not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDS with Spring Framework 6.1]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/04/cds-with-spring-framework-6-1</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/04/cds-with-spring-framework-6-1"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Deleuze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From trial to production: 5 key components of an optimal Elastic Cloud production deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-key-components-optimal-elastic-cloud-production-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-key-components-optimal-elastic-cloud-production-deployment"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ready to move beyond your Elastic Cloud trial and set yourself up for success in your Elastic Cloud journey? Learn the important factors to consider as you begin building out your production deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemendra Singh Lodhi,Tamara Rosini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From trial to production: 5 key components of an optimal Elastic Cloud production deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-key-components-optimal-elastic-cloud-production-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-key-components-optimal-elastic-cloud-production-deployment"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In our previous blog, How to get the most from your Elastic Cloud Trial, we showed how customers can benefit from using Elastic® Cloud trials and available resources to test and implement business use cases.

In this blog, we will discuss the critical factors that govern success in Elastic Cloud production deployment. After successful testing, customers should consider these factors to reliably launch an efficient and performant production deployment.
Next steps: Moving beyond the trial,
After successful completion of testing or proof of concept, customers can move on to the next phase, which is getting ready for production launch. There are a number of things to consider to ensure ongoing success in the Elastic Cloud journey.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemendra Singh Lodhi,Tamara Rosini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Typography]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2863/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2863/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/space_typography.png" title="And over heeee[...]eeeere (i)s Saturn." alt="And over heeee[...]eeeere (i)s Saturn." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[True/useful]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47924</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/843666284/0/sethsblog~Trueuseful/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a simple grid that might change the way you think about internal stories: When we believe in something that’s useful but not true, it can serve a helpful purpose. The tooth fairy, perhaps. When we act on something that’s useful and also true, we’ve found a resilient path forward. That’s because the truth doesn’t […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When was the last time you used a compass?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46220</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/843556193/0/sethsblog~When-was-the-last-time-you-used-a-compass/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-02T10:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How about an astrolabe? Or even a watch? Technology advances, and sooner or later, the old stuff gets left behind. It’s easy to romanticize some of the classic devices that we built civilization on, and it’s worth remembering that the tech we’re wrestling with now will soon be faded away, with some folks nostalgic for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsupervised speech-to-speech translation from monolingual data]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/unsupervised-speech-to-speech.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/unsupervised-speech-to-speech.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eliya Nachmani, Research Scientist, and Michelle Tadmor Ramanovich, Software Engineer, Google Research






Speech-to-speech translation (S2ST) is a type of machine translation that converts spoken language from one language to another. This technology has the potential to break down language barriers and facilitate communication between people from different cultures and backgrounds. 




Previously, we introduced Translatotron 1 and Translatotron 2, the first ever models that were able to directly translate speech between two languages. However they were trained in supervised settings with parallel speech data. The scarcity of parallel speech data is a major challenge in this field, so much that most public datasets are semi- or fully-synthesized from text. This adds additiona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Work Items in Visual Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68130</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/work-items-in-visual-studio/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T14:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several years ago, with the introduction of Visual Studio 2019, we launched a completely revamped work item experience. This updated view operates entirely on REST, replacing the deprecated SOAP APIs utilized in the legacy version. Although Visual Studio 2022 still includes the option to revert to the legacy view,
The post Work Items in Visual Studio appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the committee decides]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46212</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/843346175/0/sethsblog~When-the-committee-decides/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T09:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They’re almost always conservative. Whether it’s a governmental body, the strategy group at a big company or the membership panel at the local country club, we can learn a lot by seeing what they approve and when they stall. Of course, each of us know a lot about our offering, the change we seek to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of generative AI in public sector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-future-of-generative-ai-in-public-sector</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-future-of-generative-ai-in-public-sector"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts from IDC and Elastic weigh in on how government and education organizations are approaching early generative AI use cases, the roadmap for future generative AI implementation, and how to address concerns around privacy and security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Erickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of generative AI in public sector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-future-of-generative-ai-in-public-sector</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-future-of-generative-ai-in-public-sector"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Recently, I sat down with Adelaide O’Brien, research vice president at IDC Government Insights, to discuss the current and future state of generative AI in the public sector worldwide. The full conversation is available to view on demand, but I also wanted to highlight some of the takeaways from the discussion. Our goal was to discuss use cases we’re seeing right now, what roadblocks public organizations are facing, and trade best practices on how organizations can harness the value of generative AI for employees, constituents, and larger digital transformation. 
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltdb1caed2d9a65e10/656a038e7539113410d0751e/RAG.png,RAG.pngHow RAG with Elastic can benefit public sector,

Grounded on facts: Use synced data in Elastic for accurate,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Erickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typical Seating Chart]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2862/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2862/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/typical_seating_chart.png" title="Now that airlines have started adding wheel locks to their drink carts, less than half of flights have one accidentally fall out through the hole." alt="Now that airlines have started adding wheel locks to their drink carts, less than half of flights have one accidentally fall out through the hole." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use AWS Fault Injection Service to demonstrate multi-region and multi-AZ application resilience]]></title>
        <id>b5f470ba74c346ed6f525a2a5e92522dc46cd4d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-aws-fault-injection-service-to-demonstrate-multi-region-and-multi-az-application-resilience/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Fault Injection Service (FIS) helps you to put chaos engineering into practice at scale. Today we are launching new scenarios that will let you demonstrate that your applications perform as intended if an AWS Availability Zone experiences a full power interruption or connectivity from one AWS region to another is lost. You can use […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zonal autoshift – Automatically shift your traffic away from Availability Zones when we detect potential issues]]></title>
        <id>f677c6705f71814fd999f39b325af14c6e9289e9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/zonal-autoshift-automatically-shift-your-traffic-away-from-availability-zones-when-we-detect-potential-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re launching zonal autoshift, a new capability of Amazon Route 53 Application Recovery Controller that you can enable to automatically and safely shift your workload’s traffic away from an Availability Zone when AWS identifies a potential failure affecting that Availability Zone and shift it back once the failure is resolved. When deploying resilient applications, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IDE extension for AWS Application Composer enhances visual modern applications development with AI-generated IaC]]></title>
        <id>66dd6400ac1e7d9ba598572e5cd829f82e8b6c05</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/ide-extension-for-aws-application-composer-enhances-visual-modern-applications-development-with-ai-generated-iac/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to share the integrated development environment (IDE) extension for AWS Application Composer. Now you can use AWS Application Composer directly in your IDE to visually build modern applications and iteratively develop your infrastructure as code templates with Amazon CodeWhisperer. Announced as preview at AWS re:Invent 2022 and generally available in March 2023, Application Composer is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Studio adds web-based interface, Code Editor, flexible workspaces, and streamlines user onboarding]]></title>
        <id>8202e0701d0edec7189fd74a2684035983c2a23f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-studio-adds-web-based-interface-code-editor-flexible-workspaces-and-streamlines-user-onboarding/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing an improved Amazon SageMaker Studio experience! The new SageMaker Studio web-based interface loads faster and provides consistent access to your preferred integrated development environment (IDE) and SageMaker resources and tooling, irrespective of your IDE choice. In addition to JupyterLab and RStudio, SageMaker Studio now includes a fully managed Code Editor based […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three new capabilities for Amazon Inspector broaden the realm of vulnerability scanning for workloads]]></title>
        <id>dbd84d0e15dc49a513d11dc8814a2ace24c64aef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/three-new-capabilities-for-amazon-inspector-broaden-the-realm-of-vulnerability-scanning-for-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon Inspector adds three new capabilities to increase the realm of possibilities when scanning your workloads for software vulnerabilities: Amazon Inspector introduces a new set of open source plugins and an API allowing you to assess your container images for software vulnerabilities at build time directly from your continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insider newsletter digest: How to use GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-30-from-the-pages-of-our-insider-newsletter-how-to-use-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-30-from-the-pages-of-our-insider-newsletter-how-to-use-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore the July edition, featuring prompts, tips, and use cases for GitHub Copilot.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-30-from-the-pages-of-our-insider-newsletter-how-to-use-github-copilot/">Insider newsletter digest: How to use GitHub Copilot</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudWatch Application Signals for automatic instrumentation of your applications (preview)]]></title>
        <id>1d6092ef569153d497e5ee163eee98821d30bf12</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-cloudwatch-application-signals-for-automatic-instrumentation-of-your-applications-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the challenges with distributed systems is that they are made up of many interdependent services, which add a degree of complexity when you are trying to monitor their performance. Determining which services and APIs are experiencing high latencies or degraded availability requires manually putting together telemetry signals. This can result in time and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New myApplications in the AWS Management Console simplifies managing your application resources]]></title>
        <id>ec4fc257d1c6efc31dbdad1cfa3fa78ebe223b5a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-myapplications-in-the-aws-management-console-simplifies-managing-your-application-resources/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the general availability of myApplications supporting application operations, a new set of capabilities that help you get started with your applications on AWS, operate them with less effort, and move faster at scale. With myApplication in the AWS Management Console, you can more easily manage and monitor the cost, health, security […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing our home labs: Home Assistant code review]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-30-securing-our-home-labs-home-assistant-code-review/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-30-securing-our-home-labs-home-assistant-code-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T13:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The GitHub Security Lab examined the most popular open source software running on our home labs, with the aim of enhancing its security. Here's what we found and what you can do to better protect your own smart home.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-30-securing-our-home-labs-home-assistant-code-review/">Securing our home labs: Home Assistant code review</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The thing about Hobson]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42495</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/843081119/0/sethsblog~The-thing-about-Hobson/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People talk about Hobson’s choice as if it’s always a bad thing. A liveryman in pre-industrial London, he rented horses. And every customer was allowed to take the horse closest to the door. Hobson’s choice is no choice at all. Of course, this system meant that the horses were rotated, and the fanciest ones weren’t […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily deploy SaaS products with new Quick Launch in AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>165f32cc180f9fa0cf1f36aff4e46a246fa890b6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/easily-deploy-saas-products-with-new-quick-launch-in-aws-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are excited to announce the general availability of SaaS Quick Launch, a new feature in AWS Marketplace that makes it easy and secure to deploy SaaS products. Before SaaS Quick Launch, configuring and launching third-party SaaS products could be time-consuming and costly, especially in certain categories like security and monitoring. Some products require […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Security legend Laura Spilca joins us to talk Spring Authorization Server and upgrading to Spring Boot 3]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-legend-laura-spilca-joins-us-to-talk</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-legend-laura-spilca-joins-us-to-talk"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paving the way for modern search workflows and generative AI apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-search-workflows-generative-ai-apps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-search-workflows-generative-ai-apps"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic is the best developer platform for building AI search and generative AI apps with expanded ecosystem partners, full document vector search, a proprietary ML model for semantic search now in GA, and a simple API-first developer experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Riley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paving the way for modern search workflows and generative AI apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-search-workflows-generative-ai-apps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-search-workflows-generative-ai-apps"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In this blog, we want to share the investments that Elastic® is making to simplify your experience as you build AI applications. We know that developers have to stay nimble in today’s fast-evolving AI environment. Yet, common challenges make building generative AI applications needlessly rigid and complicated. To name just a few:


Vectors — from how many to which ones you can use and how to chunk large passages of text

Evaluating, swapping, and managing large language models (LLMs)

Setting up effective semantic search (particularly if your development team has limited resources or skill gaps) 

Leveraging existing investments and current architectures while balancing tech debt

Scaling from proof-of-concept to production 

Making sure that end-user applications are fast and cost-effec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Riley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All of Netflix’s HDR video streaming is now dynamically optimized]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e9e0cb15f2ba</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/all-of-netflixs-hdr-video-streaming-is-now-dynamically-optimized-e9e0cb15f2ba?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by  Aditya Mavlankar, Zhi Li, Lukáš Krasula and Christos Bampis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Package and deploy models faster with new tools and guided workflows in Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>9dfa4013fdeb3ce3b8c9cd5ded8657c6f07139cc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/package-and-deploy-models-faster-with-new-tools-and-guided-workflows-in-amazon-sagemaker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that Amazon SageMaker now comes with an improved model deployment experience to help you deploy traditional machine learning (ML) models and foundation models (FMs) faster. As a data scientist or ML practitioner, you can now use the new ModelBuilder class in the SageMaker Python SDK to package models, perform local inference […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use natural language to explore and prepare data with a new capability of Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>52022c89be15e7efe7a0e5d886a1b76e6bb36028</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-natural-language-to-explore-and-prepare-data-with-a-new-capability-of-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to introduce the ability to use natural language instructions in Amazon SageMaker Canvas to explore, visualize, and transform data for machine learning (ML). SageMaker Canvas now supports using foundation model-(FM) powered natural language instructions to complement its comprehensive data preparation capabilities for data exploration, analysis, visualization, and transformation. Using natural language instructions, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker adds new inference capabilities to help reduce foundation model deployment costs and latency]]></title>
        <id>070abf1c19c0afcc710d7953b53d84a40e4e4b82</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-adds-new-inference-capabilities-to-help-reduce-foundation-model-deployment-costs-and-latency/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing new Amazon SageMaker inference capabilities that can help you optimize deployment costs and reduce latency. With the new inference capabilities, you can deploy one or more foundation models (FMs) on the same SageMaker endpoint and control how many accelerators and how much memory is reserved for each FM. This helps to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage foundation models for business analysis at scale with Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>286f7dd53aa2b49a2bbca8dcddcd42842c920920</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/leverage-foundation-models-for-business-analysis-at-scale-with-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m excited to introduce a new capability in Amazon SageMaker Canvas to use foundation models (FMs) from Amazon Bedrock and Amazon SageMaker Jumpstart through a no-code experience. This new capability makes it easier for you to evaluate and generate responses from FMs for your specific use case with high accuracy. Every business has its […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing highly durable Amazon OpenSearch Service clusters with 30% price/performance improvement]]></title>
        <id>9254592bff3a8ff942fbbd9434437e0a80455403</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-highly-durable-amazon-opensearch-service-clusters-with-30-price-performance-improvement/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the new OR1 instances to create Amazon OpenSearch Service clusters that use Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) for primary storage. You can ingest, store, index, and access just about any imaginable amount of data, while also enjoying a 30% price/performance improvement over existing instance types, eleven nines of data durability, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Clarify makes it easier to evaluate and select foundation models (preview)]]></title>
        <id>8eb45aec03e2c9174185648ea2e15d148920732c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-clarify-makes-it-easier-to-evaluate-and-select-foundation-models-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that Amazon SageMaker Clarify now supports foundation model (FM) evaluation (preview). As a data scientist or machine learning (ML) engineer, you can now use SageMaker Clarify to evaluate, compare, and select FMs in minutes based on metrics such as accuracy, robustness, creativity, factual knowledge, bias, and toxicity. This new capability adds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluate, compare, and select the best foundation models for your use case in Amazon Bedrock (preview)]]></title>
        <id>d609890b177381df2b101da3ee61fcba234993e4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/evaluate-compare-and-select-the-best-foundation-models-for-your-use-case-in-amazon-bedrock-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that you can now evaluate, compare, and select the best foundation models (FMs) for your use case in Amazon Bedrock. Model Evaluation on Amazon Bedrock is available today in preview. Amazon Bedrock offers a choice of automatic evaluation and human evaluation. You can use automatic evaluation with predefined metrics such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift adds new AI capabilities, including Amazon Q, to boost efficiency and productivity]]></title>
        <id>d33d7b803e5c2060a28968285e9fa1f2403b84ce</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-redshift-adds-new-ai-capabilities-to-boost-efficiency-and-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift puts artificial intelligence (AI) at your service to optimize efficiencies and make you more productive with two new capabilities that we are launching in preview today. First, Amazon Redshift Serverless becomes smarter. It scales capacity proactively and automatically along dimensions such as the complexity of your queries, their frequency, the size of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Clean Rooms Differential Privacy enhances privacy protection of your users’ data (preview)]]></title>
        <id>046eaa3e0b7d8591180c049c34b977499c294c70</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-clean-rooms-differential-privacy-enhances-privacy-protection-of-your-users-data-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can use AWS Clean Rooms Diﬀerential Privacy (preview) to help protect the privacy of your users with mathematically backed and intuitive controls in a few steps. As a fully managed capability of AWS Clean Rooms, no prior differential privacy experience is needed to help you prevent the reidentification of your users. AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Clean Rooms ML helps customers and partners apply ML models without sharing raw data (preview)]]></title>
        <id>30344b64e2852c44c41aaa3fee6ef1070e91cf3a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-clean-rooms-ml-helps-customers-and-partners-apply-ml-models-without-sharing-raw-data-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re introducing AWS Clean Rooms ML (preview), a new capability of AWS Clean Rooms that helps you and your partners apply machine learning (ML) models on your collective data without copying or sharing raw data with each other. With this new capability, you can generate predictive insights using ML models while continuing to protect your sensitive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon OpenSearch Service zero-ETL integration with Amazon S3 (preview)]]></title>
        <id>eda84244f81c1f8800d261452c3a2b4a004d3ae9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-opensearch-service-zero-etl-integration-with-amazon-s3-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing a preview of Amazon OpenSearch Service zero-ETL integration with Amazon S3, a new way to query operational logs in Amazon S3 and S3-based data lakes without needing to switch between services. You can now analyze infrequently queried data in cloud object stores and simultaneously use the operational analytics and visualization capabilities […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyze large amounts of graph data to get insights and find trends with Amazon Neptune Analytics]]></title>
        <id>d94eeba2eb21724f0c373832cdac1c7163b8aa8d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-neptune-analytics-a-high-performance-graph-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am happy to announce the general availability of Amazon Neptune Analytics, a new analytics database engine that makes it faster for data scientists and application developers to quickly analyze large amounts of graph data. With Neptune Analytics, you can now quickly load your dataset from Amazon Neptune or your data lake on Amazon Simple […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your Terraform development with Amazon CodeWhisperer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerate-your-terraform-development-with-amazon-codewhisperer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerate-your-terraform-development-with-amazon-codewhisperer"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improve the developer experience writing Terraform code with the help of generative AI powered by Amazon CodeWhisperer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第242話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755511181824</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755511181824"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform delivers launch-day support for Amazon S3 Express]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-delivers-launch-day-support-for-amazon-s3-express</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-delivers-launch-day-support-for-amazon-s3-express"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s Terraform provider for AWS now enables users to manage their S3 Express buckets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updated: Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68117</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-1-rtw-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[12/5 Update: There is a known issue where the Agent version does not update after upgrading to Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 and using Update Agent in Agent Pool configuration. We are currently working on a patch to resolve this issue and will share updates in the Developer Community as we make progress.
The post Updated: Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: New Experimental Features in Gateway API v1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/28/gateway-api-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/28/gateway-api-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Candace Holman (Red Hat), Dave Protasowski (VMware), Gaurav K Ghildiyal (Google), John Howard (Google), Simone Rodigari (IBM)
Recently, the Gateway API announced its v1.0 GA release, marking a huge milestone for the project.
Along with stabilizing some of the core functionality in the API, a number of exciting new experimental features have been added.
Backend TLS Policy
BackendTLSPolicy is a new Gateway API type used for specifying the TLS configuration of the connection from the Gateway to backend Pods via the Service API object.
It is specified as a Direct PolicyAttachment without defaults or overrides, applied to a Service that accesses a backend, where the BackendTLSPolicy resides in the same namespace as the Service to which it is applied.
All Gateway API Routes that point t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform extension for VS Code adds Terraform Cloud view]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-extension-for-vs-code-adds-terraform-cloud-view</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-extension-for-vs-code-adds-terraform-cloud-view"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new view in the HashiCorp Terraform extension for Visual Studio Code shows your Terraform Cloud workspaces and runs, reducing context-switching.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at re:Invent 2023: A year of collaboration with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-re-invent-2023-a-year-of-collaboration-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-re-invent-2023-a-year-of-collaboration-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recap of HashiCorp infrastructure and security news and developments on AWS from the past year, from self-service provisioning to fighting secrets sprawl and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault benchmark testing tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-benchmark-testing-tool</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-benchmark-testing-tool"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault benchmark is an open source tool that tests the performance of HashiCorp Vault auth methods and secrets engines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - 28 November, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/this-week-in-spring-28-november-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/this-week-in-spring-28-november-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.15, 3.0.10, 3.1.6 and 3.2.0-RC1 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/spring-shell-2-1-15-3-0-10-3-1-6-and-3-2-0-rc1-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/spring-shell-2-1-15-3-0-10-3-1-6-and-3-2-0-rc1-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step guide to creating custom ES Rally tracks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ES Rally is a benchmarking tool for Elasticsearch, enabling performance testing and decision-making through custom data tracks and comparative analysis. This comprehensive guide will show you the steps to take to craft personalized ES Rally tracks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alejandro Sánchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step guide to creating custom ES Rally tracks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is ES Rally, and what is it for?,
ES Rally is a tool for testing performance on Elasticsearch® that allows you to run and record comparative tests.

Decision-making can be difficult, especially when you don't have the information you need and only have guesses or experience from past changes that have been positive or negative.

If we add to this that the data world must be flexible, as it evolves rapidly and therefore our Elasticsearch must adapt to it, this tool will help us to be able to measure all the changes and evolutions that we make over time and evaluate their impact. And most importantly, we can then obtain the information needed to make the right decisions.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt1d9db82a7e208b53/6566052e3994175cc8b4981b/1-elastic-bl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alejandro Sánchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Original Research: MIT CODE 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9340b879176a</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/netflix-original-research-mit-code-2023-9340b879176a?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix was thrilled to be the premier sponsor for the 2nd year in a row at the 2023 Conference on Digital Experimentation (CODE@MIT).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gain operator confidence with HCP Consul Central observability features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/gain-operator-confidence-with-hcp-consul-central-observability-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/gain-operator-confidence-with-hcp-consul-central-observability-features"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul Central’s new observability features were recently used by a customer to help troubleshoot an issue with assistance from HashiCorp engineers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform stacks, explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-stacks-explained</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-stacks-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform stacks simplify provisioning and managing resources at scale, reducing the time and overhead of managing infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing resources with the Terraform AWS Cloud Control provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Cloud Control provider — built around the AWS Cloud Control API — is designed to bring new services to HashiCorp Terraform faster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-34053, CVE-2023-34055: Spring Framework and Spring Boot vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/27/cve-2023-34053-cve-2023-34055-spring-framework-and-spring-boot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/27/cve-2023-34053-cve-2023-34055-spring-framework-and-spring-boot"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Causal Machine Learning for Creative Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4b0ce22a8a96</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/causal-machine-learning-for-creative-insights-4b0ce22a8a96?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T01:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A framework to identify the causal impact of successful visual components.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.1 GA and 1.0.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/24/spring-modulith-1-1-ga-and-1-0-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/24/spring-modulith-1-1-ga-and-1-0-3-released"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/24/sig-testing-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/24/sig-testing-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sandipan Panda
Welcome to another edition of the SIG spotlight blog series, where we
highlight the incredible work being done by various Special Interest
Groups (SIGs) within the Kubernetes project. In this edition, we turn
our attention to SIG Testing,
a group interested in effective testing of Kubernetes and automating
away project toil. SIG Testing focus on creating and running tools and
infrastructure that make it easier for the community to write and run
tests, and to contribute, analyze and act upon test results.
To gain some insights into SIG Testing, Sandipan
Panda spoke with Michelle Shepardson,
a senior software engineer at Google and a chair of SIG Testing, and
Patrick Ohly, a software engineer and architect at
Intel and a SIG Testing Tech Lead.
Meet the contributors
San…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closing the skills and talent divide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/closing-the-skills-and-talent-divide</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/closing-the-skills-and-talent-divide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the HashiCast: Navigating the Cloud for C-Suites podcast addresses how to close the skills gap. Guest James Footman, Head of Talent for EMEA at HashiCorp, highlights the key takeaways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving simulations of clouds and their effects on climate]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/improving-simulations-of-clouds-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/improving-simulations-of-clouds-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tapio Schneider, Visiting Researcher, and Yi-fan Chen, Engineering Lead, Google Research




Today’s climate models successfully capture broad global warming trends. However, because of uncertainties about processes that are small in scale yet globally important, such as clouds and ocean turbulence, these models’ predictions of upcoming climate changes are not very accurate in detail. For example, predictions of the time by which the global mean surface temperature of Earth will have warmed 2℃, relative to preindustrial times, vary by 40–50 years (a full human generation) among today’s models. As a result, we do not have the accurate and geographically granular predictions we need to plan resilient infrastructure, adapt supply chains to climate disruption, and assess the risks of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability monitors metrics for Google Cloud in just minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow this step-by-step process to enable Elastic Observability for Google Cloud Platform metrics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon,Eric Lowry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability monitors metrics for Google Cloud in just minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Developers and SREs choose to host their applications on Google Cloud Platform (GCP) for its reliability, speed, and ease of use. On Google Cloud, development teams are finding additional value in migrating to Kubernetes on GKE, leveraging the latest serverless options like Cloud Run, and improving traditional, tiered applications with managed services.
Elastic Observability offers 16 out-of-the-box integrations for Google Cloud services with more on the way. A full list of Google Cloud integrations can be found in our online documentation.
In addition to our native Google Cloud integrations, Elastic Observability aggregates not only logs but also metrics for Google Cloud services and the applications running on Google Cloud compute services (Compute Engine, Cloud Run, Cloud Functions, K…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon,Eric Lowry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open sourcing Project Guideline: A platform for computer vision accessibility technology]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/open-sourcing-project-guideline.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/open-sourcing-project-guideline.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dave Hawkey, Software Engineer, Google Research




Two years ago we announced Project Guideline, a collaboration between Google Research and Guiding Eyes for the Blind that enabled people with visual impairments (e.g., blindness and low-vision) to walk, jog, and run independently. Using only a Google Pixel phone and headphones, Project Guideline leverages on-device machine learning (ML) to navigate users along outdoor paths marked with a painted line. The technology has been tested all over the world and even demonstrated during the opening ceremony at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games.



Since the original announcement, we set out to improve Project Guideline by embedding new features, such as obstacle detection and advanced path planning, to safely and reliably navigate users t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at AWS re:Invent: Your blueprint for cloud success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-your-blueprint-for-cloud-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-your-blueprint-for-cloud-success"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re attending AWS re:Invent in Las Vegas, Nov. 27 - Dec. 1, visit us for breakout sessions, expert talks, and product demos to learn how to accelerate your adoption of a cloud operating model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Fall Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68016</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-fall-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T16:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have been following these posts, then you are more than familiar with our New Boards Hub initiative. We have been doing our best to keep our community informed of the new features and our rollout plans. Now is a good time to provide an update on where things are at with a couple of our new preview features,
The post New Boards Hub, Fall Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Processing using Netflix Maestro and Apache Iceberg]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b8ba072ddeeb</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/incremental-processing-using-netflix-maestro-and-apache-iceberg-b8ba072ddeeb?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T05:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Jun He, Yingyi Zhang, and Pawan Dixit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C-suite insights on the transformative power of generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore insights from top IT leaders on leveraging generative AI for enhancing operational resilience, mitigating security risk, and creating exceptional customer experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Klinger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C-suite insights on the transformative power of generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Generative AI is revolutionizing the way businesses operate, from improving operational resilience to mitigating security risks and enhancing customer experiences. In a recent roundup of c-suite insights from three IT leaders — Matt Minetola, CIO, Mandy Andress, CISO, and Rick Laner, chief customer officer — we gain a comprehensive understanding of how generative AI is being used to improve business outcomes across organizations.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt3135954a466f9c02/655d0750107d423a15b7b191/1-elastic-blog-matt-minetola.png,1-elastic-blog-matt-minetola.png,
Matt Minetola, CIO at Elastic, highlights the use of generative AI in improving operational resilience. He points out that organizations already possess a wealth of telemetry data, which is cr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Klinger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault integrations with Intel, Pure Storage, Red Hat, and more continue to strengthen customer security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-intel-pure-storage-red-hat-and-more-continue-to-strengthe</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-intel-pure-storage-red-hat-and-more-continue-to-strengthe"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10 new HashiCorp Vault ecosystem integrations extend security use cases for customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging practices for Society-Centered AI]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/emerging-practices-for-society-centered.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/emerging-practices-for-society-centered.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Anoop Sinha, Research Director, Technology & Society, and Yossi Matias, Vice President, Google Research




The first of Google’s AI Principles is to “Be socially beneficial.” As AI practitioners, we’re inspired by the transformative potential of AI technologies to benefit society and our shared environment at a scale and swiftness that wasn’t possible before. From helping address the climate crisis to helping transform healthcare, to making the digital world more accessible, our goal is to apply AI responsibly to be helpful to more people around the globe. Achieving global scale requires researchers and communities to think ahead — and act — collectively across the AI ecosystem.



We call this approach Society-Centered AI. It is both an extension and an expansion of Human-Cente…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps’ First Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68002</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-first-consensus-assessment-initiative-questionnaire-caiq-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am thrilled to announce that we have now published, for the first time, a Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) specific to Azure DevOps. The Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) is a tool developed by the Cloud Security Alliance (CSA). It serves as a standard set of questions aimed at helping potential cloud customers evaluate the security capabilities of cloud service providers.
The post Azure DevOps’ First Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) Now Available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benibo Ajumogobia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Adversarial testing for generative AI safety]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research_16.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research_16.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kathy Meier-Hellstern, Building Responsible AI & Data Systems, Director, Google Research




The Responsible AI and Human-Centered Technology (RAI-HCT) team within Google Research is committed to advancing the theory and practice of responsible human-centered AI through a lens of culturally-aware research, to meet the needs of billions of users today, and blaze the path forward for a better AI future. The BRAIDS (Building Responsible AI Data and Solutions) team within RAI-HCT aims to simplify the adoption of RAI practices through the utilization of scalable tools, high-quality data, streamlined processes, and novel research with a current emphasis on addressing the unique challenges posed by generative AI (GenAI).





GenAI models have enabled unprecedented capabilities leading …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Removals, Deprecations, and Major Changes in Kubernetes 1.29]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/kubernetes-1-29-upcoming-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/kubernetes-1-29-upcoming-changes/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Carol Valencia, Kristin Martin, Abigail McCarthy, James Quigley, Hosam Kamel
As with every release, Kubernetes v1.29 will introduce feature deprecations and removals. Our continued ability to produce high-quality releases is a testament to our robust development cycle and healthy community. The following are some of the deprecations and removals coming in the Kubernetes 1.29 release.
The Kubernetes API removal and deprecation process
The Kubernetes project has a well-documented deprecation policy for features. This policy states that stable APIs may only be deprecated when a newer, stable version of that same API is available and that APIs have a minimum lifetime for each stability level. A deprecated API is one that has been marked for removal in a future Kubernetes release; it w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: The Case for Kubernetes Resource Limits: Predictability vs. Efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/the-case-for-kubernetes-resource-limits/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/the-case-for-kubernetes-resource-limits/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Milan Plžík (Grafana Labs)
There’s been quite a lot of posts suggesting that not using Kubernetes resource limits might be a fairly useful thing (for example, For the Love of God, Stop Using CPU Limits on Kubernetes or Kubernetes: Make your services faster by removing CPU limits ). The points made there are totally valid – it doesn’t make much sense to pay for compute power that will not be used due to limits, nor to artificially increase latency. This post strives to argue that limits have their legitimate use as well.
As a Site Reliability Engineer on the Grafana Labs platform team, which maintains and improves internal infrastructure and tooling used by the product teams, I primarily try to make Kubernetes upgrades as smooth as possible. But I also spend a lot of time going down…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solutions to secret sprawl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/solutions-to-secret-sprawl</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/solutions-to-secret-sprawl"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret sprawl makes companies more vulnerable to data breaches. Learn how to locate and centralize secrets in a single location for greater security and simplified management and compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第241話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755451951724</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755451951724"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agentless configuration drift detection and remediation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/agentless-configuration-drift-detection-and-remediation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/agentless-configuration-drift-detection-and-remediation"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over time, application owners find themselves compelled to continuously refine their applications and the underlying infrastructure to enhance the products they deliver, whether to internal or external customers. These modifications inevitably lead to changes in the configuration of both applications and infrastructure. While some of these changes may be benign, others can unintentionally steer the systems away from their securely configured state, a phenomenon commonly referred to as "configuration drift." Left unaddressed, the extent of this drift can introduce substantial risks to the organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bforrest@redhat.com (Ben Forrester)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Psyberg: Automated end to end catch up]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/260fbe366fe2</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/3-psyberg-automated-end-to-end-catch-up-260fbe366fe2?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T03:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Abhinaya Shetty, Bharath Mummadisetty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving Deeper into Psyberg: Stateless vs Stateful Data Processing]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1d273b3aaefb</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/2-diving-deeper-into-psyberg-stateless-vs-stateful-data-processing-1d273b3aaefb?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T03:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Abhinaya Shetty, Bharath Mummadisetty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1. Streamlining Membership Data Engineering at Netflix with Psyberg]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f68830617dd1</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/1-streamlining-membership-data-engineering-at-netflix-with-psyberg-f68830617dd1?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T03:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Abhinaya Shetty, Bharath Mummadisetty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling multimodal understanding to long videos]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/scaling-multimodal-understanding-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/scaling-multimodal-understanding-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T20:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Isaac Noble, Software Engineer, Google Research, and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientist, Google DeepMind 





When building machine learning models for real-life applications, we need to consider inputs from multiple modalities in order to capture various aspects of the world around us. For example, audio, video, and text all provide varied and complementary information about a visual input. However, building multimodal models is challenging due to the heterogeneity of the modalities. Some of the modalities might be well synchronized in time (e.g., audio, video) but not aligned with text. Furthermore, the large volume of data in video and audio signals is much larger than that in text, so when combining them in multimodal models, video and audio often cannot be fully consumed a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[November patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67953</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/november-patches-for-azure-devops-server-and-team-foundation-server/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T18:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server, as well as Team Foundation Server 2018.3.2.
Note: If you have Azure DevOps Server 2022, you should first update to Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 and then install Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 Patch 5.
The post November patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Speech and Music in Audio Content]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/afd64e6a5bf8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/detecting-speech-and-music-in-audio-content-afd64e6a5bf8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T01:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iroro Orife, Chih-Wei Wu and Yun-Ning (Amy) Hung]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform integrations with Dell, DNSimple, Fortinet, Palo Alto Networks, Juniper Networks, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-dell-dnsimple-fortinet-palo-alto-networks-juniper</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-dell-dnsimple-fortinet-palo-alto-networks-juniper"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[18 new Terraform integration partners provide more options to automate and secure cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling large-scale health studies for the research community]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/enabling-large-scale-health-studies-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/enabling-large-scale-health-studies-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Chintan Ghate, Software Engineer, and Diana Mincu, Research Engineer, Google Research




As consumer technologies like fitness trackers and mobile phones become more widely used for health-related data collection, so does the opportunity to leverage these data pathways to study and advance our understanding of medical conditions. We have previously touched upon how our work explores the use of this technology within the context of chronic diseases, in particular multiple sclerosis (MS). This effort leverages the FDA MyStudies platform, an open-source platform used to create clinical study apps, that makes it easier for anyone to run their own studies and collect good quality healthcare data, in a trusted and safe way.


 


Today, we describe the setup that we developed by expan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks 2024: 24-hours of virtual knowledge sharing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2024-24-hours-of-virtual-knowledge-sharing</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2024-24-hours-of-virtual-knowledge-sharing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks returns on February 15, 2024. Join our global community for 24 hours of knowledge sharing. The call for proposals is open through November 30, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Context in AI Research (CAIR)]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T22:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Katherine Heller, Research Scientist, Google Research, on behalf of the CAIR Team




Artificial intelligence (AI) and related machine learning (ML) technologies are increasingly influential in the world around us, making it imperative that we consider the potential impacts on society and individuals in all aspects of the technology that we create. To these ends, the Context in AI Research (CAIR) team develops novel AI methods in the context of the entire AI pipeline: from data to end-user feedback. The pipeline for building an AI system typically starts with data collection, followed by designing a model to run on that data, deployment of the model in the real world, and lastly, compiling and incorporation of human feedback. Originating in the health space, and now expanded to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming leakage on error-corrected quantum processors]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/overcoming-leakage-on-error-corrected.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/overcoming-leakage-on-error-corrected.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:20:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kevin Miao and Matt McEwen, Research Scientists, Quantum AI Team




The qubits that make up Google quantum devices are delicate and noisy, so it’s necessary to incorporate error correction procedures that identify and account for qubit errors on the way to building a useful quantum computer. Two of the most prevalent error mechanisms are bit-flip errors (where the energy state of the qubit changes) and phase-flip errors (where the phase of the encoded quantum information changes). Quantum error correction (QEC) promises to address and mitigate these two prominent errors. However, there is an assortment of other error mechanisms that challenges the effectiveness of QEC.



While we want qubits to behave as ideal two-level systems with no loss mechanisms, this is not the case in r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Kubernetes ingress with HashiCorp Boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/secure-kubernetes-ingress-with-hashicorp-boundary</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/secure-kubernetes-ingress-with-hashicorp-boundary"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See a potential method for securing application content and components hosted within Kubernetes using Boundary as an alternative to ingress controllers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>