<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-11T01:08:52.027Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-11T01:08:52.027Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital shortcuts and cognitive load]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45507</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/792939341/0/sethsblog~Digital-shortcuts-and-cognitive-load/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to drive 200 miles to Boston once a week or so. After a few trips on the highway, my subconscious figured out that getting behind a few trucks for the entire ride enabled me to spend four hours without using much conscious effort on driving. Every day, we make decisions. These require effort, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Santa problem]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47121</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/792875188/0/sethsblog~The-Santa-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T08:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An echo chamber is created by a marketer to assemble a group of people who are insulated from conventional discourse. It can happen to sports and music fans, to investors, to companies that have confidence in their view of the world, or to social or political gatherings. We support an echo chamber when we can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All together now: Spring Boot 3.2, GraalVM native images, Java 21, and virtual threads with Project Loom,]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/09/all-together-now-spring-boot-3-2-graalvm-native-images-java-21-and-virtual</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/09/all-together-now-spring-boot-3-2-graalvm-native-images-java-21-and-virtual"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the new CLion Conan Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=386308</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/09/introducing-the-new-clion-conan-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a cross-post from the Conan blog. In this post, we are thrilled to announce the launch of the new version of the Conan CLion Plugin, now compatible with the 2.X versions of Conan. The new plugin is designed to bring more ease and control to developers using CLion (with version higher than 2022.3) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new cooperative workshop]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47178</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/792748517/0/sethsblog~A-new-cooperative-workshop/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My colleague Ava Morris is running her Song of Significance Workshop on Friday, October 6. It’s powerful, effective and personal. It runs worldwide, in Zoom, and it’s completely interactive–every participant participates. This will be the third session… the first two got rave reviews, and some folks even returned to do it again. It’s two hours […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No lunging]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45509</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/792736457/0/sethsblog~No-lunging/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T08:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been working hard on my juggling (actual juggling, not metaphorical juggling). The secret, as I wrote about in The Practice is the throwing, not the catching. If you get the throws right, the catches are easy. The way to focus on the throws is simple but culturally difficult: Errant throws don’t earn a lunge. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New version of ServiceNow Terraform Catalog enables resource updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-of-servicenow-terraform-catalog-enables-resource-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-of-servicenow-terraform-catalog-enables-resource-updates"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ServiceNow Service Catalog for Terraform now lets you update existing Terraform workspaces and reprovision resources with new variables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 steps UK government can take to reduce legacy IT and streamline budget]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/uk-government-reduce-legacy-it-streamline-budget</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/uk-government-reduce-legacy-it-streamline-budget"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 25% of the UK government’s digital budget is spent on reducing legacy IT and cybersecurity. An IT modernisation project can be daunting — but the upside is reduced risk, tool consolidation, operational efficiencies, and long-term cost savings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Dutton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 steps UK government can take to reduce legacy IT and streamline budget]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/uk-government-reduce-legacy-it-streamline-budget</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/uk-government-reduce-legacy-it-streamline-budget"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
According to the National Audit Office (NAO), more than 25% of the UK government’s total digital budget is being spent on reducing legacy IT and cybersecurity. That trend is also apparent when examining individual department spending. The NAO notes that the Department of Food and Rural Affairs (DEFRA) spends 76% of their digital budget on maintaining legacy IT.

In working with government leaders for years, I recognise that modernising legacy IT systems is undoubtedly a daunting endeavour, one which comes with disruption to teams, processes, and even departmental culture. 

It can also be tempting to deem the problem as one limited to only the IT department. In reality, however, legacy IT can significantly compromise the security and operations of your entire organisation. As David Knott, CTO for the UK government, wrote recently on LinkedIn, “The practices used to manage your technology are as fundamental to your business success as the practices you use to manage your people and your processes. If your business is plagued by legacy technology, that is the result of a series of management choices, choices about the importance of infrastructure quality and code quality.”
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Dutton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2826/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2826/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/gold.png" title="It can be expensive to hire a professional spectroscopist for your wedding, but the quality of the spectra you get is worth it." alt="It can be expensive to hire a professional spectroscopist for your wedding, but the quality of the spectra you get is worth it." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A novel computational fluid dynamics framework for turbulent flow research]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/a-novel-computational-fluid-dynamics.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/a-novel-computational-fluid-dynamics.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shantanu Shahane, Software Engineer, and Matthias Ihme, Research Scientist, Athena Team




Turbulence is ubiquitous in environmental and engineering fluid flows, and is encountered routinely in everyday life. A better understanding of these turbulent processes could provide valuable insights across a variety of research areas — improving the prediction of cloud formation by atmospheric transport and the spreading of wildfires by turbulent energy exchange, understanding sedimentation of deposits in rivers, and improving the efficiency of combustion in aircraft engines to reduce emissions, to name a few. However, despite its importance, our current understanding and our ability to reliably predict such flows remains limited. This is mainly attributed to the highly chaotic nature a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon EC2 R7iz Instances are Optimized for High CPU Performance, Memory-Intensive Workloads]]></title>
        <id>8ba74cddc223f444061c3b940056b7e5bf430c07</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-r7iz-instances-memory-optimized-for-high-cpu-performance-memory-intensive-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re announcing general availability of the Amazon EC2 R7iz instances. R7iz instances are the fastest 4th Generation Intel Xeon Scalable-based (Sapphire Rapids) instances in the cloud with 3.9 GHz sustained all-core turbo frequency. R7iz instances are suitable for workloads where there’s a requirement for more memory to process additional data, larger sizes of instances […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power of Automation: Enhancing Your Manual Code Review Process]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=qodana&amp;p=385463</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/qodana/2023/09/the-power-of-automation-enhancing-your-manual-code-review-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T13:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code reviews help you strategically dig deeper into your work. They enable you to identify bugs, potential fixes, vulnerabilities, and much more to ultimately improve the quality of your source code and your knowledge of it. This can have a direct impact on team learning, project build speed and quality, and product outcomes, in addition […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kerry Beetge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | September 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=385738</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/09/07/net-annotated-monthly-september-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T10:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? The original usage of the term “computer” referred to people (mostly women), not machines. It’s possible that one day the word “programmer” could morph into meaning “AI”, and no longer refers to a person. .NET news Featured content  We bring this month’s featured content to you from….the .NET community speakers and the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Marketplace Celebrates 5 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=383963</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2023/09/jetbrains-marketplace-celebrates-5-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T09:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Half a decade ago, JetBrains Plugin Repository officially transformed into JetBrains Marketplace. As we celebrate this milestone, we’d like to take this opportunity to reflect on the incredible journey we’ve taken together. TL;DR: Read this blog post to learn how you can join the ongoing celebrations and possibly get your very own gifts. Alternatively, you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The paradox of insular language]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47170</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/792637607/0/sethsblog~The-paradox-of-insular-language/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T08:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often develop slang or codewords to keep the others from understanding what we’re saying. Here’s an example (thanks BK) of the lengths that some are going to be able to talk about Chinese politics. Of course, if you come up with a concealed enough code, the people you’re talking to won’t have a clue […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2 of the Packer Azure plugin is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/version-2-packer-azure-plugin-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/version-2-packer-azure-plugin-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Packer Azure plugin has migrated to the HashiCorp Go Azure SDK to address known Azure SDK deprecations and provide a consistent foundation for managing Azure infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast:  Spring Security lead Rob Winch]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/07/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-lead-rob-winch</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/07/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-lead-rob-winch"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TSMixer: An all-MLP architecture for time series forecasting]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/tsmixer-all-mlp-architecture-for-time.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/tsmixer-all-mlp-architecture-for-time.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Si-An Chen, Student Researcher, Cloud AI Team, and Chun-Liang Li, Research Scientist, Cloud AI Team




Time series forecasting is critical to various real-world applications, from demand forecasting to pandemic spread prediction. In multivariate time series forecasting (forecasting multiple variants at the same time), one can split existing methods into two categories: univariate models and multivariate models. Univariate models focus on inter-series interactions or temporal patterns that encompass trends and seasonal patterns on a time series with a single variable. Examples of such trends and seasonal patterns might be the way mortgage rates increase due to inflation, and how traffic peaks during rush hour. In addition to inter-series patterns, multivariate models process intr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build an enterprise LLM application: Lessons from GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-06-how-to-build-an-enterprise-llm-application-lessons-from-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-06-how-to-build-an-enterprise-llm-application-lessons-from-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The team behind GitHub Copilot shares its lessons for building an LLM app that delivers value to both individuals and enterprise users at scale. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-06-how-to-build-an-enterprise-llm-application-lessons-from-github-copilot/">How to build an enterprise LLM application: Lessons from GitHub Copilot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The newest AWS Heroes are here – September 2023]]></title>
        <id>191318f95fbfcb42c00d05fc4648b0a473270294</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/the-newest-aws-heroes-are-here-september-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each quarter, the AWS Heroes program recognizes technical enthusiasts who lift up the greater AWS community through various approaches. While these inspirational individuals are driven to knowledge share, they sometimes discover novel and fun ways of using technology, such as leveraging LEDs to create a magical display of holiday lights. Many are also contributing heavily […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第236話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755178180638</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755178180638"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy’s New Projects and Topics: September Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=385540</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/09/06/jetbrains-academy-s-new-projects-and-topics-september-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September is a month of change and excitement, and we’re here to make it even more inviting with our latest updates. Our team has prepared four new Python projects and more than 90 new educational topics. Let’s look at these updates in more detail. Python 🆕 Project: Rhythm Store (Beta). Medium. In this project, you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Regina Muradova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate OpenShift with Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automate-openshift-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automate-openshift-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy an application to OpenShift and configure it with Ansible Automation Platform using the Red Hat Certified Collection for OpenShift.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachna Dodia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big-O conundrum]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47097</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/792507371/0/sethsblog~The-BigO-conundrum/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T08:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In computer science, Big-O notation is a way of talking about what happens to a solution method when the inputs start to increase. For example, sorting numbers is an easy problem when there are only five or six, but when you have to sort 5,000, a totally different algorithm is needed. Business models have this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.13 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-13-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-13-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julio Santana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.9.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-9-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-9-2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julio Santana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting guide: Solving 6 common issues in Kibana Discover load]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-guide-common-issues-kibana-discover-load</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-guide-common-issues-kibana-discover-load"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post provides a troubleshooting guide for the Kibana® Discover UI view, including long loads, time outs, and errors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steffanie Nestor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asuka Nakajima aspired to be a hacker. Now she’s a security research engineer.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-asuka-nakajima-hacker-security-research-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-asuka-nakajima-hacker-security-research-engineer"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Women in tech: Asuka Nakajima followed her childhood dream into cybersecurity. Now she’s a security research engineer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.13 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-13-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-13-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 7.17.13 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.13 over 7.17.12 and 7.16.x releases.
The 7.17.13 patch release contains fixes for potential security vulnerabilities. Please see our security advisory for more details.For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julio Santana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.9.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-9-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-9-2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 8.9.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.9.2 over 8.9.1 and 8.8.x releases.
The 8.9.2 patch release contains fixes for potential security vulnerabilities. Please see our security advisory for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julio Santana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting guide: Solving 6 common issues in Kibana Discover load]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-guide-common-issues-kibana-discover-load</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-guide-common-issues-kibana-discover-load"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Discover is Elastic®’s core Kibana® UI to search, filter, and inspect (time series) data. Visualizations are used for data aggregations/summaries. The Discover UI is resilient to large data Elasticsearch® responses, but it can sometimes experience issues due to (uncompressed) response size, mapping explosion, and browser limits. 

Below, we’ll summarize the most common historical issues, including long loads, time outs, and errors, and provide a sequential troubleshooting walk-through for solving them. Note: This article’s APIs are written to v8.6, but the general troubleshooting flow applies to earlier and later versions.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt4d546fa9f18d5ffe/64f3ade84d5ab557c94a5282/elastic-blog-1-kibana-event-log.png,elastic-blog-1-kibana-even…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steffanie Nestor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asuka Nakajima aspired to be a hacker. Now she’s a security research engineer.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-asuka-nakajima-hacker-security-research-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-asuka-nakajima-hacker-security-research-engineer"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Asuka Nakajima aspired to be a hacker after picking up a copy of Project SEVEN when she was 14 years old.
The book tells the story of a high school girl who was a hacker and saved the world from cyber terrorists. 
Asuka made that dream a reality. Now, she is a security research engineer at Elastic®, focusing on the endpoint security product’s (Elastic Defend) research and development. 
“More precisely, I am currently working on developing the EDR (Endpoint Detection and Response) feature, for Windows platform,” she says. 
After finishing Project SEVEN she realized how little she knew about IT, so she started an IT certification to learn the basics of computers. At university, she studied programming and security, and improved her technical skills by interning at various companies and par…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autumn and Fall]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2825/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2825/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/autumn_and_fall.png" title="Of course in reality this is just a US/UK thing; in British English, 'fall' is the brief period in between and 'autumn' is the main season." alt="Of course in reality this is just a US/UK thing; in British English, 'fall' is the brief period in between and 'autumn' is the main season." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS End User Computing Innovation Day 2023:  Architecting End User Computing for Change and Agility]]></title>
        <id>bbcc0023eaa53f35fd89db9349acde25fa3f6254</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-end-user-computing-innovation-day-2023-architecting-end-user-computing-for-change-and-agility/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on Wednesday, September 13, for a free-to-attend online event, AWS End User Computing Innovation Day 2023. AWS will stream the event simultaneously across multiple platforms, including LinkedIn Live, Twitter, YouTube, and Twitch. Adapting to a complex landscape shaped by return-to-oﬃce mandates, pressure to migrate out of self-operated data centers, escalating security concerns, scarcity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vercel Shipped Cron Jobs in 2 Months Using Amazon EventBridge Scheduler]]></title>
        <id>b17a63568d9769bf55a6e0e7bf657f0b4f373478</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-vercel-shipped-cron-jobs-in-2-months-using-amazon-eventbridge-scheduler/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vercel implemented Cron Jobs using Amazon EventBridge Scheduler, enabling their customers to create, manage, and run scheduled tasks at scale. The adoption of this feature was rapid, reaching over 7 million weekly cron invocations within a few months of release. This article shows how they did it and how they handle the massive scale they’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Busy Plugin Developers Newsletter – Summer 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=385255</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2023/09/busy-plugin-developers-newsletter-summer-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T16:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marketplace updates: ⭐ Marketplace main page redesign Our main page has a new look! With cleaned up visuals, the new design ensures smooth navigation through JetBrains Marketplace, allowing users to focus on what truly matters: finding the plugins that best meet their needs. ⭐️ Auto-approval for non-stable release channels Plugins can be deployed to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Kerpeleva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Datalore Enterprise 2023.4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=385018</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2023/09/05/what-s-new-in-datalore-enterprise-2023-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T14:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, Datalore Enterprise 2023.4 is out! This version includes comments for notebooks and reports, a new Viewer license type, report sharing via email invitations, a new Export to database cell type, SMB/CIFS folder support, and other quality improvements and bug fixes.  Upgrade to the newest version and read on to discover what’s new in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Anikina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is REST API in Java? Guide with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89827</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/what-is-rest-api-in-java-guide-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the basics, learn the specifics, and get hands-on with examples of using REST API in Java. 
The post What is REST API in Java? Guide with Examples appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – September 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=384951</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/09/java-annotated-monthly-september-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T13:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The September edition of Java Annotated Monthly is here! With this month’s release of Java 21 approaching, we’re excited to bring you a final sneak peek into its crucial features. But that’s not all! This edition is packed with helpful articles about cutting-edge AI technologies, including updates about the latest enhancements in IntelliJ IDEA’s AI […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Maryasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2023.3 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=384826</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/09/05/resharper-2023-3-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T09:53:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Early Access Program (EAP) for ReSharper version 2023.3 is right around the corner, so it’s high time to let you know what we’ll be working on in the coming months. This roadmap is just a preliminary plan and may be adjusted depending on our priorities and resources as well as changes in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2023.3 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=384823</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/09/05/rider-2023-3-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T09:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we gear up for the beginning of the Early Access Program (EAP) for Rider 2023.3, we wanted to take a moment to share our plans for this upcoming release.  These plans are subject to change, and some features and improvements may need to be pushed to a future version.  Additionally, be sure to check […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Le Guin precepts]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45495</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/792298160/0/sethsblog~The-Le-Guin-precepts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T08:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fabled author Ursula Le Guin had a sign over her desk: Not a bad place to begin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 5th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/05/this-week-in-spring-september-5th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/05/this-week-in-spring-september-5th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic instrumentation with OpenTelemetry for Python applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrumentation-of-python-applications-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrumentation-of-python-applications-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to auto-instrument Python applications using OpenTelemetry. With standard commands in a Docker file, applications can be instrumented quickly without writing code in multiple places, enabling rapid change, scale, and easier management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manual instrumentation of .NET applications with OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/manual-instrumentation-of-net-applications-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/manual-instrumentation-of-net-applications-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we will look at how to manually instrument your .NET applications using OpenTelemetry, which provides a set of APIs, libraries, and agents to capture distributed traces and metrics from your application. You can analyze them in Elastic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 tech challenges that can be collaboration opportunities for global governments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/7-tech-challenges-collaboration-opportunities-global-governments</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/7-tech-challenges-collaboration-opportunities-global-governments"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments around the world face similar challenges, such as cybersecurity, legacy IT, and the ethical use of AI. Rather than addressing each issue on their own, agencies can learn from each other's experiences and collaborate when appropriate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manual instrumentation of Java applications with OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/manual-instrumentation-of-java-applications-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/manual-instrumentation-of-java-applications-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTelemetry provides an observability framework for cloud-native software, allowing us to trace, monitor, and debug applications seamlessly. In this post, we'll explore how to manually instrument a Java application using OpenTelemetry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic instrumentation with OpenTelemetry for Node.js applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrument-nodejs-applications-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrument-nodejs-applications-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to auto-instrument Node.js applications using OpenTelemetry. With standard commands in a Docker file, applications can be instrumented quickly without writing code in multiple places, enabling rapid change, scale, and easier management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic instrumentation with OpenTelemetry for Python applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrumentation-of-python-applications-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrumentation-of-python-applications-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
DevOps and SRE teams are transforming the process of software development. While DevOps engineers focus on efficient software applications and service delivery, SRE teams are key to ensuring reliability, scalability, and performance. These teams must rely on a full-stack observability solution that allows them to manage and monitor systems and ensure issues are resolved before they impact the business.  

Observability across the entire stack of modern distributed applications requires data collection, processing, and correlation often in the form of dashboards. Ingesting all system data requires installing agents across stacks, frameworks, and providers — a process that can be challenging and time-consuming for teams who have to deal with version changes, compatibility issues, and propr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manual instrumentation of .NET applications with OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/manual-instrumentation-of-net-applications-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/manual-instrumentation-of-net-applications-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In the fast-paced universe of software development, especially in the cloud-native realm, DevOps and SRE teams are increasingly emerging as essential partners in application stability and growth.
DevOps engineers continuously optimize software delivery, while SRE teams act as the stewards of application reliability, scalability, and top-tier performance. The challenge? These teams require a cutting-edge observability solution, one that encompasses full-stack insights, empowering them to rapidly manage, monitor, and rectify potential disruptions before they culminate into operational challenges.
Observability in our modern distributed software ecosystem goes beyond mere monitoring — it demands limitless data collection, precision in processing, and the correlation of this data into action…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 tech challenges that can be collaboration opportunities for global governments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/7-tech-challenges-collaboration-opportunities-global-governments</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/7-tech-challenges-collaboration-opportunities-global-governments"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
So far the twenty-first century has unleashed a torrent of technological innovations, becoming a double-edged sword for governments worldwide. The growing burden of legacy IT systems, cybersecurity threats, AI incorporation, data privacy concerns, budgetary constraints, and shifting geopolitical landscapes puts governments at the forefront of a rapidly evolving environment. 

Governments around the world face similar challenges, and — rather than addressing each issue on their own — they can learn from each other's experiences. These seven technology obstacles are similar across regions and have the potential to spark larger conversations and collaboration, where appropriate.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manual instrumentation of Java applications with OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/manual-instrumentation-of-java-applications-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/manual-instrumentation-of-java-applications-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In the fast-paced universe of software development, especially in the cloud-native realm, DevOps and SRE teams are increasingly emerging as essential partners in application stability and growth.
DevOps engineers continuously optimize software delivery, while SRE teams act as the stewards of application reliability, scalability, and top-tier performance. The challenge? These teams require a cutting-edge observability solution, one that encompasses full-stack insights, empowering them to rapidly manage, monitor, and rectify potential disruptions before they culminate into operational challenges.
Observability in our modern distributed software ecosystem goes beyond mere monitoring—it demands limitless data collection, precision in processing, and the correlation of this data into actionab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic instrumentation with OpenTelemetry for Node.js applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrument-nodejs-applications-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrument-nodejs-applications-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
DevOps and SRE teams are transforming the process of software development. While DevOps engineers focus on efficient software applications and service delivery, SRE teams are key to ensuring reliability, scalability, and performance. These teams must rely on a full-stack observability solution that allows them to manage and monitor systems and ensure issues are resolved before they impact the business.  

Observability across the entire stack of modern distributed applications requires data collection, processing, and correlation often in the form of dashboards. Ingesting all system data requires installing agents across stacks, frameworks, and providers — a process that can be challenging and time-consuming for teams who have to deal with version changes, compatibility issues, and propr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Farewell EC2-Classic, EBS at 15 Years, and More (Sept. 4, 2023)]]></title>
        <id>1a569d832e6d0012825fad5a9dbc82223bec7711</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-farewell-ec2-classic-ebs-at-15-years-and-more-sept-4-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, there was some great reading about Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) and Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) written by AWS tech leaders. Dr. Werner Vogels wrote Farewell EC2-Classic, it’s been swell, celebrating the 17 years of loyal duty of the original version that started what we now know as cloud computing. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSS Power-Ups: bUnit – Webinar Recording]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=384712</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/09/04/oss-power-ups-bunit-webinar-recording/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T13:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recording of our webinar, OSS Power-Ups: bUnit, with Egil Hansen and Steven Giesel, is available. This was the twelfth episode of our OSS Power-Ups series, where we put a spotlight on open-source .NET projects. Subscribe to our community newsletter to receive notifications about future webinars. In this talk, you will learn how to get started […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias Koch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Next: WebStorm 2023.3 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=384500</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/09/2023-3-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T13:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We released WebStorm 2023.2, our second major update in 2023, just over a month ago. First of all, we’d like to thank every one of you that are already using it and providing us with feedback. Today, we’ll give you a little look into what we’ve got planned for the next release of WebStorm, which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[But what if it’s voluntary?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47138</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/792092951/0/sethsblog~But-what-if-its-voluntary/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For more than 130 years, we’ve celebrated Labor Day in the US and Canada. And May Day has been around about as long. Around here, it’s become mostly a seasonal marker, but it was founded to devote just a day to something that deserves much more… to commemorate and celebrate the workers who sacrifice and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract Pickup]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2824/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2824/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/abstract_pickup.png" title="Escape Artist Frees Self From Conversation With Pickup Artist" alt="Escape Artist Frees Self From Conversation With Pickup Artist" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Informed consent (rarely is)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45008</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/792014279/0/sethsblog~Informed-consent-rarely-is/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adults make choices and live with the consequences. No one else should tell us what flavor of ice cream we prefer, or what career to choose. We’re good at knowing what we want. In practice, this works really well for certain kinds of decisions. But when we add the network effect, profit-seeking industrial entities, statistics, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The empathy of useful feedback]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45149</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/791824298/0/sethsblog~The-empathy-of-useful-feedback/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When a friend shows you work in progress, your best contribution is to imagine the point of view and preferences of the person it is being created for. “I don’t like it,” isn’t useful, because it’s not for you. “I could imagine that someone who wants x, y or z would be looking for…” is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join us at CamundaCon 2023 for Everything Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89745</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/join-us-camundacon-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2023 is right around the corner. Check out everything there is to see and learn at the leading process orchestration conference.
The post Join us at CamundaCon 2023 for Everything Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with edge computing]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-01-getting-started-with-edge-computing/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-01-getting-started-with-edge-computing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Edge computing practitioners answer your questions about when and why to build applications at the edge.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-01-getting-started-with-edge-computing/">Getting started with edge computing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-Driven Ansible - ChatOps - From Chat to Action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-chatops-from-chat-to-action</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-chatops-from-chat-to-action"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implement Automated ChatOps: Learn how to use event-driven automation to take action from chat information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fossil]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2823/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2823/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/fossil.png" title="The two best reasons to get into fossils are booping trilobites and getting to say the word &quot;fossiliferous&quot; a lot." alt="The two best reasons to get into fossils are booping trilobites and getting to say the word &quot;fossiliferous&quot; a lot." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Legacy Package Repositories Will Be Frozen On September 13, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/31/legacy-package-repository-deprecation/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/31/legacy-package-repository-deprecation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Bob Killen (Google), Chris Short (AWS), Jeremy Rickard (Microsoft), Marko Mudrinić (Kubermatic), Tim Bannister (The Scale Factory)
On August 15, 2023, the Kubernetes project announced the general availability of
the community-owned package repositories for Debian and RPM packages available
at pkgs.k8s.io. The new package repositories are replacement for the legacy
Google-hosted package repositories: apt.kubernetes.io and yum.kubernetes.io.
The
announcement blog post for pkgs.k8s.io
highlighted that we will stop publishing packages to the legacy repositories in
the future.
Today, we're formally deprecating the legacy package repositories (apt.kubernetes.io
and yum.kubernetes.io), and we're announcing our plans to freeze the contents of
the repositories as of September 13, 2023.
Ple…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WeatherBench 2: A benchmark for the next generation of data-driven weather models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/weatherbench-2-benchmark-for-next.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/weatherbench-2-benchmark-for-next.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T17:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Stephan Rasp, Research Scientist, and Carla Bromberg, Program Lead, Google Research





In 1950, weather forecasting started its digital revolution when researchers used the first programmable, general-purpose computer ENIAC to solve mathematical equations describing how weather evolves. In the more than 70 years since, continuous advancements in computing power and improvements to the model formulations have led to steady gains in weather forecast skill: a 7-day forecast today is about as accurate as a 5-day forecast in 2000 and a 3-day forecast in 1980. While improving forecast accuracy at the pace of approximately one day per decade may not seem like a big deal, every day improved is important in far reaching use cases, such as for logistics planning, disaster management, agr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimize your GitHub Codespaces costs with upgraded virtual machines]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-31-how-github-reduces-costs-with-upgraded-codespaces/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-31-how-github-reduces-costs-with-upgraded-codespaces/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T15:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>See how much more you can get out of GitHub Codespaces by taking advantage of the improved processing power and increased headroom in the next generation of virtual machines.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-31-how-github-reduces-costs-with-upgraded-codespaces/">Optimize your GitHub Codespaces costs with upgraded virtual machines</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Security and Kubernetes legend Daniel Garnier-Moiroux]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/31/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-and-kubernetes-legend-daniel-garnier</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/31/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-and-kubernetes-legend-daniel-garnier"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is the Beginning of the End of the N+1 Problem: Introducing Single Query Loading.]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/31/this-is-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-n-1-problem-introducing-single-query</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/31/this-is-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-n-1-problem-introducing-single-query"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Schauder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modeling and improving text stability in live captions]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/modeling-and-improving-text-stability.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/modeling-and-improving-text-stability.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T19:34:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Vikas Bahirwani, Research Scientist, and Susan Xu, Software Engineer, Google Augmented Reality





Automatic speech recognition (ASR) technology has made conversations more accessible with live captions in remote conferencing software, mobile applications, and head-worn displays. However, to maintain real-time responsiveness, live caption systems often display interim predictions that are updated as new utterances are received. This can cause text instability (a “flicker” where previously displayed text is updated, shown in the captions on the left in the video below), which can impair users' reading experience due to distraction, fatigue, and difficulty following the conversation.






In “Modeling and Improving Text Stability in Live Captions”, presented at ACM CHI 2023, we f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon Managed Service for Apache Flink Renamed from Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics]]></title>
        <id>e40c4472300bd8097a0fe160c607a0e9eeb6e5d5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-managed-service-for-apache-flink-renamed-from-amazon-kinesis-data-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T17:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the rename of Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics to Amazon Managed Service for Apache Flink, a fully managed and serverless service for you to build and run real-time streaming applications using Apache Flink. We continue to deliver the same experience in your Flink applications without any impact on ongoing operations, developments, or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Rust is the most admired language among developers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-30-why-rust-is-the-most-admired-language-among-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-30-why-rust-is-the-most-admired-language-among-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T14:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Rust continues to top the charts as the most admired and desired language by developers, and in this post, we dive a little deeper into how (and why) Rust is stealing the hearts of developers around the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-30-why-rust-is-the-most-admired-language-among-developers/">Why Rust is the most admired language among developers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Azure Infrastructure for High Availability Web Hosting with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-azure-infrastructure-for-high-availability-web-hosting-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-azure-infrastructure-for-high-availability-web-hosting-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it a hassle to set up the infrastructure for a new website every time you need to run a short-term project, such as a marketing campaign or just for testing? Do you spend too much on resources that are only used for a short period? Look no further, because automation is here to save the day!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Leiva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Configuration Service Mesh with On-Demand Cluster Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ac6483b52a51</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/zero-configuration-service-mesh-with-on-demand-cluster-discovery-ac6483b52a51?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T23:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix’s service mesh adoption: history, motivations, and how we worked with the Envoy community on a feature to streamline mesh adoption]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SayTap: Language to quadrupedal locomotion]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/saytap-language-to-quadrupedal.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/saytap-language-to-quadrupedal.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T19:57:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yujin Tang and Wenhao Yu, Research Scientists, Google




Simple and effective interaction between human and quadrupedal robots paves the way towards creating intelligent and capable helper robots, forging a future where technology enhances our lives in ways beyond our imagination. Key to such human-robot interaction systems is enabling quadrupedal robots to respond to natural language instructions. Recent developments in large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated the potential to perform high-level planning. Yet, it remains a challenge for LLMs to comprehend low-level commands, such as joint angle targets or motor torques, especially for inherently unstable legged robots, necessitating high-frequency control signals. Consequently, most existing work presumes the provision of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.10 is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-29-github-enterprise-server-3-10-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-29-github-enterprise-server-3-10-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T18:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Customers using GHES can now ensure secure development is a top priority with enhanced security and compliance controls for their repositories.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-29-github-enterprise-server-3-10-is-now-generally-available/">GitHub Enterprise Server 3.10 is now generally available</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Gateway API v0.8.0: Introducing Service Mesh Support]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/29/gateway-api-v0-8/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/29/gateway-api-v0-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Flynn (Buoyant), John Howard (Google), Keith Mattix (Microsoft), Michael Beaumont (Kong), Mike Morris (independent), Rob Scott (Google)
We are thrilled to announce the v0.8.0 release of Gateway API! With this
release, Gateway API support for service mesh has reached Experimental
status. We look forward to your feedback!
We're especially delighted to announce that Kuma 2.3+, Linkerd 2.14+, and Istio
1.16+ are all fully-conformant implementations of Gateway API service mesh
support.
Service mesh support in Gateway API
While the initial focus of Gateway API was always ingress (north-south)
traffic, it was clear almost from the beginning that the same basic routing
concepts should also be applicable to service mesh (east-west) traffic. In
2022, the Gateway API subproject started the G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My SpringOne 2023 Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/my-springone-2023-recap</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/my-springone-2023-recap"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 29th, 2023 - the post SpringOne recovery blog]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/this-week-in-spring-august-29th-2023-the-post-springone-recovery-blog</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/this-week-in-spring-august-29th-2023-the-post-springone-recovery-blog"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data JDBC - How To Maintain Your Database Schema]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/spring-data-jdbc-how-to-maintain-your-database-schema</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/spring-data-jdbc-how-to-maintain-your-database-schema"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Schauder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – AWS Dedicated Local Zones, Events and More – August 28, 2023]]></title>
        <id>b149aa31ec92d6b50f0246dd76f4b269e108440e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-dedicated-zones-events-and-more-august-28-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T21:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I will meet our customers and partners at the AWS Summit Mexico. If you are around, please come say hi at the community lounge and at the F1 Game Day where I will spend most of my time. I would love to discuss your developer experience on AWS and listen to your stories […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RO-ViT: Region-aware pre-training for open-vocabulary object detection with vision transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/ro-vit-region-aware-pre-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/ro-vit-region-aware-pre-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:59:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dahun Kim and Weicheng Kuo, Research Scientists, Google



The ability to detect objects in the visual world is crucial for computer vision and machine intelligence, enabling applications like adaptive autonomous agents and versatile shopping systems. However, modern object detectors are limited by the manual annotations of their training data, resulting in a vocabulary size significantly smaller than the vast array of objects encountered in reality. To overcome this, the open-vocabulary detection task (OVD) has emerged, utilizing image-text pairs for training and incorporating new category names at test time by associating them with the image content. By treating categories as text embeddings, open-vocabulary detectors can predict a wide range of unseen objects. Various techniqu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 things you didn’t know you could do with GitHub Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-28-10-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-github-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-28-10-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-github-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to optimize your usage of GitHub Projects to plan and track your work from idea to production.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-28-10-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-github-projects/">10 things you didn’t know you could do with GitHub Projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: A New (alpha) Mechanism For Safer Cluster Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/28/kubernetes-1-28-feature-mixed-version-proxy-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/28/kubernetes-1-28-feature-mixed-version-proxy-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Richa Banker (Google)
This blog describes the mixed version proxy, a new alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.28. The
mixed version proxy enables an HTTP request for a resource to be served by the correct API server
in cases where there are multiple API servers at varied versions in a cluster. For example,
this is useful during a cluster upgrade, or when you're rolling out the runtime configuration of
the cluster's control plane.
What problem does this solve?
When a cluster undergoes an upgrade, the kube-apiservers existing at different versions in that scenario can serve different sets (groups, versions, resources) of built-in resources. A resource request made in this scenario may be served by any of the available apiservers, potentially resulting in the request ending up at an apiserve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Community Podcast Recap: Inbound and Outbound Connectors: “Woah, it’s so easy!”]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89567</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/camunda-community-podcast-recap-inbound-outbound-connectors-so-easy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T20:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missed the latest episode of the Camunda Community Podcast? Catch up with a quick recap.
The post Camunda Community Podcast Recap: Inbound and Outbound Connectors: “Woah, it’s so easy!” appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · August 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-25-game-bytes-august-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-25-game-bytes-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T18:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-25-game-bytes-august-2023/">Game Bytes · August 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Perception Fairness]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T17:38:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Susanna Ricco and Utsav Prabhu, co-leads, Perception Fairness Team, Google Research





Google’s Responsible AI research is built on a foundation of collaboration — between teams with diverse backgrounds and expertise, between researchers and product developers, and ultimately with the community at large. The Perception Fairness team drives progress by combining deep subject-matter expertise in both computer vision and machine learning (ML) fairness with direct connections to the researchers building the perception systems that power products across Google and beyond. Together, we are working to intentionally design our systems to be inclusive from the ground up, guided by Google’s AI Principles.






Perception Fairness research spans the design, development, and deployment of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: cloud native Chris Richardson]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-cloud-native-chris-richardson</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-cloud-native-chris-richardson"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.28: Introducing native sidecar containers]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/25/native-sidecar-containers/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/25/native-sidecar-containers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Todd Neal (AWS), Matthias Bertschy (ARMO), Sergey Kanzhelev (Google), Gunju Kim (NAVER), Shannon Kularathna (Google)
This post explains how to use the new sidecar feature, which enables restartable init containers and is available in alpha in Kubernetes 1.28. We want your feedback so that we can graduate this feature as soon as possible.
The concept of a “sidecar” has been part of Kubernetes since nearly the very beginning. In 2015, sidecars were described in a blog post about composite containers as additional containers that “extend and enhance the ‘main’ container”. Sidecar containers have become a common Kubernetes deployment pattern and are often used for network proxies or as part of a logging system. Until now, sidecars were a concept that Kubernetes users applied without n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to compare a noisy quantum processor to a classical computer]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/how-to-compare-noisy-quantum-processor.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/how-to-compare-noisy-quantum-processor.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T22:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sergio Boixo and Vadim Smelyanskiy, Principal Scientists, Google Quantum AI Team




A full-scale error-corrected quantum computer will be able to solve some problems that are impossible for classical computers, but building such a device is a huge endeavor. We are proud of the milestones that we have achieved toward a fully error-corrected quantum computer, but that large-scale computer is still some number of years away. Meanwhile, we are using our current noisy quantum processors as flexible platforms for quantum experiments. 



In contrast to an error-corrected quantum computer, experiments in noisy quantum processors are currently limited to a few thousand quantum operations or gates, before noise degrades the quantum state. In 2019 we implemented a specific computational t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A faster way to manage version updates with Dependabot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-24-a-faster-way-to-manage-version-updates-with-dependabot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-24-a-faster-way-to-manage-version-updates-with-dependabot/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Now, you can group multiple version updates in a single pull request.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-24-a-faster-way-to-manage-version-updates-with-dependabot/">A faster way to manage version updates with Dependabot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching language models to reason algorithmically]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/teaching-language-models-to-reason.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/teaching-language-models-to-reason.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T19:33:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hattie Zhou, Graduate Student at MILA, Hanie Sedghi, Research Scientist, Google




Large language models (LLMs), such as GPT-3 and PaLM, have shown impressive progress in recent years, which have been driven by scaling up models and training data sizes. Nonetheless, a long standing debate has been whether LLMs can reason symbolically (i.e., manipulating symbols based on logical rules). For example, LLMs are able to perform simple arithmetic operations when numbers are small, but struggle to perform with large numbers. This suggests that LLMs have not learned the underlying rules needed to perform these arithmetic operations. 



While neural networks have powerful pattern matching capabilities, they are prone to overfitting to spurious statistical patterns in the data. This does…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: Beta support for using swap on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/24/swap-linux-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/24/swap-linux-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Itamar Holder (Red Hat)
The 1.22 release introduced Alpha support
for configuring swap memory usage for Kubernetes workloads running on Linux on a per-node basis.
Now, in release 1.28, support for swap on Linux nodes has graduated to Beta, along with many
new improvements.
Prior to version 1.22, Kubernetes did not provide support for swap memory on Linux systems.
This was due to the inherent difficulty in guaranteeing and accounting for pod memory utilization
when swap memory was involved. As a result, swap support was deemed out of scope in the initial
design of Kubernetes, and the default behavior of a kubelet was to fail to start if swap memory
was detected on a node.
In version 1.22, the swap feature for Linux was initially introduced in its Alpha stage. This represented
a sign…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleashing GitHub Codespaces templates to ignite your development]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-24-unleashing-github-codespaces-templates-to-ignite-your-development/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-24-unleashing-github-codespaces-templates-to-ignite-your-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T16:57:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to leverage templating features in GitHub Codespaces to streamline your project setup, improve consistency, and simplify collaboration within your development team.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-24-unleashing-github-codespaces-templates-to-ignite-your-development/">Unleashing GitHub Codespaces templates to ignite your development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Community Day, Berlin 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-community-day-berlin-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-community-day-berlin-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Community Day is a day-long community-focused event to discuss the Ansible project, community, and the broader ecosystem. Announcing the upcoming one in Berlin, with a call for proposals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Ansible Community Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/24/spring-boot-3-2-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/24/spring-boot-3-2-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stéphane Nicoll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connectors: Custom Icons vs. BPMN Symbols]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89461</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/connectors-custom-icons-vs-bpmn-symbols/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T20:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We held discussions with our users on whether custom icons or original BPMN symbols were preferable. The feedback was enlightening.
The post Connectors: Custom Icons vs. BPMN Symbols appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bastian Koerber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-powered impact: GitHub Social Impact’s year ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-23-ai-powered-impact-github-social-impacts-year-ahead/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-23-ai-powered-impact-github-social-impacts-year-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How GitHub Social Impact is working with nonprofit organizations, employees, and more to create positive, lasting change in global communities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-23-ai-powered-impact-github-social-impacts-year-ahead/">AI-powered impact: GitHub Social Impact’s year ahead</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at Google Cloud Next: Seamless infrastructure deployment and management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-google-cloud-next-seamless-infrastructure-deployment-and-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-google-cloud-next-seamless-infrastructure-deployment-and-management"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit us at Google Cloud Next ‘23 in San Francisco, Aug. 29 - 31, for breakout sessions, expert talks, and product demos to accelerate your cloud strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: Node podresources API Graduates to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/23/kubelet-podresources-api-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/23/kubelet-podresources-api-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author:
Francesco Romani (Red Hat)
The podresources API is an API served by the kubelet locally on the node, which exposes the compute resources exclusively
allocated to containers. With the release of Kubernetes 1.28, that API is now Generally Available.
What problem does it solve?
The kubelet can allocate exclusive resources to containers, like
CPUs, granting exclusive access to full cores
or memory, either regions or hugepages.
Workloads which require high performance, or low latency (or both) leverage these features.
The kubelet also can assign devices to containers.
Collectively, these features which enable exclusive assignments are known as "resource managers".
Without an API like podresources, the only possible option to learn about resource assignment was to read the state files th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Azure Artifacts support for Rust Crates]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67425</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-azure-artifacts-support-for-rust-crates/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T20:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust is earning its place as a go-to language for developers everywhere. Why? It’s fast, it’s safe, and the community around it is supportive and hands-on. With clear guides and a collective push to help each other out, Rust feels less like just another tool and more like a reliable coding partner for modern programming challenges.
The post Introducing Azure Artifacts support for Rust Crates appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jorge Fernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Language to rewards for robotic skill synthesis]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/language-to-rewards-for-robotic-skill.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/language-to-rewards-for-robotic-skill.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:47:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Wenhao Yu and Fei Xia, Research Scientists, Google






Empowering end-users to interactively teach robots to perform novel tasks is a crucial capability for their successful integration into real-world applications. For example, a user may want to teach a robot dog to perform a new trick, or teach a manipulator robot how to organize a lunch box based on user preferences. The recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) pre-trained on extensive internet data have shown a promising path towards achieving this goal. Indeed, researchers have explored diverse ways of leveraging LLMs for robotics, from step-by-step planning and goal-oriented dialogue to robot-code-writing agents. 



While these methods impart new modes of compositional generalization, they focus on using lang…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp updates licensing FAQ based on community questions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-updates-licensing-faq-based-on-community-questions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-updates-licensing-faq-based-on-community-questions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp continues to update our licensing FAQ based on questions from the community about our change to the Business Source License for future releases of HashiCorp products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – AWS AppSync, AWS CodePipeline, Events and More – August 21, 2023]]></title>
        <id>47e2668ee0f78c86ac3d5a66b93a95d71f12cde4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-appsync-aws-codepipeline-events-and-more-august-21-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T18:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a few days, I will board a plane towards the south. My tour around Latin America starts. But I won’t be alone in this adventure, you can find some other News Blog authors, like Jeff or Seb, speaking at AWS Community Days and local events in Peru, Argentina, Chile, and Uruguay. If you see […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform ephemeral workspaces public beta now available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-ephemeral-workspaces-public-beta-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-ephemeral-workspaces-public-beta-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing unused infrastructure resources is important not just for cost control, but for security as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage OSPF for network automation with Ansible validated content]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/manage-ospf-for-network-automation-with-ansible-validated-content</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/manage-ospf-for-network-automation-with-ansible-validated-content"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the quickly evolving networking environment, efficient management of routing protocols is essential for reliable and optimized network performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at Interspeech 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/google-at-interspeech-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/google-at-interspeech-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T07:33:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Catherine Armato, Program Manager, Google




This week, the 24th Annual Conference of the International Speech Communication Association (INTERSPEECH 2023) is being held in Dublin, Ireland, representing one of the world’s most extensive conferences on research and technology of spoken language understanding and processing. Experts in speech-related research fields gather to take part in oral presentations and poster sessions and to build collaborations across the globe.




We are excited to be a Platinum Sponsor of INTERSPEECH 2023, where we will be showcasing more than 20 research publications and supporting a number of workshops and special sessions. We welcome in-person attendees to drop by the Google Research booth to meet our researchers and participate in Q&As and demonst…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: Improved failure handling for Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/21/kubernetes-1-28-jobapi-update/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/21/kubernetes-1-28-jobapi-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kevin Hannon (G-Research), Michał Woźniak (Google)
This blog discusses two new features in Kubernetes 1.28 to improve Jobs for batch
users: Pod replacement policy
and Backoff limit per index.
These features continue the effort started by the
Pod failure policy
to improve the handling of Pod failures in a Job.
Pod replacement policy
By default, when a pod enters a terminating state (e.g. due to preemption or
eviction), Kubernetes immediately creates a replacement Pod. Therefore, both Pods are running
at the same time. In API terms, a pod is considered terminating when it has a
deletionTimestamp and it has a phase Pending or Running.
The scenario when two Pods are running at a given time is problematic for
some popular machine learning frameworks, such as
TensorFlow and JAX, which r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autonomous visual information seeking with large language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/autonomous-visual-information-seeking.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/autonomous-visual-information-seeking.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:28:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ziniu Hu, Student Researcher, and Alireza Fathi, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception Team




There has been great progress towards adapting large language models (LLMs) to accommodate multimodal inputs for tasks including image captioning, visual question answering (VQA), and open vocabulary recognition. Despite such achievements, current state-of-the-art visual language models (VLMs) perform inadequately on visual information seeking datasets, such as Infoseek and OK-VQA, where external knowledge is required to answer the questions. 
 






Examples of visual information seeking queries where external knowledge is required to answer the question. Images are taken from the OK-VQA dataset.

AVIS: Autonomous Visual Information Seeking with Large Language Models”, we i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Hyperautomation Examples and Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89106</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/top-10-use-cases-for-hyperautomation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the top 10 use cases for hyperautomation with examples, and understand its incredible impact across industries.
The post Top 10 Hyperautomation Examples and Use Cases appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.28: Retroactive Default StorageClass move to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/18/retroactive-default-storage-class-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/18/retroactive-default-storage-class-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Roman Bednář (Red Hat)
Announcing graduation to General Availability (GA) - Retroactive Default StorageClass Assignment in Kubernetes v1.28!
Kubernetes SIG Storage team is thrilled to announce that the "Retroactive Default StorageClass Assignment" feature,
introduced as an alpha in Kubernetes v1.25, has now graduated to GA and is officially part of the Kubernetes v1.28 release.
This enhancement brings a significant improvement to how default
StorageClasses are assigned to PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs).
With this feature enabled, you no longer need to create a default StorageClass first and then a PVC to assign the class.
Instead, any PVCs without a StorageClass assigned will now be retroactively updated to include the default StorageClass.
This enhancement ensures that PVCs no longer get stuck in an unbound state, and storage provisioning works seamlessly,
even when a default StorageClass is not defined at the time of PVC creation.
What changed?
The PersistentVolume (PV) controller has been modified to automatically assign a default StorageClass to any unbound
PersistentVolumeClaim with the storageClassName not set. Additionally, the PersistentVolumeClaim
admission validation mechanism within
the API server has been adjusted to allow changing values from an unset state to an actual StorageClass name.
How to use it?
As this feature has graduated to GA, there's no need to enable a feature gate anymore.
Simply make sure you are running Kubernetes v1.28 or later, and the feature will be available for use.
For more details, read about
default StorageClass assignment in the Kubernetes documentation.
You can also read the previous blog post announcing beta graduation in v1.26.
To provide feedback, join our Kubernetes Storage Special-Interest-Group (SIG)
or participate in discussions on our public Slack channel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVA Discovery View: Surfacing Authentic Moments]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b8cd145491cc</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/ava-discovery-view-surfacing-authentic-moments-b8cd145491cc?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T22:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By: Hamid Shahid, Laura Johnson, Tiffany Low]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 Hpc7a Instances Powered by 4th Gen AMD EPYC Processors Optimized for High Performance Computing]]></title>
        <id>b86f604c4015c28675b8f90e5913de842828c831</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-hpc7a-instances-powered-by-4th-gen-amd-epyc-processors-optimized-for-high-performance-computing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January 2022, we launched Amazon EC2 Hpc6a instances for customers to efficiently run their compute-bound high performance computing (HPC) workloads on AWS with up to 65 percent better price performance over comparable x86-based compute-optimized instances. As their jobs grow more complex, customers have asked for more cores with more compute performance and more memory […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neural network pruning with combinatorial optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/neural-network-pruning-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/neural-network-pruning-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T18:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hussein Hazimeh, Research Scientist, Athena Team, and Riade Benbaki, Graduate Student at MIT





Modern neural networks have achieved impressive performance across a variety of applications, such as language, mathematical reasoning, and vision. However, these networks often use large architectures that require lots of computational resources. This can make it impractical to serve such models to users, especially in resource-constrained environments like wearables and smartphones. A widely used approach to mitigate the inference costs of pre-trained networks is to prune them by removing some of their weights, in a way that doesn’t significantly affect utility. In standard neural networks, each weight defines a connection between two neurons. So after weights are pruned, the input…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.18 reduces synthesization time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-18-reduces-synthesization-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-18-reduces-synthesization-time"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newest CDKTF release cuts synthesization times for TypeScript, Python, and Java, drastically improving the user experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYC Automation for Banks: 5 Biggest Benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=88965</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/kyc-automation-banks-5-biggest-benefits/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T21:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With KYC in banking, there are a lot of advantages that every bank should know about. Read on to learn more about KYC automation and how it works.
The post KYC Automation for Banks: 5 Biggest Benefits appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: Non-Graceful Node Shutdown Moves to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/16/kubernetes-1-28-non-graceful-node-shutdown-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/16/kubernetes-1-28-non-graceful-node-shutdown-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Xing Yang (VMware) and Ashutosh Kumar (Elastic)
The Kubernetes Non-Graceful Node Shutdown feature is now GA in Kubernetes v1.28.
It was introduced as
alpha
in Kubernetes v1.24, and promoted to
beta
in Kubernetes v1.26.
This feature allows stateful workloads to restart on a different node if the
original node is shutdown unexpectedly or ends up in a non-recoverable state
such as the hardware failure or unresponsive OS.
What is a Non-Graceful Node Shutdown
In a Kubernetes cluster, a node can be shutdown in a planned graceful way or
unexpectedly because of reasons such as power outage or something else external.
A node shutdown could lead to workload failure if the node is not drained
before the shutdown. A node shutdown can be either graceful or non-graceful.
The Graceful Node Shutd…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curbing Connection Churn in Zuul]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2feb273a3598</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/curbing-connection-churn-in-zuul-2feb273a3598?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix’s Zuul Gateway eliminated tens of millions of connections and reduced almost all connection churn to backends]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join AWS Hybrid Cloud & Edge Day to Learn How to Deploy Your Applications in the Everywhere Cloud]]></title>
        <id>6a2ca8d5448ccbca3f8b3089d50548e5662fbc19</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/join-aws-hybrid-cloud-edge-day-to-learn-how-to-deploy-your-applications-in-the-everywhere-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editor’s note: The live event has ended, but you may still watch the video on demand on Twitch. In his keynote of AWS re:Invent 2021, Dr. Werner Vogels shared the insight of how “the everywhere cloud” is bringing AWS to new locales through AWS hardware and services and spotlighted it as one of his tech […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M7a General Purpose Instances Powered by 4th Gen AMD EPYC Processors]]></title>
        <id>aa69e34d695f6dcbf492a7e3a606a2ef16eeda02</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-m7a-general-purpose-instances-powered-by-4th-gen-amd-epyc-processors/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T22:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2021, we launched Amazon EC2 M6a instances, powered by 3rd Gen AMD EPYC (Milan) processors, running at frequencies up to 3.6 GHz, which offer you up to 35 percent improvement in price performance compared to M5a instances. Many customers who run workloads that are dependent on x86 instructions, such as SAP, are looking […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching Camunda – An Interview with Achim Dannecker]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=88857</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/teaching-camunda-interview-achim-dannecker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about why Achim Dannecker uses Camunda in his classroom, how students work with it and what he hopes everyone can take away from his course.
The post Teaching Camunda – An Interview with Achim Dannecker appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: pkgs.k8s.io: Introducing Kubernetes Community-Owned Package Repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/15/pkgs-k8s-io-introduction/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/15/pkgs-k8s-io-introduction/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Marko Mudrinić (Kubermatic)
On behalf of Kubernetes SIG Release, I am very excited to introduce the
Kubernetes community-owned software
repositories for Debian and RPM packages: pkgs.k8s.io! The new package
repositories are replacement for the Google-hosted package repositories
(apt.kubernetes.io and yum.kubernetes.io) that we've been using since
Kubernetes v1.5.
This blog post contains information about these new package repositories,
what does it mean to you as an end user, and how to migrate to the new
repositories.
ℹ️ Update (August 31, 2023): the legacy Google-hosted repositories are deprecated
and will be frozen starting with September 13, 2023.
Check out the deprecation announcement
for more details about this change.
What you need to know about the new package repositories?…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STUDY: Socially aware temporally causal decoder recommender systems]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/study-socially-aware-temporally-causal.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/study-socially-aware-temporally-causal.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T19:59:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eltayeb Ahmed, Research Engineer, and Subhrajit Roy, Senior Research Scientist, Google Research




Reading has many benefits for young students, such as better linguistic and life skills, and reading for pleasure has been shown to correlate with academic success. Furthermore students have reported improved emotional wellbeing from reading, as well as better general knowledge and better understanding of other cultures. With the vast amount of reading material both online and off, finding age-appropriate, relevant and engaging content can be a challenging task, but helping students do so is a necessary step to engage them in reading. Effective recommendations that present students with relevant reading material helps keep students reading, and this is where machine learning (ML) c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform integrations with ServiceNow, GitHub, Confluent, VMware, Cisco, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-servicenow-github-confluent-vmware-cisco-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-servicenow-github-confluent-vmware-cisco-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Cloud and community integration partners provide more options to automate and secure cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.28: Planternetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/15/kubernetes-v1-28-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/15/kubernetes-v1-28-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes v1.28 Release Team
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.28 Planternetes, the second release of 2023!
This release consists of 45 enhancements. Of those enhancements, 19 are entering Alpha, 14 have graduated to Beta, and 12 have graduated to Stable.
Release Theme And Logo
Kubernetes v1.28: Planternetes
The theme for Kubernetes v1.28 is Planternetes.
Each Kubernetes release is the culmination of the hard work of thousands of individuals from our community. The people behind this release come from a wide range of backgrounds, some of us industry veterans, parents, others students and newcomers to open-source. We combine our unique experience to create a collective artifact with global impact.
Much like a garden, our release has ever-changing growth, challenges and oppor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – Amazon MWAA, EMR Studio, Generative AI, and More – August 14, 2023]]></title>
        <id>095ee594cacd2042f3e53487e4fe1b5590a0d5e7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-mwaa-emr-studio-generative-ai-and-more-august-14-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T17:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I enjoyed a few days off in California to get a dose of vitamin sea, a lot has happened in the AWS universe. Let’s take a look together! Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my attention: Amazon MWAA now supports Apache Airflow version 2.6 – Amazon Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Secrets extends secret sync to GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-secrets-extends-secret-sync-to-github-actions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-secrets-extends-secret-sync-to-github-actions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Secrets extends secret sync capabilities to GitHub Actions secrets, improves secret versioning, and adds a tutorial on using HCP Vault Secrets with Terraform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interfaces Management with Ansible validated content using the network.interfaces collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/interfaces-management-with-ansible-validated-content-using-the-network.interfaces-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/interfaces-management-with-ansible-validated-content-using-the-network.interfaces-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
 
At AnsibleFest 2022, we announced a new addition to the content ecosystem offered through Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform: Ansible validated content. Ansible validated content is use case-focused and provides an expert-guided path for performing operational tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwini Mhatre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG ContribEx]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/14/sig-contribex-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/14/sig-contribex-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fyka Ansari
Welcome to the world of Kubernetes and its vibrant contributor
community! In this blog post, we'll be shining a spotlight on the
Special Interest Group for Contributor
Experience
(SIG ContribEx), an essential component of the Kubernetes project.
SIG ContribEx in Kubernetes is responsible for developing and
maintaining a healthy and productive community of contributors to the
project. This involves identifying and addressing bottlenecks that may
hinder the project's growth and feature velocity, such as pull request
latency and the number of open pull requests and issues.
SIG ContribEx works to improve the overall contributor experience by
creating and maintaining guidelines, tools, and processes that
facilitate collaboration and communication among contributors. They
als…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>