<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-02-26T00:19:27.708Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-02-26T00:19:27.708Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The grey goo]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48621</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872136446/0/sethsblog~The-grey-goo/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-25T09:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we take a big enough dataset… Add to it machine learning and autotune and the race to fit in and reach the masses… We end up with a relentless march toward mediocrity. Mediocre is another word for average. It has always happened as industries matured (whether it’s Motown or blenders). But then, often, a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A transformative summer]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48567</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872078612/0/sethsblog~A-transformative-summer/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T10:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Living indoors, connected to a screen, it’s easy for the months and years to blur together. The seasons used to matter more. But for young adults, they still do. Transitions are built around the seasons, and the headlong rush to a career is still sometimes interrupted by months where there’s a chance to reset and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=447091</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/02/java-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good code follows certain rules, and knowing them increases your chances of success. We’d like to share some Java best practices that will help you on your way. We’ll cover the must-know tips and tricks, from broad advice on software development to Java- and project-specific know-how. Let’s get started! General Let’s keep the following general […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Mariasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picking the Perfect Process for Your Camunda POC]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101958</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/picking-perfect-process-camunda-proof-of-concept/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picking the right process to use for your proof-of-concept is critical. In the next post in our series on creating a Camunda POC, learn how to choose the right one,
The post Picking the Perfect Process for Your Camunda POC appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI models coming soon to Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>308fb7192ffb87eae22e5e1a861fa7efc2aa36a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/mistral-ai-models-coming-soon-to-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI, an AI company based in France, is on a mission to elevate publicly available models to state-of-the-art performance. They specialize in creating fast and secure large language models (LLMs) that can be used for various tasks, from chatbots to code generation. We’re pleased to announce that two high-performing Mistral AI models, Mistral 7B […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from Git 2.44]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-23-highlights-from-git-2-44/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-23-highlights-from-git-2-44/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The first Git release of 2024 is here! Take a look at some of our highlights on what's new in Git 2.44.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-23-highlights-from-git-2-44/">Highlights from Git 2.44</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the difference? Elastic and Splunk data tiers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-splunk-data-tiers-differences</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-splunk-data-tiers-differences"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T15:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post provides a brief overview of the key differences between the Elastic and Splunk data management offerings and will help you understand the key factors that affect the performance and co...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugo Sangiorgi,Matt Wehle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the difference? Elastic and Splunk data tiers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-splunk-data-tiers-differences</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-splunk-data-tiers-differences"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T15:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of data management, terms like Hot, Warm, and Cold get tossed around frequently when discussing how data should be made available and/or retained given different performance requirements.
With unique, sometimes conflicting terminology associated with both Elastic® and Splunk’s offerings, our aim is to unravel these differences and present a clearer picture to enable strategic, cost-effective approaches to your data management needs.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt459380602e60b0bb/65d618698d55b07c8c6159b0/image2.png,image2.png

Layer A: Data is usually first written here, and we have the best possible performance for indexing and search.

Layer B: Data is moved here from other layers and it is searchable, although the performance is not as good a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugo Sangiorgi,Matt Wehle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI for PHP: How to Make AI Assistant Generate Test Implementations]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=447243</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2024/02/ai-for-php-how-to-make-ai-assistant-generate-test-implementations/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T11:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We started this series by looking at how JetBrains AI Assistant can generate tests from an existing implementation. But what if we want to use AI Assistant the other way around? What if we want to take a more test-driven-development approach, writing our tests first, and having AI Assistant generate an implementation for us? Let’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And it can also do that]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48600</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872005994/0/sethsblog~And-it-can-also-do-that/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T09:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you were around when the Model T was first announced, you could have built the organizations that became Disney, McDonald’s and Holiday Inn, all of which were powered by cheap, plentiful cars. You could have become a major developer of suburbs, mortgage banking and even pop music record labels (car radios changed the way […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity Roadmap Q1–Q2 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=448028</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2024/02/teamcity-roadmap-q1-q2-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T09:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, we introduced a number of highly anticipated features to TeamCity. The long-awaited dark theme is now available in both TeamCity Cloud and On-Premises. We’ve also introduced agent terminals that allow users to open remote terminals on agent machines directly from the TeamCity UI.  The Matrix Build feature in TeamCity now allows you to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.0.6, 1.1.3 and 1.2 M2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/23/spring-modulith-1-0-6-1-1-3-and-1-2-m2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/23/spring-modulith-1-0-6-1-1-3-and-1-2-m2-released"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring AI 0.8.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/23/spring-ai-0-8-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/23/spring-ai-0-8-0-released"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Pollack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Timefold Solver AI lead Geoffrey De Smet]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/23/a-bootiful-podcast-timefold-solver-ai-lead-geoffrey-de-smet</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/23/a-bootiful-podcast-timefold-solver-ai-lead-geoffrey-de-smet"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orbital Argument]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2898/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2898/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/orbital_argument.png" title="&quot;Some people say light is waves, and some say it's particles, so I bet light is some in-between thing that's both wave and particle depending on how you look at it. Am I right?&quot; &quot;YES, BUT YOU SHOULDN'T BE!&quot;" alt="&quot;Some people say light is waves, and some say it's particles, so I bet light is some in-between thing that's both wave and particle depending on how you look at it. Am I right?&quot; &quot;YES, BUT YOU SHOULDN'T BE!&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VideoPrism: A foundational visual encoder for video understanding]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/videoprism-foundational-visual-encoder.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/videoprism-foundational-visual-encoder.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Long Zhao, Senior Research Scientist, and Ting Liu, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research




An astounding number of videos are available on the Web, covering a variety of content from everyday moments people share to historical moments to scientific observations, each of which contains a unique record of the world. The right tools could help researchers analyze these videos, transforming how we understand the world around us.

 

Videos offer dynamic visual content far more rich than static images, capturing movement, changes, and dynamic relationships between entities. Analyzing this complexity, along with the immense diversity of publicly available video data, demands models that go beyond traditional image understanding. Consequently, many of the approaches that be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI code generation works]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-22-how-ai-code-generation-works/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-22-how-ai-code-generation-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore the capabilities and benefits of AI code generation, and how it can improve the developer experience for your enterprise.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-22-how-ai-code-generation-works/">How AI code generation works</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Livestream – Debug Like a Pro: JavaScript Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=447523</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2024/02/livestream-debug-like-a-pro-javascript-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T17:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on Tuesday, March 5, at 11:00 am EST / 5:00 pm CET (check other timezones) for our new livestream, “Debug Like a Pro: JavaScript Edition”. Developers write code, run code, and when they hit problems, they debug code. Or do they? WebStorm’s debugger is powerful, but it’s also easy and user-friendly. We want […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Aganezova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2024.1 EAP 6: Improved Workflow for Logs, Inline Breakpoints, In-Editor Code Review, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=447285</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/02/intellij-idea-2024-1-eap-6/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T16:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2024.1 EAP 6 is here! This new build is packed with a bunch of updates anticipated for the next major release. Highlights include an enhanced user experience with logs, advanced debugging capabilities, and improved integration with version control systems. You can download the new version from our website, update directly from the IDE […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insider newsletter digest: Cook up a controller with GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-22-insider-newsletter-digest-cook-up-a-controller-with-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-22-insider-newsletter-digest-cook-up-a-controller-with-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T16:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Whether you're coding up a storm or cooking up code, building a controller function with AI is your secret sauce to a flavorful app.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-22-insider-newsletter-digest-cook-up-a-controller-with-github-copilot/">Insider newsletter digest: Cook up a controller with GitHub Copilot</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.12.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-12-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-12-2-released"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T15:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.

...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Snehal Adlinge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.12.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-12-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-12-2-released"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T15:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.12.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.12.2 over 8.12.1 and 8.11.x releases.
The 8.12.2 patch release contains a performance issue fix in the Elastic Security Solution. Please see our Elastic Security Solution release notes for more details. 
The 8.12.2 patch release also contains a fix for an upgrade issue where, in some cases, upgrade to 8.12.0 and 8.12.1 may fail. Please see our Elasticsearch release notes for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Snehal Adlinge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Has Received Its SOC2 Audit Report]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=security&amp;p=447543</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/security/2024/02/jetbrains-has-received-its-soc2-audit-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T14:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOC 2 (Service Organization Control II) is a comprehensive audit framework developed by the American Institute of CPAs (AICPA). This framework assesses the controls a service organization has in place in terms of security, availability, processing integrity, confidentiality, and privacy. A SOC 2 Type II report evaluates the design and suitability of these controls. This […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilya Pleskunin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finally Something Fun for Your Inbox – DataLead Season 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=447215</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2024/02/22/finally-something-fun-for-your-inbox-datalead-season-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T11:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there! At Datalore, we’re launching the first season of DataLead. It’s a unique kind of newsletter – like a TV show but about data. Get ready to dive into the lives of our two DataLeaders, Sarita and José, as they navigate the data-related challenges of 2024. For Sarita, a lead data analyst at a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Queued]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46803</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/871932524/0/sethsblog~Queued/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T09:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s sort of the opposite of “cued.” In addition to being delightful to spell, the idea of work that’s queued up is energizing. The chapter ahead of schedule, the process in place for the next quarter, the continued commitment to learning… It is locked, loaded and ready to go. It’s work that requires timing and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.3.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/22/spring-boot-3-3-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/22/spring-boot-3-3-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Frederick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/22/spring-boot-3-2-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/22/spring-boot-3-2-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Frederick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.9 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/22/spring-boot-3-1-9-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/22/spring-boot-3-1-9-available-now"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Workflow Orchestration? Guide with Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101616</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/what-is-workflow-orchestration-guide-use-cases/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what workflow orchestration is, how it works, its benefits, and how you can get started using it today.
The post What is Workflow Orchestration? Guide with Use Cases appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A look into the Kubernetes Book Club]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/02/22/k8s-book-club/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/02/22/k8s-book-club/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
Learning Kubernetes and the entire ecosystem of technologies around it is not without its
challenges. In this interview, we will talk with Carlos Santana
(AWS) to learn a bit more about how he created the
Kubernetes Book Club, how it works, and
how anyone can join in to take advantage of a community-based learning experience.

Frederico Muñoz (FSM): Hello Carlos, thank you so much for your availability. To start with,
could you tell us a bit about yourself?
Carlos Santana (CS): Of course. My experience in deploying Kubernetes in production six
years ago opened the door for me to join Knative and then contribute to
Kubernetes through the Release Team. Working on upstream Kubernetes has been one of the best
experiences I've had in open-source. Over the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2024.1 EAP 6: In-editor Code Review]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=447024</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2024/02/2024-1-eap-6/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T22:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our new EAP build for PyCharm 2024.1 is now available for you to download! This new build is packed with a bunch of updates to the integration with version control systems. You can download the new version from our website, update directly from the IDE or via the free Toolbox App, or use snaps for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advances in private training for production on-device language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/advances-in-private-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/advances-in-private-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zheng Xu, Research Scientist, and Yanxiang Zhang, Software Engineer, Google




Language models (LMs) trained to predict the next word given input text are the key technology for many applications [1, 2]. In Gboard, LMs are used to improve users’ typing experience by supporting features like next word prediction (NWP), Smart Compose, smart completion and suggestion, slide to type, and proofread. Deploying models on users’ devices rather than enterprise servers has advantages like lower latency and better privacy for model usage. While training on-device models directly from user data effectively improves the utility performance for applications such as NWP and smart text selection, protecting the privacy of user data for model training is important. 









Gboard features powe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 AI search trends impacting developers in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ai-search-trends-developers</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ai-search-trends-developers"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T18:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After an incredibly fast-moving 2023, what does the future hold for AI and search? We assessed the current state of search and weighed in on a few key themes on the horizon for all things AI in 2024....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Meiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 AI search trends impacting developers in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ai-search-trends-developers</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ai-search-trends-developers"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T18:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After an incredibly fast-moving 2023, what does the future hold for AI and search? Conversational generative AI leapt into the public consciousness over the past year, and organizations scrambled to define their strategy for capitalizing on the trend. AI-boosted relevance is reshaping the way users experience search — and elevating their expectations for the quality of the interaction. 
In a recent discussion with product and engineering leaders from Adobe, Hugging Face, You.com, and Elastic, we assessed the current state of search and weighed in on these AI-fueled trends. Here are a few key themes they see on the horizon for all things AI in 2024:
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt31b2b145b770ea9e/65ca676cf48bc2462850ec23/top-5-trends-search-ai-2024.png,top-5-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Meiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Terminal (Beta) Is Now in JetBrains IDEs]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=446724</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/02/the-new-terminal-beta-is-now-in-jetbrains-ides/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T18:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR: The new terminal (Beta) is now in JetBrains IDEs and will be available in the new UI starting from the 2024.1 version of the IDEs. You can switch between the old and new terminal in Settings/Preferences | Tools | Terminal | Enable New Terminal. Currently, it supports only Bash, Zsh, and PowerShell, with other […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Shabalina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HelloWorld’ and ‘main()’ meet minimalistic]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=445755</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/02/helloworld-and-main-meet-minimalistic/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T18:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Just ignore the terms class, public, static and args[] for now; we’ll talk about it later”. If you have ever mentioned these lines to a new Java student, who is about to execute their first ‘HelloWorld’ program, know that this is changing. If you are that student, well, congratulations, getting started is simpler in Java […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mala Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to stay safe from repo-jacking]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-21-how-to-stay-safe-from-repo-jacking/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-21-how-to-stay-safe-from-repo-jacking/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T17:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Repo-jacking is a specific type of supply chain attack. This blog post explains what it is, what the risk is, and what you can do to stay safe.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-21-how-to-stay-safe-from-repo-jacking/">How to stay safe from repo-jacking</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving memory allocation with Libbeat output client and Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-memory-allocation-libbeat-output-client-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-memory-allocation-libbeat-output-client-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T16:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Filebeat or any other beat is publishing events to a remote Elasticsearch, it relies on its _bulk API, meaning that Beats doesn’t only make requests to Elasticsearch but also parses its responses...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandros Sapranidis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving memory allocation with Libbeat output client and Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-memory-allocation-libbeat-output-client-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-memory-allocation-libbeat-output-client-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T16:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our journey of improving performance is not complete without diving into the path events follow toward their destination. When Filebeat or any other beat is publishing events to a remote Elasticsearch®, it relies on its _bulk API. This means that Beats doesn’t only make requests to Elasticsearch, but it also parses its responses, which increases the memory utilization as a result. 

Previously, we showed how we managed to reduce Beats allocation by reducing the use of Logger in the event’s hot path, which reduced the overall allocated memory.

In this post, we will dive into the path of the publishing method and discuss how we managed to improve the memory allocation, which results in a direct increase of speed.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blta44802b59581cce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandros Sapranidis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering all developers to build without barriers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-21-empowering-all-developers-to-build-without-barriers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-21-empowering-all-developers-to-build-without-barriers/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T15:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub has been awarded the 2024 Axe Accessibility at Scale Award from Deque Systems. Read more about how we’ve implemented accessibility at scale.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-21-empowering-all-developers-to-build-without-barriers/">Empowering all developers to build without barriers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第247話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:2550668106003104547</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/2550668106003104547"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use AI Assistant to Generate Test Data For .NET Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=423846</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/02/21/jetbrains-ai-assistant-generate-test-data-for-dotnet/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T13:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In software development, writing tests is equivalent to exercising and eating vegetables; everyone knows they should be doing more but likely don’t do enough. One of the reasons folks avoid writing tests is the tedium of constructing test cases that help make a test valuable and worth maintaining. A test that is too simple can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spire confusion]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46782</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/871852679/0/sethsblog~Spire-confusion/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When architects show off their work, or propose a bold new building complex or even ask for a zoning variance, the public sees the external photos. The tall spire, the innovative use of glass, the weird hole in the center of the building. And when a car company shows off a new model at a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding AI search algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/understanding-ai-search-algorithms</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/understanding-ai-search-algorithms"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T01:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock the potential of AI search algorithms. Understand the importance and applications of these algorithms, explore their key elements, and discover the different types available. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Taylor,Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding AI search algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/understanding-ai-search-algorithms</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/understanding-ai-search-algorithms"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T01:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence tools are everywhere, and it’s no mystery why. They can carry out a huge variety of tasks and find the solutions to many everyday problems. But these apps are only as good as their AI search algorithm.
In simple terms, an AI search algorithm is the decision-making formula an AI tool uses to find the optimal solution to your specific problem. Search algorithms may make trade-offs between speed, relevance, or another weighted factor. It takes into account the query’s constraints and goals and presents back what it has calculated to be the best solution.
In this post, we’ll go through:

The importance and applications of AI search algorithms

Elements of AI search algorithms

The different types of AI search algorithms

AI search algorithm use cases

The challenges and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Taylor,Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.2.2, 6.1.7, and 5.8.10 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/21/spring-security-6-2-2-6-1-7-and-5-8-10-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/21/spring-security-6-2-2-6-1-7-and-5-8-10-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Cummings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring LDAP 3.1.4 and 3.2.2 are available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/21/spring-ldap-3-1-4-and-3-2-2-are-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/21/spring-ldap-3-1-4-and-3-2-2-are-available"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Cummings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.5 and 5.1.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/21/spring-batch-5-0-5-and-5-1-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/21/spring-batch-5-0-5-and-5-1-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmoud Ben Hassine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.3 M1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/21/spring-for-graphql-1-3-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/21/spring-for-graphql-1-3-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rossen Stoyanchev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christine Weng on why she took time to explore and reflect before pivoting from accounting to tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-explore-reflect-before-pivoting-into-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-explore-reflect-before-pivoting-into-tech"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christine reflected on what she wanted in her career before making the switch to software development. See how she pivoted from accounting to software engineering....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know the Elastic Community series: Meet Wagner Souza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/get-to-know-the-elastic-community-series-meet-wagner-souza</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/get-to-know-the-elastic-community-series-meet-wagner-souza"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wagner Souza has been working in the information security area for five years. In this blog, he delves into his journey with Elastic, from his initial experience to participating in community events a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ully Sampaio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christine Weng on why she took time to explore and reflect before pivoting from accounting to tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-explore-reflect-before-pivoting-into-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-explore-reflect-before-pivoting-into-tech"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christine Weng began her career in accounting — tax accounting to be exact. But during her first year in a full-time accounting role she realized she was more interested in the technology side of things.
“Ever since I started actually working, I realized I enjoyed automations, problem solving, and process development,” Christine says.
She took the time to explore her options by working with a group at her company that did tech consulting, but was still focused on accounting.
“Exploring isn’t a bad thing,” Christine says. “If you try something and you don’t like it then, at least you know.”
Christine’s interests stem from pain points in her previous job, she says. The tools she was working with didn’t have certain features and there weren't the resources to fix that.
She spent a few years t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know the Elastic Community series: Meet Wagner Souza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/get-to-know-the-elastic-community-series-meet-wagner-souza</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/get-to-know-the-elastic-community-series-meet-wagner-souza"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wagner Souza has been working in the information security area for five years, specializing in computer network security and processes involving ISO/IEC 27001 audit projects and personal data protection (LGPD/GDPR). He is part of a Security Operation Center (SOC) team focused on monitoring, threat detection, and vulnerability management.
When did you first embrace Elastic as a technology?
In 2021, I was challenged to apply information security knowledge using Elastic Security in monitoring and threat detection activities in our clients' environments. This experience was very interesting as it gave me great learning and a desire to explore further the power of the Elastic Stack in security operations.
What is the most memorable moment in your career?
It was the recognition I received from t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ully Sampaio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Light Leap Years]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2897/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2897/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/light_leap_years.png" title="When Pope Gregory XIII briefly shortened the light-year in 1582, it led to navigational chaos and the loss of several Papal starships." alt="When Pope Gregory XIII briefly shortened the light-year in 1582, it led to navigational chaos and the loss of several Papal starships." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I use Boundary to build automation for live streams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-i-use-boundary-to-build-automation-for-live-streams</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-i-use-boundary-to-build-automation-for-live-streams"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how HashiCorp Developer Advocate Rosemary Wang uses HashiCorp Boundary on live streams to automate access to servers and record commands to build into future automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy/lazy tech journalism]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48508</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/871744184/0/sethsblog~Easylazy-tech-journalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choose either one: When a new technology comes out, review it breathlessly. Explain without nuance or caution how it will instantly change the world. Go into the details of this first instantiation of it and assume it will never change, it’s done, here we go. When a new technology comes out, describe the scam that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Jeneeta O’Connor builds community at work — and beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-build-community-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-build-community-at-work"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To find community in a new place, Jeneeta O’Connor dives right in. Hear why community and connection is so important to her and get her tips for creating your own. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Jeneeta O’Connor builds community at work — and beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-build-community-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-build-community-at-work"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To find community in a new place, Jeneeta O’Connor dives right in. There’s no point in having a toe in the water, she says.
When Jeneeta joined Elastic® in 2023, that’s exactly what she did. She created a list of people she wanted to reach out to and became a member of an ERG right away. She also signed up for the coffee connects facilitated by Slack’s Donut plug in. 
In previous roles, she found success meeting co-workers for coffee, and going to events where she could network. Since taking these intentional steps to find connection worked well before, she took the same approach at Elastic to develop her own sense of community.
“I wanted to immediately get embedded in the culture,” Jeneeta says.
Jeneeta has always been purposeful about building connections and broadening her reach, someth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing Rally: Running your first Elasticsearch performance benchmark and air-gapped]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/installing-rally-elasticsearch-performance-benchmark-air-gapped</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/installing-rally-elasticsearch-performance-benchmark-air-gapped"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T19:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ES Rally is a proven tool to benchmark Elasticsearch performance. In this blog, we will walk you through installing and running your first race....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing Rally: Running your first Elasticsearch performance benchmark and air-gapped]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/installing-rally-elasticsearch-performance-benchmark-air-gapped</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/installing-rally-elasticsearch-performance-benchmark-air-gapped"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T19:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rally, also known as ES Rally, is the benchmarking tool that Elastic® relies on to identify Elasticsearch® performance improvements, regressions, and more. It is run nightly against a nightly build of Elasticsearch. You can also use it to benchmark your Elasticsearch cluster and identify any performance issues related to your setup. If you want to ingest 5TB of data daily, follow this blog post and the entire series to identify how you can ensure that your hardware is capable of this. If your workload is more on the search side, we will also cover that!
Installing Rally
All of the installation steps are described in the official Rally documentation. You don’t need a Java installation when not benchmarking source build. This blog post series focuses on benchmarking an Elasticsearch running …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — AWS Control Tower new API, TLS 1.3 with API Gateway, Private Marketplace Catalogs, and more — February 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>b59bdf9a07666673edfdba0242f35b6312ab73cb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-control-tower-new-api-tls-1-3-with-api-gateway-private-marketplace-catalogs-and-more-february-19-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T18:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past week, our service teams have continued to innovate on your behalf, and a lot has happened in the Amazon Web Services (AWS) universe that I want to tell you about. I’ll also share about all the AWS Community events and initiatives that are happening around the world. Let’s dive in! Last week’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Rider and the .NET Aspire Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=438860</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/02/19/jetbrains-rider-and-the-net-aspire-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T14:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the .NET 8 announcement, developers were surprised to learn of a new opinionated, cloud-ready stack for building observable distributed applications. Of course, we’re talking about .NET Aspire, a solution of tools and patterns delivered to developers via the NuGet workloads found in newer versions of the .NET SDK, similar to Multi-Application UI or MAUI. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make or buy?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46774</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/871659551/0/sethsblog~Make-or-buy/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T09:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a writer, it probably doesn’t pay to chop down trees and make your own paper, or even to set up a little machine shop to make your own pens. That’s pretty obvious. Should the smoothie shop make its own almond milk? It’s pretty clear that Starbucks should have a team of architects, lawyers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crossword Constructors]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2896/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2896/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/crossword_constructors.png" title="Also, we would really appreciate it if you could prominently refer to it as an 'eHit'." alt="Also, we would really appreciate it if you could prominently refer to it as an 'eHit'." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The illusion of concern]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46772</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/871470614/0/sethsblog~The-illusion-of-concern/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-18T10:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When organizations reach scale, digital interactions belie our expectation that someone in charge actually gives a damn. Once there’s math to do, the CFO does the math. It quickly reveals that no, the search engine shouldn’t bother having a customer support team. That UPS or Fedex should simply hang up on you if your package […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problems and the clover]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43868</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/870671705/0/sethsblog~Problems-and-the-clover/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T09:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Systemic and existential problems dance their way through three circles: If it’s not solvable, we’ll pretend it’s not a problem. If the cultural cost of solving the problem is too high, we’ll pretend there’s no solution. People don’t spend a lot of time planning for death because there’s no solution to it and the social […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Pipelines deprecated tasks retirement schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68388</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-pipelines-deprecated-tasks-retirement-schedule/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T15:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Pipelines includes around 150 build & release tasks as well as many more task extensions. Various included tasks have multiple (major) versions bringing the total to over included 200 tasks.
The post Azure Pipelines deprecated tasks retirement schedule appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How NatWest Built a Center of Excellence to Improve Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101178</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/learn-how-natwest-built-a-center-of-excellence-to-improve-process-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how NatWest accelerated their process automation and orchestration, even as their usage grew, with a CoE using Camunda.
The post Learn How NatWest Built a Center of Excellence to Improve Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strengthening small utilities: The power of public-private partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/small-utilities-power-of-public-private-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/small-utilities-power-of-public-private-partnership"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T14:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattacks against water utilities show the vulnerability of local entities dependent on operational technology. Private and public collaboration, such as the Elastic and Dragos partnership, can be ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strengthening small utilities: The power of public-private partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/small-utilities-power-of-public-private-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/small-utilities-power-of-public-private-partnership"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T14:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of recent cyber attacks against US water utilities, the vulnerability of local entities dependent on operational technology (OT) has been starkly highlighted. This danger was further emphasized last week when Congress held a hearing titled Securing Operational Technology: A Deep Dive into the Water Sector. Witnesses at the hearing painted a stark picture of the significant cybersecurity risks facing small utility companies today.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trading trust]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48545</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/870579488/0/sethsblog~Trading-trust/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T09:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Brookings Institution did a fascinating survey series over the last five years. I have two takeways from this: The first is that focused and persistent propaganda is able to shift public opinion about institutions they don’t have direct interaction with. The more important one is this: Many companies, particularly tech ones, are deliberately trading […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasure Chests]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2895/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2895/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/treasure_chests.png" title="[earlier] &quot;Your vintage-style handmade chest business is struggling. But I have a plan.&quot;" alt="[earlier] &quot;Your vintage-style handmade chest business is struggling. But I have a plan.&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Modeling Faster with the New Simplified Modeling Canvas]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101261</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/model-faster-simplified-modeling-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T21:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out our cleaner and more intuitive modeling UI, coming later this month.
The post Start Modeling Faster with the New Simplified Modeling Canvas appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build code security skills with the GitHub Secure Code Game]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-15-build-code-security-skills-with-the-github-secure-code-game/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-15-build-code-security-skills-with-the-github-secure-code-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T21:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn to find and fix security issues while having fun with Secure Code Game, now with new challenges focusing on JavaScript, Python, Go, and GitHub Actions!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-15-build-code-security-skills-with-the-github-secure-code-game/">Build code security skills with the GitHub Secure Code Game</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of SSH-RSA support for Azure Repos]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68534</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/ssh-rsa-deprecation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T17:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Repos provides two methods for users to access a git repository in Azure Repos – HTTPS and SSH. To use SSH, you need to create a key pair using one of the supported encryption methods. In the past we’ve been supporting only SSH-RSA and we’ve asked users to enable the SSH-RSA here.
The post End of SSH-RSA support for Azure Repos appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bohdan Janousek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform integrations with Wiz, Cisco, Palo Alto Networks, Couchbase, VMware, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-wiz-cisco-palo-alto-networks-couchbase-vmware</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-wiz-cisco-palo-alto-networks-couchbase-vmware"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[17 new Terraform integrations from 14 partners provide more options to automate and secure cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUnit Attachments Support for Publish Test Results]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67933</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/junit-attachments-support-for-publish-test-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T16:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve recently made some improvements to the Publish Test Results task in Azure Pipelines. This task now supports file attachments when publishing test results from a JUnit report.
The post JUnit Attachments Support for Publish Test Results appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Paquette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-14-github-availability-report-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-github-availability-report-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T20:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In January, we experienced three incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-github-availability-report-january-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: January 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning the importance of training data under concept drift]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/learning-importance-of-training-data.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/learning-importance-of-training-data.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T18:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nishant Jain, Pre-doctoral Researcher, and Pradeep Shenoy, Research Scientist, Google Research




The constantly changing nature of the world around us poses a significant challenge for the development of AI models. Often, models are trained on longitudinal data with the hope that the training data used will accurately represent inputs the model may receive in the future. More generally, the default assumption that all training data are equally relevant often breaks in practice. For example, the figure below shows images from the CLEAR nonstationary learning benchmark, and it illustrates how visual features of objects evolve significantly over a 10 year span (a phenomenon we refer to as slow concept drift), posing a challenge for object categorization models. 








Sample ima…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing security vulnerabilities with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-14-fixing-security-vulnerabilities-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-fixing-security-vulnerabilities-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A peek under the hood of GitHub Advanced Security code scanning autofix.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-fixing-security-vulnerabilities-with-ai/">Fixing security vulnerabilities with AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault integrations with New Relic, Cloudbees, Coder, and more continue to strengthen customer security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-new-relic-cloudbees-coder-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-new-relic-cloudbees-coder-and-more"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight new HashiCorp Vault ecosystem integrations extend security use cases for customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DP-Auditorium: A flexible library for auditing differential privacy]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/dp-auditorium-flexible-library-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/dp-auditorium-flexible-library-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T22:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mónica Ribero Díaz, Research Scientist, Google Research





Differential privacy (DP) is a property of randomized mechanisms that limit the influence of any individual user’s information while processing and analyzing data. DP offers a robust solution to address growing concerns about data protection, enabling technologies across industries and government applications (e.g., the US census) without compromising individual user identities.  As its adoption increases, it’s important to identify the potential risks of developing mechanisms with faulty implementations. Researchers have recently found errors in the mathematical proofs of private mechanisms, and their implementations. For example, researchers compared six sparse vector technique (SVT) variations and found that only two…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[February patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68473</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/february-patches-for-azure-devops-server-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T21:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 Patch 2
The post February patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequential A/B Testing Keeps the World Streaming Netflix
Part 1: Continuous Data]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/cba6c7ed49df</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/sequential-a-b-testing-keeps-the-world-streaming-netflix-part-1-continuous-data-cba6c7ed49df?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T19:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lindon, Chris Sanden, Vache Shirikian, Yanjun Liu, Minal Mishra, Martin Tingley]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing npm registry services to GitHub Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-13-bringing-npm-registry-services-to-github-codespaces/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-13-bringing-npm-registry-services-to-github-codespaces/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T18:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The npm engineering team recently transitioned to using GitHub Codespaces for local development for npm registry services. This shift to Codespaces has substantially reduced the friction of our inner development loop and boosted developer productivity.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-13-bringing-npm-registry-services-to-github-codespaces/">Bringing npm registry services to GitHub Codespaces</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Alpha Release February 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101141</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/camunda-alpha-release-february-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to announce the February 2024 alpha release of Camunda. Check out what's new.
The post Camunda Alpha Release February 2024 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering advancements of AI in the open: Apply now to GitHub Accelerator]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-13-powering-advancements-of-ai-in-the-open-apply-now-to-github-accelerator/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-13-powering-advancements-of-ai-in-the-open-apply-now-to-github-accelerator/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T17:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Funding AI advancements in the open, and opening applications for second Accelerator cohort.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-13-powering-advancements-of-ai-in-the-open-apply-now-to-github-accelerator/">Powering advancements of AI in the open: Apply now to GitHub Accelerator</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing SafeTest: A Novel Approach to Front End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/37f9f88c152d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/introducing-safetest-a-novel-approach-to-front-end-testing-37f9f88c152d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T16:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workload identity federation for Azure deployments is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68479</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/workload-identity-federation-for-azure-deployments-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T07:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September, we announced the ability to configure Azure service connections that do not need a secret. Azure service connections that use workload identity federation are easier to manage and more secure. Many customers have adopted this feature and we’re excited to announce it is now generally available!
The post Workload identity federation for Azure deployments is now generally available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planning Your Camunda Proof of Concept]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101054</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/planning-your-camunda-proof-of-concept/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T22:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over half of software projects fail. A well-planned and executed POC makes a difference, and this post will help show you how to plan yours.
The post Planning Your Camunda Proof of Concept appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock now supports Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL and Cohere embedding models]]></title>
        <id>88d3cbd7b505e228dadab86f0501d5938c543301</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/knowledge-bases-for-amazon-bedrock-now-supports-amazon-aurora-postgresql-and-cohere-embedding-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T21:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During AWS re:Invent 2023, we announced the general availability of Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock. With a knowledge base, you can securely connect foundation models (FMs) in Amazon Bedrock to your company data for Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG). In my previous post, I described how Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock manages the end-to-end RAG workflow […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Happy Lunar New Year, IaC generator, NFL’s digital athlete, AWS Cloud Clubs, and more — February 12, 2024]]></title>
        <id>568484dcfa30bc001b0bf56c13972382e5ce2537</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-happy-lunar-new-year-iac-generator-nfls-digital-athlete-aws-cloud-clubs-and-more-february-12-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T20:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Lunar New Year! Wishing you a year filled with joy, success, and endless opportunities! May the Year of the Dragon bring uninterrupted connections and limitless growth 🐉 ☁️ In case you missed it, here’s outstanding news you need to know as you plan your year in early 2024. AWS was named as a Leader […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform gains upgrades for module tests, explorer, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-gains-upgrades-for-module-tests-explorer-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-gains-upgrades-for-module-tests-explorer-and-more"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest Terraform Cloud and Enterprise enhancements help users leverage high-quality modules, monitor their workspace health, minimize management overhead, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing HashiCorp tools in Alpine Linux containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/installing-hashicorp-tools-in-alpine-linux-containers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/installing-hashicorp-tools-in-alpine-linux-containers"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the installation and verification workflow for any Linux distribution that does not include HashiCorp software in its package repository.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Artificial Intelligence can Enhance Your Business Process]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=100753</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/how-artificial-intelligence-can-enhance-business-process/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T22:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can AI and automation help you improve your business processes? Learn how AI can effectively enable process orchestration.
The post How Artificial Intelligence can Enhance Your Business Process appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault chaos engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-chaos-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-chaos-engineering"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to make your Vault clusters more resilient with Gremlin chaos engineering tests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第246話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:11341664176591995253</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/11341664176591995253"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graph neural networks in TensorFlow]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/graph-neural-networks-in-tensorflow.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/graph-neural-networks-in-tensorflow.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T19:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dustin Zelle, Software Engineer, Google Research, and Arno Eigenwillig, Software Engineer, CoreML




Objects and their relationships are ubiquitous in the world around us, and relationships can be as important to understanding an object as its own attributes viewed in isolation — take for example transportation networks, production networks, knowledge graphs, or social networks. Discrete mathematics and computer science have a long history of formalizing such networks as graphs, consisting of nodes connected by edges in various irregular ways. Yet most machine learning (ML) algorithms allow only for regular and uniform relations between input objects, such as a grid of pixels, a sequence of words, or no relation at all. 




Graph neural networks, or GNNs for short, have emerged…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zeebe Performance 2023 Year In Review]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=100364</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/zeebe-performance-2023-year-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T21:56:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 was quite a year for Zeebe, and the team has been hard at work improving performance. Get an overview of all the latest technical improvements.
The post Zeebe Performance 2023 Year In Review appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Kujawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Amazon Q in AWS Glue, Amazon PartyRock Hackathon, CDK Migrate, and more — February 5, 2024]]></title>
        <id>4fc2f407c1e21338432c1d42fc0eef0044baf085</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-q-in-aws-glue-amazon-partyrock-hackathon-cdk-migrate-and-more-february-5-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T20:52:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With all the generative AI announcements at AWS re:invent 2023, I’ve committed to dive deep into this technology and learn as much as I can. If you are too, I’m happy that among other resources available, the AWS community also has a space that I can access for generative AI tools and guides. Last week’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regenerating secrets for Azure DevOps OAuth applications]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68431</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/regenerating-secrets-for-azure-devops-oauth-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T20:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now self-regenerate new client secrets as needed for apps made on top of the Azure DevOps’ OAuth platform. A valid, active client secret is critical for getting a refresh token to continue using your app. Once the secret has expired,
The post Regenerating secrets for Azure DevOps OAuth applications appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Boards + GitHub improvements in private preview]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68428</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-boards-github-improvements-in-private-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T20:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are happy to announce several improvements to our GitHub integration story. These improvements are vital for those customers who are seeking better traceability between Azure Boards and GitHub repositories.
The post Azure Boards + GitHub improvements in private preview appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary 0.15 adds new storage policies and desktop/CLI features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-15-adds-new-storage-policies-and-desktop-cli-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-15-adds-new-storage-policies-and-desktop-cli-features"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.15 improves governance and end user workflows with session recording storage policies and UX upgrades such as target search and filtering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS named as a Leader in 2023 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Strategic Cloud Platform Services for thirteenth year in a row]]></title>
        <id>c97eadb106f4d1e2efc5452b309c20366a06a93e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/read-the-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-strategic-cloud-platform-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T16:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On December 4, 2023, AWS was named as a Leader in the 2023 Magic Quadrant for Strategic Cloud Platform Services (SCPS). AWS is the longest-running Magic Quadrant Leader, with Gartner naming AWS a Leader for the thirteenth consecutive year. AWS is placed highest on the Ability to Execute axis. SCPS, previously known as Magic Quadrant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Community Podcast Recap: A Developer-friendly Citizen Developer, They DO Exist]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=100389</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/camunda-community-podcast-recap-developer-friendly-citizen-developer-do-exist/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T20:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missed the latest episode of the Camunda Community Podcast? Catch up with a quick recap and learn about Maria's journey to becoming a citizen developer.
The post Camunda Community Podcast Recap: A Developer-friendly Citizen Developer, They DO Exist appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A decoder-only foundation model for time-series forecasting]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/a-decoder-only-foundation-model-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/a-decoder-only-foundation-model-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rajat Sen and Yichen Zhou, Google Research





Time-series forecasting is ubiquitous in various domains, such as retail, finance, manufacturing, healthcare and natural sciences. In retail use cases, for example, it has been observed that improving demand forecasting accuracy can meaningfully reduce inventory costs and increase revenue. Deep learning (DL) models have emerged as a popular approach for forecasting rich, multivariate, time-series data because they have proven to perform well in a variety of settings (e.g., DL models performed well in the M5 competition).



At the same time, there has been rapid progress in large foundation language models used for natural language processing (NLP) tasks, such as translation, retrieval-augmented generation, and code completion. Thes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intervening on early readouts for mitigating spurious features and simplicity bias]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/intervening-on-early-readouts-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/intervening-on-early-readouts-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rishabh Tiwari, Pre-doctoral Researcher, and Pradeep Shenoy, Research Scientist, Google Research




Machine learning models in the real world are often trained on limited data that may contain unintended statistical biases. For example, in the CELEBA celebrity image dataset, a disproportionate number of female celebrities have blond hair, leading to classifiers incorrectly predicting “blond” as the hair color for most female faces — here, gender is a spurious feature for predicting hair color. Such unfair biases could have significant consequences in critical applications such as medical diagnosis. 





Surprisingly, recent work has also discovered an inherent tendency of deep networks to amplify such statistical biases, through the so-called simplicity bias of deep learning. T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Docs AI Taking the Developer Experience to a New Level]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=100239</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/camunda-docs-ai-developer-experience-new-level/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T22:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our new AI-powered docs chatbot, powered by a LLM trained on our own sources, makes it easier than ever to get answers to your technical questions in one place.
The post Camunda Docs AI Taking the Developer Experience to a New Level appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MobileDiffusion: Rapid text-to-image generation on-device]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/01/mobilediffusion-rapid-text-to-image.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/01/mobilediffusion-rapid-text-to-image.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T21:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yang Zhao, Senior Software Engineer, and Tingbo Hou, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Core ML




Text-to-image diffusion models have shown exceptional capabilities in generating high-quality images from text prompts. However, leading models feature billions of parameters and are consequently expensive to run, requiring powerful desktops or servers (e.g., Stable Diffusion, DALL·E, and Imagen). While recent advancements in inference solutions on Android via MediaPipe and iOS via Core ML have been made in the past year, rapid (sub-second) text-to-image generation on mobile devices has remained out of reach.
 

To that end, in “MobileDiffusion: Subsecond Text-to-Image Generation on Mobile Devices”, we introduce a novel approach with the potential for rapid text-to-image generation on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New chat experience for AWS Glue using natural language – Amazon Q data integration in AWS Glue (Preview)]]></title>
        <id>00fe6143fdb2ce2534fe7235e77304059e873396</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-chat-experience-for-aws-glue-using-natural-language-amazon-q-data-integration-in-aws-glue-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T17:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re previewing a new chat experience for AWS Glue that will let you use natural language to author and troubleshoot data integration jobs. Amazon Q data integration in AWS Glue will reduce the time and effort you need to learn, build, and run data integration jobs using AWS Glue data integration engines. You can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build secure AI applications on Azure with HashiCorp Terraform and Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/build-secure-ai-applications-on-azure-with-hashicorp-terraform-and-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/build-secure-ai-applications-on-azure-with-hashicorp-terraform-and-vault"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to deploy, secure, and enable AI-based applications with Terraform and Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup —  AWS Step Functions, Amazon ECS, Amazon EKS, Amazon LightSail, Amazon VPC, and more — January 29, 2024]]></title>
        <id>cf2ae0f8dcf717f9aae1eae3b7fa65ab65e82958</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-api-gateway-aws-step-functions-amazon-ecs-amazon-eks-amazon-lightsail-amazon-vpc-and-more-january-29-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T20:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This past week our service teams continue to innovate on your behalf, and a lot has happened in the Amazon Web Services (AWS) universe. I’ll also share about all the AWS Community events and initiatives that are happening around the world. Let’s dive in! Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>