<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-02T01:57:21.302Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-02T01:57:21.302Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Read to your kids/read to your parents]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42852</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/693746912/0/sethsblog~Read-to-your-kidsread-to-your-parents/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-01T09:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Launching today, a free ebook: Generation Carbon: A Carbon Almanac for Kids. A worldwide team of volunteers wrote, designed and illustrated this free PDF. The hope is that you’ll grab a copy and share it with ten people. That you’ll read it to your parents or to your kids. There are all sorts of bonuses […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making our decisions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42782</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/693567724/0/sethsblog~Making-our-decisions/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-30T08:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For trivial matters, it’s efficient and perhaps useful to simply follow a crowd or whatever leader we’ve chosen. But when it matters, we need to make (and own) our own decisions. To do that effectively, consider: Do the reading Show your work Avoid voices with a long track record of being wrong Ask, “and then […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extracting Skill-Centric State Abstractions from Value Functions]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/extracting-skill-centric-state.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/extracting-skill-centric-state.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T17:02:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dhruv Shah, Intern, and Brian Ichter, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google 
Advances in reinforcement learning (RL) for robotics have enabled robotic agents to perform increasingly complex tasks in challenging environments. Recent results show that robots can learn to fold clothes, dexterously manipulate a rubik’s cube, sort objects by color, navigate complex environments and walk on difficult, uneven terrain. But "short-horizon" tasks such as these, which require very little long-term planning and provide immediate failure feedback, are relatively easy to train compared to many tasks that may confront a robot in a real-world setting. Unfortunately, scaling such short-horizon skills to the abstract, long horizons of real-world tasks is difficult. For example, how would one trai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.1.1 Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=243994</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/04/phpstorm-2022-1-1-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T15:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a new preview available of PhpStorm 2022.1.1, the newest minor release of PhpStorm. It brings a bunch of bug fixes and quality-of-life improvements. Blade formatting fixes (WI-37087) The @case and @break directives within a @switch directive weren’t properly formatted by PhpStorm. That’s now fixed. Default property visibility (WI-50274) PhpStorm allows you to define the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing code navigation to communities]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-29-bringing-code-navigation-to-communities/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-29-bringing-code-navigation-to-communities/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T15:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the efforts of the Elixir community, GitHub supports code navigation for Elixir repositories. Read how favorite language can add this support too!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion Roadmap for 2022.2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=244043</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/04/clion-roadmap-for-2022-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T12:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.1 was released a couple of weeks ago and is focused on quality improvements. It enhances existing workflows for remote development, Docker, CMake projects, and CUDA debugging. Now it’s time to share what the team will be focusing on over the coming months and is aiming to deliver in 2022.2 (or in later releases). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper and Rider 2022.1.1 bug fixes have landed]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=244040</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/04/29/resharper-rider-2022-1-1-bug-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T11:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, The ReSharper and Rider 2022.1.1 bug-fix releases are now available! Let’s go over the most important updates. ReSharper Fixed the Stack Trace Explorer that had difficulty working with multitarget projects (RSRP-488300). Fixed an error that emerged when the test method’s name is set to the same as the value of the [TestName] attribute […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asia Rudenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“The market has spoken”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41909</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/693362356/0/sethsblog~The-market-has-spoken/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would someone buy a share of stock for $945? One reason might be that they think they can sell it tomorrow for $950. A more common reason is that someone bought it an hour ago for $940. Of course, this applies to more than equities. Why buy a Birkin bag for more than $25,000? […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bad Map Projection: Madagascator]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2613/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2613/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/bad_map_projection_madagascator.png" title="The projection's north pole is in a small lake on the island of Mahé in the Seychelles, which is off the top of the map and larger than the rest of the Earth's land area combined." alt="The projection's north pole is in a small lake on the island of Mahé in the Seychelles, which is off the top of the map and larger than the rest of the Earth's land area combined." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Simon Ritter, Java Champion and deputy CTO at Azul]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/28/a-bootiful-podcast-simon-ritter-java-champion-and-deputy-cto-at-azul</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/28/a-bootiful-podcast-simon-ritter-java-champion-and-deputy-cto-at-azul"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Azul Deputy CTO and Java’s own mad scientist and luminary Simon Ritter (@speakjava)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon MSK Serverless Now Generally Available–No More Capacity Planning for Your Managed Kafka Clusters]]></title>
        <id>305f11c2d5084adabac03bcf0422320fe63911fe</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-msk-serverless-now-generally-available-no-more-capacity-planning-for-your-managed-kafka-clusters/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T18:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are making Amazon MSK Serverless generally available to help you reduce even more the operational overhead of managing an Apache Kafka cluster by offloading the capacity planning and scaling to AWS. In May 2019, we launched Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka to help our customers stream data using Apache Kafka. Apache Kafka […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices to keep your projects secure on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-28-best-practices-to-keep-your-projects-secure-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-28-best-practices-to-keep-your-projects-secure-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days software is subject to an ever-changing threat landscape. Check out the many ways you can keep your projects secure on GitHub today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2022.04: Parallel Tests, Improved Integration with Amazon AWS, Built-in Code Quality Analysis, Updated VCS Integrations, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=243767</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2022/04/teamcity-2022-04-parallel-tests-improved-integration-with-amazon-aws-built-in-code-quality-analysis-updated-vcs-integrations-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2022.04 introduces the new Parallel Tests feature that delivers an extraordinary speed boost when testing your projects. New powerful code analysis features will cut the time you spend on code reviews and increase the maintainability of your projects. Users who run their builds in the cloud will love the improved integration with Amazon S3 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Rassokhin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Next: GoLand 2022.2 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=243724</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/04/28/goland-2022-2-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week we released GoLand 2022.1. The first major update brings support for generics and Go workspaces and new features for working with microservices, such as the ability to see all endpoints in a dedicated tool window and to generate HTTP requests right from your Go files.  Learn more on our What’s New page, where […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Zharova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phone Calls with .NET and Twilio – Webinar Recording]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=243275</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/04/28/phone-calls-with-net-and-twilio-webinar-recording/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T11:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recording for our webinar, Phone Calls with .NET and Twilio with software engineer and technical content creator at Twilio – Niels Swimberghe, is now available. Subscribe to our community newsletter to receive notifications about future webinars. In this webinar, learn how to add phone calls to your .NET applications using Twilio APIs! In this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote Development With JetBrains Gateway and Gitpod]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=229291</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/blog/2022/04/28/jetbrains_partners_with_gitpod/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T10:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are pleased to join our friends at Gitpod in announcing the integration between Gitpod and JetBrains Gateway, our remote development solution. This means you can access source code hosted in an ephemeral development environment from your favorite JetBrains IDE, running in the cloud whenever you need it. All language processing happens in your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools Plugin 2022.4 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=242933</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/04/28/edutools-plugin-2022-4-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2022.4 of EduTools is now out! With this release, we continue to focus on the overall quality of the plugin and on fixing bugs. Read on to learn about the most notable fixes and improvements. INSTALL EDUTOOLS PLUGIN EDU-4985: Fixes the issue causing choice tasks not to be submitted to Stepik. EDU-4994 and EDU-4995: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our areas of expertise]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41877</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/693175748/0/sethsblog~Our-areas-of-expertise/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of all, we’re experts in our own narrative, our feelings, our lived experience. No one has had that but us, and while it might be unexamined or instinctive, we’re the experts. Experts in who we associate with and what we choose to believe. And many of us are experts in what we do all […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic on Elastic: How we saved $100,000/month by keeping our own software up to date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-clusters-upgrade-latest-release-save-money</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-clusters-upgrade-latest-release-save-money"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T22:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's start with the bottom line: When we upgraded to Elasticsearch 7.15 last year, our internal observability clusters saw a reduction in inter-node traffic from 464TB to 204.5TB per day. We monitored this reduction through subsequent upgrades and noticed its impact on our data transfer and storage costs. So here it is: upgrading saved Elastic $3,500 per day, or approximately $100,000 a month, or $1.2 million annually. We are excited to see these innovations directly lower the total cost of ownership and potentially save money for our customers. Here's a closer look at how we did it, and how you can, too.
Note: As of the date of this blog post, the latest Elastic release is 8.1 — however rest assured that if you're upgrading to the latest release, you're getting the data (and cost) saving…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic on Elastic: How we saved $100,000/month by keeping our own software up to date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-clusters-upgrade-latest-release-save-money</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-clusters-upgrade-latest-release-save-money"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T22:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch enhancements added in 7.15+, lowers data transfer and storage (DTS) and can lower your Elastic Cloud bills. Learn how our cloud observability team saved $100,000 and upgrade to 8.1 today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Storage-Optimized Amazon EC2 Instances (I4i) Powered by Intel Xeon Scalable (Ice Lake) Processors]]></title>
        <id>6d11b906558df90e167a43676ae4febc00ab2a71</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-storage-optimized-amazon-ec2-instances-i4i-powered-by-intel-xeon-scalable-ice-lake-processors/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years we have released multiple generations of storage-optimized Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances including the HS1 (2012) , D2 (2015), I2 (2013) , I3 (2017), I3en (2019), D3/D3en (2020), and Im4gn/Is4gen (2021). These instances are used to host high-performance real-time relational databases, distributed file systems, data warehouses, key-value stores, and more. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.2 Brings New Cross-Namespace Controls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-2-brings-new-cross-namespace-controls</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-2-brings-new-cross-namespace-controls"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.2, now generally available, enhances the gateway’s traffic management capabilities by adding cross-namespace reference policy enforcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2022 HashiCorp SI & Reseller Partner Network Award Winners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2022-hashicorp-si-reseller-partner-network-award-winners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2022-hashicorp-si-reseller-partner-network-award-winners"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 HashiCorp Partner Network Awards for Systems Integrators and Resellers have been announced. Find out who the winners are in our five categories this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect Credential Access with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-credential-access-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-credential-access-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we detail a series of tactics for hunting with new data types and fields within Elastic and how to leverage Elastic Security to its fullest potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect Credential Access with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-credential-access-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-credential-access-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Within our Elastic Security research group, a strong area of focus is implementing detection mechanisms for capabilities we understand adversaries are currently exploiting within environments. We’ll often wait to see the impact that bringing these capabilities to market will have from a detection standpoint. This allows our researchers to explore different detection strategies through these additions, providing deep insight into how effective the Elastic Security platform can be.

When we released Elastic Endpoint Security, our team added new file and registry events to provide defenders with better visibility on techniques and procedures involving some form of sensitive files and/or registry objects access:

T1555.003 Credentials from Web Browsers
T1003.002 Security Account Manager
T100…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第208話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496898209741</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496898209741"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Live Stream Recording: WebStorm’s Power User Manual]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=243358</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/04/recording-webstorms-power-user-manual/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recording from the WebStorm’s Power User Manual live stream is now available on the JetBrains YouTube channel! In this live stream, two WebStorm Power Users, Margaux Flores and Dave Stewart, shared some of their favorite features and tricks that they use in their day-to-day work. Whether you are just starting out with WebStorm or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Aganezova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MPS Is Skipping the 2022.1 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=mps&amp;p=243311</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/mps/2022/04/mps-is-skipping-the-2022-1-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MPS 2022.1 was supposed to be released this month, but we unfortunately have to announce that this is not going to happen. The previous release, MPS 2021.3, was released late, which gave us a shorter time frame for fixing the bugs of the new features, while also developing functionality for MPS 2022.1. Rather than risk […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oscar Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode 2022.1: Swift Support Improvements, Xcode 13.3 Support, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=objc&amp;p=236850</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/04/appcode-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T13:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please welcome our first major update this year – AppCode 2022.1! Swift Language support AppCode 2022.1 includes support for the following Swift features: SE-0298: async sequences First part of SE-0313: support for isolation control specifiers in Swift parser SE-0308: #if for postfix member expressions Swift Package Manager We’ve added an ability to update Swift Package […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanislav Dombrovsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTMX for ASP.NET Core Developers – Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=240045</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/04/27/htmx-for-asp-net-core-developers-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T13:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re developing ASP.NET Core applications, and are looking at building a rich client-side experience, you’re in luck. We just published a new tutorial to the JetBrains .NET Guide: HTMX for ASP.NET Core Developers In this tutorial, our developer advocate Khalid Abuhakmeh introduces you to HTMX, and how to integrate it into your ASP.NET Core […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maarten Balliauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Conversations: Uwe Koch, HDI Insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51911</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/community-conversations-uwe-koch-hdi-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the first installment of our Community Conversations blog series with Uwe Koch, a Camunda Champion and enterprise architect.
The post Community Conversations: Uwe Koch, HDI Insurance appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two kinds of useful help]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41911</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/692977912/0/sethsblog~Two-kinds-of-useful-help/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T07:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first kind, the common kind, is when someone helps you with advice or labor to accomplish what you’ve already set out to do. The second kind, more rare and more useful, is when someone helps you realize that your original plan wasn’t as good as you thought it was, and helps you come up […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 26th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/this-week-in-spring-april-26th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/this-week-in-spring-april-26th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! This week I was hoping to be in glorious Chicago, Illinois for the first in-person SpringOne Tour installment since the pandemic. But, alas, I couldn’t go because - out of an abundance of caution, and since I was exposed to COVID19 in Atlanta, GA - it was thought to be safer to keep some folks home and virtual. Sigh. This policy makes perfect sense and it’s what I wanted. But it’s still a smidge disappointing to not be there. I miss y’all! It was fun at least doing a remote presentation. 

Anyway, without further ado, let’s get into today’s roundup! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud legend Glenn Renfro about batch processing, tasks, stream processing, data flow, and t-shirts

  
Add Prefix to All Spring Boot Controllers

  
CVE report published for Spring Security OAuth

  
JobRunr 5.0 is out now and it supports Spring Native!

  
GraalVM 22.1: Developer experience improvements, Apple Silicon builds, and more

  
I love Spring GraphQL, but its not the only option out there. GraphQL Using Netflix’s DGS Framework & Spring-Boot (Schema-First Approach)

  
Kafka With Java, Spring, and Docker — Asynchronous Communication Between Microservices

  
Mayunk Jain on Twitter

  
Serverless with Spring. 1. Introduction:  In this article, we… | by Apurv Sheth | Mar, 2022 | Medium

  
Spring Boot 2.5.13 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.6.7 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.7.0-RC1 is now available

  
Spring Boot Tutorial - Nice & Easy

  
Spring Session 2021.2.0-RC1, 2021.1.3 and 2021.0.6 released

  
Spring Tools 4.14.1 released

  
Spring for GraphQL 1.0 RC1 Released]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nimbuspwn: Leveraging vulnerabilities to exploit Linux via Privilege Escalation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/nimbuspwn-leveraging-vulnerabilities-to-exploit-linux-via-privilege-escalation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/nimbuspwn-leveraging-vulnerabilities-to-exploit-linux-via-privilege-escalation"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsofts’ 365 Defender team released a post detailing several identified vulnerabilities. that allow adversarial groups to easily privilege escalate on Linux systems allowing deployment of payloads, ransomware, or other malicious actions. The vulnerabilities, now collectively known as Nimbuspwn include a series of security issues within networkd-dispatcher, specifically directory traversal, symlink race, and TOCTU race conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nimbuspwn: Leveraging vulnerabilities to exploit Linux via Privilege Escalation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/nimbuspwn-leveraging-vulnerabilities-to-exploit-linux-via-privilege-escalation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/nimbuspwn-leveraging-vulnerabilities-to-exploit-linux-via-privilege-escalation"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Summary

The Microsoft 365 Defender team released a post detailing several identified vulnerabilities. These vulnerabilities allow adversarial groups to easily escalate privileges on Linux systems, allowing for deployment of payloads, ransomware, or other malicious actions. Collectively known as Nimbuspwn, these vulnerabilities include a series of security issues within networkd-dispatcher, specifically directory traversal, symlink race, and TOCTU race conditions.

Details are covered in their detailed post, and further information will be available within the two requested CVEs: CVE-2022-29799 and CVE-2022-29800. At the time of publication these CVE IDs are still reserved.

While this class of vulnerability requires local shell access to exploit, it should be considered important for th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightsabers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2612/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2612/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/lightsabers.png" title="A lot of Jedi romances start with this turning into a Lady and the Tramp spaghetti situation." alt="A lot of Jedi romances start with this turning into a Lady and the Tramp spaghetti situation." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.2 Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/spring-cloud-2021-0-2-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/spring-cloud-2021-0-2-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T22:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Service Release 2 of the Spring Cloud 2021.0 Release Train is available today. This was primarily a bug fix release. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2021.0.2 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0.2 Release Train

See the project page for all issues included in the release.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Pass request data context in blocking LoadBalancer client (1090)

  
Support custom HTTP status code in LoadBalancer lifecycle (1066)

  
Support URI without port for default ServiceInstance ([1054]https://github.com/spring-cloud/spring-cloud-commons/pull/1054))

  
Improved calculating Round Robin LoadBalancer position ([1078]https://github.com/spring-cloud/spring-clo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolution of ML Fact Store]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5941d3231762</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/evolution-of-ml-fact-store-5941d3231762?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T20:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Vivek Kaushal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.14.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/spring-tools-4-14-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/spring-tools-4-14-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.14.1 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: use startupSnapshot instead of startup timer call to avoid wiping out the underlying data

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: When vscode opens a Java project for about 2 hours, the suggestion function will fail (#750)

  
(VSCode) enhancement: live hovers are now automatically show up when you launch a Spring Boot application in VSCode. Additional JVM args for the Spring Boot app to enable JMX are added to the launch automatically. More details can be found in the user guide section about Live Application Information.

  
(VSCode) enhancement: add extension APIs to get live data (#751) - contributed by @Eskibear


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog/#2022-04-27-4141-release-incl-language-servers-version-1330

Spring Tools 4.15.0 is scheduled to be released in mid June 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Desktop 3.0 brings better integration for your pull requests]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-26-github-desktop-3-0-brings-better-integration-for-your-pull-requests/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-26-github-desktop-3-0-brings-better-integration-for-your-pull-requests/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T16:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Desktop 3.0 brings better integration with your GitHub Pull Requests. You can now receive real time notifications and review the status of your check runs for your pull request.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Wavelength Zone in Toronto – The First in Canada]]></title>
        <id>0536fdf5007395f77dfe25feb6e76bd15622ea6a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-wavelength-zone-in-toronto-the-first-in-canada/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T15:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless communication has put us closer to each other. 5G networks increase the reach of what we can achieve to new use cases that need end-to-end low latency. With AWS Wavelength, you can deploy AWS compute and storage services within telecommunications providers’ data centers at the edge of the 5G networks. Your applications can then […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yelling “fire”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=29441</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/692814328/0/sethsblog~Yelling-fire/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the possible exception of hockey games, there have been few places in our modern lives where public interactions are supposed to be coarse. If (back when we could, and soon when we can again) you go to the theater, a museum, the mall, a restaurant, the library, school, the supermarket, the park, or yes, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your co-workers with autistic children want you to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-what-your-coworkers-with-autistic-children-want-you-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-what-your-coworkers-with-autistic-children-want-you-to-know"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting our Elasticians that have children with special needs starts with understanding, empathy, and support.
Here are a few things to know in order to better understand and support your co-workers who are raising an autistic child.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud is now available on Microsoft Azure in 4 new regions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-available-on-microsoft-azure-in-4-new-regions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-available-on-microsoft-azure-in-4-new-regions"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud helps you quickly and easily find information, gain insights, and protect your technology investments across Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your co-workers with autistic children want you to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-what-your-coworkers-with-autistic-children-want-you-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-what-your-coworkers-with-autistic-children-want-you-to-know"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,,
Autism isn’t one size fits all
April is Autism Awareness Month in the United States and according to the Centers for Disease Control, 1 in 44 children will be diagnosed with autism in the U.S. Supporting our Elasticians that have children with special needs starts with understanding, empathy, and support.

At Elastic we believe in flexibility. In fact, it’s part of our Source Code. We believe in our employees having the flexibility to work and care for their responsibilities at home. 

For those with a child with autism, those responsibilities outside of work might look a lot different (and more demanding) than yours. Here are a few things to know in order to better understand and support your co-workers who are raising an autistic child.
Things are constantly changing
While those on th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud is now available on Microsoft Azure in 4 new regions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-available-on-microsoft-azure-in-4-new-regions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-available-on-microsoft-azure-in-4-new-regions"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re pleased to announce you can now run Elastic Cloud on Microsoft Azure in the following regions to help you accelerate results that matter, securely and at cloud scale:

Azure Brazil South (São Paulo State)
Azure Canada Central (Toronto)
Azure South Africa North (Johannesburg)
Azure Central India (Pune)

With solutions in Enterprise Search, Observability, and Security, Elastic helps you enhance customer and employee search experiences, keep mission-critical applications running smoothly, and protect against cyber threats.

Easily search applications, websites, and workplace content platforms for information. Quickly gain deep insights into your environment by monitoring applications and uptime as well as analyzing centralized logs and metrics. You can also help protect your technolog…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ICLR 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/google-at-iclr-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/google-at-iclr-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T19:46:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cat Armato and Callan Hajosy, Program Managers 
The 10th International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR 2022) kicks off this week, bringing together researchers, entrepreneurs, engineers and students alike to discuss and explore the rapidly advancing field of deep learning. Entirely virtual this year, ICLR 2022 offers conference and workshop tracks that present some of the latest research in deep learning and its applications to areas ranging from computer vision, speech recognition and text understanding to robotics, computational biology, and more. 
 As a Platinum Sponsor of ICLR 2022 and Champion DEI Action Fund contributor, Google will have a robust presence with nearly 100 accepted publications and extensive participation on organizing committees and in workshops…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 25, 2022]]></title>
        <id>0fb329a009aafc65690dcbba4bb516553ed47289</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-25-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! The first in this year’s series of AWS Summits took place in San Francisco this past week and we had a bunch of great announcements. Let’s take a closer look… […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friendly forks 101]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-25-the-friend-zone-friendly-forks-101/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-25-the-friend-zone-friendly-forks-101/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first post in a two-part series describing friendly forks and alternative strategies for managing them. Stay tuned for part two coming in May!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Tips for Making the Most of Camunda Community Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51741</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/4-tips-for-making-the-most-of-camunda-community-summit/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Community Summit 2022 features our most varied and engaging agenda to date. Follow these tips to take full advantage of your experience.
The post 4 Tips for Making the Most of Camunda Community Summit appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Thengvall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Cloud Search to Streamline Workspace Search and Switching]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-cloud-search-to-streamline-workspace-search-and-switching</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-cloud-search-to-streamline-workspace-search-and-switching"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new search capability available for all tiers in Terraform Cloud will allow you to easily switch between workspaces and organizations in the UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-driven remediation with systemd and Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-remediation-with-systemd-and-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-remediation-with-systemd-and-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform can assist you here with not only keeping your infrastructure in check, but also giving your teams the peace of mind that systems are running as they should.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The answer imperative]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42802</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/692668932/0/sethsblog~The-answer-imperative/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T08:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“C’mon, c’mon, c’mon…” We’re standing on one foot, impatiently waiting for the shortcut, the method, the guarantee. Skip the preamble and the analysis–what’s your take? Don’t talk to me about genre and method and history. No time for that. What are we supposed to do right now? Perhaps the reason we’re struggling is that along […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cutest-Sounding Scientific Effects]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2611/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2611/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/cutest_sounding_scientific_effects.png" title="The Stroop-YORP number of a scientific paper is how many of the 16 finalist names (sans 'effect') it manages to casually sneak into the text." alt="The Stroop-YORP number of a scientific paper is how many of the 16 finalist names (sans 'effect') it manages to casually sneak into the text." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The win-win fallacy]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41832</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/692569710/0/sethsblog~The-winwin-fallacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-24T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some problems where a useful solution is a win for everyone. But not many. Certainly not the problems that have been around for a while. If there were a win win solution, someone would have probably found it already. For significant problems, someone is going to lose in the short run. Leadership is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Because it’s more convenient”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42787</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/692449354/0/sethsblog~Because-its-more-convenient/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T09:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a terrible reason to do something that makes things a little worse for other people. And a common one, of course. Much of the time, we’re willing to go out of our way to do work we’re proud of. Unless it would be inconvenient to do so. One of the reasons our best […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating 40 years of ZX Spectrum ❤️ 💛 💚 💙]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-23-zx-spectrum-40-year-anniversary/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-23-zx-spectrum-40-year-anniversary/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T07:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ZX Spectrum, one of the best-selling microcomputers of all time, celebrates its 40 years anniversary today. Read more about how the community is still active - creating new content, archiving old content, and hacking on all sorts of hardware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.22.04]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63912</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-22-04/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T02:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back this week for another top stories from the #AzureDevOps #Community!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.22.04 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pix2Seq: A New Language Interface for Object Detection]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pix2seq-new-language-interface-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pix2seq-new-language-interface-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T20:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ting Chen and David Fleet, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Object detection is a long-standing computer vision task that attempts to recognize and localize all objects of interest in an image. The complexity arises when trying to identify or localize all object instances while also avoiding duplication. Existing approaches, like Faster R-CNN and DETR, are carefully designed and highly customized in the choice of architecture and loss function. This specialization of existing systems has created two major barriers: (1) it adds complexity in tuning and training the different parts of the system (e.g., region proposal network, graph matching with GIOU loss, etc.), and (2), it can reduce the ability of a model to generalize, necessitating a redesign of the model for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss Re’s Journey Toward a Cloud-Native Orchestration Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51662</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/swiss-res-journey-toward-a-cloud-native-orchestration-solution/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ready for a digital transformation? Learn why Swiss Re selected Camunda Platform 8 as its cloud-native process orchestration solution.
The post Swiss Re’s Journey Toward a Cloud-Native Orchestration Solution appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing the stigma of a CVE]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-22-removing-the-stigma-of-a-cve/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-22-removing-the-stigma-of-a-cve/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you worry that a CVE will hurt the reputation of your project? In reality, CVEs are a tracking number, and nothing more. Here's how we think of them at GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.12 Hardens Security on Kubernetes with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-12-hardens-security-on-kubernetes-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-12-hardens-security-on-kubernetes-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This release strengthens zero trust security architecture by leveraging HashiCorp Vault to reduce secrets sprawl and automate server TLS certificate rotation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 simple things every developer can do to ship more secure code]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-22-5-simple-things-every-developer-can-do-to-ship-more-secure-code/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-22-5-simple-things-every-developer-can-do-to-ship-more-secure-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T14:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From plug-and-play automations to protected branches, here are simple ways any developer can build more secure software on GitHub—all with a free account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The traffic metaphors]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41890</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/692313834/0/sethsblog~The-traffic-metaphors/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your mileage may vary. Speeding up to get to a red light faster just wastes energy. Honking doesn’t make traffic go away. Doesn’t matter how fancy your car is, it’s not worth very much if they close the road. One of the worst ways to get to where you’re going is to always drive in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud legend Glenn Renfro about batch processing, tasks, stream processing, data flow, and t-shirts]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-legend-glenn-renfro-about-batch-processing-tasks-stream-processing-data-flow-and-t-shirts</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-legend-glenn-renfro-about-batch-processing-tasks-stream-processing-data-flow-and-t-shirts"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of A Bootiful Podcast! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring Cloud luminary and all around lovable guy Glenn Renfro (@cppwfs) about batch processing, tasks, messaging, integration, data flow, and a million other things. Also: t-shirts!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assigning Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2610/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2610/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/assigning_numbers.png" title="Gödel should do an article on which branches of math have the lowest average theorem number." alt="Gödel should do an article on which branches of math have the lowest average theorem number." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing My Fire Service Notification System with Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51389</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/implementing-my-fire-service-notification-system-with-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever struggled to notify the right people during an emergency? Learn how a fire service notification system was built with BPMN and Camunda Platform 8.
The post Implementing My Fire Service Notification System with Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0-RC1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-7-0-rc1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-7-0-rc1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T22:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0-RC1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes more than a 100 bug fixes, enhancements, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Auto-configuration for Kafka Retry Topics

  
Auto-configuration for RSocket support in GraphQL


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your guide to GitHub InFocus: Improving the way software development teams work in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-21-guide-to-github-infocus-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-21-guide-to-github-infocus-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T21:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re kicking off InFocus, a global virtual event focused on accelerating, securing, and improving the way software development teams work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden Interfaces for Ambient Computing]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/hidden-interfaces-for-ambient-computing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/hidden-interfaces-for-ambient-computing.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T19:59:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alex Olwal, Research Scientist, Google Augmented Reality and Artem Dementyev, Hardware Engineer, Google Research 
As consumer electronics and internet-connected appliances are becoming more common, homes are beginning to embrace various types of connected devices that offer functionality like music control, voice assistance, and home automation. A graceful integration of devices requires adaptation to existing aesthetics and user styles rather than simply adding screens, which can easily disrupt a visual space, especially when they become monolithic surfaces or black screens when powered down or not actively used. Thus there is an increasing desire to create connected ambient computing devices and appliances that can preserve the aesthetics of everyday materials, while providing …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Serverless Inference – Machine Learning Inference without Worrying about Servers]]></title>
        <id>3f2dde001172ce44e72138f038da17f0191c2c33</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-serverless-inference-machine-learning-inference-without-worrying-about-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T17:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December 2021, we introduced Amazon SageMaker Serverless Inference (in preview) as a new option in Amazon SageMaker to deploy machine learning (ML) models for inference without having to configure or manage the underlying infrastructure. Today, I’m happy to announce that Amazon SageMaker Serverless Inference is now generally available (GA). Different ML inference use cases […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Aurora Serverless v2 is Generally Available: Instant Scaling for Demanding Workloads]]></title>
        <id>94931a6d5038a338992ac375a270cfd3a1a2c213</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-aurora-serverless-v2-is-generally-available-instant-scaling-for-demanding-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are very excited to announce that Amazon Aurora Serverless v2 is generally available for both Aurora PostgreSQL and MySQL. Aurora Serverless is an on-demand, auto-scaling configuration for Amazon Aurora that allows your database to scale capacity up or down based on your application’s needs. Amazon Aurora is a MySQL- and PostgreSQL-compatible relational database […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the General Availability of AWS Amplify Studio]]></title>
        <id>a646396f947ba813c8558c3ba67d16b8e63ee6bd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-general-availability-of-aws-amplify-studio/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amplify Studio is a visual interface that simplifies front- and backend development for web and mobile applications. We released it as a preview during AWS re:Invent 2021, and today, I’m happy to announce that it is now generally available (GA). A key feature of Amplify Studio is integration with Figma, helping designers and front-end developers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IoT TwinMaker Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>0bc74371fc1afc6c01a04e5c726c01a6a266613e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-iot-twinmaker-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year at AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced the preview of AWS IoT TwinMaker, a new AWS IoT service that makes it faster and easier to create digital twins of real-world systems and use them to monitor and optimize industrial operations. A digital twin is a living digital representation of an individual physical system that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Git push times through faster server side hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-21-improving-git-push-times-through-faster-server-side-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-21-improving-git-push-times-through-faster-server-side-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The history of pre-receive hooks, how we discovered that the performance was problematic, and how we went about safely replacing them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Count Downloads in the Public Terraform Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-count-downloads-in-the-public-terraform-registry</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-count-downloads-in-the-public-terraform-registry"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how download metrics are calculated in the HashiCorp Terraform Registry, and how that count has evolved over time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Detect Operational Issues in Lambda Functions with Amazon DevOps Guru for Serverless]]></title>
        <id>8268d306374a02f09df77e136e38f9dbf78c0766</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/automatically-detect-operational-issues-in-lambda-functions-with-amazon-devops-guru-for-serverless/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T15:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing Amazon DevOps Guru for Serverless, a new capability for Amazon DevOps Guru. It allows developers to improve the operational performance and availability of serverless applications. AWS pioneered the serverless computing space with the launch of AWS Lambda in 2014. Today, hundreds of thousands of customers are using AWS Lambda. Lambda allows […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.7 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-6-7-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-6-7-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T11:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.7 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 38 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE report published for Spring Security OAuth]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/cve-report-published-for-spring-security-oauth</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/cve-report-published-for-spring-security-oauth"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Spring Security OAuth 2.5.2 to address the following CVE report.


  
CVE-2022-22969: Denial-of-Service (DoS) in spring-security-oauth2


This vulnerability exposes OAuth 2.0 Client applications only.

Please review the information in the CVE report and upgrade immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.13 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-5-13-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-5-13-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T08:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.13 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 31 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing the future of search relevance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/embracing-the-future-of-search-relevance</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/embracing-the-future-of-search-relevance"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an effort to provide the most relevant, accurate search possible, developers must learn how to integrate machine learning into thier solutions. Starting in Elastic 8.0, the story around machine learning and how to embrace it is more clear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing the future of search relevance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/embracing-the-future-of-search-relevance</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/embracing-the-future-of-search-relevance"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
When looking for new opportunities to innovate and compete, companies today need to look no further than search, which has come a long way from the search bar of old. Whether you’re enabling search across integrations your business relies on or building a state-of-the-art website experience, search is on the critical path to research and discovery. 
The canonical search bar in mobile apps and websites is only the first step in the journey though. Additional value gets added when intelligent, robust solutions come together to build visually engaging customer experiences.

With the release of Elastic 8.0, we lowered the barrier of entry for teams to build intelligent, relevant search. This release brings more machine learning (ML) capabilities into the core of the Elastic Search Platform, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Session 2021.2.0-RC1, 2021.1.3 and 2021.0.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/20/spring-session-2021-2-0-rc1-2021-1-3-and-2021-0-6-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/20/spring-session-2021-2-0-rc1-2021-1-3-and-2021-0-6-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T23:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Session 2021.2.0-RC1, 2021.1.3 and 2021.0.6.
The 2021.2.0 release train is entering the RC phase. If you haven’t done so yet, please give it a try!
The 2021.1.3 and 2021.0.6 releases deliver bug fixes and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot will pick up these artifacts with its upcoming releases.

The following modules were updated as part of 2021.2.0-RC1:


  
Spring Session Core 2.7.0-RC1 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 2.7.0-RC1 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 2.7.0-RC1 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 2.7.0-RC1 - release notes

  
Spring Session MongoDB 2.7.0-RC1 - release notes

  
Spring Session for Apache Geode 2.7.0-RC1


The following modules were updated as part of 2021.1.3:


  
Spring Session Core 2.6.3 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 2.6.3 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 2.6.3 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 2.6.3 - release notes

  
Spring Session MongoDB 2.6.3 - release notes

  
Spring Session for Apache Geode 2.6.1


The following modules were updated as part of 2021.0.6:


  
Spring Session Core 2.5.6 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 2.5.6 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 2.5.6 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 2.5.6 - release notes

  
Spring Session for Apache Geode 2.5.6]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FormNet: Beyond Sequential Modeling for Form-Based Document Understanding]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/formnet-beyond-sequential-modeling-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/formnet-beyond-sequential-modeling-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T20:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Chen-Yu Lee and Chun-Liang Li, Research Scientists, Google Research, Cloud AI Team 
Form-based document understanding is a growing research topic because of its practical potential for automatically converting unstructured text data into structured information to gain insight about a document’s contents. Recent sequence modeling, which is a self-attention mechanism that directly models relationships between all words in a selection of text, has demonstrated state-of-the-art performance on natural language tasks. A natural approach to handle form document understanding tasks is to first serialize the form documents (usually in a left-to-right, top-to-bottom fashion) and then apply state-of-the-art sequence models to them.  
 However, form documents often have more complex layouts …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#CamundaSummit: Unconference Agenda Announced]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51431</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/camundasummit-unconference-agenda-announced/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T19:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Unconference agenda is now live! Check out the lineup of peer-led sessions we have in store for you on April 27.
The post #CamundaSummit: Unconference Agenda Announced appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organization profiles leading the way]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-20-organization-profiles-leading-the-way/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-20-organization-profiles-leading-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T18:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organization profiles can now display custom content visible only to members of the organization. A new Member view can be tailored to show an alternative README and pinned private repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp and AWS Make it Easier to Secure Workloads in EKS with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-and-aws-partner-to-enhance-kubernetes-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-and-aws-partner-to-enhance-kubernetes-security"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp has partnered with AWS to enhance security on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service with Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opt-in to Auditing on Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63895</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/opt-in-to-auditing-on-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T17:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Auditing has now been made an opt-in feature on Azure DevOps. In our last blog post about Auditing, we discussed the exciting changes coming to the Auditing feature on Azure DevOps, as we work on bringing the feature to general availability.
The post Opt-in to Auditing on Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Migration Hub Orchestrator – New Migration Orchestration Capability with Customizable Workflow Templates]]></title>
        <id>0f99199a54f5eb036f2cc7d2f96cd7faee3329da</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-migration-hub-orchestrator-new-migration-orchestration-capability-with-customizable-workflow-templates/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T16:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can migrate any workload from an on-premises environment to AWS. The key to a successful migration to AWS is a well-thought-out plan, informative tools, prior migration experience, and a quality implementation. Every step along the way, you can use AWS’s years of experience to build your organizational, operational, and technical capabilities so that you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New reference architecture: Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 1.2 to 2 Migration Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-1.2-to-2-migration-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-1.2-to-2-migration-guide"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[we created a simple reference architecture to help guide you migrate from Ansible Automation Platform 1.2 to Ansible Automation Platform 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0 RC1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/20/spring-for-graphql-1-0-rc1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/20/spring-for-graphql-1-0-rc1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of everyone involved, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the first and final release candidate of Spring for GraphQL 1.0. We’re finally going to release a 1.0 version on May 17, the reference version for Spring Boot 2.7.0. We’ve shipped a few noteworthy changes and one important new feature in this release.

Note: The Spring for GraphqL Boot starter is up-to-date with the changes discussed in this post and Spring Boot 2.7.0-RC1 is scheduled to be released on Thursday this week.
GraphQL over RSocket

Spring for GraphQL started out with the HTTP and WebSocket transports - must haves in the GraphQL world. Our programming model allows adding others too, and our existing infrastructure pointed at another clear candidate: the RSocket protocol. In RC1 we’ve added client and s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.17.3 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.3 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
The 7.17.3 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security announcement for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
7.17.3 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia Mitter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.1.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.1.3 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
The 8.1.3 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security announcement for more details.
This release addresses some notable issues in our Observability and Security solutions:
A bug where the APM Server might run out of memory when overloaded by too many incoming requests. Users running APM Server versions 8.0.0 up to 8.1.2 are advised to upgrade immediately.
Multiple issues that impacted Elastic Security UI performance in environments with a high number of field mappings.
A bug where the binary verification will fail when upgrading the Elastic Agent through the upgrade cli command or through the Fleet UI upgrade feature. The bug was impacting 8.1.1 and 8.1.2 releases.
This 8.1.3 patch release contains other fixes and small enhancements for the stack. For more details and a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
8.1.3 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia Mitter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.3 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Logstash, Beats, APM, Enterprise Search, Elastic Security, and ECK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia Mitter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.1.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.1.3 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Logstash, Beats, APM, Enterprise Search, Elastic Security, and ECK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia Mitter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic announces TISAX certification, enhancing security in connected vehicles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-tisax-certification-security-connected-vehicles</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-tisax-certification-security-connected-vehicles"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T21:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, connected vehicles are proliferating, smart cities are translating from vision to reality, and cloud-based connectivity services are increasing. Advanced connectivity solutions like 5G, cloud-based services and automations, and personalization are redefining in-vehicle experiences. In addition, the growth of an intelligent Edge, smart infrastructure, and the Internet of Things are pushing the boundaries of the connected car. 
Automakers worldwide have slowly but steadily come to terms with what is commonly known as the “software-defined vehicle.” It will not be an exaggeration to say that the car of the future will be primarily software-driven, and the digital chassis will control every element within the car from autonomy to driver assistance to cockpit and telematics. 
“Security b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic announces TISAX certification, enhancing security in connected vehicles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-tisax-certification-security-connected-vehicles</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-tisax-certification-security-connected-vehicles"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T21:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic is excited to add TISAX certification to the list of several key information security standards and regulations that it has acquired.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 19th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/19/this-week-in-spring-april-19th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/19/this-week-in-spring-april-19th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! It’s been quite the week since we last talked! I flew to Atlanta, GA, for my first in-person show since the pandemic - Devnexus 2022. I loved the experience! Hopefully, the only souvenirs I’ll have are the amazing memories and not COVID. I loved to see so many smiling faces. Thanks so much for having me, Devnexus, and for running an amazing show. It was a privilege to return. 

And now, without further ado, let’s dive right into the roundup. 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Cloud guru Tiffany Jernigan

  
Jacky Chan on Twitter: “My new open source tool httpx, CLI and IDE plugins to test REST API, GraphQL, gRPC, RSocket, Kafka etc services with HTTP DSL https://t.co/jkvJG2syff JetBrains/Neovim plugins are all ready. Support by @java and @graalvm” / Twitter

  
Ngrok Spring Boot Starter - Tunneling The Easy Way

  
Spring Boot with Drools Engine. In this blog we would see how Spring integrates with Drools Engine. | CodeX

  
Spring Data 2021.2.0-RC1, 2021.1.4, and 2021.0.11 released

  
Spring Framework 5.3.19 and 5.2.21 available now

  
Spring Framework Data Binding Rules Vulnerability (CVE-2022-22968)

  
Spring Security 5.6.3 and 5.5.6 available now

  
Spring Security 5.7.0-RC1 released

  
Build or migrate great applications that deliver great value to your customers. Register now]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Prompt for Continual Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/learning-to-prompt-for-continual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/learning-to-prompt-for-continual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T17:00:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zifeng Wang, Student Researcher, and Zizhao Zhang, Software Engineer, Google Research
Supervised learning is a common approach to machine learning (ML) in which the model is trained using data that is labeled appropriately for the task at hand. Ordinary supervised learning trains on independent and identically distributed (IID) data, where all training examples are sampled from a fixed set of classes, and the model has access to these examples throughout the entire training phase. In contrast, continual learning tackles the problem of training a single model on changing data distributions where different classification tasks are presented sequentially. This is particularly important, for example, to enable autonomous agents to process and interpret continuous streams of informati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.2.0-RC1, 2021.1.4, and 2021.0.11 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/19/spring-data-2021-2-0-rc1-2021-1-4-and-2021-0-11-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/19/spring-data-2021-2-0-rc1-2021-1-4-and-2021-0-11-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2021.2.0 release train is entering the RC phase. If you haven’t done so yet, please give it a try! The 2021.1.4 and 2021.0.11 service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades. For your convenience those will be picked up by Spring Boot in the upcoming days.

To round things off, here are the links to the individual modules, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.2.0-RC1


  
Spring Data Commons 2.7 RC1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.4 RC1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.7 RC1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data for Apache Geode 2.7 RC1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data for Apache Cassandra 3.4 RC1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kubernetes to Nomad Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-kubernetes-to-nomad-cheat-sheet</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-kubernetes-to-nomad-cheat-sheet"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Kubernetes users looking to learn HashiCorp Nomad concepts and commands  — or vice versa — we’ve designed a cheat sheet for quick reference and a fast onramp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify your Elastic on AWS deployment with the Elastic Cloud Quick Start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/simplify-your-elastic-on-aws-deployment-with-the-elastic-cloud-quick-start</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/simplify-your-elastic-on-aws-deployment-with-the-elastic-cloud-quick-start"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline your Elastic on AWS deployment with the Elastic Cloud Quick Start — an automated reference deployment — with just a few steps. And easily migrate your on-prem Elastic workloads into Elastic on AWS after your deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy,Antony Prasad Thevaraj, AWS,Battulga Purevragchaa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify your Elastic on AWS deployment with the Elastic Cloud Quick Start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/simplify-your-elastic-on-aws-deployment-with-the-elastic-cloud-quick-start</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/simplify-your-elastic-on-aws-deployment-with-the-elastic-cloud-quick-start"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Now it is even easier to deploy, ingest, and migrate data into Elastic within your Amazon Web Services (AWS) environment,  so you can quickly capture, store, and search your data. Quickly build and start your environment by leveraging the Elastic Cloud Quick Start — an automated reference deployment — that significantly reduces prior manual procedures to just a few steps. 

In this blog we will go over the details of the deployment environment, benefits of Elastic on AWS, and resources available if you require migration.
Deploy Elastic on AWS with ease
Streamline your deployment with the Elastic Cloud Quick Start. If you have on-prem Elastic workloads, you can easily migrate them into Elastic on AWS after your deployment. 
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blte6…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy,Antony Prasad Thevaraj, AWS,Battulga Purevragchaa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Performance of Parallel Tasks in Camunda Platform 8 is so Good]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51170</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/why-performance-of-parallel-tasks-in-camunda-platform-8-is-so-good/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the fundamental redesigns we've made to Camunda Platform 8 to avoid some challenges present in Camunda Platform 7. 
The post Why Performance of Parallel Tasks in Camunda Platform 8 is so Good appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.0-RC1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/18/spring-security-5-7-0-rc1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/18/spring-security-5-7-0-rc1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T20:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Security 5.7.0-RC1!



In addition to dependency upgrades, bug fixes, and minor enhancements, the release candidate contains a few noteworthy changes:





Introduced SecurityContextHolderFilter - Ability to require explicit saving of the SecurityContext



Added DSL support for Cross Origin Policies headers



Allow configuring PKCE for confidential clients



Added SAML 2.0 Login & Single Logout XML support





This release candidate is a good opportunity to give feedback before the actual GA release in mid-May. We look forward to hearing from you.



You can find the complete details in the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.6.3 and 5.5.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/18/spring-security-5-6-3-and-5-5-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/18/spring-security-5-6-3-and-5-5-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T20:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.6.3 and 5.5.6 are available now.



You can find more details about the respective releases here and
 here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 18, 2022]]></title>
        <id>ef7b946d35336128b5b4045b8988427e735ae9f3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-18-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T18:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Here we are with another roundup of the most significant AWS launches from the previous week. Among the news, we have a new deployment option for Amazon FSx for NetApp […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Partner Network (APN) – 10 Years and Going Strong]]></title>
        <id>8ef86720707ad81177cef1eb9b0d2fe43d2e7cc6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-partner-network-apn-10-years-and-going-strong/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T15:27:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten years ago we launched AWS Partner Network (APN) in beta form for our partners and our customers. In his post for the beta launch, my then-colleague Jinesh Varia noted that: Partners are an integral part of the AWS ecosystem as they enable customers and help them scale their business globally. Some of our greatest […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep dive on Ansible VScode extension]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/deep-dive-on-ansible-vscode-extension</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/deep-dive-on-ansible-vscode-extension"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible as part of the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform continues to grow and mature. Recent enhancements include Ansible Content Collections, automation execution environments, and an increasing list of integrations using plugins and modules. It is more important than ever that both new and experienced content creators have access to tools that help them write better content faster. The newly created Ansible Devtools initiative focuses on developing and enhancing tools like ansible-navigator, Ansible VScode extension, ansible-lint and so on to help ease the Ansible automation content creator experience. In this blog, we will do a deep dive into the Ansible VSCode extension, giving an overview of how it works and the initial setup required to get it working after installation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Studio: A Hands-on Guided Tour of Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=50634</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/code-studio-a-hands-on-guided-tour-of-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready for our first Code Studio based on Camunda Platform 8 with breakout rooms and a collaborative design. 
The post Code Studio: A Hands-on Guided Tour of Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Cloud guru Tiffany Jernigan]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/14/a-bootiful-podcast-cloud-guru-tiffany-jernigan</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/14/a-bootiful-podcast-cloud-guru-tiffany-jernigan"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talk about his first in-person conference since the pandemic descended upon us -the fabulous Devnexus 2022 show - and talks to colleague, teacher, friend, and Kubernetes legend Tiffany Jernigan (@tiffanyfayj).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Locked-Image Tuning: Adding Language Understanding to Image Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/locked-image-tuning-adding-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/locked-image-tuning-adding-language.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T21:41:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Andreas Steiner and Basil Mustafa, Research Software Engineers at Google Research, Brain team 
The ability to classify images into categories has been transformed by deep learning. It has also been significantly accelerated by transfer learning, whereby models are first pre-trained on large datasets, like ImageNet, to learn visual representations that are then transferred via fine-tuning to a new task with less data (e.g., classifying animals). Previous works such as BiT and ViT employed these methods to achieve state-of-the-art performance on a wide range of classification tasks, such as the VTAB benchmark. 
However, fine-tuning has some downsides: though pre-training is done only once, fine-tuning is necessary on every new dataset for which task-specific data is needed. Multimo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Achieves AWS DevOps Competency Status]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-achieves-aws-devops-competency-status</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-achieves-aws-devops-competency-status"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The all-new AWS DevSecOps Competency includes HashiCorp as a Day 1 launch partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 – A 10-Year Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=50440</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/camunda-platform-8-a-10-year-journey/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how a bold idea with ten years of research, development, and hardening it in practice has resulted in the launch of Camunda Platform 8. 
The post Camunda Platform 8 – A 10-Year Journey appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP Update – New Single-AZ Deployment Type]]></title>
        <id>6c44f453a20a0ebed0a4e44b2abe9e79c0c320de</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap-update-new-single-az-deployment-type/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T19:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year I told you about Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP and showed you how you can create a file system in minutes with just a couple of clicks. You can use these high-performance, scalable (up to 176 PiB) file systems to migrate your on-premises applications to the cloud and to build new, cloud-native applications. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple and Effective Zero-Shot Task-Oriented Dialogue]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/simple-and-effective-zero-shot-task.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/simple-and-effective-zero-shot-task.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T17:06:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeffrey Zhao and Raghav Gupta, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Modern conversational agents need to integrate with an ever-increasing number of services to perform a wide variety of tasks, from booking flights and finding restaurants, to playing music and telling jokes. Adding this functionality can be difficult — for each new task, one needs to collect new data and retrain the models that power the conversational agent. This is because most task-oriented dialogue (TOD) models are trained on a single task-specific ontology. An ontology is generally represented as a list of possible user intents (e.g., if the user wants to book a flight, if the user wants to play some music, etc.) and possible parameter slots to extract from the conversation (e.g., the date of the flight, the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco, Datadog, Fortinet, VMware & Others Add Consul Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cisco-datadog-fortinet-vmware-others-add-consul-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cisco-datadog-fortinet-vmware-others-add-consul-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Consul ecosystem has experienced rapid growth in the past six months, recording a total of 10 new integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#CamundaSummit Unconference: Cast Your Vote]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=50343</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/camunda-summit-unconference-cast-your-vote/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for your submissions! From now until April 16, cast your vote for the discussion topics you want on the Unconference agenda.
The post #CamundaSummit Unconference: Cast Your Vote appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework Data Binding Rules Vulnerability (CVE-2022-22968)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/13/spring-framework-data-binding-rules-vulnerability-cve-2022-22968</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/13/spring-framework-data-binding-rules-vulnerability-cve-2022-22968"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table of Contents


  
Overview

  
Does This Affect My Application?

  
Reassessing Your Data Binding Approach


Overview

While investigating the Spring Framework RCE vulnerability CVE-2022-22965 and the suggested workaround, we realized that the disallowedFields configuration setting on WebDataBinder is not intuitive and is not clearly documented. We have fixed that but also decided to be on the safe side and announce a follow-up CVE, in order to ensure application developers are alerted and have a chance to review their configuration.


  
CVE-2022-22968: Spring Framework Data Binding Rules Vulnerability


We have released Spring Framework 5.3.19 and 5.2.21 which contain the fix. Spring Boot 2.6.7 and 2.5.13 are scheduled to be released on April 21, 2022.


  
Until Spring …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Insights for Ansible Automation Platform New Report : Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-insights-for-ansible-automation-platform-new-report-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-insights-for-ansible-automation-platform-new-report-modules"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Insights is a suite of cloud services available on the Red Hat Hybrid Cloud Console, powered by an expert system that is built upon years of data collected from across Red Hat’s worldwide customer base. For Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform customers, it provides predictive analytical reporting of your Ansible automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.19 and 5.2.21 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/13/spring-framework-5-3-19-and-5-2-21-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/13/spring-framework-5-3-19-and-5-2-21-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T11:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.19 and 5.2.21 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.19 includes 12 fixes and improvements. Spring Framework 5.2.21 includes 5 selected fixes and improvements.

In addition, Spring Framework 5.3.19 and 5.2.21 include a fix for CVE-2022-22968: Spring Framework Data Binding Rules Vulnerability and are recommended upgrades for all Spring production scenarios.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 12th, 2022 (Devnexus 2022 Edition!!)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/12/this-week-in-spring-april-12th-2022-devnexus-2022-edition</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/12/this-week-in-spring-april-12th-2022-devnexus-2022-edition"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - Devnexus Edition

Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring - I’m at my first in-person event since the virus: Devnexus! WOOHOOO!! Well, technically I’m still in San Francisco as I write this, but I’ll be in Atlanta, GA tomorrow for… Devnexus! I hope if you’re there that you’ll reach out! 

Friends, colleagues, and community members from the Spring, Tanzu, and adjoining communities will also be there! Here are some of the people I hope to nab a selfie with and whose talks I hope to see! 


  
Glenn Renfro

  
Adib Saikali

  
Joe Grandja

  
Whitney Lee

  
Hillmer Chona

  
Jonatan Ivanov

  
Josh Cummings

  
Alberto C. Rios

  
Simon Brown


And of course I’ll be doing two talks, as well, (one on GraalVm and another on edge services) and I hope you’ll come see those, too! 

And with that out of the way, let’s get on with our regularly scheduled roundup!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: GraphQL Java founder Andi Marek

  
Asir V Selvasingh on Twitter

  
Blog: Kubernetes Removals and Deprecations In 1.24

  
Congrats to the Hibernate team for reaching Hibernate 6.0

  
SivaLabs has a nice post called, “My attempt to understand why people perceive Java as complex.”  What do you think?

  
Spring Cloud Data Flow 2.9.4 Released

  
 Spring Cloud Azure 4.0 integrations are generally available.  Congrats to the teams at Microsoft and the community on such an epic release!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lidar-Camera Deep Fusion for Multi-Modal 3D Detection]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/lidar-camera-deep-fusion-for-multi.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/lidar-camera-deep-fusion-for-multi.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T19:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yingwei Li, Student Researcher, Google Cloud and Adams Wei Yu, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team  
LiDAR and visual cameras are two types of complementary sensors used for 3D object detection in autonomous vehicles and robots. LiDAR, which is a remote sensing technique that uses light in the form of a pulsed laser to measure ranges, provides low-resolution shape and depth information, while cameras provide high-resolution shape and texture information. While the features captured by LiDAR and cameras should be merged together to provide optimal 3D object detection, it turns out that most state-of-the-art 3D object detectors use LiDAR as the only input. The main reason is that to develop robust 3D object detection models, most methods need to augment and transform th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Netflix Content Engineering makes a federated graph searchable]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5c0c1c7d7eaf</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/how-netflix-content-engineering-makes-a-federated-graph-searchable-5c0c1c7d7eaf?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T17:16:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Alex Hutter, Falguni Jhaveri and Senthil Sayeebaba]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul on Amazon ECS 0.4 Now Supports Multi-Tenancy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-4-now-supports-multi-tenancy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-4-now-supports-multi-tenancy"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest version of HashiCorp Consul on Amazon ECS adds support for multi-tenancy with administrative partitions and namespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 – Orchestrate All the Things]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=48495</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/camunda-platform-8-orchestrate-all-the-things/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 is here! Find out why we built Camunda Platform 8, what problems it solves, and why it’s a universal process orchestrator. 
The post Camunda Platform 8 – Orchestrate All the Things appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 11, 2022]]></title>
        <id>6021dc6654c0552b04372a3d6090b690a95a121e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-11-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T18:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! As spring arrives in the Northern Hemisphere, tulips, sunshine, and cherry blossoms finally appear to be in bloom—surely signs of warmer days to come in North America, Asia, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate Your Application with Vault: Static Secrets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-integrate-your-application-with-vault-static-secrets</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-integrate-your-application-with-vault-static-secrets"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to retrieve static secrets from HashiCorp Vault in a real-world setting using a new sample application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large-Scale Matrix Factorization on TPUs]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/large-scale-matrix-factorization-on-tpus.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/large-scale-matrix-factorization-on-tpus.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T17:52:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Harsh Mehta, Software Engineer, Google Research 
Matrix factorization is one of the oldest, yet still widely used, techniques for learning how to recommend items such as songs or movies from user ratings. In its basic form, it approximates a large, sparse (i.e., mostly empty) matrix of user-item interactions with a product of two smaller, denser matrices representing learned item and user features. These dense matrices, in turn, can be used to recommend items to a user with which they haven't interacted before. 
Despite its algorithmic simplicity, matrix factorization can still achieve competitive performance in recommender benchmarks. Alternating least squares (ALS), and especially its implicit variation, is a fundamental algorithm to learn the parameters of matrix factorization…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.08.04]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63867</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-08-04/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back for another top stories from the #AzureDevOps #Community! After last weeks’ ‘catch-up’ from the last month, this week feels so much quieter, but there is some awesome content for you!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.08.04 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VDTTS: Visually-Driven Text-To-Speech]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/vdtts-visually-driven-text-to-speech.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/vdtts-visually-driven-text-to-speech.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T20:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tal Remez, Software Engineer, Google Research and Micheal Hassid, Software Engineer Intern, Google Research   
Recent years have seen a tremendous increase in the creation and serving of video content to users across the world in a variety of languages and over numerous platforms. The process of creating high quality content can include several stages from video capturing and captioning to  video and audio editing. In some cases dialogue is re-recorded (referred to as dialog replacement, post-sync or dubbing) in a studio in order to achieve high quality and replace original audio that might have been recorded in noisy conditions. However, the dialog replacement process can be difficult and tedious because the newly recorded audio needs to be well synced with the video, requiring …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: GraphQL Java founder Andi Marek]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/07/a-bootiful-podcast-graphql-java-founder-andi-marek</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/07/a-bootiful-podcast-graphql-java-founder-andi-marek"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment of a Bootiful Podcast, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to the GraphQL Java project founder and lead, Atlassian engineer, and Spring GraphQL cofounder Andi Marek (@andimarek).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.8 Adds Secret Values for Input Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-8-adds-secret-values-for-input-variables</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-8-adds-secret-values-for-input-variables"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint 0.8 introduces targetable runners, secret values for input variables, and a new command line tool that adds new insight to Waypoint operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 Beta Adds Native Service Discovery and Edge Workload Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 includes built-in service discovery, improved edge compute support, Container Storage Interface (CSI) general availability, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Login MFA Support Added to Vault Open Source and HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/login-mfa-support-added-to-vault-open-source-and-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/login-mfa-support-added-to-vault-open-source-and-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp expands MFA support across open source and all HCP Vault tiers, previously available only through Vault Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing AWS Lambda Function URLs: Built-in HTTPS Endpoints for Single-Function Microservices]]></title>
        <id>b2c24ddd82a7e2defa1973b188f7be843a16b154</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-aws-lambda-function-urls-built-in-https-endpoints-for-single-function-microservices/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are adopting microservices architectures to build resilient and scalable applications using AWS Lambda. These applications are composed of multiple serverless functions that implement the business logic. Each function is mapped to API endpoints, methods, and resources using services such as Amazon API Gateway and Application Load Balancer. But sometimes all you need is a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Casalboni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第207話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496856368973</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496856368973"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficiently Initializing Reinforcement Learning With Prior Policies]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/efficiently-initializing-reinforcement.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/efficiently-initializing-reinforcement.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T14:38:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ikechukwu Uchendu, AI Resident and Ted Xiao, Software Engineer, Robotics at Google 
Reinforcement learning (RL) can be used to train a policy to perform a task via trial and error, but a major challenge in RL is learning policies from scratch in environments with hard exploration challenges. For example, consider the setting depicted in the door-binary-v0 environment from the adroit manipulation suite, where an RL agent must control a hand in 3D space to open a door placed in front of it. 
   


An RL agent must control a hand in 3D space to open a door placed in front of it. The agent receives a reward signal only when the door is completely open.

   
Since the agent receives no intermediary rewards, it cannot measure how close it is to completing the task, and so must explore …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reproducibility in Deep Learning and Smooth Activations]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/reproducibility-in-deep-learning-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/reproducibility-in-deep-learning-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T17:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Gil Shamir and Dong Lin, Research Software Engineers, Google Research 
Ever queried a recommender system and found that the same search only a few moments later or on a different device yields very different results? This is not uncommon and can be frustrating if a person is looking for something specific. As a designer of such a system, it is also not uncommon for the metrics measured to change from design and testing to deployment, bringing into question the utility of the experimental testing phase. Some level of such irreproducibility can be expected as the world changes and new models are deployed. However, this also happens regularly as requests hit duplicates of the same model or models are being refreshed.  
Lack of replicability, where researchers are unable to reproduce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 4, 2022]]></title>
        <id>6e8469ff0f01ab8c8b1e0c9ad99babde49d94aea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-4-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T20:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Welcome to the April 4 edition of the AWS Week in Review. This week, alongside the main launches, I also captured a couple of new capabilities, such as a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63769</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-lean-product-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T18:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product has three parts; this is Part 2. In this blog, we discuss why lean product, what is lean product, how to approach lean product, and then we demonstrate How we apply lean product to build our own lean product in Dojo.  Finally, we ask a question if we should scale process or scale leaders. 
The post DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 2 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pathways Language Model (PaLM): Scaling to 540 Billion Parameters for Breakthrough Performance]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pathways-language-model-palm-scaling-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pathways-language-model-palm-scaling-to.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T16:01:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sharan Narang and Aakanksha Chowdhery, Software Engineers, Google Research 
In recent years, large neural networks trained for language understanding and generation have achieved impressive results across a wide range of tasks. GPT-3 first showed that large language models (LLMs) can be used for few-shot learning and can achieve impressive results without large-scale task-specific data collection or model parameter updating. More recent LLMs, such as GLaM, LaMDA, Gopher, and Megatron-Turing NLG, achieved state-of-the-art few-shot results on many tasks by scaling model size, using sparsely activated modules, and training on larger datasets from more diverse sources. Yet much work remains in understanding the capabilities that emerge with few-shot learning as we push the limits of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Kubernetes Secrets for Flux with HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/manage-kubernetes-secrets-for-flux-with-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/manage-kubernetes-secrets-for-flux-with-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure the Secrets Store CSI driver with HashiCorp Vault to securely inject secrets into Flux or other GitOps tools on Kubernetes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>