<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-27T01:49:51.887Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-06-27T01:49:51.887Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Step Functions Versions and Aliases, EC2 Instances with Graviton3E Processors, and More – June 26, 2023]]></title>
        <id>b5f480df9c754ac5d9a62c25e2a998f30d088412</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-step-functions-versions-and-aliases-ec2-instances-with-graviton3e-processors-and-more-june-26-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s now summer in the northern hemisphere, and you can feel it in London where I live. But let’s not get distracted by the nice weather and go through your AWS updates from the previous seven days. Last Week’s Launches Another interesting week with many announcements! Here are some that got more of my attention: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New tool to secure your GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-26-new-tool-to-secure-your-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-26-new-tool-to-secure-your-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T16:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a new tool to monitor and control the permissions of the repository token for GitHub Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Terraform continuous validation use cases for AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/8-terraform-continuous-validation-use-cases-for-aws-google-cloud-and-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/8-terraform-continuous-validation-use-cases-for-aws-google-cloud-and-azure"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can use Terraform check blocks and continuous validation with AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on AWS to AWS GovCloud in the United States]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-aws-to-aws-govcloud-in-the-us</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-aws-to-aws-govcloud-in-the-us"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is co-authored by Zack Kayyali and Hicham (he-sham) Mourad
 
Deploying Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform Foundation
 
The steps below detail how to install Ansible Automation Platform on AWS United States GovCloud from the AWS Marketplace. The steps to deploy into AWS GovCloud and AWS Commercial cloud are nearly identical. Before starting your deployment process, please ensure the AWS account you are using to deploy has the following IAM roles. These IAM roles are required to deploy the AWS foundation stack offering. The foundation stack offering here refers to the base Ansible Automation Platform 2 deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary Kayyali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Ansible Lightspeed with IBM Watson Code Assistant Technical Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/welcome-to-the-ansible-lightspeed-technical-preview</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/welcome-to-the-ansible-lightspeed-technical-preview"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T12:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of what to expect with the technology preview of Ansible Lightspeed with IBM Watson Code Assistant, a new generative AI service available now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crispiness]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44788</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/748820093/0/sethsblog~Crispiness/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T08:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crisp faces many opponents: entropy, laziness, time, compromise and false shortcuts. And fear. Most of all, fear. Things rarely become crispy on their own. Instead, it requires care and effort. An ume shiso hand roll begins with a crisp piece of nori, but within a minute or two, though the ingredients are the same, it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing an observability solution to gain valuable insights into business operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-solution-valuable-insights-business-operations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-solution-valuable-insights-business-operations"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how businesses can use observability solutions to gain valuable insights into their operations by analyzing data from various sources. They can show how apps perform, where bottlenecks and issues occur, and how users interact with the system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calizo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing an observability solution to gain valuable insights into business operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-solution-valuable-insights-business-operations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-solution-valuable-insights-business-operations"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In my previous articles, I discussed how to design considerations for observability solutions and how observability can augment your security implementation.
In this article, I will discuss how an observability solution can provide valuable insights into your business operations through the collected data from various systems, applications, and services. By using observability tools, businesses can gain a comprehensive view of their entire system, including performance metrics, logs, traces, and other data that can provide insights into potential issues and areas of improvement.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt8cc58f7c181738d4/6495f33c7e68bb5b71abc457/elastic-blog-monitor-behavior.png,elastic-blog-monitor-behavior.png2. Identifying performance bottlenecks,
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calizo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alphabet Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2794/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2794/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/alphabet_notes.png" title="Listen, you're very cute, but if you rearrange the alphabet to put U and I together it will RUIN the spacing!" alt="Listen, you're very cute, but if you rearrange the alphabet to put U and I together it will RUIN the spacing!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A finite ordered set of interesting objects]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46560</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/748647716/0/sethsblog~A-finite-ordered-set-of-interesting-objects/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T15:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The alphabet is one. 26 letters, no more. One order, that’s it. The Beatles are another. John, Paul, George and then Ringo. The Marx Brothers, the Three Stooges, The Supremes. The astrological zodiac gets us to twelve, but I’m having a really difficult time finding a memorable set with more than that. When we start […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When we get to where we’re going]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44771</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/748557542/0/sethsblog~When-we-get-to-where-were-going/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[…perhaps we should stop. Unless the going was the point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Open Source Software Gives You Access to Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84019</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/how-open-source-software-gives-you-access-to-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open source software provides access to innovations and latest technologies. Check out this post to explore some of the ways that open source software gives companies access to innovation.
The post How Open Source Software Gives You Access to Innovation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overstuffed]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44757</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/748311080/0/sethsblog~Overstuffed/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T08:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The empty part of the drawer is what makes it a useful tool. Same goes for a filing cabinet, a toolbox and a calendar. Slack is underrated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.1.3 is released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=365813</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/06/phpstorm-2023-1-3-is-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T19:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new bug-fix update for PhpStorm 2023.1 is now available. You can update to it using the Toolbox App or right from inside the IDE. You can also download PhpStorm 2023.1.3 from the website. Notable changes in this update: The full list of changes is available in the release notes.And as always, please feel free […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preference learning with automated feedback for cache eviction]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/preference-learning-with-automated.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/preference-learning-with-automated.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T19:24:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ramki Gummadi, Software Engineer, Google and Kevin Chen, Software Engineer, YouTube





Caching is a ubiquitous idea in computer science that significantly improves the performance of storage and retrieval systems by storing a subset of popular items closer to the client based on request patterns. An important algorithmic piece of cache management is the decision policy used for dynamically updating the set of items being stored, which has been extensively optimized over several decades, resulting in several efficient and robust heuristics. While applying machine learning to cache policies has shown promising results in recent years (e.g., LRB, LHD, storage applications), it remains a challenge to outperform robust heuristics in a way that can generalize reliably beyond benchmar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A HashiCorp Ambassador at HashiDays London]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-hashicorp-ambassador-at-hashidays-london</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-hashicorp-ambassador-at-hashidays-london"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Ambassador Chris van Meer shares his experiences at HashiDays London.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper and Rider 2023.1.3 – Another Set of Bug-fixes Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=365207</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/06/23/rsrp-and-rd-2023-1-3-bug-fix/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T10:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, ReSharper and Rider just got  another set of bug fixes for the 2023.1 release! Let’s take a look at the most crucial issues resolved. ReSharper ReSharper 2023.1.3 comes with a fix for a performance issue where ReSharper 2023.1.1 would cause Visual Studio to take an excessive amount of time to display the splash […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The right marketing question]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46540</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/748119233/0/sethsblog~The-right-marketing-question/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T08:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wrong question is, “our project isn’t catching on, how do we promote it better?” The right question is a little more nuanced and far more important, “We’re seeking to make a change in part of the world. How do we find the right people and tell them the right (true) story that helps them […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2023.1.3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=355612</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2023/06/2023-1-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T08:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2023.1.3 brings you fixes for disappearing notebook cells, invisible DataFrame rows and cell focus bugs. Download the new version from our website, directly from the IDE, via the free Toolbox App, or use snaps for Ubuntu. Download DataSpell 2023.1.3 Disappearing notebook cells In DataSpell 2023.1, when pasting text into a new notebook cell added […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ciara Byrne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.0 M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/23/spring-modulith-1-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/23/spring-modulith-1-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Testcontainers Support in Spring Boot 3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/23/improved-testcontainers-support-in-spring-boot-3-1</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/23/improved-testcontainers-support-in-spring-boot-3-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garden Path Sentence]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2793/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2793/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/garden_path_sentence.png" title="Arboretum Owner Denied Standing in Garden Path Suit on Grounds Grounds Appealing Appealing" alt="Arboretum Owner Denied Standing in Garden Path Suit on Grounds Grounds Appealing Appealing" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoundStorm: Efficient parallel audio generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/soundstorm-efficient-parallel-audio.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/soundstorm-efficient-parallel-audio.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T18:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zalán Borsos, Research Software Engineer, and Marco Tagliasacchi, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Research







The recent progress in generative AI unlocked the possibility of creating new content in several different domains, including text, vision and audio. These models often rely on the fact that raw data is first converted to a compressed format as a sequence of tokens. In the case of audio, neural audio codecs (e.g., SoundStream or EnCodec) can efficiently compress waveforms to a compact representation, which can be inverted to reconstruct an approximation of the original audio signal. Such a representation consists of a sequence of discrete audio tokens, capturing the local properties of sounds (e.g., phonemes) and their temporal structure (e.g., prosody). By re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.14 brings ACME for PKI, AWS roles, and more improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-14-brings-acme-for-pki-aws-roles-and-more-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-14-brings-acme-for-pki-aws-roles-and-more-improvements"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.14 includes the Vault Secrets Operator GA, ACME PKI, and a new OpenLDAP secrets engine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Machine Learning in Go Have a Future?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=358126</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2023/06/22/does-machine-learning-in-go-have-a-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T13:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was written by an external contributor. Go is an open-source programming language originally designed by Google to optimize the construction and use of system-level services, work easily on large codebases, and utilize multi-core networked machines. Initially introduced in 2009, Go, as a statically typed and compiled programming language, is heavily influenced by C […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the Elastic Agent to monitor Amazon ECS and AWS Fargate with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-monitor-ecs-aws-fargate-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-monitor-ecs-aws-fargate-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll guide you through how to install the Elastic Agent with the AWS Fargate integration as a sidecar container to send host metrics and logs to Elastic Observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexis Roberson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the Elastic Agent to monitor Amazon ECS and AWS Fargate with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-monitor-ecs-aws-fargate-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-monitor-ecs-aws-fargate-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Serverless and AWS ECS Fargate
AWS Fargate is a serverless pay-as-you-go engine used for Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS) to run Docker containers without having to manage servers or clusters. The goal of Fargate is to containerize your application and specify the OS, CPU and memory, networking, and IAM policies needed for launch. Additionally, AWS Fargate can be used with Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS) in a similar manner.

Although the provisioning of servers would be handled by a third party, the need to understand the health and performance of containers within your serverless environment becomes even more vital in identifying root causes and system interruptions. Serverless still requires observability. Elastic Observability can provide observability for not only AWS ECS wit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexis Roberson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Cloud Automation with amazon.aws 6.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-6.0.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-6.0.0"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to Amazon Web Services (AWS) infrastructure automation, the latest release of the certified amazon.aws Collection for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform brings a number of enhancements to improve the overall user experience and speed up the process from development to production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laravel Best Practices: How to Automate Your Routine]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=363697</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/06/laravel-best-practices-how-to-automate-your-routine/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T12:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re a Laravel developer, a web artisan. You want to be more productive, right? In this blog post, you’ll learn how to increase your productivity using PhpStorm with the Laravel Idea plugin. Smart autocompletion One crucial feature that boosts the productivity of Laravel developers is autocompletion for the actions they use on a daily basis. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tania Goral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.1.3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=365419</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/06/2023-1-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T12:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third bug-fix update for version 2023.1 is now available. You can update to this version from inside the IDE, using the Toolbox App, or using snaps if you are a Ubuntu user. You can also download it from our website. Download PyCharm 2023.1.3 Here are the most notable fixes and updates that PyCharm 2023.1.3 brings: You […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peer support]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46533</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/747871169/0/sethsblog~Peer-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T08:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Treasure it when you find it. Offer it when you can. One of the greatest joys of being an author is the other authors. The game theory would indicate that authors are competitors–there are a scarce number of publishers, of bookshelf slots, of readers. But, being the only author in the world wouldn’t just be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/22/spring-boot-3-1-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/22/spring-boot-3-1-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Wilkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.8 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/22/spring-boot-3-0-8-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/22/spring-boot-3-0-8-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Wilkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.13 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/22/spring-boot-2-7-13-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/22/spring-boot-2-7-13-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Wilkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Micrometer lead Tommy Ludwig]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/22/a-bootiful-podcast-micrometer-lead-tommy-ludwig-from-spring-io-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/22/a-bootiful-podcast-micrometer-lead-tommy-ludwig-from-spring-io-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainability is Elastic: 6 months of reflection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/sustainability-elastic-6-months-reflection</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/sustainability-elastic-6-months-reflection"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic has released its first full Sustainability Report. The comprehensive report highlights our advancements in key environmental, social, and governance areas and outlines our operational and product sustainability strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keith Littlejohns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The generative AI societal shift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/generative-ai-societal-shift</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/generative-ai-societal-shift"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Elastic is at the forefront of the Large Language Models revolution –– helping users take LLMs to new heights by providing real-time information and integrating LLMs into search, observability, and security systems for data analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Vestal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transforming defence with Elastic AI and data capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/transforming-defence-elastic-ai-data-capabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/transforming-defence-elastic-ai-data-capabilities"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using the power of its data and AI, the Ministry of Defence (MoD) in the UK can outpace adversaries and gain multi-domain operational efficiency, increase cyber resiliency, and achieve rapid decision-making superiority.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Boschier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainability is Elastic: 6 months of reflection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/sustainability-elastic-6-months-reflection</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/sustainability-elastic-6-months-reflection"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
This week Elastic released its first full Sustainability Report. Comprehensive in scope and topics covered, the report highlights our advancements in key environmental, social, and governance (ESG) areas and outlines our wider operational and product sustainability strategy and future ambition.
Building a stronger Elastic and a better shared future
I just passed the six-month mark as Elastic’s director of sustainability and ESG, which provided the chance to reflect back. One thing I discovered early on is that our leadership team not only supports ESG-related initiatives wholeheartedly, but they also encourage a sustainability mindset that aligns with our values and helps build a stronger Elastic. This has been invaluable. And thanks to our unique Source Code, a clear set of ideas helped…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keith Littlejohns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The generative AI societal shift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/generative-ai-societal-shift</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/generative-ai-societal-shift"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone societal shift: The dawn of a new era,
Once upon a time, not so long ago, the world was a different place. The idea of a "smartphone" was still a novelty, and the mobile phone was primarily a tool for making calls and, perhaps, sending the occasional text message. Yes, we had "smart" phones, but they were simpler, mostly geared toward business users and mostly used for, well, phone stuff. Web browsing? It was there, but light, not something you'd do for hours.

In 2007, a giant wave crashed onto the shores of our everyday lives, and the world has never been the same since. This wave was the iPhone. Despite being initially met with a blend of excitement, skepticism, and even downright dismissal (remember BlackBerry's response?), the iPhone quickly became a societal game-changer.
http…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Vestal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transforming defence with Elastic AI and data capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/transforming-defence-elastic-ai-data-capabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/transforming-defence-elastic-ai-data-capabilities"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
What a time it is for data and the UK Ministry of Defence (MoD), with large language models (LLMs) and artificial intelligence (AI) innovation accelerating at unprecedented speed. 

How quickly can the MoD take operational advantage of these advancements?

Now is the time to unleash the power of data and transform how the MoD approaches cybersecurity to outpace adversaries, gain multi-domain operational efficiency, and of course, attain rapid decision-making superiority. 

We know cybersecurity is a data problem. We know operational observability is a data problem, and we know mission search is also a data problem. This brings me to the punch line: these are all data problems. And the most common form that these use cases tackle is unstructured data — that is, open source intelligence and troves of data in hard-to-reach places. Elastic, because of its foundation as a search platform, has been especially instrumental in helping solve these use cases for the MoD and government.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Boschier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source challenge results from Gamedev.js Jam 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-21-gamedev-js-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-21-gamedev-js-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T22:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlighting 13 of the top games plus source from the latest Gamedev.js jam–by GitHub Star and event organizer, Andrzej Mazur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: AI for Social Good]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/responsible-ai-at-google-research-ai.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/responsible-ai-at-google-research-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T20:57:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jimmy Tobin and Katrin Tomanek, Software Engineers, Google Research, AI for Social Good


Google’s AI for Social Good team consists of researchers, engineers, volunteers, and others with a shared focus on positive social impact. Our mission is to demonstrate AI’s societal benefit by enabling real-world value, with projects spanning work in public health, accessibility, crisis response, climate and energy, and nature and society. We believe that the best way to drive positive change in underserved communities is by partnering with change-makers and the organizations they serve.


 


In this blog post we discuss work done by Project Euphonia, a team within AI for Social Good, that aims to improve automatic speech recognition (ASR) for people with disordered speech. For people with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging code and community]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-21-bridging-code-and-community/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-21-bridging-code-and-community/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T20:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the impact of non-code contributions—and why they are often undervalued, the challenges of using open source in regulated environments, and the art of managing projects at the scale of Kubernetes, now on The ReadME Podcast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting a better, faster code view]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-21-crafting-a-better-faster-code-view/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-21-crafting-a-better-faster-code-view/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T17:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new GitHub Code View brings users many new features to improve the code reading and exploration experiences, and we overcame a number of unique technical hurdles in order to deliver those features without compromising performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s first braiding of non-Abelian anyons]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/the-worlds-first-braiding-of-non.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/the-worlds-first-braiding-of-non.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T17:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Trond Andersen and Yuri Lensky, Research Scientists, Google Quantum AI Team  






Imagine you’re shown two identical objects and then asked to close your eyes. When you open your eyes, you see the same two objects in the same position. How can you determine if they have been swapped back and forth? Intuition and the laws of quantum mechanics agree: If the objects are truly identical, there is no way to tell. 



While this sounds like common sense, it only applies to our familiar three-dimensional world. Researchers have predicted that for a special type of particle, called an anyon, that is restricted to move only in a two-dimensional (2D) plane, quantum mechanics allows for something quite different. Anyons are indistinguishable from one another and some, non-Abelian anyons, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ready or Not? Two Approaches for a Smoother Camunda 7 to Camunda 8 Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83750</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/ready-or-not-two-approaches-for-a-smoother-camunda-7-to-camunda-8-migration/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T16:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two approaches to making it easier to migrate from Camunda 7 to Camunda 8. Read this post to learn which tools you'll need.
The post Ready or Not? Two Approaches for a Smoother Camunda 7 to Camunda 8 Migration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.1.3 Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=363092</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/06/webstorm-2023-1-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T15:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.1.3, the third bug-fix update for WebStorm 2023.1, is now available! You can update to v2023.1.3 by using the Toolbox App, installing it right from the IDE, or downloading it from our website. Volar support for Vue We have some great news for all of you using Vue in WebStorm. We’ve implemented Volar support […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project management]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46067</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/747727124/0/sethsblog~Project-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A project is a promise. It’s about coordinating unknowable future events to deliver something of value. Showing up on time for a meeting is a project (airlines! traffic! weather!) and so is building a skyscraper. That next podcast you’re going to publish is a project, and so is cooking dinner for guests. There’s always uncertainty […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Compose Support in Spring Boot 3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/21/docker-compose-support-in-spring-boot-3-1</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/21/docker-compose-support-in-spring-boot-3-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to remove PII from your Elastic data in 3 easy steps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-remove-pii-elastic-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-remove-pii-elastic-data"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Personally Identifiable Information compliance is an ever increasing challenge for any organization. With Elastic's intuitive ML interface and parsing capabilities, sensitive data may be easily redacted from unstructured data with ease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Titov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to remove PII from your Elastic data in 3 easy steps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-remove-pii-elastic-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-remove-pii-elastic-data"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Personally identifiable information (PII) compliance is an ever-increasing challenge for any organization. Whether you’re in ecommerce, banking, healthcare, or other fields where data is sensitive, PII may inadvertently be captured and stored. Having structured logs enables quick identification, removal, and protection of sensitive data fields easily; but what about unstructured messages? Or perhaps call center transcriptions?
Elasticsearch, with its long experience in machine learning, provides various options to bring in custom models, such as large language models (LLMs), and provides its own models. These models will help implement PII redaction. 
If you would like to learn more about natural language processing, machine learning, and Elastic, please be sure to check out these relate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Titov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Solstice]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2792/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2792/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/summer_solstice.png" title="Then I'll start work on my lunar engines to line the Moon up with the ecliptic so we can have a solar eclipse every month (with a little wobble so they're not always on the equator.)" alt="Then I'll start work on my lunar engines to line the Moon up with the ecliptic so we can have a solar eclipse every month (with a little wobble so they're not always on the equator.)" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 Hpc7g Instances Powered by AWS Graviton3E Processors Optimized for High Performance Computing Workloads]]></title>
        <id>5ea979c45bdfa8e4b408386066d2c67700c1c40d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-hpc7g-instances-powered-by-aws-graviton3e-processors-optimized-for-high-performance-computing-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T20:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2022, Adam Selipsky, CEO of AWS, explained high performance computing (HPC) workloads typically can either be compute-intensive, compute- and networking-intensive, or data- and memory-intensive in his keynote. Compute workloads include weather forecasting, computational fluid dynamics, and financial options pricing. To help with this, you have Amazon EC2 Hpc6a instances, which deliver up […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon EC2 C7gn Instances: Graviton3E Processors and Up To 200 Gbps Network Bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>4b5a7a85829664e1b14fef7adcba05a5d8436262</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c7gn-instances-graviton3e-processors-and-up-to-200-gbps-network-bandwidth/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T20:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The C7gn instances that we previewed last year are now available and you can start using them today. The instances are designed for your most demanding network-intensive workloads (firewalls, virtual routers, load balancers, and so forth), data analytics, and tightly-coupled cluster computing jobs. They are powered by AWS Graviton3E processors and support up to 200 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2023.2 EAP 2 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=364835</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2023/06/dataspell-2023-2-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T18:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second EAP build for DataSpell 2023.2 we improved Jupyter Notebooks synchronization with external applications. To catch up on all of the new features DataSpell 2023.2 will bring, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanislav Garkusha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to streamline and secure your SaaS applications at AWS Applications Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>5dc3826279a8cfb6eabd79bfa44f3c629827141f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/learn-how-to-streamline-and-secure-your-saas-applications-at-aws-applications-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T18:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies continue to adopt software as a service (SaaS) applications at a rapid clip, with recent research showing that the average SaaS portfolio now has at least 200 applications. While organizations purchase these purpose-built tools to make their employees more productive, they now must contend with growing security complexities, context switching, and data silos. If […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Goldstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1.3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=365135</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/06/intellij-idea-2023-1-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T17:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third bug-fix update for v2023.1 is now available. You can update to this version from inside the IDE, using the Toolbox App, or using snaps if you are a Ubuntu user. You can also download it from our website. Here are the most notable fixes and updates that IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1.3 brings: You can find a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toolbox App 2.0 Beta Streamlines Installation and Improves Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=toolbox-app&amp;p=364611</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/toolbox-app/2023/06/toolbox-app-2-0-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T16:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re starting a preview of the biggest update to the Toolbox App yet! We’ve listened to the feedback we’ve received from our users, analyzed the most voted bug reports in our tracker, and refactored the installation layout to address most of the pain points. To try out the Beta, make sure you’re using Toolbox App […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Kropp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Scene Changes in Audiovisual Content]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/77a61d3eaad6</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/detecting-scene-changes-in-audiovisual-content-77a61d3eaad6?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T16:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avneesh Saluja, Andy Yao, Hossein Taghavi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use GitHub Copilot: Prompts, tips, and use cases]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-20-how-to-write-better-prompts-for-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-20-how-to-write-better-prompts-for-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T16:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this prompt guide for GitHub Copilot, two GitHub developer advocates, Rizel and Michelle, will share examples and best practices for communicating your desired results to the AI pair programmer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking the 2023 HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey [Video]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/unpacking-the-2023-hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-video</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/unpacking-the-2023-hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-video"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch this 10-minute video for an insightful overview of the survey’s key findings and how HashiCorp can help your organization make the most of the cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering the New UI]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=364771</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2023/06/mastering-the-new-ui/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T13:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! We’re excited to introduce a new series of blog posts showcasing our favorite RubyMine features. Join us as we explore tips, tricks, and enhancements that will boost your productivity and streamline your development process. In the first blog post, we’ll dive into RubyMine’s freshly-introduced user interface (UI). We revamped the IDE’s look and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Zykova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which team?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44722</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/747381941/0/sethsblog~Which-team/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T08:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Culture seeks shortcuts. The oldest shortcut is: “Friend or foe?” If we know the answer to that, a whole bunch of time gets saved, and fear is reduced as well. The labeling goes beyond which team, cadre, tribe or village someone is part of. It extends to the ways we demonstrate which box we’ve chosen–fashion, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elasticsearch machine learning helps telcos reduce power consumption in 5G networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-machine-learning-telcos-reduce-power-consumption-5g-networks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-machine-learning-telcos-reduce-power-consumption-5g-networks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telcos are exploring various solutions to reduce power consumption in 5G networks. Machine learning from Elasticsearch is one such solution that can help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juergen Obermann,Piotr Kobziakowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elasticsearch machine learning helps telcos reduce power consumption in 5G networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-machine-learning-telcos-reduce-power-consumption-5g-networks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-machine-learning-telcos-reduce-power-consumption-5g-networks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As telcos deploy 5G networks, power consumption has become a significant concern. These networks require a large number of base stations and powerful hardware components to offer higher data rates and improved capacity. As a result, telcos are exploring various solutions to reduce power consumption in 5G networks. Machine learning from Elasticsearch® is one such solution that can help telcos reduce power consumption in several ways.
Intelligent network planning
Machine learning can help telcos analyze data from existing 5G networks, such as user traffic patterns and base station performance, to optimize network planning. By predicting future traffic patterns and base station usage, telcos can build more efficient and power-friendly networks. This can help reduce capital expenditure on ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juergen Obermann,Piotr Kobziakowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.1.1, 6.0.4, 5.8.4, 5.7.9, 5.6.11 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/20/spring-security-6-1-1-6-0-4-5-8-4-5-7-9-5-6-11-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/20/spring-security-6-1-1-6-0-4-5-8-4-5-7-9-5-6-11-released"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Winch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 1.1.1, 1.0.3 and 0.4.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/20/spring-authorization-server-1-1-1-1-0-3-and-0-4-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/20/spring-authorization-server-1-1-1-1-0-3-and-0-4-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Grandja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.1.5 and 1.2.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/20/spring-for-graphql-1-1-5-and-1-2-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/20/spring-for-graphql-1-1-5-and-1-2-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A modern SIEM for whole-of-state cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-siem-whole-of-state-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-siem-whole-of-state-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State CISOs in the US are thinking of "whole-of-state cybersecurity," which requires rethinking technology based on speed and scale, especially for SIEM solutions. Here's what state security leaders should consider when scaling their SIEM solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A modern SIEM for whole-of-state cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-siem-whole-of-state-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-siem-whole-of-state-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
US state and local government agencies continue to contend with a dizzyingly complex IT environment, which includes data silos, tool sprawl, rising cyber threats, and limited availability of cybersecurity experts. In response, many state CISOs are exploring a “whole-of-state” cybersecurity strategy, which aims to bolster their state’s security through centralization and collaboration.  
According to a Deloitte/NASCIO study, 42% of states have instituted legislation or funding for a state-wide cybersecurity program or framework — evidence that a whole-of-state approach is putting down some solid roots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Amazon EC2 Instance Connect Endpoint, Detective, Amazon S3 Dual Layer Encryption, Amazon Verified Permission – June 19, 2023]]></title>
        <id>3652b5bcb9a6bda391b1dd7ad03ab1fb81ac3d06</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-amazon-ec2-instance-connect-endpoint-detective-amazon-s3-dual-layer-encryption-amazon-verified-permission-june-19-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T19:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I’ll meet you at AWS partner’s Jamf Nation Live in Amsterdam where we’re showing how to use Amazon EC2 Mac to deploy your remote developer workstations or configure your iOS CI/CD pipelines in the cloud. Last Week’s Launches While I was traveling last week, I kept an eye on the AWS News. Here […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developers need the right to challenge junk patents]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-19-developers-need-the-right-to-challenge-junk-patents/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-19-developers-need-the-right-to-challenge-junk-patents/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T19:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO) recently proposed rule changes that will make it harder to challenge low quality patents. Without the ability to quickly and efficiently challenge wrongly granted patents, innovation and developers suffer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 223]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67177</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-223/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T18:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the risk of sounding repetitive, sprint 223 was dedicated to resolving bugs. Looks like sprint 224 will be much of the same. We continue to make great progress, but we have a little way to go before the New Boards Hub is ready for general availability.
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 223 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2023.2 EAP 5: Improved User Experience and New Live Templates]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=363868</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2023/06/rubymine-2023-2-eap-5-improved-user-experience-and-new-live-templates/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T18:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest EAP version of RubyMine 2023.2 is now available. You can download it from our website or via the free Toolbox App. We’ll be outlining some of the key improvements in this post. Pinned run configurations in the Run widget To enhance the experience of managing multiple run configurations, we have made it possible […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iryna Pisklyarova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can’t wait]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46490</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/747223817/0/sethsblog~Cant-wait/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T08:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The urgent problem might actually benefit from a short cooling-off period. But important challenges can’t wait. Today is a good day to remember that better is possible, and that we shouldn’t wait for the problem to become easy or fade away. Better begins with each of us, but it evaporates when we settle for less. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bookshelf Sorting]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2791/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2791/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/bookshelf_sorting.png" title="Of course, I sort all my bookshelves the normal way, alphabetically (by first sentence)." alt="Of course, I sort all my bookshelves the normal way, alphabetically (by first sentence)." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at CVPR 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/google-at-cvpr-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/google-at-cvpr-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T18:00:00.018Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shaina Mehta, Program Manager, Google




This week marks the beginning of the premier annual Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition conference (CVPR 2023), held in-person in Vancouver, BC (with additional virtual content). As a leader in computer vision research and a Platinum Sponsor, Google Research will have a strong presence across CVPR 2023 with ~90 papers being presented at the main conference and active involvement in over 40 conference workshops and tutorials.




If you are attending CVPR this year, please stop by our booth to chat with our researchers who are actively exploring the latest techniques for application to various areas of machine perception. Our researchers will also be available to talk about and demo several recent efforts, including on-device ML applic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding agency]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46321</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/747013484/0/sethsblog~Finding-agency/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T08:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first few moves of a chess game give the player almost unlimited freedom. There are countless legal moves, and nothing to constrain the choices that a player makes among them. But as we add leverage to our culture and our organizations, the choices aren’t as easy. Jerry Garcia couldn’t easily change the Grateful Dead’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GoDaddy Implemented a Multi-Region Event-Driven Platform at Scale]]></title>
        <id>a98489d395f0c435cc777fcf89a3a9ff10dd4933</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-godaddy-implemented-a-multi-region-event-driven-platform-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T17:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoDaddy, a leading global provider of domain registration and web hosting services, has served over 84 million domains and 22 million customers since its establishment in 1997. Among its various internal systems, the Customer Signal Platform provides tooling to capture, analyze, and act on customer and product data to drive better business outcomes. With this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speed is all you need: On-device acceleration of large diffusion models via GPU-aware optimizations]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/speed-is-all-you-need-on-device.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/speed-is-all-you-need-on-device.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Juhyun Lee and Raman Sarokin, Software Engineers, Core Systems & Experiences




The proliferation of large diffusion models for image generation has led to a significant increase in model size and inference workloads. On-device ML inference in mobile environments requires meticulous performance optimization and consideration of trade-offs due to resource constraints. Running inference of large diffusion models (LDMs) on-device, driven by the need for cost efficiency and user privacy, presents even greater challenges due to the substantial memory requirements and computational demands of these models.
 

We address this challenge in our work titled “Speed Is All You Need: On-Device Acceleration of Large Diffusion Models via GPU-Aware Optimizations” (to be presented at the CVPR 20…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline Processes by Using Inbound Webhook Connectors as Intermediate Events]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83717&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83717</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/streamline-processes-inbound-webhook-connectors-intermediate-events/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can use our inbound connectors within a process as an Intermediate Event, making your processes more efficient.
The post Streamline Processes by Using Inbound Webhook Connectors as Intermediate Events appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring GitHub with the redesigned navigation, now in public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-15-exploring-github-with-the-redesigned-navigation-now-in-public-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-15-exploring-github-with-the-redesigned-navigation-now-in-public-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T16:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub’s redesigned navigation is enabled for all users as a public beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL zero to hero part 2: getting started with CodeQL]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-15-codeql-zero-to-hero-part-2-getting-started-with-codeql/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-15-codeql-zero-to-hero-part-2-getting-started-with-codeql/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T12:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the basics of CodeQL and how to use it for security research! In this blog, we will teach you how to leverage GitHub’s static analysis tool CodeQL to write custom CodeQL queries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch and data architecture: 4 essential tools for improved analysis and storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-data-architecture-tools-improved-analysis-storage</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-data-architecture-tools-improved-analysis-storage"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​​Organizations are becoming more reliant on data to make effective, evidence-based decisions to drive business outcomes. Learn how to solve challenges with data attribution and analysis and why data from multiple sources is critical.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily McAlister</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving citizen experience with generative AI: Navigating a new era for state and local government]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-citizen-experience-generative-ai-state-local-government</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-citizen-experience-generative-ai-state-local-government"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how the power of generative AI –– when combined with an agency's proprietary data in Elasticsearch –– can lead to improved citizen engagement, public services, employee productivity, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch and data architecture: 4 essential tools for improved analysis and storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-data-architecture-tools-improved-analysis-storage</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-data-architecture-tools-improved-analysis-storage"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Organizations are becoming increasingly more reliant on data to make effective, evidence-based decisions to drive business outcomes. Whether this be assessing market conditions and improving customer experience, ensuring application uptime, or securing an organization, data from multiple sources — including consumers and internal systems — is critical to day-to-day operations. 

This data-driven approach requires organizations to collect, store, and analyze mountainous volumes of data at speed for timely decision making. Often this means performing correlation and analysis across multiple sources and formats of varying degrees of complexity at scale. 

Elasticsearch® provides the scalability and flexibility to ingest, store, and search these data sets to find relevant and actionable insi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily McAlister</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving citizen experience with generative AI: Navigating a new era for state and local government]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-citizen-experience-generative-ai-state-local-government</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-citizen-experience-generative-ai-state-local-government"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Last week, I wanted to find out the process for my fifteen year old daughter to get her first driver's license. Sounds simple enough. However, I ended up spending a good portion of my weekend searching for definitive answers — navigating multiple websites, without the option of asking a real, live person. In the very near future, I'll simply be able to ask a chatbot. The chatbot, using its natural language model trained on relevant government data, would provide a simple, step-by-step guide, explaining the entire process, required documents, and applicable fees. 

Using generative artificial intelligence (GAI), state and local governments have the potential to build applications that can interact with citizens in natural language, answering their questions accurately and instantly. Such …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Forms Faster with Camunda Form Builder and Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83625&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83625</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/build-forms-faster-camunda-form-builder-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can take advantage of generative AI to build forms faster and incorporate them into your processes.
The post Build Forms Faster with Camunda Form Builder and Generative AI appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: May 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-14-github-availability-report-may-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-14-github-availability-report-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May, we experienced four incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. This report also sheds light into three April incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover How AWS Designed Silicon Fuels Customer Outcomes at AWS Silicon Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>bb29bbbb082903bdd1939aafdeb231b3d1b0b260</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/discover-how-aws-designed-silicon-fuels-customer-outcomes-at-aws-silicon-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We hope you will join us on Wednesday, June 21, for a free-to-attend online event, AWS Silicon Innovation Day. AWS will stream the event simultaneously across multiple platforms, including LinkedIn Live, Twitter, YouTube, and Twitch. AWS Silicon Innovation Day is a one-day virtual event on June 21, 2023, that will allow you to better understand […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating Netflix to GraphQL Safely]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8e1e4d4f1e72</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/migrating-netflix-to-graphql-safely-8e1e4d4f1e72?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T17:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jennifer Shin, Tejas Shikhare, Will Emmanuel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reconstructing indoor spaces with NeRF]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/reconstructing-indoor-spaces-with-nerf.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/reconstructing-indoor-spaces-with-nerf.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marcos Seefelder, Software Engineer, and Daniel Duckworth, Research Software Engineer, Google Research




When choosing a venue, we often find ourselves with questions like the following: Does this restaurant have the right vibe for a date? Is there good outdoor seating? Are there enough screens to watch the game? While photos and videos may partially answer questions like these, they are no substitute for feeling like you’re there, even when visiting in person isn't an option.



Immersive experiences that are interactive, photorealistic, and multi-dimensional stand to bridge this gap and recreate the feel and vibe of a space, empowering users to naturally and intuitively find the information they need. To help with this, Google Maps launched Immersive View, which uses advances in machin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第231話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361338687718</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361338687718"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[June patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67125</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/june-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T22:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1
Azure DevOps Server 2022
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 Patch 1
The post June patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.11.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83469&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83469</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/camunda-optimize-3-11-alpha2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the latest release of Camunda Optimize. Optimize makes it possible to evaluate the success of your process automation initiative.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.11.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating Critical Traffic At Scale with No Downtime — Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4b1c8c7155c1</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/migrating-critical-traffic-at-scale-with-no-downtime-part-2-4b1c8c7155c1?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shyam Gala, Javier Fernandez-Ivern, Anup Rokkam Pratap, Devang Shah]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling delightful user experiences via predictive models of human attention]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/enabling-delightful-user-experiences.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/enabling-delightful-user-experiences.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:18:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Junfeng He, Senior Research Scientist, and Kai Kohlhoff, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research




People have the remarkable ability to take in a tremendous amount of information (estimated to be ~1010 bits/s entering the retina) and selectively attend to a few task-relevant and interesting regions for further processing (e.g., memory, comprehension, action). Modeling human attention (the result of which is often called a saliency model) has therefore been of interest across the fields of neuroscience, psychology, human-computer interaction (HCI) and computer vision. The ability to predict which regions are likely to attract attention has numerous important applications in areas like graphics, photography, image compression and processing, and the measurement of visual quali…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon S3 Dual-Layer Server-Side Encryption with Keys Stored in AWS Key Management Service (DSSE-KMS)]]></title>
        <id>39a5ab2cc8c64f5065441628593ff4c960f92836</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-s3-dual-layer-server-side-encryption-with-keys-stored-in-aws-key-management-service-dsse-kms/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are launching Amazon S3 dual-layer server-side encryption with keys stored in AWS Key Management Service (DSSE-KMS), a new encryption option in S3 that applies two layers of encryption to objects when they are uploaded to an S3 bucket. DSSE-KMS is designed to meet National Security Agency CNSSP 15 for FIPS compliance and Data-at-Rest Capability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at AWS re:Inforce: Zero trust security and secrets sync with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-re-inforce-zero-trust-security-and-secrets-sync</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-re-inforce-zero-trust-security-and-secrets-sync"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp is at AWS re:Inforce sharing expert talks, product demos, and several news announcements..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify How You Manage Authorization in Your Applications with Amazon Verified Permissions – Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>a981b6168d5668e3fdbb5ece89da38241976219a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-how-you-manage-authorization-in-your-applications-with-amazon-verified-permissions-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T16:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing a new application or integrating an existing one into a new environment, user authentication and authorization require significant effort to be correctly implemented. In the past, you would have built your own authentication system, but today you can use an external identity provider like Amazon Cognito. Yet, authorization logic is typically implemented in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Survey reveals AI’s impact on the developer experience]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-13-survey-reveals-ais-impact-on-the-developer-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-13-survey-reveals-ais-impact-on-the-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T15:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We surveyed 500 U.S.-based developers at companies with 1,000-plus employees about how managers should consider developer productivity, collaboration, and AI coding tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Kerberos for Windows in Ansible Automation Platform 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/using-kerberos-for-windows-in-ansible-automation-platform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/using-kerberos-for-windows-in-ansible-automation-platform-2"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kerberos is often the preferred authentication method for managing Windows servers in a domain environment. Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform has allowed customers to leverage Kerberos authentication for a number of years now. So why revisit this subject?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Vault Secrets public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-vault-secrets-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-vault-secrets-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Secrets is a new SaaS-based secrets management platform that enables developers to centrally store, access, and sync secrets when and where they need them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault Secrets Operator for Kubernetes now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-secrets-operator-for-kubernetes-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-secrets-operator-for-kubernetes-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vault Secrets Operator implements a first-class Kubernetes Operator for Vault, along with CRDs responsible for synchronizing Vault secrets to Kubernetes Secrets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Boundary session recording, self-managed Boundary Enterprise, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-13-introduces-ssh-session-recording-boundary-enterprise-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-13-introduces-ssh-session-recording-boundary-enterprise-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Additional new HashiCorp Boundary 0.13 capabilities include LDAP auth method, customer-specified HCP Boundary maintenance windows, and other improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Cloud capabilities to import, view, and manage infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-cloud-capabilities-to-import-view-and-manage-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-cloud-capabilities-to-import-view-and-manage-infrastructure"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds an explorer for workspace visibility and upcoming ephemeral workspaces, while bringing checks into continuous validation and config-driven import from Terraform 1.5.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.16 enhances service mesh reliability, user experience, and security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-16-enhances-service-mesh-reliability-user-experience-and-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-16-enhances-service-mesh-reliability-user-experience-and-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.16 adds new reliability, scalability, security, service mesh UX, extensibility, and service discovery capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Consul management plane with  cloud-based observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-consul-management-plane-with-cloud-based-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-consul-management-plane-with-cloud-based-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HCP Consul management plane now offers deeper insights to your Consul deployments via cloud-based observability and seamlessly links new and existing self-managed Consul clusters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Automate DLQ Redrive for SQS, Lambda Supports Ruby 3.2, and More – June 12, 2023]]></title>
        <id>47ede5cd57805e92230d6b074902e95e9f86e431</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-automate-dlq-redrive-for-sqs-lambda-supports-ruby-3-2-and-more-june-12-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I’m boarding a plane for Madrid. I will attend the AWS Summit Madrid this Thursday, and I will take Serverlesspresso with me. Serverlesspresso is a demo that we take to events, in where you can learn how to build event-driven architectures with serverless. If you are visiting an AWS Summit, most probably you will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Escrow Buddy: An open-source tool from Netflix for remediation of missing FileVault keys in MDM]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/815aef5107cd</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/escrow-buddy-an-open-source-tool-from-netflix-for-remediation-of-missing-filevault-keys-in-mdm-815aef5107cd?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix has open-sourced Escrow Buddy, which helps Security and IT teams ensure they have valid FileVault recovery keys for all their Macs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.5 brings config-driven import and checks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-5-brings-config-driven-import-and-checks</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-5-brings-config-driven-import-and-checks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform 1.5 is now generally available, featuring a config-driven import workflow and a new language primitive for infrastructure validations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Move Payment Processing to the Cloud with AWS Payment Cryptography]]></title>
        <id>c1170395355163b53838018742052c096320018c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-move-payment-processing-to-the-cloud-with-aws-payment-cryptography/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T15:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptography is everywhere in our daily lives. If you’re reading this blog, you’re using HTTPS, an extension of HTTP that uses encryption to secure communications. On AWS, multiple services and capabilities help you manage keys and encryption, such as: AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS), which you can use to create and protect keys to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey 2023: Maturity drives operational efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-maturity-drives-operational-efficiency</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-maturity-drives-operational-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite macroeconomic pressure, cloud-mature companies — as measured by technological and operational best practices — boosted cloud investment and realized better business outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to Approvals and Checks]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67096</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/updates-to-approvals-and-checks/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T07:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approvals and Checks provide increased security to your YAML pipelines. They allow you to control if a pipeline run is allowed to access a resource.
The post Updates to Approvals and Checks appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silviu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep-Dive into the Architecture of Connectors]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83340&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83340</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/architecture-connectors/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T19:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this deep-dive into the architecture of Camunda Connectors. Learn about custom Connectors, Connector reusability, and more.
The post A Deep-Dive into the Architecture of Connectors appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagen Editor and EditBench: Advancing and evaluating text-guided image inpainting]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/imagen-editor-and-editbench-advancing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/imagen-editor-and-editbench-advancing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T19:09:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Su Wang and Ceslee Montgomery, Research Engineers, Google Research





In the last few years, text-to-image generation research has seen an explosion of breakthroughs (notably, Imagen, Parti, DALL-E 2, etc.) that have naturally permeated into related topics. In particular, text-guided image editing (TGIE) is a practical task that involves editing generated and photographed visuals rather than completely redoing them. Quick, automated, and controllable editing is a convenient solution when recreating visuals would be time-consuming or infeasible (e.g., tweaking objects in vacation photos or perfecting fine-grained details on a cute pup generated from scratch). Further, TGIE represents a substantial opportunity to improve training of foundational models themselves. Multimodal mode…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: dl.k8s.io to adopt a Content Delivery Network]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/06/09/dl-adopt-cdn/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/06/09/dl-adopt-cdn/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Arnaud Meukam (VMware), Hannah Aubry (Fastly), Frederico
Muñoz (SAS Institute)
We're happy to announce that dl.k8s.io, home of the official Kubernetes
binaries, will soon be powered by Fastly.
Fastly is known for its high-performance content delivery network (CDN) designed
to deliver content quickly and reliably around the world. With its powerful
network, Fastly will help us deliver official Kubernetes binaries to users
faster and more reliably than ever before.
The decision to use Fastly was made after an extensive evaluation process in
which we carefully evaluated several potential content delivery network
providers. Ultimately, we chose Fastly because of their commitment to the open
internet and proven track record of delivering fast and secure digital
experiences to some of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the latest AWS Heroes – June 2023]]></title>
        <id>e9ae654d1e07cf92fd2b19f7642aa831e76734c1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-latest-aws-heroes-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T19:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Heroes dedicate their time to help others build better and faster on AWS. Heroes support and give back to the community in a variety of ways: contributing to open source projects, organizing AWS Community Days, speaking at conferences, leading workshops, mentoring builders, hosting meetups, and much more. Please welcome and say hello to our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The evolution of quality assurance and how Azure Test Plans is driving the future of manual testing]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67073</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/the-evolution-of-quality-assurance-and-how-azure-test-plans-is-driving-the-future-of-manual-testing/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Deming Prize from Japan is the highest honour in Total Quality Management in the world. Japanese products are known for their superior quality, but it wasn’t always the case. In the 1950s fresh out of defeat in the World War 2,
The post The evolution of quality assurance and how Azure Test Plans is driving the future of manual testing appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravi Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Set of APIs for Amazon SQS Dead-Letter Queue Redrive]]></title>
        <id>7b5e7954e50551cca8437cf748cfe4d427841232</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/a-new-set-of-apis-for-amazon-sqs-dead-letter-queue-redrive/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we launch a new set of APIs for Amazon SQS. These new APIs allow you to manage dead-letter queue (DLQ) redrive programmatically. You can now use the AWS SDKs or the AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI) to programmatically move messages from the DLQ to their original queue, or to a custom queue destination, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible for Disaster Recovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-for-disaster-recovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-for-disaster-recovery"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disaster Recovery" class="hs-featured-image" style="width:auto !important; max-width:50%; float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;">  
 
Overview
 
When we get into the nuts and bolts of implementing a disaster recovery (DR) plan, an important step is to evaluate the tech stack that’s hosting the critical applications. The techstack oftentimes determines the order of operations and execution needed to effect the DR. Most organizations have the following tech stack pattern for their data centers:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>achenamp@redhat.com (Ajay Chenampara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluating speech synthesis in many languages with SQuId]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/evaluating-speech-synthesis-in-many.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/evaluating-speech-synthesis-in-many.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T18:07:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Thibault Sellam, Research Scientist, Google





Previously, we presented the 1,000 languages initiative and the Universal Speech Model with the goal of making speech and language technologies available to billions of users around the world. Part of this commitment involves developing high-quality speech synthesis technologies, which build upon projects such as VDTTS and AudioLM, for users that speak many different languages.






listening tests, during which dozens of annotators listen to the utterances one after the other to determine how natural they sound. While humans are still unbeaten at detecting whether a piece of text sounds natural, this process can be impractical — especially in the early stages of research projects, when engineers need rapid feedback to test and re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual captions: Using large language models to augment video conferences with dynamic visuals]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/visual-captions-using-large-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/visual-captions-using-large-language.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T16:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ruofei Du, Research Scientist, and Alex Olwal, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Augmented Reality




Recent advances in video conferencing have significantly improved remote video communication through features like live captioning and noise cancellation. However, there are various situations where dynamic visual augmentation would be useful to better convey complex and nuanced information. For example, when discussing what to order at a Japanese restaurant, your friends could share visuals that would help you feel more confident about ordering the “Sukiyaki”. Or when talking about your recent family trip to San Francisco, you may want to show a photo from your personal album.




In “Visual Captions: Augmenting Verbal Communication With On-the-fly Visuals”, presented at …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring the Vault Secrets Operator with Prometheus and Grafana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/monitoring-the-vault-secrets-operator-with-prometheus-and-grafana</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/monitoring-the-vault-secrets-operator-with-prometheus-and-grafana"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use the Prometheus Operator with the new Vault Secrets Operator for Kubernetes to monitor secrets in a Grafana dashboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.20.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83178&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83178</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/camunda-automation-platform-7-20-0-alpha2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next alpha release of Camunda Automation Runtime 7.20 is here, with new features, security patches and bug fixes.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.20.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Camunda Platform 8 to Orchestrate Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83146&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83146</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/how-to-use-camunda-platform-8-orchestrate-microservices/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this fun example using Camunda Platform 8 to coordinate the use of several popular internet services, providing a nice end-user experience. 
The post How to use Camunda Platform 8 to Orchestrate Microservices appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Paroulek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Amazon Security Lake Now GA, New Actions on AWS Fault Injection Simulator, and More – June 5, 2023]]></title>
        <id>150a33c67132a6adb31e40c0e37dd808c3b9a192</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-amazon-security-lake-now-ga-new-actions-on-aws-fault-injection-simulator-and-more-june-5-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T20:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Wednesday, I traveled to Cape Town to speak at the .Net Developer User Group. My colleague Francois Bouteruche also gave a talk but joined virtually. I enjoyed my time there—what an amazing community! Join the group in order to learn about upcoming events. Now onto the AWS updates from last week. There was a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REST vs GraphQL vs gRPC: Which API is Right for Your Project?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=82149&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=82149</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/rest-vs-graphql-vs-grpc-which-api-for-your-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T18:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the difference between REST, GraphQL and gRPC. Understand the pros and cons and top use cases of each API to help you choose the right one.
The post REST vs GraphQL vs gRPC: Which API is Right for Your Project? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Frame Rate Playback]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6c87836a948</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/native-frame-rate-playback-6c87836a948?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T16:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article talks about a novel HDMI technology and how it is used within the Netflix Application to improve a user’s experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 7’s Road to Jakarta EE 10]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83116&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83116</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/camunda-platform-7-road-to-jakarta-ee-10/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-03T00:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the path we've taken to support Jakarta EE 10 on Wildfly 27 as smoothly as possible for our customers.
The post Camunda Platform 7’s Road to Jakarta EE 10 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kelemen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVFormer: Injecting vision into frozen speech models for zero-shot AV-ASR]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/avformer-injecting-vision-into-frozen.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/avformer-injecting-vision-into-frozen.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Arsha Nagrani and Paul Hongsuck Seo, Research Scientists, Google Research






Automatic speech recognition (ASR) is a well-established technology that is widely adopted for various applications such as conference calls, streamed video transcription and voice commands. While the challenges for this technology are centered around noisy audio inputs, the visual stream in multimodal videos (e.g., TV, online edited videos) can provide strong cues for improving the robustness of ASR systems — this is called audiovisual ASR (AV-ASR).
 

Although lip motion can provide strong signals for speech recognition and is the most common area of focus for AV-ASR, the mouth is often not directly visible in videos in the wild (e.g., due to egocentric viewpoints, face coverings, and low resolution…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS DMS Serverless: Automatically Provisions and Scales Capacity for Migration and Data Replication]]></title>
        <id>11cf7a26044d162c01f7bcb7a694b6e89decc031</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-dms-serverless-automatically-provisions-and-scales-capacity-for-migration-and-data-replication/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T23:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the vast amount of data being created today, organizations are moving to the cloud to take advantage of the security, reliability, and performance of fully managed database services. To facilitate database and analytics migrations, you can use AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS). First launched in 2016, AWS DMS offers a simple migration process […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring the Successful Launch of Ads on Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f99490fdf1ba</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/ensuring-the-successful-launch-of-ads-on-netflix-f99490fdf1ba?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T19:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jose Fernandez, Ed Barker, Hank Jacobs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented visual-language pre-training]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/retrieval-augmented-visual-language-pre.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/retrieval-augmented-visual-language-pre.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ziniu Hu, Student Researcher, and Alireza Fathi, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception Team





Large-scale models, such as T5, GPT-3, PaLM, Flamingo and PaLI, have demonstrated the ability to store substantial amounts of knowledge when scaled to tens of billions of parameters and trained on large text and image datasets. These models achieve state-of-the-art results on downstream tasks, such as image captioning, visual question answering and open vocabulary recognition. Despite such achievements, these models require a massive volume of data for training and end up with a tremendous number of parameters (billions in many cases), resulting in significant computational requirements. Moreover, the data used to train these models can become outdated, requiring re-training…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Snowball Edge Storage Optimized Devices with More Storage and Bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>bc2108141ac815b7f74d0e72d658b6327572e9bf</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-snowball-edge-storage-optimized-devices-with-more-storage-and-bandwidth/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T20:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Snow Family devices are used to cost-effectively move data to the cloud and to process data at the edge. The enhanced Snowball Edge Storage Optimized devices are designed for your petabyte-scale data migration projects, with 210 terabytes of NVMe storage and the ability to transfer up to 1.5 gigabytes of data per second. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large sequence models for software development activities]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/large-sequence-models-for-software.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/large-sequence-models-for-software.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:13:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Petros Maniatis and Daniel Tarlow, Research Scientists, Google




Software isn’t created in one dramatic step. It improves bit by bit, one little step at a time — editing, running unit tests, fixing build errors, addressing code reviews, editing some more, appeasing linters, and fixing more errors — until finally it becomes good enough to merge into a code repository. Software engineering isn’t an isolated process, but a dialogue among human developers, code reviewers, bug reporters, software architects and tools, such as compilers, unit tests, linters and static analyzers. 




Today we describe DIDACT (​​Dynamic Integrated Developer ACTivity), which is a methodology for training large machine learning (ML) models for software development. The novelty of DIDACT is that it uses …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown editor for comments (preview)]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67042</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/markdown-editor-for-comments-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T15:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are delighted to announce the long-awaited private preview of the new Markdown editor for the work item discussion. This exciting feature empowers you to utilize the Markdown syntax and editor for all future comments. The Markdown editor aligns with the same experience you encounter in other parts of the product,
The post Markdown editor for comments (preview) appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第230話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361290517894</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361290517894"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 222]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67023</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-222/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T17:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This sprint marked another milestone for New Boards. We successfully activated the “Try the New Boards Hub” message for a large chunk of customers. As a result, a greater number of users have had the opportunity to engage with the New Boards Hub and share feedback.
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 222 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – AWS Wickr, Amazon Redshift, Generative AI, and More – May 29, 2023]]></title>
        <id>fe3d1e8a253e9523034a3a21219b3a0a80c584ae</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-aws-wickr-amazon-redshift-generative-ai-and-more-may-29-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T21:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This edition of Week in Review marks the end of the month of May. In addition, we just finished all of the in-person AWS Summits in Asia-Pacific and Japan starting from AWS Summit Sydney and AWS Summit Tokyo in April to AWS Summit ASEAN, AWS Summit Seoul, and AWS Summit Mumbai in May. Thank you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>