<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-03-30T01:24:07.772Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-03-30T01:24:07.773Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Validating Admission Policies: A Practical Example]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/30/kubescape-validating-admission-policy-library/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/30/kubescape-validating-admission-policy-library/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Craig Box (ARMO), Ben Hirschberg (ARMO)
Admission control is an important part of the Kubernetes control plane, with several internal
features depending on the ability to approve or change an API object as it is submitted to the
server. It is also useful for an administrator to be able to define business logic, or policies,
regarding what objects can be admitted into a cluster. To better support that use case, Kubernetes
introduced external admission control in
v1.7.
In addition to countless custom, internal implementations, many open source projects and commercial
solutions implement admission controllers with user-specified policy, including
Kyverno and Open Policy Agent’s
Gatekeeper.
While admission controllers for policy have seen adoption, there are blockers for their widespr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault Secrets Operator: A new method for Kubernetes integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-secrets-operator-a-new-method-for-kubernetes-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-secrets-operator-a-new-method-for-kubernetes-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vault Secrets Operator implements a first-class Kubernetes Operator pattern for HashiCorp Vault along with a set of CRDs responsible for synchronizing Vault secrets to Kubernetes Secrets natively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Ecosystem passes 3,000 providers with over 250 partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-ecosystem-passes-3-000-providers-with-over-250-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-ecosystem-passes-3-000-providers-with-over-250-partners"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform integrations ecosystem has reached a new milestone, surpassing 3,000 providers in the registry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opening the pod bay door]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45532</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/733117916/0/sethsblog~Opening-the-pod-bay-door/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A brand new episode of Akimbo this week, all about artificial intelligence. Part one of of two on mediocrity and the choices we’re going to need to make. And, a while in the making, an experimental AI chat bot that has been trained on all 5,000,000 words of this blog. You can find it here. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Context Propagation with Project Reactor 2 - The bumpy road of Spring Cloud Sleuth]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/29/context-propagation-with-project-reactor-2-the-bumpy-road-of-spring-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/29/context-propagation-with-project-reactor-2-the-bumpy-road-of-spring-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dariusz Jędrzejczyk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hexagonal spatial analytics in Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/hexagonal-spatial-analytics-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/hexagonal-spatial-analytics-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 8.7 can do some very cool geo-spatial aggregations over a hexagonal grid, which has nice advantages over the existing rectangular grid. This feature has been introduced over the last few releases and is now ready for prime time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Taverner,Ignacio Vera Sequeiros,Nathan Reese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hexagonal spatial analytics in Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/hexagonal-spatial-analytics-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/hexagonal-spatial-analytics-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elasticsearch 8.7.0 can do some very cool geo-spatial aggregations over a hexagonal grid, which has nice advantages over the existing rectangular grid we’ve been using for years. This feature has been introduced over the last few releases and is now really worth bragging about.

How did we get there? In 2018 Uber announced it had open sourced the H3 library, enabling hexagonal tiling of the planet for much better analytics of the company’s traffic and regional pricing models.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blta3da2d14ce40fea0/641de54c05105b4fc3bf4f86/blog-elastic-hexagonal-tiling.png,blog-elastic-hexagonal-tiling.png,
In late 2021, we evaluated the option of porting the Uber H3 library from C to Java for possible inclusion in Elasticsearch. This project went …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Taverner,Ignacio Vera Sequeiros,Nathan Reese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualifications]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2756/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2756/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/qualifications.png" title="'So how DID you go from working at the employment records office to becoming president of MIT and CEO of IBM?' 'I guess I just have an eye for opportunities.'" alt="'So how DID you go from working at the employment records office to becoming president of MIT and CEO of IBM?' 'I guess I just have an eye for opportunities.'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging transfer learning for large scale differentially private image classification]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/leveraging-transfer-learning-for-large.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/leveraging-transfer-learning-for-large.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T18:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Harsh Mehta, Software Engineer, and Walid Krichene, Research Scientist, Google Research  
Large deep learning models are becoming the workhorse of a variety of critical machine learning (ML) tasks. However, it has been shown that without any protection it is plausible for bad actors to attack a variety of models, across modalities, to reveal information from individual training examples. As such, it’s essential to protect against this sort of information leakage. 

Differential privacy (DP) provides formal protection against an attacker who aims to extract information about the training data. The most popular method for DP training in deep learning is differentially private stochastic gradient descent (DP-SGD). The core recipe implements a common theme in DP: “fuzzing” an algorit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=336803</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/03/intellij-idea-2023-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T18:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 is now available, and it comes with a host of improvements and valuable new features! You can download the new version from our website, update directly from the IDE or via the free Toolbox App, or use snaps for Ubuntu. IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 includes refinements for the new UI, which has been […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing self-service SBOMs]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-03-28-introducing-self-service-sboms/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-03-28-introducing-self-service-sboms/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T17:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers and compliance teams get a new SBOM generation tool for cloud repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Galaxy 2023: Empower developer teams with a new developer experience]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-03-28-github-galaxy-2023-empower-developer-teams-with-a-new-developer-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-03-28-github-galaxy-2023-empower-developer-teams-with-a-new-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T17:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how GitHub’s one, integrated platform–powered by AI and secure at every step—helps developer teams be more productive, collaborative, and efficient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.1: Improved New UI, TypeScript Support in Vue Templates, Astro Support, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=333788</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/03/webstorm-2023-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T15:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our first major release of 2023 is here! This version includes lots of new features and improvements to the IDE. You’ll find support for Astro, Tailwind CSS configuration, TypeScript support for Vue template expressions, refinements to the new UI, and much more. DOWNLOAD WEBSTORM 2023.1 If you only have a few minutes to explore what’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the GitHub Actions extension for VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-03-28-announcing-the-github-actions-extension-for-vs-code/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-03-28-announcing-the-github-actions-extension-for-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T15:09:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to announce the release of the public beta of the official GitHub Actions VS Code extension, which provides support for authoring and editing workflows and helps you manage workflow runs without leaving your IDE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.1 RC2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=337285</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/03/phpstorm-2023-1-rc2/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T14:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second release candidate for PhpStorm 2023.1 is now available. It’s the final build before the stable release. Unlike EAP builds, this RC requires you to have a valid PhpStorm license. Let’s take a brief look at some of the most interesting improvements coming in v2023.1: 3v4l.org integration New UI (Beta) Performance improvements Data Flow […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2023.1 Quality Release]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=335116</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2023/03/28/datagrip-2023-1-quality-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T12:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello!  For DataGrip 2023.1, we focused entirely on quality. We’ve fixed many bugs that had accumulated in our public issue tracker (not the most fun part of the job, but important nonetheless). While there won’t be any new features for you to explore this time, we hope you’ll notice improvements in your daily work with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking the Sports-Industrial Complex]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45523</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/732994307/0/sethsblog~Rethinking-the-SportsIndustrial-Complex/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[School sports can have some valuable outputs: And yet, many schools act as if all they have is a trophy shortage. They bench kids who might not (yet) have the physical attributes necessary to win, or they build huge stadiums, go on long road trips, berate students that make an error or simply act as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The producer-consumer infrastructure model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-producer-consumer-infrastructure-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-producer-consumer-infrastructure-model"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure producers and consumers require very different capabilities from their automation tools. Vendors need to provide a flexible infrastructure as code solution that meets users at their different levels of expertise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - March 28th, 202]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/28/this-week-in-spring-march-28th-202</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/28/this-week-in-spring-march-28th-202"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Context Propagation with Project Reactor 1 - The Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/28/context-propagation-with-project-reactor-1-the-basics</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/28/context-propagation-with-project-reactor-1-the-basics"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dariusz Jędrzejczyk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability: Built for open technologies like Kubernetes, OpenTelemetry, Prometheus, Istio, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/kubernetes-k8s-observability-elasticsearch-cncf</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/kubernetes-k8s-observability-elasticsearch-cncf"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s long history in open source means that our observability solution integrates easily with popular open source CNCF projects like Kubernetes, OpenTelemetry, Prometheus, Istio, and more. Learn why open standards are crucial to the future of your observability platform!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KubeCon Europe 2023: Kubernetes, OpenTelemetry, Istio, and more with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/2023-kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/2023-kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet up with the experts at Elastic for any of your Kubernetes observability or security questions! We’ll have some great demos to help you understand how Elasticsearch can help, along with some fun swag.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Observability Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability: Built for open technologies like Kubernetes, OpenTelemetry, Prometheus, Istio, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/kubernetes-k8s-observability-elasticsearch-cncf</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/kubernetes-k8s-observability-elasticsearch-cncf"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As an operations engineer (SRE, IT Operations, DevOps), managing technology and data sprawl is an ongoing challenge. Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) projects are helping minimize sprawl and standardize technology and data, from Kubernetes, OpenTelemetry, Prometheus, Istio, and more. 

Kubernetes and OpenTelemetry are becoming the de facto standard for deploying and monitoring a cloud native application. Regardless of what cloud you use, Kubernetes provides the ability to deploy anywhere and OpenTelemetry gives you the opportunity to use any observability tool of choice, without having to re-instrument.  

As a single platform, Elastic helps SREs unify and correlate limitless telemetry data, including metrics, logs, and traces, into a single datastore, Elasticsearch. By then appl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KubeCon Europe 2023: Kubernetes, OpenTelemetry, Istio, and more with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/2023-kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/2023-kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
KubeCon Europe 2023 is right around the corner, and we look forward to meeting you in person in Amsterdam this year! We love talking about technology and finding answers to your problems, whether you need help around observability and security for your Kubernetes environments or want to learn more about OpenTelemetry, Istio, machine learning, and beyond. 
What can you expect from Elastic at KubeCon EMEA 2023? 
Dive into all things Elastic, and be sure to drop by our booth #G3 at the RAI Convention Center to chat with our engineers, solution architects, developer advocates, and Community team. We’ll have all the usual cool Elastic swag, along with some great demos of what Elastic can do for your observability and security needs.

If you’d like some individual time with one of our experts, feel free to schedule a meeting with us! We also have an Elastic User Group meetup running on April 18th (the first day of KubeCon Europe), in our Elastic office in Amsterdam, located at Keizersgracht 281, 1016 ED Amsterdam.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt6bdef75632f75ba8/642312aa18bad210b77f80ec/blog-elastic-amsterdam-user-group.png,blog-elastic-amsterdam-user-group.png,
Doors open at 17.30, and the presentations begin at 18.00. Food, refreshments, and networking to follow. If you weren’t familiar, Elasticsearch was founded in Amsterdam back in 2012!   

If you’re interested in learning more about monitoring your Kubernetes with Elastic Observability, check out our resource links below. We will see you soon in Amsterdam and look forward to connecting with the community again!

Elastic’s support for Kubernetes and OpenTelemetry:

Elastic Observability: Built for open technologies like Kubernetes, OpenTelemetry, Prometheus, Istio, and more
The basics of observing Kubernetes
Managing Kubernetes cluster with Elastic Observability
How to monitor Kubernetes Clusters with Elastic
Modern Observability and security on Kubernetes with Elastic and OpenTelemetry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Observability Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of Step-by-Step Guides for Amazon Connect Agent Workspace]]></title>
        <id>6042ead436a3e7e535833ae688a6be1bd85467e5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-general-availability-of-step-by-step-guides-for-amazon-connect-agent-workspace/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T20:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2022 we announced the availability of step-by-step guides for Amazon Connect agent workspace in preview. My colleagues who collaborated to write the announcement post wrote about some of the challenges that contact centers face with training new agents to get up to speed with their agent desktop. They also mentioned that until […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How French Broadcaster TF1 Used AWS Cloud Technology and Expertise to Bring the FIFA World Cup to Millions]]></title>
        <id>f6b8b5588b3c1c2f89dc45e1ebb462cb3a116aa7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-french-broadcaster-tf1-used-aws-cloud-technology-and-expertise-to-bring-the-fifa-world-cup-to-millions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T19:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three years before millions of viewers saw, arguably, one of the most thrilling World Cup Finals ever broadcast, TF1, the leading private TV channel in France, started a project to redefine the foundations of its broadcasting platform, including adopting a new cloud-based architecture. They, and all other broadcasters, have been observing diminishing audiences for traditional […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESTO – A multilingual dataset for parsing realistic task-oriented dialogues]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/presto-multilingual-dataset-for-parsing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/presto-multilingual-dataset-for-parsing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T17:02:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rahul Goel and Aditya Gupta, Software Engineers, Google Assistant  
Virtual assistants are increasingly integrated into our daily routines. They can help with everything from setting alarms to giving map directions and can even assist people with disabilities to more easily manage their homes. As we use these assistants, we are also becoming more accustomed to using natural language to accomplish tasks that we once did by hand.  
   
One of the biggest challenges in building a robust virtual assistant is identifying what a user wants and what information is needed to perform the task at hand. In the natural language processing (NLP) literature, this is mainly framed as a task-oriented dialogue parsing task, where a given dialogue needs to be parsed by a system to understand the u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise adds projects, drift detection, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-projects-drift-detection-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-projects-drift-detection-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent Terraform Enterprise releases include powerful new features such as projects, native OPA support, dynamic provider credentials, and drift detection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Validated Content: Introduction to infra.osbuild Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-introduction-to-infra.osbuild-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-introduction-to-infra.osbuild-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to the Image builder use case
 
During the last year we met with multiple edge customers, covering the automation needs for IT Linux infrastructure at scale across remote locations where there is often no IT staff on site. Think about retail stores, dark stores and warehouses where self-checkout, handhelds and POS devices hosting RHEL are distributed everywhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Santiago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service Major Updates: Import and Export Feature, Source Server Migration Metrics Dashboard, and Additional Post-Launch Actions]]></title>
        <id>fa10696bac0b9446bb6ac881cb730c11e3d02931</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-application-migration-service-major-updates-import-and-export-feature-source-server-migration-metrics-dashboard-and-additional-post-launch-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T15:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service (AWS MGN) can simplify and expedite your migration to AWS by automatically converting your source servers from physical, virtual, or cloud infrastructure to run natively on AWS. In the post, How to Use the New AWS Application Migration Server for Lift-and-Shift Migrations, Channy introduced us to Application Migration Service and how […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Chime SDK Call Analytics: Real-Time Voice Tone Analysis and Speaker Search]]></title>
        <id>b5892bef67fe0abef13300dedbfb49b1a69ff7fa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-chime-sdk-call-analytics-real-time-voice-tone-analysis-and-speaker-search/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T15:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am pleased to announce the availability of Amazon Chime SDK call analytics, a new set of capabilities that helps make it easier and cost effective to record and generate insights on real-time audio calls: transcription, voice tone analysis, and speaker search. We’ve also improved the Amazon Chime SDK section of the AWS Management […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 27, 2023]]></title>
        <id>36af7fde9b2b41d5310560b417ffc23471afa1e9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-27-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! In Finland, where I live, spring has arrived. The snow has melted, and the trees have grown their first buds. But I don’t get my hopes high, as usually around […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting to a Running Docker Container Shell]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=321721</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/03/27/connecting-to-a-running-docker-container-shell/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T13:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When using Docker in your development workflow, it is sometimes necessary to connect to a running Docker container to perform critical tasks or troubleshoot issues. For example, you may want to explore the file system, look at processes running in the container, tail a log file in the container, and more. You can connect to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maarten Balliauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoid unnecessary amplifiers]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44136</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/732886814/0/sethsblog~Avoid-unnecessary-amplifiers/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T07:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is extremely unique vs This is unique I’m very upset vs I’m upset and I love you a ton vs I love you Sometimes, more words aren’t better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java 20 and IntelliJ IDEA]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=333459</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/03/java-20-and-intellij-idea/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T03:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been writing about the new Java releases for a while now (since Java 10) and I like how we developers get to know about and use the new Java features every six months. Compared to some of its previous releases, Java 20 adds relatively fewer features. It introduces Scoped Values as an incubating API […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mala Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration for AWS 3.0.0-M2 and Spring Cloud Stream Kinesis Binder 4.0.0-M1 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/27/spring-integration-for-aws-3-0-0-m2-and-spring-cloud-stream-kinesis-binder-4</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/27/spring-integration-for-aws-3-0-0-m2-and-spring-cloud-stream-kinesis-binder-4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Bilan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability: A solution for today’s “always-on” world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-powerful-flexible-efficient</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-powerful-flexible-efficient"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Achieve operational excellence and efficiency with the Elastic Observability platform. Our unique approach to unifying observability data on an open and flexible platform with sophisticated AIOps and machine learning will prepare you for the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability: A solution for today’s “always-on” world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-powerful-flexible-efficient</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-powerful-flexible-efficient"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Our lives are completely controlled by applications. Whether it's for business or personal use, we expect these applications to be “always-on” with an ability to have immediate responses. These high expectations create an enormous set of demands on developers and operations staff. 

Managing these applications requires SREs to analyze enormous amounts of data from not only the application, but also the infrastructure it's running on. Additionally, SREs ensure the proper tools are utilized (or built) in their operational processes. Hence, managing the exponential data growth, resolving daily issues, and constantly grappling with tools and operation processes leaves limited time to understand business performance.

With Elastic Observability, SREs can not only consolidate and analyze all t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effect Size]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2755/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2755/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/effect_size.png" title="Subgroup analysis is ongoing." alt="Subgroup analysis is ongoing." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hegelochus lesson]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43151</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/732773150/0/sethsblog~The-Hegelochus-lesson/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-26T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 2,000 years ago, an actor in Greece botched a line in a play. In an inflection error, he said “weasel” when he meant to say “calm sea.” As a result, he was mocked by Sannyrion and then Aristophanes and others. He never worked again. The lesson might be that one innocent slip and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flashing on contempt]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45480</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/732681719/0/sethsblog~Flashing-on-contempt/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-25T08:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn’t have to happen with intent, in fact, it rarely does. Micro-emotions appear on our face and then disappear in less than a second. Blink and you’ll miss them. But sometimes, people don’t blink. We’ve evolved to be hyperware of these tiny displays of emotion. And yet, most of us don’t even realize it’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting novel systemic biomarkers in external eye photos]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/detecting-novel-systemic-biomarkers-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/detecting-novel-systemic-biomarkers-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T19:13:00.009Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Boris Babenko, Software Engineer, and Akib Uddin, Product Manager, Google Research    
Last year we presented results demonstrating that a deep learning system (DLS) can be trained to analyze external eye photos and predict a person’s diabetic retinal disease status and elevated glycated hemoglobin (or HbA1c, a biomarker that indicates the three-month average level of blood glucose). It was previously unknown that external eye photos contained signals for these conditions. This exciting finding suggested the potential to reduce the need for specialized equipment since such photos can be captured using smartphones and other consumer devices. Encouraged by these findings, we set out to discover what other biomarkers can be found in this imaging modality. 

In “A deep learning model…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2023.1 Release Candidate Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=336092</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2023/03/24/goland-2023-1-release-candidate-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T16:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2023.1 Release Candidate is now available. Please note that to use GoLand 2023.1 RC, you need to have an active subscription or start a 30-day trial. In this build, we have fixed some bugs. We’ve also updated the Code Vision feature.  Please read this Beta 2 blog post if you want to find out […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 RC2 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=333574</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/03/intellij-idea-2023-1-rc2/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T15:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second Release Candidate build for IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 has been released.  You can download the new version from our website, update directly from the IDE or via the free Toolbox App, or use snaps for Ubuntu. To access this build, an active subscription to IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate is required.  We encourage you to test […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Update for the Aqua Public Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=qa&amp;p=335814</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/qa/2023/03/new-update-for-the-aqua-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T15:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have been working hard to make Aqua more stable and bring increased functionality that test engineers need. For this update, we want to share some fixes and new features that are ready for you to try. You can download the latest version from our website, update directly from the IDE, or update via the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oscar Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delivering good taste]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45449</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/732575573/0/sethsblog~Delivering-good-taste/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lots of books on creating cooking, photography, writing and music. But they can’t possibly help you do better until you see and taste and appreciate what you’re trying to create. If you think what you’re serving is good, but others don’t, more recipes aren’t going to help. That’s why so much type is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We updated our RSA SSH host key]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-03-23-we-updated-our-rsa-ssh-host-key/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-03-23-we-updated-our-rsa-ssh-host-key/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T05:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At approximately 05:00 UTC on March 24, out of an abundance of caution, we replaced our RSA SSH host key used to secure Git operations for GitHub.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/24/spring-boot-3-1-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/24/spring-boot-3-1-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Wilkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 0.5.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/24/spring-modulith-0-5-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/24/spring-modulith-0-5-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Pulsar 0.2.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/24/spring-for-apache-pulsar-0-2-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/24/spring-for-apache-pulsar-0-2-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bono</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relative Terms]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2754/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2754/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/relative_terms.png" title="Small sewing machines are sewing machines that are smaller than a sewing machine. A sewing machine is larger than a small sewing machine, but quieter than a loud sewing machine." alt="Small sewing machines are sewing machines that are smaller than a sewing machine. A sewing machine is larger than a small sewing machine, but quieter than a loud sewing machine." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.1 Release Candidate]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=335842</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/03/clion-2023-1-release-candidate/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T22:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.1 is on its way, and the release candidate for v2023.1 is now available! To install CLion 2023.1 RC (build 231.8109.141), download it from the website, update via the Toolbox App, or use this snap package (for Ubuntu). You need an active subscription or a trial license to use CLion 2023.1 RC. DOWNLOAD CLION […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.1 Release Candidate 2 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=335817</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/03/2023-1-rc-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T21:22:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second PyCharm 2023.1 Release Candidate (RC) build is here. To see what has already been added in the PyCharm 2023.1 Early Access Program (EAP), take a look at our EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the new version, but you can also manually download the EAP builds from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual language maps for robot navigation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/visual-language-maps-for-robot.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/visual-language-maps-for-robot.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T19:08:00.012Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Oier Mees, PhD Student, University of Freiburg, and Andy Zeng, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google   
People are excellent navigators of the physical world, due in part to their remarkable ability to build cognitive maps that form the basis of spatial memory — from localizing landmarks at varying ontological levels (like a book on a shelf in the living room) to determining whether a layout permits navigation from point A to point B. Building robots that are proficient at navigation requires an interconnected understanding of (a) vision and natural language (to associate landmarks or follow instructions), and (b) spatial reasoning (to connect a map representing an environment to the true spatial distribution of objects). While there have been many recent advances in training jo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.1 Release Candidate 2 Is Out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=334241</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/03/webstorm-2023-1-rc2/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T16:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year’s first major release of WebStorm is just days away! Try the WebStorm 2023.1 Release Candidate 2 build today and test out what we’ve implemented in WebStorm 2023.1. DOWNLOAD WEBSTORM 2023.1 RC2 Please note that, unlike our previous EAP builds, you must have an active WebStorm license to use it. Otherwise, you’ll need to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a secure code mindset with the GitHub Secure Code Game]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-03-23-build-a-secure-code-mindset-with-the-github-secure-code-game/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-03-23-build-a-secure-code-mindset-with-the-github-secure-code-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T16:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing secure code is as much of an art as writing functional code, and it is the only way to write quality code. Learn how our Secure Code Game can provide you with hands-on training to spot and fix security issues in your code so that you can build a secure code mindset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running dynamic, ephemeral multi-hop workers for HCP Boundary: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-dynamic-ephemeral-multi-hop-workers-for-hcp-boundary-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-dynamic-ephemeral-multi-hop-workers-for-hcp-boundary-part-1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worker management is very dynamic in Boundary and HCP Boundary. With a new custom plugin, you can automate even more tasks, including worker cleanup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deeper Look: Red Hat Named a Leader in the Forrester Wave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/a-deeper-look-red-hat-named-a-leader-in-the-forrester-wave</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/a-deeper-look-red-hat-named-a-leader-in-the-forrester-wave"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we announced that Red Hat has been named a leader in The Forrester Wave™ Infrastructure Automation, Q1 2023. In an effort to help explain this result from our point of view, the following blog answers some of the most frequently asked questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andriusb@redhat.com (Andrius Benokraitis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test as You Go: Rapid Process Development and Continuous Improvement]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=76773&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=76773</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/rapid-process-development-continuous-improvement/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T14:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Alpha release of the new rapid process testing functionality which is now available in Camunda Platform 8.
The post Test as You Go: Rapid Process Development and Continuous Improvement appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Inozemtceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They will lose your data]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45488</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/732446456/0/sethsblog~They-will-lose-your-data/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rules are pretty consistent: We’re all creators now. Podcasting, videoing, photographing, spreadsheeting… and we’re building a foundation of valuable data as we go. The software companies that produce the tools we use push their engineers in many ways, but not to create resilient storage systems that are sure to honor the effort and care […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Federal Sales Director Kathy Hsu thinks authenticity is important in sales. Hear why.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My passion is to work with the federal government and see how I can be a part of the mission. That’s why I wanted to work at Elastic. 

I first discovered my passion for tech sales as a college graduate working in Silicon Valley. I worked at Apple as a Technical Consultant and got my start in channel sales and the network IP space at a large company that provided solutions for semiconductor and infrastructure software. Then I moved to a startup that gave me the opportunity to support Civilian agencies, the Department of Defense (DoD), and the Intelligence Community. In this role, I spent a lot of time flying between California and Washington D.C. and quickly realized that I had a great sense of fire and purpose when serving the federal government. 

These early experiences helped me find m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Hsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Federal Sales Director Kathy Hsu thinks authenticity is important in sales. Hear why.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Hsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast:  Mark Thomas, Apache Tomcat contributor extraordinaire]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/23/a-bootiful-podcast-mark-thomas-apache-tomcat-contributor-extraordinaire</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/23/a-bootiful-podcast-mark-thomas-apache-tomcat-contributor-extraordinaire"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration 5.5.17, 6.0.4 and 6.1.0-M2 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/23/spring-integration-5-5-17-6-0-4-and-6-1-0-m2-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/23/spring-integration-5-5-17-6-0-4-and-6-1-0-m2-available"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Bilan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/23/spring-boot-3-0-5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/23/spring-boot-3-0-5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Wilkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of observability: Trends and predictions business leaders should plan for in 2023 and beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-predictions-trends-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-predictions-trends-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a rapidly changing macroeconomic backdrop, leaders look to do more with their people and technology. This blog provides an overview of key observability trends and predictions for the upcoming year, influenced by a cost-constrained environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of observability: Trends and predictions business leaders should plan for in 2023 and beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-predictions-trends-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-predictions-trends-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
If the past year has taught us anything, it’s that the more things change, the more things stay the same. The whiplash and pivot from the go-go economy post-pandemic to a belt-tightening macroeconomic environment induced by higher inflation and interest rates has been seen before, but rarely this quickly. Technology leaders have always had to do more with less, but this slowdown may be unpredictable, longer, and more pronounced than expected. So let’s take a look into our cloud and observability crystal ball to identify some key trends and predictions that we see impacting the industry this coming year and beyond.
1. Tightening macroeconomic conditions drive focus on TCO
With tightening macroeconomic conditions, organizations will continue to focus on accelerating cloud adoption for enab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 219]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66630</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-219/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T17:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sprint 219 was dedicated to fixing bugs. We continue to drive down the bug backlog as quickly as we can. We will also have a couple new preview features coming that will be announced in the 219 sprint notes.
Issue
Delivery plans tab name
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 219 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第227話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361072081927</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361072081927"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot X: The AI-powered developer experience]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-03-22-github-copilot-x-the-ai-powered-developer-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-03-22-github-copilot-x-the-ai-powered-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T13:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot is evolving to bring chat and voice interfaces, support pull requests, answer questions on docs, and adopt OpenAI’s GPT-4 for a more personalized developer experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to change the world]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42147</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/732322589/0/sethsblog~How-to-change-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T08:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All successful cultural change (books, movies, public health), has a super-simple two-step loop: AWARENESSTENSION–>Loop<– It’s easy to focus on awareness. Get the word out. Hype. Promo. I think that’s a mistake. Because awareness without tension is useless. The tension is like pulling back a rubber band. WHY would someone who becomes aware take action? Is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air Handler]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2753/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2753/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/air_handler.png" title="It maintains odor levels in a normal familiar range, so if you open the windows and the air gets too fresh, it filters it through some dirty laundry samples to compensate." alt="It maintains odor levels in a normal familiar range, so if you open the windows and the air gets too fresh, it filters it through some dirty laundry samples to compensate." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66621</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/march-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T20:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Addressed issue that required restarting tfsjobagent service and Azure DevOps Server application pool after updating SMTP-related setting in the Azure DevOps Server Management Console.
The post March patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Clean Rooms Now Generally Available — Collaborate with Your Partners without Sharing Raw Data]]></title>
        <id>7489dac1ba7077e7020fc13589c13c0455e7b4d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-clean-rooms-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T19:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies across multiple industries, such as advertising and marketing, retail, consumer packaged goods (CPG), travel and hospitality, media and entertainment, and financial services, increasingly look to supplement their data with data from business partners, to build a complete view of their business. Let’s take a marketing use case as an example. Brands, publishers, and their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Camunda 8 on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=76579&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=76579</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/running-camunda-8-on-openshift/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T18:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you use Red Hat OpenShift? We've greatly improved how Camunda Platform 8 runs on OpenShift. Learn what's new and see an installation step by step.
The post Running Camunda 8 on OpenShift appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 20, 2023]]></title>
        <id>d37a1df2b4b3f11486d8d054016088476bc57107</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-20-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T15:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! A new week starts, and Spring is almost here! If you’re curious about AWS news from the previous seven days, I got you covered. Last Week’s Launches Here are the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New reference architecture: Deploying Ansible Automation Platform 2 on Red Hat OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-deploying-ansible-automation-platform-2-on-red-hat-openshift</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-deploying-ansible-automation-platform-2-on-red-hat-openshift"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest reference architecture showcasing the best practices for deploying Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 on Red Hat OpenShift!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to every question]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45447</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/732193586/0/sethsblog~The-answer-to-every-question/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the thing of the moment is the answer to every single question, you might be in a bubble. If, regardless of the problem, the answer is crypto, homeopathy, or the internet, or perhaps GPT, essential oils or decarbonization, it’s possible we’re taking an easy way out. A new technology or approach could be the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leading With Business Integrity at the Intersection of Legal and Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-leading-business-integrity-intersection-of-legal-and-technology-at-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-leading-business-integrity-intersection-of-legal-and-technology-at-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carolyn Herzog was supposed to be a concert violinist. She instead forged a career path that would take her from international development work for Africa to Chief Legal Officer at various technology companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leading With Business Integrity at the Intersection of Legal and Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-leading-business-integrity-intersection-of-legal-and-technology-at-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-leading-business-integrity-intersection-of-legal-and-technology-at-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Carolyn Herzog was supposed to be a concert violinist.

“To this day, my father is utterly confused by my career choice. In fact, I saw my parents last week and they started a sentence again with, ‘Aren’t you surprised…?,’” Carolyn shares, laughing.

Despite her parents' resistance, Carolyn realized that music was not where her heart lay. She instead forged a career path that would take her from international development work for Africa to Chief Legal Officer at various technology companies.

You could say that Carolyn trusts the process.

“Trust, in the end, is everything,” Carolyn mentions, referring to her leadership style. With trust as her cornerstone, Carolyn now leads a global legal team at Elastic, the platform for search-powered solutions, as their Chief Legal Officer.

Her work…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Android applications with Elastic APM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-android-applications-elastic-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-android-applications-elastic-apm"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic has launched its APM agent for Android applications, allowing developers to track key aspects of applications to help troubleshoot issues and performance flaws with mobile applications, corresponding backend services, and their interactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Wert,Cesar Munoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Android applications with Elastic APM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-android-applications-elastic-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-android-applications-elastic-apm"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
People are handling more and more matters on their smartphones through mobile apps both privately and professionally. With thousands or even millions of users, ensuring great performance and reliability is a key challenge for providers and operators of mobile apps and related backend services. Understanding the behavior of mobile apps, the occurrences and types of crashes, the root causes of slow response times, and the real user impact of backend issues is key to managing the performance of mobile apps and associated backend services.
Elastic has launched its application performance monitoring (APM) agent for Android applications, allowing developers to keep track of key aspects of their applications, from crashes and HTTP requests to screen rendering times and end-to-end distributed tr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Wert,Cesar Munoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Providing Terraform with that Ansible Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/providing-terraform-with-that-ansible-magic</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/providing-terraform-with-that-ansible-magic"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Late last year, we introduced a Red Hat Ansible Certified Collection Collection for Terraform. This was an important step in automation, as these two tools really are great together and leveraging Ansible's ability to orchestrate other tools in the enterprise made this a no-brainer. Terraform with its infrastructure as code (IaC) provisioning and Ansible’s strength in configuration as code are a synergy that cannot be ignored - we are better together! Organizations are now in the position to utilize their existing infrastructure as code manifests and extend their automation with Terraform and Ansible together.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ghost in the machine]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45477</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/732064934/0/sethsblog~The-ghost-in-the-machine/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T08:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The computer wants you to click this button.” “It thinks you asked for something else.” “He’s mad at you.” Thousands of generations ago, we evolved our way into a magnificent hack. It turns out that we can more safely navigate the world by imagining that other people have a little voice in their heads just […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vid2Seq: a pretrained visual language model for describing multi-event videos]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/vid2seq-pretrained-visual-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/vid2seq-pretrained-visual-language.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T17:52:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Antoine Yang, Student Researcher, and Arsha Nagrani, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception team    
Videos have become an increasingly important part of our daily lives, spanning fields such as entertainment, education, and communication. Understanding the content of videos, however, is a challenging task as videos often contain multiple events occurring at different time scales. For example, a video of a musher hitching up dogs to a dog sled before they all race away involves a long event (the dogs pulling the sled) and a short event (the dogs being hitched to the sled). One way to spur research in video understanding is via the task of dense video captioning, which consists of temporally localizing and describing all events in a minutes-long video. This differs from s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partnering with EU policymakers to ensure the Cyber Resilience Act works for developers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-03-17-partnering-with-eu-policymakers-to-ensure-the-cyber-resilience-act-works-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-03-17-partnering-with-eu-policymakers-to-ensure-the-cyber-resilience-act-works-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T15:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re looking forward to working with policymakers to improve cybersecurity and support developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Removals and Major Changes In v1.27]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/17/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-v1-27/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/17/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-v1-27/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Harshita Sao
As Kubernetes develops and matures, features may be deprecated, removed, or replaced
with better ones for the project's overall health. Based on the information available
at this point in the v1.27 release process, which is still ongoing and can introduce
additional changes, this article identifies and describes some of the planned changes
for the Kubernetes v1.27 release.
A note about the k8s.gcr.io redirect to registry.k8s.io
To host its container images, the Kubernetes project uses a community-owned image
registry called registry.k8s.io. On March 20th, all traffic from the out-of-date
k8s.gcr.io registry will be redirected
to registry.k8s.io. The deprecated
k8s.gcr.io registry will eventually be phased out.
What does this change mean?
If you are a subproject maintai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Chatbot Now Integrates With Microsoft Teams]]></title>
        <id>173381d3f83132268431d2b67f1614ae358dbea3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-chatbot-now-integrates-with-microsoft-teams/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T21:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that, starting today, you can use AWS Chatbot to troubleshoot and operate your AWS resources from Microsoft Teams. Communicating and collaborating on IT operation tasks through chat channels is known as ChatOps. It allows you to centralize the management of infrastructure and applications, as well as to automate and streamline […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: The Impact Lab]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T20:13:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jamila Smith-Loud, Human Rights & Social Impact Research Lead, Google Research, Responsible AI and Human-Centered Technology Team 
    

Globalized technology has the potential to create large-scale societal impact, and having a grounded research approach rooted in existing international human and civil rights standards is a critical component to assuring responsible and ethical AI development and deployment. The Impact Lab team, part of Google’s Responsible AI Team, employs a range of interdisciplinary methodologies to ensure critical and rich analysis of the potential implications of technology development. The team’s mission is to examine socioeconomic and human rights impacts of AI,  publish foundational research, and incubate novel mitigations enabling machine learning (ML) …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Godot 4.0 Release Party 🎉]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-03-16-godot-4-0-release-party/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-03-16-godot-4-0-release-party/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T19:14:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are delighted to host the Godot 4.0 Release Party at GitHub HQ on Wednesday, March 22 from 6:30 pm to 9:30 pm. And you're invited!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds new Sentinel policy review UI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-new-sentinel-policy-review-ui</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-new-sentinel-policy-review-ui"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a more efficient, streamlined way of managing policy as code workflows in Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Meets Event-Driven Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/kubernetes-meets-event-driven-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/kubernetes-meets-event-driven-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s fast paced world, every second counts and the ability to react to activities in a timely fashion can mean the difference between satisfying the needs of consumers and meeting Service-Level Agreements. Each are goals of Event-Driven Ansible, which seeks to further the reach of Ansible based automation by responding to events that meet certain criteria. These events can originate from a variety of sources, such as from an HTTP endpoint, messages on a queue or topic, or from public cloud resources. Kubernetes has become synonymous with managing infrastructure and applications in cloud native architectures and many organizations are reliant on these systems for running their business critical workloads. Automation and Kubernetes go hand in hand and Ansible already plays a role within this ecosystem. A new capability leveraging the Event-Driven Ansible framework is now available that extends the integration between both Ansible and Kubernetes so that Ansible automation activities can be triggered based on events and actions occurring within a Kubernetes cluster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ablock@redhat.com (Andrew Block)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NORBr leverages Elastic to keep payments on track and improve key business metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/norbr-elastic-payments-on-track-improve-key-business-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/norbr-elastic-payments-on-track-improve-key-business-metrics"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NORBr creates the perfect match between digital merchants and payment companies via a no-code routing engine to send transactions to the best-performing payment service providers with Elastic Search.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Cyril Tanneau, NORBr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NORBr leverages Elastic to keep payments on track and improve key business metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/norbr-elastic-payments-on-track-improve-key-business-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/norbr-elastic-payments-on-track-improve-key-business-metrics"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
NORBr is the #1 global distributor of payment services for digital merchants, allowing customers to connect, manage, and benchmark all their payment services through a single API and single platform. NORBr creates the perfect match between digital merchants and payment companies via a no-code routing engine to send transactions to the best-performing payment service providers. This allows merchants to focus on their business performance and optimize their payment processing costs.

NORBr was built on the premise that the payment ecosystem is becoming increasingly complicated. For merchants, there is a growing need for orchestration — payment stacks have become very complex and have affected their agility, time-to-market, and overall performance and costs. By offering an automated marketp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Cyril Tanneau, NORBr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RPA + BPMN = True End-to-End Business Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=76245&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=76245</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/rpa-bpmn-process-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T21:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BPMN is an ideal tool for visualizing and controlling end-to-end business processes, including those that invoke RPA bots. Learn how to use them together.
The post RPA + BPMN = True End-to-End Business Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Grafana Alerting team scales their issue management with GitHub Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-03-15-how-the-grafana-alerting-team-scales-their-issue-management-with-github-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-03-15-how-the-grafana-alerting-team-scales-their-issue-management-with-github-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T21:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hear from Grafana Labs' Armand Grillet about how his team uses GitHub Projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Linux 2023, a Cloud-Optimized Linux Distribution with Long-Term Support]]></title>
        <id>222e76bc4fa032f0a04b7b011b60ef08bec89805</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-linux-2023-a-cloud-optimized-linux-distribution-with-long-term-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T20:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am excited to announce the general availability of Amazon Linux 2023 (AL2023). AWS has provided you with a cloud-optimized Linux distribution since 2010. This is the third generation of our Amazon Linux distributions. Every generation of Amazon Linux distribution is secured, optimized for the cloud, and receives long-term AWS support. We built Amazon Linux […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximum Process Flexibility with Inbound Webhook Connectors]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=75153&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=75153</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/inbound-webhook-connectors/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T18:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to share that an inbound HTTP Webhook Connector and an inbound GitHub Webhook Connector are now available in Camunda Platform 8.
The post Maximum Process Flexibility with Inbound Webhook Connectors appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Elastic’s EMEA Go-To-Market Sales Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-the-team-at-elastic-emea-go-to-market</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-the-team-at-elastic-emea-go-to-market"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Field Operations is an important team here at Elastic. They cover all go-to-market (GTM) functions related to customer acquisition, expansion, and retention. As a team, they think globally and act locally with teams covering every major international market.
Our Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) sales team is rapidly growing, so we wanted to take a moment to highlight some of our GTM Elasticians working in the region and hear a bit about the work they do and why they value Elastic as an employer.
Charlotte van Dijk, commercial account executive, north EMEA

I work in the commercial sector within the Benelux region as an Account Executive. I started my career at Elastic as a User Success Manager nearly 5 years ago. As a User Success Manager, I had the opportunity to work with a lot of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Elastic’s EMEA Go-To-Market Sales Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-the-team-at-elastic-emea-go-to-market</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-the-team-at-elastic-emea-go-to-market"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you based in Europe and considering a role in sales? Hear from some of our EMEA sales team about their roles and the work they do that contributes to Elastic’s success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Elastic to observe GKE Autopilot clusters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observe-gke-autopilot-clusters</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observe-gke-autopilot-clusters"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how deploying the Elastic Agent onto a GKE Autopilot cluster makes observing the cluster’s behavior easy. Kibana integrations make visualizing the behavior a simple addition to your observability dashboards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Lowry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Linux 2023 — Flexibility to deploy the Elastic Stack wherever you need]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/amazon-linux-2023-flexibility-deploy-elastic-stack</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/amazon-linux-2023-flexibility-deploy-elastic-stack"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic continues to strengthen our partnership of innovation with AWS to provide options for customers to run the Elastic Stack on the latest operating systems, including Amazon Linux 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Elastic to observe GKE Autopilot clusters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observe-gke-autopilot-clusters</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observe-gke-autopilot-clusters"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic has formally supported Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) since January 2020, when Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes was announced. Since then, Google has expanded GKE, with new service offerings and delivery mechanisms. One of those new offerings is GKE Autopilot. Where GKE is a managed Kubernetes environment, GKE Autopilot is a mode of Kubernetes operation where Google manages your cluster configuration, scaling, security, and more. It is production ready and removes many of the challenges associated with tasks like workload management, deployment automation, and scalability rules. Autopilot lets you focus on building and deploying your application while Google manages everything else.

Elastic is committed to supporting Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) in all of its delivery modes. In Oct…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Lowry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Linux 2023 — Flexibility to deploy the Elastic Stack wherever you need]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/amazon-linux-2023-flexibility-deploy-elastic-stack</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/amazon-linux-2023-flexibility-deploy-elastic-stack"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic is pleased to announce our AWS Service Validation for Amazon Linux 2023 for the Elastic Stack! Customers can now deploy Elasticsearch, Kibana, Logstash, and the Elastic Agent on Amazon Linux 2023 and benefit from its reliability and stability. 
As an AWS partner in the AWS Service Ready Program, this achievement certifies we’ve passed a thorough technical validation for sound architecture and software quality assurance. Now, you can run your Elastic Stack as a qualified package on Amazon Linux 2023. 
This announcement underlines our continued innovation momentum with our partner, AWS, and ensures you’re able to run your self-managed Elastic Stack on whatever operating system suits your needs. 
We already offer 19 Elastic Cloud regions on AWS around the world. But for customers wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrate Amazon S3’s 17th birthday at AWS Pi Day 2023]]></title>
        <id>48daf1f1e1724b4a81e1785becca7b650d3031a9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/celebrate-amazon-s3s-17th-birthday-at-aws-pi-day-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T19:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Pi Day 2023 is live today starting at 13:00 PDT; join us on the AWS on Air channel on Twitch. On this day 17 years ago, we launched a very simple object storage service. It allowed developers to create, list, and delete private storage spaces (known as buckets), upload and download files, and manage […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub celebrates the ingenuity of developers with disabilities in new video series]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-03-14-github-celebrates-the-ingenuity-of-developers-with-disabilities-in-new-video-series/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-03-14-github-celebrates-the-ingenuity-of-developers-with-disabilities-in-new-video-series/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T18:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how developers with disabilities are pushing the boundaries of accessibility with ingenuity, open source, and generative AI on The ReadME Project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning from deep learning: a case study of feature discovery and validation in pathology]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/learning-from-deep-learning-case-study.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/learning-from-deep-learning-case-study.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T18:16:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ellery Wulczyn and Yun Liu, Google Research  
When a patient is diagnosed with cancer, one of the most important steps is examination of the tumor under a microscope by pathologists to determine the cancer stage and to characterize the tumor. This information is central to understanding clinical prognosis (i.e., likely patient outcomes) and for determining the most appropriate treatment, such as undergoing surgery alone versus surgery plus chemotherapy. Developing machine learning (ML) tools in pathology to assist with the microscopic review represents a compelling research area with many potential applications. 

Previous studies have shown that ML can accurately identify and classify tumors in pathology images and can even predict patient prognosis using known pathology feature…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Use Amazon S3 Object Lambda with Amazon CloudFront to Tailor Content for End Users]]></title>
        <id>bb8eafd170bc0a7a2a4f58cc640790b11357cb96</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-use-amazon-s3-object-lambda-with-amazon-cloudfront-to-tailor-content-for-end-users/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T17:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With S3 Object Lambda, you can use your own code to process data retrieved from Amazon S3 as it is returned to an application. Over time, we added new capabilities to S3 Object Lambda, like the ability to add your own code to S3 HEAD and LIST API requests, in addition to the support for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault client libraries for Go and .NET are now in public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-client-libraries-for-go-and-net-are-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-client-libraries-for-go-and-net-are-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp expands its client libraries to include Go & .NET. The Vault 1.13 release includes support for Go & .NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Media Understanding Platform for ML Innovations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9bef9962dcb7</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/building-a-media-understanding-platform-for-ml-innovations-9bef9962dcb7?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T15:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The media understanding platform serves as an abstraction layer between Machine Learning (ML) algos and various applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.10.0-alpha5 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=75110&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=75110</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/camunda-optimize-3-10-0-alpha5/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the latest release of Camunda Optimize. Optimize makes it possible to evaluate the success of your process automation initiative.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.10.0-alpha5 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.19.0-alpha4 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=75119&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=75119</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/camunda-automation-platform-7-19-0-alpha4/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth alpha release of Camunda Automation Runtime 7.19 features new job due date functionality, support for Quarkus 2.16.4 and more.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.19.0-alpha4 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 13, 2023]]></title>
        <id>cb1390189c6b6ce821906a8bb9260207f9ef1972</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-13-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T03:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems like only yesterday I was last writing the Week in Review post, at the end of January, and now here we are almost mid-way through March, almost into spring in the northern hemisphere, and close to a quarter way through 2023. Where does time fly?! Last Week’s LaunchesHere’s some of the launches and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing channel assignment history and rollback for HCP Packer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-channel-assignment-history-and-rollback-for-hcp-packer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-channel-assignment-history-and-rollback-for-hcp-packer"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer’s new channel assignment history and rollback provide a complete record of artifacts in a channel and enable a simple, one-click rollback to previous iterations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing/Maximizing your Scaling capability with Automation Controller 2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/enhancing/maximizing-your-scaling-capability-with-automation-controller-2.3</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/enhancing/maximizing-your-scaling-capability-with-automation-controller-2.3"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 is the next generation automation platform from Red Hat’s trusted enterprise technology experts. We are excited to announce that the Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 release includes automation controller 4.3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch Indexing Strategy in Asset Management Platform (AMP)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/99332231e541</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/elasticsearch-indexing-strategy-in-asset-management-platform-amp-99332231e541?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T22:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Burak Bacioglu, Meenakshi Jindal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Reprocessing Pipeline in Asset Management Platform @Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/46fe225c35c9</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/data-reprocessing-pipeline-in-asset-management-platform-netflix-46fe225c35c9?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T22:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Meenakshi Jindal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PaLM-E: An embodied multimodal language model]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/palm-e-embodied-multimodal-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/palm-e-embodied-multimodal-language.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T17:25:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Danny Driess, Student Researcher, and Pete Florence, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google  
Recent years have seen tremendous advances across machine learning domains, from models that can explain jokes or answer visual questions in a variety of languages to those that can produce images based on text descriptions. Such innovations have been possible due to the increase in availability of large scale datasets along with novel advances that enable the training of models on these data. While scaling of robotics models has seen some success, it is outpaced by other domains due to a lack of datasets available on a scale comparable to large text corpora or image datasets.  
  
Today we introduce PaLM-E, a new generalist robotics model that overcomes these issues by transferring know…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: k8s.gcr.io Redirect to registry.k8s.io - What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/10/image-registry-redirect/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/10/image-registry-redirect/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Bob Killen (Google), Davanum Srinivas (AWS), Chris Short (AWS), Frederico Muñoz (SAS
Institute), Tim Bannister (The Scale Factory), Ricky Sadowski (AWS), Grace Nguyen (Expo), Mahamed
Ali (Rackspace Technology), Mars Toktonaliev (independent), Laura Santamaria (Dell), Kat Cosgrove
(Dell)
On Monday, March 20th, the k8s.gcr.io registry will be redirected to the community owned
registry,
registry.k8s.io .
TL;DR: What you need to know about this change
On Monday, March 20th, traffic from the older k8s.gcr.io registry will be redirected to
registry.k8s.io with the eventual goal of sunsetting k8s.gcr.io.
If you run in a restricted environment, and apply strict domain name or IP address access policies
limited to k8s.gcr.io, the image pulls will not function after k8s.gcr.io starts redire…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why SüdLeasing Chose Camunda Platform 8 SaaS]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=74641&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=74641</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/why-camunda-platform-8-suedleasing/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why SüdLeasing, a major German financial services institution, is setting up all their new processes in Camunda Platform 8 SaaS.
The post Why SüdLeasing Chose Camunda Platform 8 SaaS appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Schroth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five tips for growing your career in tech sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-five-tips-for-growing-your-career-in-tech-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-five-tips-for-growing-your-career-in-tech-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Rain Hu's favorite moments of the day is her early morning run. "I run six kilometers minimum daily, rain or shine," she says. "I enjoy the time alone because it allows me to have time for self-reflection and self-conversation." 
The discipline that it takes to maintain a healthy lifestyle is carried throughout her life. As a wife, mother of two young boys, and sales leader, Rain optimizes her time so that she can show up fully and authentically in all aspects of her life. 
We sat down with Rain, Area Vice President, ASEAN and Greater China  at Elastic, to learn how she has built a career she loves. Read on to learn about how she grew her career in tech sales and what advice she has for others looking to do the same. 


Launching a career in tech sales
Shortly after graduating with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mara Gates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five tips for growing your career in tech sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-five-tips-for-growing-your-career-in-tech-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-five-tips-for-growing-your-career-in-tech-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Mara Gates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Forensic container analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/10/forensic-container-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/10/forensic-container-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Adrian Reber (Red Hat)
In my previous article, Forensic container checkpointing in
Kubernetes, I introduced checkpointing in Kubernetes
and how it has to be setup and how it can be used. The name of the
feature is Forensic container checkpointing, but I did not go into
any details how to do the actual analysis of the checkpoint created by
Kubernetes. In this article I want to provide details how the
checkpoint can be analyzed.
Checkpointing is still an alpha feature in Kubernetes and this article
wants to provide a preview how the feature might work in the future.
Preparation
Details about how to configure Kubernetes and the underlying CRI implementation
to enable checkpointing support can be found in my Forensic container
checkpointing in Kubernetes article.
As an example I prepa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The BirdCLEF 2023 Challenge: Pushing the frontiers of biodiversity monitoring]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/the-birdclef-2023-challenge-pushing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/the-birdclef-2023-challenge-pushing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T19:27:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tom Denton, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team   
Worldwide bird populations are declining at an alarming rate, with approximately 48% of existing bird species known or suspected to be experiencing population declines. For instance, the U.S. and Canada have reported 29% fewer birds since 1970. 

Effective monitoring of bird populations is essential for the development of solutions that promote conservation. Monitoring allows researchers to better understand the severity of the problem for specific bird populations and evaluate whether existing interventions are working. To scale monitoring, bird researchers have started analyzing ecosystems remotely using bird sound recordings instead of physically in-person via passive acoustic monitoring. Researchers can gather thou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the Newest AWS Heroes – March 2023]]></title>
        <id>23c2f55be52d9c2b3b30a239f3c22b95b0fc3586</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/meet-the-newest-aws-heroes-march-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T18:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Heroes are passionate AWS experts who are dedicated to sharing their in-depth knowledge within the community. They inspire, uplift, and motivate the global AWS community, and today, we’re excited to announce and recognize the newest Heroes in 2023! Aidan Steele – Melbourne, Australia Serverless Hero Aidan Steele is a Senior Engineer at Nightvision. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic provider credentials now generally available for Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dynamic-provider-credentials-now-ga-for-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dynamic-provider-credentials-now-ga-for-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform’s dynamic provider credentials enable secure, short-lived authentication for HashiCorp Vault and cloud providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Took the Camunda Meet-up Program to the Next Level in Just 10 Steps]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=74618&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=74618</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/how-we-took-camunda-meet-up-program-next-level/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T01:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was a big year for the Camunda Meet-up program! Learn how we did it and how you can level up your own programs. 
The post How We Took the Camunda Meet-up Program to the Next Level in Just 10 Steps appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Alcantara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.4 improves the CLI experience for Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-4-improves-the-cli-experience-for-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-4-improves-the-cli-experience-for-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.4 is now generally available, featuring enhanced run output in Terraform Cloud, support for OPA policy results in the CLI, and a native replacement for the null resource.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Your Bicep Files in Visual Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66578</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/write-your-bicep-files-in-visual-studio/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T16:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The growth of Bicep has increased massively over the last few years for those of you deploying into Azure. The community made it clear that being able to work in Visual Studio and not have to interrupt their workflow was critical to them.
The post Write Your Bicep Files in Visual Studio appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第226話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361028382901</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361028382901"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data ingestion pipeline with Operation Management]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3c5c638740a8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/data-ingestion-pipeline-with-operation-management-3c5c638740a8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T20:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Varun Sekhri, Meenakshi Jindal, Burak Bacioglu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 218 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66586</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-218-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T18:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not a lot to report other than a list of issues fixed 😁. Bug fixes will continue at full speed through sprint 219 as well.
Issue
Save Comments permission preventing the saving of images in discussion
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 218 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Composer Now Generally Available – Visually Build Serverless Applications Quickly]]></title>
        <id>0f9980e3eaee926b64a383bc5bc095caeb46293d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-application-composer-now-generally-available-visually-build-serverless-applications-quickly/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T18:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2022, we previewed AWS Application Composer, a visual builder for you to compose and configure serverless applications from AWS services backed by deployment-ready infrastructure as code (IaC). In the keynote, Dr. Werner Vogels, CTO of Amazon.com said: Developers that never used serverless before. How do they know where to start? Which services […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the ICDAR 2023 Competition on Hierarchical Text Detection and Recognition]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/announcing-icdar-2023-competition-on.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/announcing-icdar-2023-competition-on.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T18:10:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shangbang Long, Software Engineer, Google Research   
The last few decades have witnessed the rapid development of Optical Character Recognition (OCR) technology, which has evolved from an academic benchmark task used in early breakthroughs of deep learning research to tangible products available in consumer devices and to third party developers for daily use. These OCR products digitize and democratize the valuable information that is stored in paper or image-based sources (e.g., books, magazines, newspapers, forms, street signs, restaurant menus) so that they can be indexed, searched, translated, and further processed by state-of-the-art natural language processing techniques.  
 
Research in scene text detection and recognition (or scene text spotting) has been the major drive…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load shedding in the Nomad eval broker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/load-shedding-in-the-nomad-eval-broker</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/load-shedding-in-the-nomad-eval-broker"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the internals of Nomad's evaluation broker and how we recently reduced scheduler loads by 90% during rapid cluster changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subscribe to AWS Daily Feature Updates via Amazon SNS]]></title>
        <id>72dd09e4eceab939f2728e9149f87cff9f1f7f72</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/subscribe-to-aws-daily-feature-updates-via-amazon-sns/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T16:05:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Way back in 2015 I showed you how to Subscribe to AWS Public IP Address Changes via Amazon SNS. Today I am happy to tell you that you can now receive timely, detailed information about releases and updates to AWS via the same, simple mechanism. Daily Feature Updates Simply subscribe to topic arn:aws:sns:us-east-1:692768080016:aws-new-feature-updates using the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate Azure Load Testing into Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66568</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/integrate-azure-load-testing-into-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T15:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Load Testing became generally available in February 2023. It shipped with a lot of new features that were requested by you, the community. You can get started quickly from within the Azure portal, or upload your own custom JMeter script.
The post Integrate Azure Load Testing into Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 6, 2023]]></title>
        <id>40de9aac0b551134c097c6476cec6fc674aa7563</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-6-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T18:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a week full of interesting launches and I am thrilled to be able to share them with you today. We’ve got a new region in the works, a new tool for researchers, updates to Amazon Timestream, Control Tower, and Amazon Inspector, Lambda Powertools for .NET, existing services in new locations, lots of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Universal Speech Model (USM): State-of-the-art speech AI for 100+ languages]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/universal-speech-model-usm-state-of-art.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/universal-speech-model-usm-state-of-art.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T18:06:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yu Zhang, Research Scientist, and James Qin, Software Engineer, Google Research  
Last November, we announced the 1,000 Languages Initiative, an ambitious commitment to build a machine learning (ML) model that would support the world’s one thousand most-spoken languages, bringing greater inclusion to billions of people around the globe. However, some of these languages are spoken by fewer than twenty million people, so a core challenge is how to support languages for which there are relatively few speakers or limited available data. 

Today, we are excited to share more about the Universal Speech Model (USM), a critical first step towards supporting 1,000 languages. USM is a family of state-of-the-art speech models with 2B parameters trained on 12 million hours of speech and 28 b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grafana Labs, Rancher, Splunk, and Zscaler integrations expand Consul ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/grafana-labs-rancher-splunk-and-zscaler-integrations-expand-consul-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/grafana-labs-rancher-splunk-and-zscaler-integrations-expand-consul-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Consul ecosystem continues its growth with the addition of 13 new Consul integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.13 adds Kubernetes Operator, MFA improvements, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-13-adds-kubernetes-operator-mfa-improvements-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-13-adds-kubernetes-operator-mfa-improvements-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.13 brings enhancements to team workflows, integrations, and visibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build, test and deploy your application using Azure and GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66549</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/how-to-build-test-and-deploy-your-application-using-azure-and-github/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T10:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog-tutorial you will:
Use GitHub Codespaces (or your own IDE)
Note Using GitHub Codespaces can incur costs.
The post How to build, test and deploy your application using Azure and GitHub appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Azure DevOps Management Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66543</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/create-azure-devops-management-reports/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-05T17:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When managing any sized organization, there is always the question of how to track and review your existing policies on every single project. There is a solution that can query your exiting projects and provide management reports for a multitude of reports.
The post Create Azure DevOps Management Reports appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zeebe, or How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Batch Processing]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=74258&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=74258</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/zeebe-batch-processing/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T20:18:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how we successfully reduced Zeebe's process execution latency with batch processing during a recent hackday.
The post Zeebe, or How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Batch Processing appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Zell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performer-MPC: Navigation via real-time, on-robot transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/performer-mpc-navigation-via-real-time.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/performer-mpc-navigation-via-real-time.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Krzysztof Choromanski, Staff Research Scientist, Robotics at Google, and Xuesu Xiao, Visiting Researcher, George Mason University   
Despite decades of research, we don’t see many mobile robots roaming our homes, offices, and streets. Real-world robot navigation in human-centric environments remains an unsolved problem. These challenging situations require safe and efficient navigation through tight spaces, such as squeezing between coffee tables and couches, maneuvering in tight corners, doorways, untidy rooms, and more. An equally critical requirement is to navigate in a manner that complies with unwritten social norms around people, for example, yielding at blind corners or staying at a comfortable distance. Google Research is committed to examining how advances in ML may enab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed differential privacy for federated learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/distributed-differential-privacy-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/distributed-differential-privacy-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T21:14:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Florian Hartmann, Software Engineer, and Peter Kairouz, Research Scientist, Google Research  
Federated learning is a distributed way of training machine learning (ML) models where data is locally processed and only focused model updates and metrics that are intended for immediate aggregation are shared with a server that orchestrates training. This allows the training of models on locally available signals without exposing raw data to servers, increasing user privacy. In 2021, we announced that we are using federated learning to train Smart Text Selection models, an Android feature that helps users select and copy text easily by predicting what text they want to select and then automatically expanding the selection for them. 
 
Since that launch, we have worked to improve the pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.5 adds single sign-on and dynamic node metadata]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-5-adds-single-sign-on-and-dynamic-node-metadata</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-5-adds-single-sign-on-and-dynamic-node-metadata"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.5, now GA, improves management of security and access with single sign-on and OIDC support, and adds dynamic node metadata, policy management in the UI, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HCP-based global management plane for Consul now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-based-global-management-plane-for-consul-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-based-global-management-plane-for-consul-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new global management plane for Consul is now generally available. Try it out to gain full visibility for both self-managed and HCP Consul clusters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Works – AWS Region in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>4806290cc23bf1fd354dcda560ac6ff620a9aca4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/in-the-works-aws-region-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T02:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched an AWS Region in Australia earlier this year, four more (Switzerland, Spain, the United Arab Emirates, and India) in 2022, and are working on regions in Canada, Israel, New Zealand, and Thailand. All told, we now have 99 Availability Zones spread across 31 geographic regions. Malaysia in the Works Today I am happy […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn, Build, and Innovate Together at the Camunda Community Summit 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=73931&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=73931</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/learn-build-innovate-camunda-community-summit-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T22:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The annual Camunda Community Summit is a true highlight in our calendar - join with the community and learn from talk tracks both onsite and online.
The post Learn, Build, and Innovate Together at the Camunda Community Summit 2023 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.15 adds Envoy extensions and enhances Envoy access logging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-15-adds-envoy-extensions-and-enhances-access-logging</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-15-adds-envoy-extensions-and-enhances-access-logging"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.15 simplifies user onboarding, enhances troubleshooting workflows, and reduces operational complexity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching old labels new tricks in heterogeneous graphs]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/teaching-old-labels-new-tricks-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/teaching-old-labels-new-tricks-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Minji Yoon, Research Intern, and Bryan Perozzi, Research Scientist, Google Research, Graph Mining Team  
Industrial applications of machine learning are commonly composed of various items that have differing data modalities or feature distributions. Heterogeneous graphs (HGs) offer a unified view of these multimodal data systems by defining multiple types of nodes (for each data type) and edges (for the relation between data items). For instance, e-commerce networks might have [user, product, review] nodes or video platforms might have [channel, user, video, comment] nodes. Heterogeneous graph neural networks (HGNNs) learn node embeddings summarizing each node’s relationships into a vector. However, in real world HGs, there is often a label imbalance issue between different node …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshoot RDS connectivity issues with Ansible validated content]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/troubleshoot-rds-connectivity-issues-with-ansible-validated-content</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/troubleshoot-rds-connectivity-issues-with-ansible-validated-content"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible validated content cloud.aws_troubleshooting introduces a role named troubleshoot_rds_connectivity. This role helps you troubleshoot AWS Relational Database Service (RDS) connectivity issues from an EC2 instance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aubin Bikouo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon Lightsail for Research with All-in-One Research Environments]]></title>
        <id>07dfbcfe7d3b5b647f48a8a1c38b105367fcaa0f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-lightsail-for-research-with-all-in-one-research-environments/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T00:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the general availability of Amazon Lightsail for Research, a new offering that makes it easy for researchers and students to create and manage a high-performance CPU or a GPU research computer in just a few clicks on the cloud. You can use your preferred integrated development environments (IDEs) like preinstalled Jupyter, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing KWOK: Kubernetes WithOut Kubelet]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/01/introducing-kwok/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/01/introducing-kwok/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Shiming Zhang (DaoCloud), Wei Huang (Apple), Yibo Zhuang (Apple)
Have you ever wondered how to set up a cluster of thousands of nodes just in seconds, how to simulate real nodes with a low resource footprint, and how to test your Kubernetes controller at scale without spending much on infrastructure?
If you answered "yes" to any of these questions, then you might be interested in KWOK, a toolkit that enables you to create a cluster of thousands of nodes in seconds.
What is KWOK?
KWOK stands for Kubernetes WithOut Kubelet. So far, it provides two tools:
kwok
kwok is the cornerstone of this project, responsible for simulating the lifecycle of fake nodes, pods, and other Kubernetes API resources.
kwokctl
kwokctl is a CLI tool designed to streamline the creation and management of clust…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Datasets at your fingertips in Google Search]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/datasets-at-your-fingertips-in-google.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/datasets-at-your-fingertips-in-google.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T22:13:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Natasha Noy, Research Scientist, and Omar Benjelloun, Software Engineer, Google Research  
Access to datasets is critical to many of today's endeavors across verticals and industries, whether scientific research, business analysis, or public policy. In the scientific community and throughout various levels of the public sector, reproducibility and transparency are essential for progress, so sharing data is vital. For one example, in the United States a recent new policy requires free and equitable access to outcomes of all federally funded research, including data and statistical information along with publications. 

To facilitate discovery of content with this level of statistical detail and better distill this information from across the web, Google now makes it easier to sear…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research, 2022 & beyond: Research community engagement]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/google-research-2022-beyond-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/google-research-2022-beyond-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T19:40:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Posted by Leslie Yeh, Director, University Relations    
    

(This is Part 9 in our series of posts covering different topical areas of research at Google. You can find other posts in the series here.)
   

Sharing knowledge is essential to Google’s research philosophy — it accelerates technological progress and expands capabilities community-wide. Solving complex problems requires bringing together diverse minds and resources collaboratively. This can be accomplished through building local and global connections with multidisciplinary experts and impacted communities. In partnership with these stakeholders, we bring our technical leadership, product footprint, and resources to make progress against some of society's greatest opportunities and challenges.   
 We at Google see i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault on Microsoft Azure is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-on-microsoft-azure-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-on-microsoft-azure-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault on Microsoft Azure is now generally available and supports production workloads running on Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>