<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-04T00:20:12.091Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-04T00:20:12.091Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[True/useful]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47924</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/843666284/0/sethsblog~Trueuseful/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a simple grid that might change the way you think about internal stories: When we believe in something that’s useful but not true, it can serve a helpful purpose. The tooth fairy, perhaps. When we act on something that’s useful and also true, we’ve found a resilient path forward. That’s because the truth doesn’t […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When was the last time you used a compass?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46220</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/843556193/0/sethsblog~When-was-the-last-time-you-used-a-compass/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-02T10:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How about an astrolabe? Or even a watch? Technology advances, and sooner or later, the old stuff gets left behind. It’s easy to romanticize some of the classic devices that we built civilization on, and it’s worth remembering that the tech we’re wrestling with now will soon be faded away, with some folks nostalgic for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsupervised speech-to-speech translation from monolingual data]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/unsupervised-speech-to-speech.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/unsupervised-speech-to-speech.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eliya Nachmani, Research Scientist, and Michelle Tadmor Ramanovich, Software Engineer, Google Research






Speech-to-speech translation (S2ST) is a type of machine translation that converts spoken language from one language to another. This technology has the potential to break down language barriers and facilitate communication between people from different cultures and backgrounds. 




Previously, we introduced Translatotron 1 and Translatotron 2, the first ever models that were able to directly translate speech between two languages. However they were trained in supervised settings with parallel speech data. The scarcity of parallel speech data is a major challenge in this field, so much that most public datasets are semi- or fully-synthesized from text. This adds additiona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Work Items in Visual Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68130</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/work-items-in-visual-studio/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T14:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several years ago, with the introduction of Visual Studio 2019, we launched a completely revamped work item experience. This updated view operates entirely on REST, replacing the deprecated SOAP APIs utilized in the legacy version. Although Visual Studio 2022 still includes the option to revert to the legacy view,
The post Work Items in Visual Studio appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Striving For Better C++ Code, Part II: Function Summaries to Speed Up the Data Flow Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=412309</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/12/striving-for-better-cpp-code-part-ii-function-summaries-to-speed-up-the-data-flow-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T12:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second blog post in the series dedicated to Data Flow Analysis (DFA) and its implementation in CLion. Read the first part here: Striving For Better C++ Code, Part I: Data Flow Analysis Basics Striving For Better C++ Code, Part II: Function Summaries to Speed Up the Data Flow Analysis (this one) Introducing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qodana for .NET 8 is almost ready! Try the EAP and let us know what you think]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=qodana&amp;p=412236</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/qodana/2023/12/qodana-for-net-8-is-almost-ready-try-the-eap-and-let-us-know-what-you-think/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T11:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you migrated to a new version of the .NET framework, you might be having some issues using the Qodana .NET linter to scan projects. We know this can be frustrating, and we’ve been working hard to provide a solution in the new EAP version of the .NET linter for .NET 8. Starting with the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kerry Beetge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the committee decides]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46212</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/843346175/0/sethsblog~When-the-committee-decides/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T09:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They’re almost always conservative. Whether it’s a governmental body, the strategy group at a big company or the membership panel at the local country club, we can learn a lot by seeing what they approve and when they stall. Of course, each of us know a lot about our offering, the change we seek to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of generative AI in public sector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-future-of-generative-ai-in-public-sector</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-future-of-generative-ai-in-public-sector"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts from IDC and Elastic weigh in on how government and education organizations are approaching early generative AI use cases, the roadmap for future generative AI implementation, and how to address concerns around privacy and security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Erickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of generative AI in public sector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-future-of-generative-ai-in-public-sector</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-future-of-generative-ai-in-public-sector"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Recently, I sat down with Adelaide O’Brien, research vice president at IDC Government Insights, to discuss the current and future state of generative AI in the public sector worldwide. The full conversation is available to view on demand, but I also wanted to highlight some of the takeaways from the discussion. Our goal was to discuss use cases we’re seeing right now, what roadblocks public organizations are facing, and trade best practices on how organizations can harness the value of generative AI for employees, constituents, and larger digital transformation. 
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltdb1caed2d9a65e10/656a038e7539113410d0751e/RAG.png,RAG.pngHow RAG with Elastic can benefit public sector,

Grounded on facts: Use synced data in Elastic for accurate,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Erickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typical Seating Chart]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2862/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2862/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/typical_seating_chart.png" title="Now that airlines have started adding wheel locks to their drink carts, less than half of flights have one accidentally fall out through the hole." alt="Now that airlines have started adding wheel locks to their drink carts, less than half of flights have one accidentally fall out through the hole." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar Recording: Signals – The Future of Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=412210</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/11/webinar-recording-signals-the-future-of-angular/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T21:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recording from the Signals – The Future of Angular webinar is now available on the JetBrains YouTube channel! Delve into Angular Signals as our guest Kevin Kreuzer explores their API and uncovers the mechanics behind the scenes. Not only will you get to see signals in action, but also check out WebStorm’s support for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Aganezova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.3 Release Candidate Is Out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=412172</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/11/2023-3-release-candidate/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T21:09:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.3 Release Candidate is now available! You can get the latest build from our website, through the free Toolbox App, or via snaps for Ubuntu. To use this build, you need to have an active subscription to PyCharm Professional. Download PyCharm 2023.3 RC As we prepare to release PyCharm 2023.3, our team is making its final […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use AWS Fault Injection Service to demonstrate multi-region and multi-AZ application resilience]]></title>
        <id>b5f470ba74c346ed6f525a2a5e92522dc46cd4d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-aws-fault-injection-service-to-demonstrate-multi-region-and-multi-az-application-resilience/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Fault Injection Service (FIS) helps you to put chaos engineering into practice at scale. Today we are launching new scenarios that will let you demonstrate that your applications perform as intended if an AWS Availability Zone experiences a full power interruption or connectivity from one AWS region to another is lost. You can use […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zonal autoshift – Automatically shift your traffic away from Availability Zones when we detect potential issues]]></title>
        <id>f677c6705f71814fd999f39b325af14c6e9289e9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/zonal-autoshift-automatically-shift-your-traffic-away-from-availability-zones-when-we-detect-potential-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re launching zonal autoshift, a new capability of Amazon Route 53 Application Recovery Controller that you can enable to automatically and safely shift your workload’s traffic away from an Availability Zone when AWS identifies a potential failure affecting that Availability Zone and shift it back once the failure is resolved. When deploying resilient applications, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IDE extension for AWS Application Composer enhances visual modern applications development with AI-generated IaC]]></title>
        <id>66dd6400ac1e7d9ba598572e5cd829f82e8b6c05</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/ide-extension-for-aws-application-composer-enhances-visual-modern-applications-development-with-ai-generated-iac/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to share the integrated development environment (IDE) extension for AWS Application Composer. Now you can use AWS Application Composer directly in your IDE to visually build modern applications and iteratively develop your infrastructure as code templates with Amazon CodeWhisperer. Announced as preview at AWS re:Invent 2022 and generally available in March 2023, Application Composer is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Studio adds web-based interface, Code Editor, flexible workspaces, and streamlines user onboarding]]></title>
        <id>8202e0701d0edec7189fd74a2684035983c2a23f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-studio-adds-web-based-interface-code-editor-flexible-workspaces-and-streamlines-user-onboarding/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing an improved Amazon SageMaker Studio experience! The new SageMaker Studio web-based interface loads faster and provides consistent access to your preferred integrated development environment (IDE) and SageMaker resources and tooling, irrespective of your IDE choice. In addition to JupyterLab and RStudio, SageMaker Studio now includes a fully managed Code Editor based […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three new capabilities for Amazon Inspector broaden the realm of vulnerability scanning for workloads]]></title>
        <id>dbd84d0e15dc49a513d11dc8814a2ace24c64aef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/three-new-capabilities-for-amazon-inspector-broaden-the-realm-of-vulnerability-scanning-for-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon Inspector adds three new capabilities to increase the realm of possibilities when scanning your workloads for software vulnerabilities: Amazon Inspector introduces a new set of open source plugins and an API allowing you to assess your container images for software vulnerabilities at build time directly from your continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insider newsletter digest: How to use GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-30-from-the-pages-of-our-insider-newsletter-how-to-use-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-30-from-the-pages-of-our-insider-newsletter-how-to-use-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore the July edition, featuring prompts, tips, and use cases for GitHub Copilot.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-30-from-the-pages-of-our-insider-newsletter-how-to-use-github-copilot/">Insider newsletter digest: How to use GitHub Copilot</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudWatch Application Signals for automatic instrumentation of your applications (preview)]]></title>
        <id>1d6092ef569153d497e5ee163eee98821d30bf12</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-cloudwatch-application-signals-for-automatic-instrumentation-of-your-applications-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the challenges with distributed systems is that they are made up of many interdependent services, which add a degree of complexity when you are trying to monitor their performance. Determining which services and APIs are experiencing high latencies or degraded availability requires manually putting together telemetry signals. This can result in time and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New myApplications in the AWS Management Console simplifies managing your application resources]]></title>
        <id>ec4fc257d1c6efc31dbdad1cfa3fa78ebe223b5a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-myapplications-in-the-aws-management-console-simplifies-managing-your-application-resources/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the general availability of myApplications supporting application operations, a new set of capabilities that help you get started with your applications on AWS, operate them with less effort, and move faster at scale. With myApplication in the AWS Management Console, you can more easily manage and monitor the cost, health, security […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 Release Candidate Is Out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=410559</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/11/intellij-idea-2023-3-release-candidate/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 Release Candidate is now available! You can get the latest build from our website, through the free Toolbox App, or via snaps for Ubuntu. To use this build, you need to have an active subscription to IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate. Download IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 RC As we prepare to release IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.3 Release Candidate]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=411494</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/11/clion-2023-3-release-candidate/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.3 is on its way, and the release candidate for v2023.3 is already available! To install CLion 2023.3 RC (build 233.11799.171), download it from the website, update via the Toolbox App, or use this snap package (for Ubuntu). You need an active subscription or a trial license to use CLion 2023.3 RC. If you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.3 RC]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=409802</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/11/phpstorm-2023-3-rc/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.3 Release Candidate is now available! Unlike previous EAP builds, this RC requires you to have a valid PhpStorm license. This build bundles the Pest plugin into PhpStorm, so you’ll now be able to enjoy it out of the box. To learn more about the this new addition, please refer to our recent blog post. See […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tania Goral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.3 Release Candidate Is Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=411556</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/11/webstorm-2023-3-rc/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the official release just around the corner, we’re happy to offer our WebStorm 2023.3 Release Candidate for you to try. Unlike our previous EAP builds, you must have an active WebStorm license to use it. Otherwise, you’ll need to sign up for a 30-day free trial to install and run this build. DOWNLOAD WEBSTORM […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Developer Ecosystem in 2023: Key Trends for C#]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=409783</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/11/30/the-developer-ecosystem-in-2023-key-trends-for-csharp/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve captured insights from 26,348 developers worldwide in our annual Developer Ecosystem Survey 2023. This recap focuses on C# and .NET, but you can see what’s trending in other languages as well. Enjoy the results and commentary, and let us know what you think! Top Discoveries We know that ASP.NET Core is the most used […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing our home labs: Home Assistant code review]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-30-securing-our-home-labs-home-assistant-code-review/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-30-securing-our-home-labs-home-assistant-code-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T13:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The GitHub Security Lab examined the most popular open source software running on our home labs, with the aim of enhancing its security. Here's what we found and what you can do to better protect your own smart home.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-30-securing-our-home-labs-home-assistant-code-review/">Securing our home labs: Home Assistant code review</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy November Digest]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=411349</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/11/30/jetbrains-academy-november-digest/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T12:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here we go again! Another exciting November at JetBrains Academy!Discover how to save up to 30% on your studies, explore the intriguing connection between pandas and coding, and find the path to a Computer Science degree with hands-on experience. Plus, there are special updates for educators and universities. Dive in below!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Sharobaeva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The thing about Hobson]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42495</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/843081119/0/sethsblog~The-thing-about-Hobson/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People talk about Hobson’s choice as if it’s always a bad thing. A liveryman in pre-industrial London, he rented horses. And every customer was allowed to take the horse closest to the door. Hobson’s choice is no choice at all. Of course, this system meant that the horses were rotated, and the fanciest ones weren’t […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Datalore Enterprise 2023.6]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=411771</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2023/11/30/what-s-new-in-datalore-enterprise-2023-6/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T10:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, Datalore Enterprise 2023.6 offers an improved UI, introduces OAuth authentication for Snowflake and BigQuery, allows you to export and import database connections in XML-like formats, and brings a number of other improvements and bug fixes. Upgrade to 2023.6 New Datalore UI The Datalore UI has been redesigned to give notebooks a simpler, cleaner, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Anikina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily deploy SaaS products with new Quick Launch in AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>165f32cc180f9fa0cf1f36aff4e46a246fa890b6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/easily-deploy-saas-products-with-new-quick-launch-in-aws-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are excited to announce the general availability of SaaS Quick Launch, a new feature in AWS Marketplace that makes it easy and secure to deploy SaaS products. Before SaaS Quick Launch, configuring and launching third-party SaaS products could be time-consuming and costly, especially in certain categories like security and monitoring. Some products require […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Security legend Laura Spilca joins us to talk Spring Authorization Server and upgrading to Spring Boot 3]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-legend-laura-spilca-joins-us-to-talk</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-legend-laura-spilca-joins-us-to-talk"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paving the way for modern search workflows and generative AI apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-search-workflows-generative-ai-apps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-search-workflows-generative-ai-apps"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic is the best developer platform for building AI search and generative AI apps with expanded ecosystem partners, full document vector search, a proprietary ML model for semantic search now in GA, and a simple API-first developer experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Riley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paving the way for modern search workflows and generative AI apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-search-workflows-generative-ai-apps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/modern-search-workflows-generative-ai-apps"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In this blog, we want to share the investments that Elastic® is making to simplify your experience as you build AI applications. We know that developers have to stay nimble in today’s fast-evolving AI environment. Yet, common challenges make building generative AI applications needlessly rigid and complicated. To name just a few:


Vectors — from how many to which ones you can use and how to chunk large passages of text

Evaluating, swapping, and managing large language models (LLMs)

Setting up effective semantic search (particularly if your development team has limited resources or skill gaps) 

Leveraging existing investments and current architectures while balancing tech debt

Scaling from proof-of-concept to production 

Making sure that end-user applications are fast and cost-effec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Riley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All of Netflix’s HDR video streaming is now dynamically optimized]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e9e0cb15f2ba</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/all-of-netflixs-hdr-video-streaming-is-now-dynamically-optimized-e9e0cb15f2ba?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by  Aditya Mavlankar, Zhi Li, Lukáš Krasula and Christos Bampis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Package and deploy models faster with new tools and guided workflows in Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>9dfa4013fdeb3ce3b8c9cd5ded8657c6f07139cc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/package-and-deploy-models-faster-with-new-tools-and-guided-workflows-in-amazon-sagemaker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that Amazon SageMaker now comes with an improved model deployment experience to help you deploy traditional machine learning (ML) models and foundation models (FMs) faster. As a data scientist or ML practitioner, you can now use the new ModelBuilder class in the SageMaker Python SDK to package models, perform local inference […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use natural language to explore and prepare data with a new capability of Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>52022c89be15e7efe7a0e5d886a1b76e6bb36028</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-natural-language-to-explore-and-prepare-data-with-a-new-capability-of-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to introduce the ability to use natural language instructions in Amazon SageMaker Canvas to explore, visualize, and transform data for machine learning (ML). SageMaker Canvas now supports using foundation model-(FM) powered natural language instructions to complement its comprehensive data preparation capabilities for data exploration, analysis, visualization, and transformation. Using natural language instructions, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker adds new inference capabilities to help reduce foundation model deployment costs and latency]]></title>
        <id>070abf1c19c0afcc710d7953b53d84a40e4e4b82</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-adds-new-inference-capabilities-to-help-reduce-foundation-model-deployment-costs-and-latency/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing new Amazon SageMaker inference capabilities that can help you optimize deployment costs and reduce latency. With the new inference capabilities, you can deploy one or more foundation models (FMs) on the same SageMaker endpoint and control how many accelerators and how much memory is reserved for each FM. This helps to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage foundation models for business analysis at scale with Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>286f7dd53aa2b49a2bbca8dcddcd42842c920920</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/leverage-foundation-models-for-business-analysis-at-scale-with-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m excited to introduce a new capability in Amazon SageMaker Canvas to use foundation models (FMs) from Amazon Bedrock and Amazon SageMaker Jumpstart through a no-code experience. This new capability makes it easier for you to evaluate and generate responses from FMs for your specific use case with high accuracy. Every business has its […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing highly durable Amazon OpenSearch Service clusters with 30% price/performance improvement]]></title>
        <id>9254592bff3a8ff942fbbd9434437e0a80455403</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-highly-durable-amazon-opensearch-service-clusters-with-30-price-performance-improvement/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the new OR1 instances to create Amazon OpenSearch Service clusters that use Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) for primary storage. You can ingest, store, index, and access just about any imaginable amount of data, while also enjoying a 30% price/performance improvement over existing instance types, eleven nines of data durability, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Clarify makes it easier to evaluate and select foundation models (preview)]]></title>
        <id>8eb45aec03e2c9174185648ea2e15d148920732c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-clarify-makes-it-easier-to-evaluate-and-select-foundation-models-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that Amazon SageMaker Clarify now supports foundation model (FM) evaluation (preview). As a data scientist or machine learning (ML) engineer, you can now use SageMaker Clarify to evaluate, compare, and select FMs in minutes based on metrics such as accuracy, robustness, creativity, factual knowledge, bias, and toxicity. This new capability adds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluate, compare, and select the best foundation models for your use case in Amazon Bedrock (preview)]]></title>
        <id>d609890b177381df2b101da3ee61fcba234993e4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/evaluate-compare-and-select-the-best-foundation-models-for-your-use-case-in-amazon-bedrock-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that you can now evaluate, compare, and select the best foundation models (FMs) for your use case in Amazon Bedrock. Model Evaluation on Amazon Bedrock is available today in preview. Amazon Bedrock offers a choice of automatic evaluation and human evaluation. You can use automatic evaluation with predefined metrics such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift adds new AI capabilities, including Amazon Q, to boost efficiency and productivity]]></title>
        <id>d33d7b803e5c2060a28968285e9fa1f2403b84ce</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-redshift-adds-new-ai-capabilities-to-boost-efficiency-and-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift puts artificial intelligence (AI) at your service to optimize efficiencies and make you more productive with two new capabilities that we are launching in preview today. First, Amazon Redshift Serverless becomes smarter. It scales capacity proactively and automatically along dimensions such as the complexity of your queries, their frequency, the size of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Clean Rooms Differential Privacy enhances privacy protection of your users’ data (preview)]]></title>
        <id>046eaa3e0b7d8591180c049c34b977499c294c70</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-clean-rooms-differential-privacy-enhances-privacy-protection-of-your-users-data-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can use AWS Clean Rooms Diﬀerential Privacy (preview) to help protect the privacy of your users with mathematically backed and intuitive controls in a few steps. As a fully managed capability of AWS Clean Rooms, no prior differential privacy experience is needed to help you prevent the reidentification of your users. AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Clean Rooms ML helps customers and partners apply ML models without sharing raw data (preview)]]></title>
        <id>30344b64e2852c44c41aaa3fee6ef1070e91cf3a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-clean-rooms-ml-helps-customers-and-partners-apply-ml-models-without-sharing-raw-data-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re introducing AWS Clean Rooms ML (preview), a new capability of AWS Clean Rooms that helps you and your partners apply machine learning (ML) models on your collective data without copying or sharing raw data with each other. With this new capability, you can generate predictive insights using ML models while continuing to protect your sensitive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon OpenSearch Service zero-ETL integration with Amazon S3 (preview)]]></title>
        <id>eda84244f81c1f8800d261452c3a2b4a004d3ae9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-opensearch-service-zero-etl-integration-with-amazon-s3-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing a preview of Amazon OpenSearch Service zero-ETL integration with Amazon S3, a new way to query operational logs in Amazon S3 and S3-based data lakes without needing to switch between services. You can now analyze infrequently queried data in cloud object stores and simultaneously use the operational analytics and visualization capabilities […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyze large amounts of graph data to get insights and find trends with Amazon Neptune Analytics]]></title>
        <id>d94eeba2eb21724f0c373832cdac1c7163b8aa8d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-neptune-analytics-a-high-performance-graph-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am happy to announce the general availability of Amazon Neptune Analytics, a new analytics database engine that makes it faster for data scientists and application developers to quickly analyze large amounts of graph data. With Neptune Analytics, you can now quickly load your dataset from Amazon Neptune or your data lake on Amazon Simple […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your Terraform development with Amazon CodeWhisperer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerate-your-terraform-development-with-amazon-codewhisperer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerate-your-terraform-development-with-amazon-codewhisperer"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improve the developer experience writing Terraform code with the help of generative AI powered by Amazon CodeWhisperer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ReSharper 2023.3 Release Candidate Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=410866</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/11/29/the-resharper-2023-3-rc/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T15:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a preview of all the latest features and improvements set to be shipped with the next major ReSharper and .NET tools releases by downloading the Release Candidate builds that have just landed. Here are the major improvements in each of the new builds: The ReSharper 2023.3 Release Candidate The ReSharper C++ 2023.3 Release Candidate […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第242話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755511181824</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755511181824"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of estimation]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47843</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/842989949/0/sethsblog~The-art-of-estimation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T09:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a freelancer or a contractor of any kind, it’s typical to be asked for an estimate or a quote. And if you’ve been doing business for a while, it’s likely that you’ve heard about price more than just about any other factor in losing an opportunity. So the pressure is on to sharpen […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X Value]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2861/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2861/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/x_value.png" title="The value of n is still unknown, but new results constrain it to fall between 8 and 10^500, ruling out popular 'n=1' and 'n=2' theories." alt="The value of n is still unknown, but new results constrain it to fall between 8 and 10^500, ruling out popular 'n=1' and 'n=2' theories." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform delivers launch-day support for Amazon S3 Express]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-delivers-launch-day-support-for-amazon-s3-express</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-delivers-launch-day-support-for-amazon-s3-express"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s Terraform provider for AWS now enables users to manage their S3 Express buckets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68117</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-1-rtw-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we released Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW. This is our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2022.1. You can directly install Azure DevOps Server 2022 Update 1 or upgrade from any version of Azure DevOps or TFS, including Team Foundation Server 2015 and newer.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: New Experimental Features in Gateway API v1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/28/gateway-api-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/28/gateway-api-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Candace Holman (Red Hat), Dave Protasowski (VMware), Gaurav K Ghildiyal (Google), John Howard (Google), Simone Rodigari (IBM)
Recently, the Gateway API announced its v1.0 GA release, marking a huge milestone for the project.
Along with stabilizing some of the core functionality in the API, a number of exciting new experimental features have been added.
Backend TLS Policy
BackendTLSPolicy is a new Gateway API type used for specifying the TLS configuration of the connection from the Gateway to backend Pods via the Service API object.
It is specified as a Direct PolicyAttachment without defaults or overrides, applied to a Service that accesses a backend, where the BackendTLSPolicy resides in the same namespace as the Service to which it is applied.
All Gateway API Routes that point t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform extension for VS Code adds Terraform Cloud view]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-extension-for-vs-code-adds-terraform-cloud-view</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-extension-for-vs-code-adds-terraform-cloud-view"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new view in the HashiCorp Terraform extension for Visual Studio Code shows your Terraform Cloud workspaces and runs, reducing context-switching.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at re:Invent 2023: A year of collaboration with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-re-invent-2023-a-year-of-collaboration-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-re-invent-2023-a-year-of-collaboration-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recap of HashiCorp infrastructure and security news and developments on AWS from the past year, from self-service provisioning to fighting secrets sprawl and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study groups]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47885</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/842651315/0/sethsblog~Study-groups/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T09:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I had to choose one metric that would determine how well someone would do in law school, it wouldn’t be the LSAT or another test. It would be whether or not they formed a study group, and who else was in it. Of course, the same is true for your project, or any sort […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - 28 November, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/this-week-in-spring-28-november-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/this-week-in-spring-28-november-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.15, 3.0.10, 3.1.6 and 3.2.0-RC1 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/spring-shell-2-1-15-3-0-10-3-1-6-and-3-2-0-rc1-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/spring-shell-2-1-15-3-0-10-3-1-6-and-3-2-0-rc1-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step guide to creating custom ES Rally tracks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ES Rally is a benchmarking tool for Elasticsearch, enabling performance testing and decision-making through custom data tracks and comparative analysis. This comprehensive guide will show you the steps to take to craft personalized ES Rally tracks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alejandro Sánchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step guide to creating custom ES Rally tracks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is ES Rally, and what is it for?,
ES Rally is a tool for testing performance on Elasticsearch® that allows you to run and record comparative tests.

Decision-making can be difficult, especially when you don't have the information you need and only have guesses or experience from past changes that have been positive or negative.

If we add to this that the data world must be flexible, as it evolves rapidly and therefore our Elasticsearch must adapt to it, this tool will help us to be able to measure all the changes and evolutions that we make over time and evaluate their impact. And most importantly, we can then obtain the information needed to make the right decisions.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt1d9db82a7e208b53/6566052e3994175cc8b4981b/1-elastic-bl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alejandro Sánchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Original Research: MIT CODE 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9340b879176a</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/netflix-original-research-mit-code-2023-9340b879176a?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix was thrilled to be the premier sponsor for the 2nd year in a row at the 2023 Conference on Digital Experimentation (CODE@MIT).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gain operator confidence with HCP Consul Central observability features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/gain-operator-confidence-with-hcp-consul-central-observability-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/gain-operator-confidence-with-hcp-consul-central-observability-features"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul Central’s new observability features were recently used by a customer to help troubleshoot an issue with assistance from HashiCorp engineers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform stacks, explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-stacks-explained</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-stacks-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform stacks simplify provisioning and managing resources at scale, reducing the time and overhead of managing infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing resources with the Terraform AWS Cloud Control provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Cloud Control provider — built around the AWS Cloud Control API — is designed to bring new services to HashiCorp Terraform faster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hard part first]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44586</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/842296271/0/sethsblog~The-hard-part-first/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T09:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re trying to reduce risk, do the hard part first. That way, if it fails, you’ll have minimized your time and effort. On the other hand, if you’re looking for buy-in and commitment so you can get through the hard part, do it last. People are terrible at ignoring sunk costs, and the early […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-34053, CVE-2023-34055: Spring Framework and Spring Boot vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/27/cve-2023-34053-cve-2023-34055-spring-framework-and-spring-boot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/27/cve-2023-34053-cve-2023-34055-spring-framework-and-spring-boot"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decay Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2860/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2860/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/decay_modes.png" title="Unlike an Iron Age collapse, a Bronze Age collapse releases energy, since copper and tin are past the iron peak on the curve of binding energy." alt="Unlike an Iron Age collapse, a Bronze Age collapse releases energy, since copper and tin are past the iron peak on the curve of binding energy." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The long-range forecast keeps shifting]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46175</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/841853183/0/sethsblog~The-longrange-forecast-keeps-shifting/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exactly. That’s why it’s a forecast, not an accurate account of what’s going to happen in the future. This seems axiomatic, but our desire for certainty keeps letting us down. The shifting of forecasts is evidence that they’re merely forecasts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After the meteorite]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43520</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/841468958/0/sethsblog~After-the-meteorite/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it slams into your house and destroys it, we’re likely to pursue one of two lines of thinking: –How did I cause this? What choices did I make, what mistakes did I permit, why did I deserve to have this damage, or who can I blame? –Well, that happened, now what should I do? […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Causal Machine Learning for Creative Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4b0ce22a8a96</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/causal-machine-learning-for-creative-insights-4b0ce22a8a96?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T01:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A framework to identify the causal impact of successful visual components.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The network scam]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47825</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/841229846/0/sethsblog~The-network-scam/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T09:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lana Swartz coined this term in her breakthrough paper on crypto. A scam always involves a transaction. In the traditional fraud, the scammer tells a lie and the buyer, either with or without diligence, believes it and loses everything. You buy the magic beans, but they don’t grow. But modern scams have a network component […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.1 GA and 1.0.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/24/spring-modulith-1-1-ga-and-1-0-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/24/spring-modulith-1-1-ga-and-1-0-3-released"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Vault 3.1 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/24/spring-vault-3-1-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/24/spring-vault-3-1-available"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oceanography Gift]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2859/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2859/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/oceanography_gift.png" title="Shipping times vary. Same-ocean delivery may only take a few years, but delivery from the Weddell Sea in Antarctica may take multiple decades, and molecules meant for inland seas like the Mediterranean may be returned as undeliverable by surface currents." alt="Shipping times vary. Same-ocean delivery may only take a few years, but delivery from the Weddell Sea in Antarctica may take multiple decades, and molecules meant for inland seas like the Mediterranean may be returned as undeliverable by surface currents." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/24/sig-testing-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/24/sig-testing-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sandipan Panda
Welcome to another edition of the SIG spotlight blog series, where we
highlight the incredible work being done by various Special Interest
Groups (SIGs) within the Kubernetes project. In this edition, we turn
our attention to SIG Testing,
a group interested in effective testing of Kubernetes and automating
away project toil. SIG Testing focus on creating and running tools and
infrastructure that make it easier for the community to write and run
tests, and to contribute, analyze and act upon test results.
To gain some insights into SIG Testing, Sandipan
Panda spoke with Michelle Shepardson,
a senior software engineer at Google and a chair of SIG Testing, and
Patrick Ohly, a software engineer and architect at
Intel and a SIG Testing Tech Lead.
Meet the contributors
San…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-2-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-2-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-1-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-1-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: iText Creator Bruno Lowagie]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/a-bootiful-podcast-itext-creator-bruno-lowagie</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/a-bootiful-podcast-itext-creator-bruno-lowagie"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.13 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-0-13-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-0-13-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closing the skills and talent divide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/closing-the-skills-and-talent-divide</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/closing-the-skills-and-talent-divide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the HashiCast: Navigating the Cloud for C-Suites podcast addresses how to close the skills gap. Guest James Footman, Head of Talent for EMEA at HashiCorp, highlights the key takeaways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving simulations of clouds and their effects on climate]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/improving-simulations-of-clouds-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/improving-simulations-of-clouds-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tapio Schneider, Visiting Researcher, and Yi-fan Chen, Engineering Lead, Google Research




Today’s climate models successfully capture broad global warming trends. However, because of uncertainties about processes that are small in scale yet globally important, such as clouds and ocean turbulence, these models’ predictions of upcoming climate changes are not very accurate in detail. For example, predictions of the time by which the global mean surface temperature of Earth will have warmed 2℃, relative to preindustrial times, vary by 40–50 years (a full human generation) among today’s models. As a result, we do not have the accurate and geographically granular predictions we need to plan resilient infrastructure, adapt supply chains to climate disruption, and assess the risks of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability monitors metrics for Google Cloud in just minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow this step-by-step process to enable Elastic Observability for Google Cloud Platform metrics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon,Eric Lowry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability monitors metrics for Google Cloud in just minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Developers and SREs choose to host their applications on Google Cloud Platform (GCP) for its reliability, speed, and ease of use. On Google Cloud, development teams are finding additional value in migrating to Kubernetes on GKE, leveraging the latest serverless options like Cloud Run, and improving traditional, tiered applications with managed services.
Elastic Observability offers 16 out-of-the-box integrations for Google Cloud services with more on the way. A full list of Google Cloud integrations can be found in our online documentation.
In addition to our native Google Cloud integrations, Elastic Observability aggregates not only logs but also metrics for Google Cloud services and the applications running on Google Cloud compute services (Compute Engine, Cloud Run, Cloud Functions, K…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon,Eric Lowry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open sourcing Project Guideline: A platform for computer vision accessibility technology]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/open-sourcing-project-guideline.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/open-sourcing-project-guideline.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dave Hawkey, Software Engineer, Google Research




Two years ago we announced Project Guideline, a collaboration between Google Research and Guiding Eyes for the Blind that enabled people with visual impairments (e.g., blindness and low-vision) to walk, jog, and run independently. Using only a Google Pixel phone and headphones, Project Guideline leverages on-device machine learning (ML) to navigate users along outdoor paths marked with a painted line. The technology has been tested all over the world and even demonstrated during the opening ceremony at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games.



Since the original announcement, we set out to improve Project Guideline by embedding new features, such as obstacle detection and advanced path planning, to safely and reliably navigate users t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Good First Issue: Introducing a new way to contribute]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-21-for-good-first-issue-introducing-a-new-way-to-contribute/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-21-for-good-first-issue-introducing-a-new-way-to-contribute/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For Good First Issue is a curated list of open source projects that are also digital public goods and need the help of developers.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-21-for-good-first-issue-introducing-a-new-way-to-contribute/">For Good First Issue: Introducing a new way to contribute</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at AWS re:Invent: Your blueprint for cloud success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-your-blueprint-for-cloud-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-your-blueprint-for-cloud-success"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re attending AWS re:Invent in Las Vegas, Nov. 27 - Dec. 1, visit us for breakout sessions, expert talks, and product demos to learn how to accelerate your adoption of a cloud operating model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Fall Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68016</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-fall-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T16:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have been following these posts, then you are more than familiar with our New Boards Hub initiative. We have been doing our best to keep our community informed of the new features and our rollout plans. Now is a good time to provide an update on where things are at with a couple of our new preview features,
The post New Boards Hub, Fall Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Processing using Netflix Maestro and Apache Iceberg]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b8ba072ddeeb</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/incremental-processing-using-netflix-maestro-and-apache-iceberg-b8ba072ddeeb?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T05:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Jun He, Yingyi Zhang, and Pawan Dixit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josey Coles shares what skills translated from the military to the corporate world and her tips for other veterans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tips-for-veterans</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tips-for-veterans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josey Coles joined the US military in 2016 as a cyber operations specialist. She has since transitioned out of the military and shares her experience and advice for other veterans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C-suite insights on the transformative power of generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore insights from top IT leaders on leveraging generative AI for enhancing operational resilience, mitigating security risk, and creating exceptional customer experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Klinger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josey Coles shares what skills translated from the military to the corporate world and her tips for other veterans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tips-for-veterans</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tips-for-veterans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Josey Coles, Sr. Manager, Education Services at Elastic®, joined the US military in 2016 as a cyber operations specialist. As a math major, cybersecurity wasn’t her background or on her list of interests but the Army gave her a lot of experience, she says.
As a cyber operations specialist, Josey was part of the Cyber Protection Brigade. She responded to incidents and was required to be onsite within 48 hours of the call. Onsite, her team would listen to network traffic, determine if the line was compromised, and put a risk mitigation plan in place to prevent future intrusions. 

After four years, and a promotion to senior network analyst, Josey transitioned out of the military for medical reasons. 

“The most challenging part was the uncertainty,” she says. “The military has a way of tak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C-suite insights on the transformative power of generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Generative AI is revolutionizing the way businesses operate, from improving operational resilience to mitigating security risks and enhancing customer experiences. In a recent roundup of c-suite insights from three IT leaders — Matt Minetola, CIO, Mandy Andress, CISO, and Rick Laner, chief customer officer — we gain a comprehensive understanding of how generative AI is being used to improve business outcomes across organizations.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt3135954a466f9c02/655d0750107d423a15b7b191/1-elastic-blog-matt-minetola.png,1-elastic-blog-matt-minetola.png,
Matt Minetola, CIO at Elastic, highlights the use of generative AI in improving operational resilience. He points out that organizations already possess a wealth of telemetry data, which is cr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Klinger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from Git 2.43]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-20-highlights-from-git-2-43/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-20-highlights-from-git-2-43/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T18:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The last Git release of 2023 is here! Take a look at some of our highlights on what's new in Git 2.43.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-20-highlights-from-git-2-43/">Highlights from Git 2.43</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault integrations with Intel, Pure Storage, Red Hat, and more continue to strengthen customer security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-intel-pure-storage-red-hat-and-more-continue-to-strengthe</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-intel-pure-storage-red-hat-and-more-continue-to-strengthe"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10 new HashiCorp Vault ecosystem integrations extend security use cases for customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging practices for Society-Centered AI]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/emerging-practices-for-society-centered.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/emerging-practices-for-society-centered.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Anoop Sinha, Research Director, Technology & Society, and Yossi Matias, Vice President, Google Research




The first of Google’s AI Principles is to “Be socially beneficial.” As AI practitioners, we’re inspired by the transformative potential of AI technologies to benefit society and our shared environment at a scale and swiftness that wasn’t possible before. From helping address the climate crisis to helping transform healthcare, to making the digital world more accessible, our goal is to apply AI responsibly to be helpful to more people around the globe. Achieving global scale requires researchers and communities to think ahead — and act — collectively across the AI ecosystem.



We call this approach Society-Centered AI. It is both an extension and an expansion of Human-Cente…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting Kibana health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-kibana-health</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-kibana-health"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post provides a troubleshooting framework for Kibana’s health overall, focusing on its Task Manager and Alerting framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stef Nestor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting Kibana health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-kibana-health</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-kibana-health"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
You can access the Elasticsearch® database through Elastic’s UI product: Kibana®. While most Elastic® services run from Elasticsearch, a handful of key features run from within Kibana’s servers: Telemetry, Rules (with associated Actions), Reporting, and Sessions. We’ll walk through troubleshooting overall Kibana health and its most popular plugins. This content is generally true for 7.x and 8.x, but it is tested directly against v8.7.1.
# undocumented, internal API
## ui
> GET KIBANA_URL/status
## api
> GET kbn:/api/status

# https://www.elastic.co/guide/en/kibana/current/task-manager-api-health.html
> GET kbn:api/task_manager/_health
,
Once you have these responses stored respectively as kibana_status.json and kibana_task_manager_health.json, then you have the two core APIs Support insp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stef Nestor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps’ First Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68002</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-first-consensus-assessment-initiative-questionnaire-caiq-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am thrilled to announce that we have now published, for the first time, a Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) specific to Azure DevOps. The Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) is a tool developed by the Cloud Security Alliance (CSA). It serves as a standard set of questions aimed at helping potential cloud customers evaluate the security capabilities of cloud service providers.
The post Azure DevOps’ First Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) Now Available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benibo Ajumogobia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Adversarial testing for generative AI safety]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research_16.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research_16.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kathy Meier-Hellstern, Building Responsible AI & Data Systems, Director, Google Research




The Responsible AI and Human-Centered Technology (RAI-HCT) team within Google Research is committed to advancing the theory and practice of responsible human-centered AI through a lens of culturally-aware research, to meet the needs of billions of users today, and blaze the path forward for a better AI future. The BRAIDS (Building Responsible AI Data and Solutions) team within RAI-HCT aims to simplify the adoption of RAI practices through the utilization of scalable tools, high-quality data, streamlined processes, and novel research with a current emphasis on addressing the unique challenges posed by generative AI (GenAI).





GenAI models have enabled unprecedented capabilities leading …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security best practices for authors of GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-16-security-best-practices-for-authors-of-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-16-security-best-practices-for-authors-of-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Improve your GitHub Action’s security posture by securing your source repository, protecting your maintainers, and making it easy to report security incidents. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-16-security-best-practices-for-authors-of-github-actions/">Security best practices for authors of GitHub Actions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and University of Canberra: A partnership for student success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-university-of-canberra-partnership-student-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-university-of-canberra-partnership-student-success"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, learn about the partnership between Elastic and the University of Canberra as well as the benefits and outcomes of the partnership for the students, the university, and the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vu Pham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching majors led Kathleen DeRusso to a career in search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-kathleen-derusso-search-software-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-kathleen-derusso-search-software-engineer"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kathleen DeRusso likes to solve problems, something she gets to do every day in her software engineering job. Read more about her career journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Support Hub moves to semantic search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-support-hub-moves-to-semantic-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-support-hub-moves-to-semantic-search"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We transitioned our Support Hub to semantic search, a more advanced search method that understands user intent rather than relying on keywords. This transition helps provide customers with more relevant search results in Elastic's support content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blaisure</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and University of Canberra: A partnership for student success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-university-of-canberra-partnership-student-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-university-of-canberra-partnership-student-success"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The IT sector is one of the most dynamic and innovative industries in the world. However, it also faces a serious challenge of finding and retaining qualified talent. The Australian Information Industry Association (AIIA) survey for 2023 revealed that skill shortages are the single biggest inhibitor to business growth in Australia. The survey also found that 49% of IT graduates in Australia needed further training to be effective employees. To address this issue, the University of Canberra (UC) is committed to delivering work-ready graduates who can meet the industry’s needs and expectations. One of the ways UC does this is by offering its final year students Capstone projects, which help them apply and improve their skills for their future careers.
Elastic®, a leading provider of softwa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vu Pham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching majors led Kathleen DeRusso to a career in search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-kathleen-derusso-search-software-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-kathleen-derusso-search-software-engineer"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
After completing a Java developer course during college, Kathleen DeRusso liked it enough to change her major from business to computer science. 

“I like to solve interesting and challenging problems,” Kathleen says.

Early in her career, she worked for a B2B product company in their search organization where she evolved their search to enable electronic parts to be searchable by number. 

“I stayed on search the entire time,” she says. “I started in a role that would probably be thought of as SRE today and then moved into search development. We had a home grown search engine over manufacturer catalogs based on Lucene, then another search product searching electronic part numbers backed by SOLR. I led the project to migrate from both homegrown and SOLR search engines to Elasticsearch®.”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Support Hub moves to semantic search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-support-hub-moves-to-semantic-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-support-hub-moves-to-semantic-search"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re excited to share a recent enhancement made to the Elastic Support Hub: it’s now powered by semantic search!
But before we go into more detail on the changes we made to the Elastic® Support Hub and its impact on our customers, it's important that we take a moment to explain the concept of semantic search. At its core, semantic search is a method of search that uses AI to return more relevant search results. Take a look at this quick video explaining the concept:
,As shown in the video, semantic search matches the intent of what the user searches to the content available rather than the words. You can read more about the AI behind it on our blog, Introducing Elastic Learned Sparse Encoder: Elastic’s AI model for semantic search. The rest of this blog tells our story about moving the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blaisure</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Removals, Deprecations, and Major Changes in Kubernetes 1.29]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/kubernetes-1-29-upcoming-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/kubernetes-1-29-upcoming-changes/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Carol Valencia, Kristin Martin, Abigail McCarthy, James Quigley, Hosam Kamel
As with every release, Kubernetes v1.29 will introduce feature deprecations and removals. Our continued ability to produce high-quality releases is a testament to our robust development cycle and healthy community. The following are some of the deprecations and removals coming in the Kubernetes 1.29 release.
The Kubernetes API removal and deprecation process
The Kubernetes project has a well-documented deprecation policy for features. This policy states that stable APIs may only be deprecated when a newer, stable version of that same API is available and that APIs have a minimum lifetime for each stability level. A deprecated API is one that has been marked for removal in a future Kubernetes release; it w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: The Case for Kubernetes Resource Limits: Predictability vs. Efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/the-case-for-kubernetes-resource-limits/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/the-case-for-kubernetes-resource-limits/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Milan Plžík (Grafana Labs)
There’s been quite a lot of posts suggesting that not using Kubernetes resource limits might be a fairly useful thing (for example, For the Love of God, Stop Using CPU Limits on Kubernetes or Kubernetes: Make your services faster by removing CPU limits ). The points made there are totally valid – it doesn’t make much sense to pay for compute power that will not be used due to limits, nor to artificially increase latency. This post strives to argue that limits have their legitimate use as well.
As a Site Reliability Engineer on the Grafana Labs platform team, which maintains and improves internal infrastructure and tooling used by the product teams, I primarily try to make Kubernetes upgrades as smooth as possible. But I also spend a lot of time going down…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Universe&#8217;s key takeaway: Innovate better with AI-powered workflows on a single, unified platform]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-15-universes-key-takeaway-innovate-better-with-ai-powered-workflows-on-a-single-unified-platform/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-15-universes-key-takeaway-innovate-better-with-ai-powered-workflows-on-a-single-unified-platform/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T21:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover new AI-powered features and tools to help developers stay in the flow and organizations innovate at scale.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-15-universes-key-takeaway-innovate-better-with-ai-powered-workflows-on-a-single-unified-platform/">Universe&#8217;s key takeaway: Innovate better with AI-powered workflows on a single, unified platform</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solutions to secret sprawl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/solutions-to-secret-sprawl</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/solutions-to-secret-sprawl"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret sprawl makes companies more vulnerable to data breaches. Learn how to locate and centralize secrets in a single location for greater security and simplified management and compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第241話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755451951724</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755451951724"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agentless configuration drift detection and remediation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/agentless-configuration-drift-detection-and-remediation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/agentless-configuration-drift-detection-and-remediation"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over time, application owners find themselves compelled to continuously refine their applications and the underlying infrastructure to enhance the products they deliver, whether to internal or external customers. These modifications inevitably lead to changes in the configuration of both applications and infrastructure. While some of these changes may be benign, others can unintentionally steer the systems away from their securely configured state, a phenomenon commonly referred to as "configuration drift." Left unaddressed, the extent of this drift can introduce substantial risks to the organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bforrest@redhat.com (Ben Forrester)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Psyberg: Automated end to end catch up]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/260fbe366fe2</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/3-psyberg-automated-end-to-end-catch-up-260fbe366fe2?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T03:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Abhinaya Shetty, Bharath Mummadisetty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving Deeper into Psyberg: Stateless vs Stateful Data Processing]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1d273b3aaefb</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/2-diving-deeper-into-psyberg-stateless-vs-stateful-data-processing-1d273b3aaefb?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T03:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Abhinaya Shetty, Bharath Mummadisetty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1. Streamlining Membership Data Engineering at Netflix with Psyberg]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f68830617dd1</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/1-streamlining-membership-data-engineering-at-netflix-with-psyberg-f68830617dd1?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T03:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Abhinaya Shetty, Bharath Mummadisetty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling multimodal understanding to long videos]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/scaling-multimodal-understanding-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/scaling-multimodal-understanding-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T20:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Isaac Noble, Software Engineer, Google Research, and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientist, Google DeepMind 





When building machine learning models for real-life applications, we need to consider inputs from multiple modalities in order to capture various aspects of the world around us. For example, audio, video, and text all provide varied and complementary information about a visual input. However, building multimodal models is challenging due to the heterogeneity of the modalities. Some of the modalities might be well synchronized in time (e.g., audio, video) but not aligned with text. Furthermore, the large volume of data in video and audio signals is much larger than that in text, so when combining them in multimodal models, video and audio often cannot be fully consumed a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[November patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67953</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/november-patches-for-azure-devops-server-and-team-foundation-server/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T18:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server, as well as Team Foundation Server 2018.3.2.
Note: If you have Azure DevOps Server 2022, you should first update to Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 and then install Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 Patch 5.
The post November patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Speech and Music in Audio Content]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/afd64e6a5bf8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/detecting-speech-and-music-in-audio-content-afd64e6a5bf8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T01:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iroro Orife, Chih-Wei Wu and Yun-Ning (Amy) Hung]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: October 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-13-github-availability-report-october-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-13-github-availability-report-october-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T20:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In October, we experienced two incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-13-github-availability-report-october-2023/">GitHub Availability Report: October 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform integrations with Dell, DNSimple, Fortinet, Palo Alto Networks, Juniper Networks, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-dell-dnsimple-fortinet-palo-alto-networks-juniper</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-dell-dnsimple-fortinet-palo-alto-networks-juniper"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[18 new Terraform integration partners provide more options to automate and secure cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling large-scale health studies for the research community]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/enabling-large-scale-health-studies-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/enabling-large-scale-health-studies-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Chintan Ghate, Software Engineer, and Diana Mincu, Research Engineer, Google Research




As consumer technologies like fitness trackers and mobile phones become more widely used for health-related data collection, so does the opportunity to leverage these data pathways to study and advance our understanding of medical conditions. We have previously touched upon how our work explores the use of this technology within the context of chronic diseases, in particular multiple sclerosis (MS). This effort leverages the FDA MyStudies platform, an open-source platform used to create clinical study apps, that makes it easier for anyone to run their own studies and collect good quality healthcare data, in a trusted and safe way.


 


Today, we describe the setup that we developed by expan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks 2024: 24-hours of virtual knowledge sharing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2024-24-hours-of-virtual-knowledge-sharing</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2024-24-hours-of-virtual-knowledge-sharing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks returns on February 15, 2024. Join our global community for 24 hours of knowledge sharing. The call for proposals is open through November 30, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating the GitHub Awards 2023 recipients 🎉]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-09-celebrating-the-github-awards-2023-recipients/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-09-celebrating-the-github-awards-2023-recipients/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T00:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The GitHub Awards recognizes and celebrates the outstanding contributions and achievements in the developer community, honoring individuals, projects, and organizations for their impactful work, innovation, thought leadership, and creating an outsized positive impact on the community.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-09-celebrating-the-github-awards-2023-recipients/">Celebrating the GitHub Awards 2023 recipients 🎉</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Context in AI Research (CAIR)]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T22:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Katherine Heller, Research Scientist, Google Research, on behalf of the CAIR Team




Artificial intelligence (AI) and related machine learning (ML) technologies are increasingly influential in the world around us, making it imperative that we consider the potential impacts on society and individuals in all aspects of the technology that we create. To these ends, the Context in AI Research (CAIR) team develops novel AI methods in the context of the entire AI pipeline: from data to end-user feedback. The pipeline for building an AI system typically starts with data collection, followed by designing a model to run on that data, deployment of the model in the real world, and lastly, compiling and incorporation of human feedback. Originating in the health space, and now expanded to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming leakage on error-corrected quantum processors]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/overcoming-leakage-on-error-corrected.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/overcoming-leakage-on-error-corrected.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:20:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kevin Miao and Matt McEwen, Research Scientists, Quantum AI Team




The qubits that make up Google quantum devices are delicate and noisy, so it’s necessary to incorporate error correction procedures that identify and account for qubit errors on the way to building a useful quantum computer. Two of the most prevalent error mechanisms are bit-flip errors (where the energy state of the qubit changes) and phase-flip errors (where the phase of the encoded quantum information changes). Quantum error correction (QEC) promises to address and mitigate these two prominent errors. However, there is an assortment of other error mechanisms that challenges the effectiveness of QEC.



While we want qubits to behave as ideal two-level systems with no loss mechanisms, this is not the case in r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Kubernetes ingress with HashiCorp Boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/secure-kubernetes-ingress-with-hashicorp-boundary</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/secure-kubernetes-ingress-with-hashicorp-boundary"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See a potential method for securing application content and components hosted within Kubernetes using Boundary as an alternative to ingress controllers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.17 GA adds locality-aware routing and multi-port support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-17-ga-adds-locality-aware-routing-and-multi-port-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-17-ga-adds-locality-aware-routing-and-multi-port-support"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.17 enhances unified workflow management, reliability, scale, and security for service networking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Step in Personalization: Dynamic Sizzles]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4dc4ce2011ef</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/the-next-step-in-personalization-dynamic-sizzles-4dc4ce2011ef?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T20:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors:Bruce Wobbe, Leticia Kwok]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest Terraform Enterprise features reduce operational burdens, save money]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/latest-terraform-enterprise-features-reduce-operational-burdens-save-money</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/latest-terraform-enterprise-features-reduce-operational-burdens-save-money"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent additions to Terraform Enterprise to enhance manageability and efficiency include flexible deployment options, ephemeral workspaces, and run data retention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Universe 2023: Copilot transforms GitHub into the AI-powered developer platform]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-08-universe-2023-copilot-transforms-github-into-the-ai-powered-developer-platform/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-08-universe-2023-copilot-transforms-github-into-the-ai-powered-developer-platform/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub is announcing general availability of GitHub Copilot Chat and previews of the new GitHub Copilot Enterprise offering, new AI-powered security features, and the GitHub Copilot Partner Program.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-08-universe-2023-copilot-transforms-github-into-the-ai-powered-developer-platform/">Universe 2023: Copilot transforms GitHub into the AI-powered developer platform</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Octoverse: The state of open source and rise of AI in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-08-the-state-of-open-source-and-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-08-the-state-of-open-source-and-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T17:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In this year’s Octoverse report, we study how open source activity around AI, the cloud, and Git are changing the developer experience. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-11-08-the-state-of-open-source-and-ai/">Octoverse: The state of open source and rise of AI in 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternating updates for efficient transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/alternating-updates-for-efficient.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/alternating-updates-for-efficient.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T20:34:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xin Wang, Software Engineer, and Nishanth Dikkala, Research Scientist, Google Research




Contemporary deep learning models have been remarkably successful in many domains, ranging from natural language to computer vision. Transformer neural networks (transformers) are a popular deep learning architecture that today comprise the foundation for most tasks in natural language processing and also are starting to extend to applications in other domains, such as computer vision, robotics, and autonomous driving. Moreover, they form the backbone of all the current state-of-the-art language models.
 

Increasing scale in Transformer networks has led to improved performance and the emergence of behavior not present in smaller networks. However, this increase in scale often comes with pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud now supports dynamic provider credentials for Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-now-supports-dynamic-provider-credentials-for-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-now-supports-dynamic-provider-credentials-for-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud dynamic provider credentials now enable automated authentication for Kubernetes via EKS and GKE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Operator v2 for Kubernetes is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-operator-v2-for-kubernetes-is-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-operator-v2-for-kubernetes-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Operator v2 for Kubernetes is now generally available, enhancing resource management and scaling of Terraform Cloud agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 use cases for automating your infrastructure with Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/5-use-cases-for-automating-your-infrastructure-with-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/5-use-cases-for-automating-your-infrastructure-with-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure automation is an area where systems administrators and  IT operations teams can see some of the biggest benefits from automation, including time savings, reducing tedious manual work, and improving the overall health of their systems. In this blog, I've identified the top 5 infrastructure automation use cases for Ansible Automation Platform that you can deploy in your own environment, and I've incorporated new capabilities like Event-Driven Ansible to make managing your infrastructure even easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>trmcconn@redhat.com (Tricia McConnell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing SIG etcd]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/07/introducing-sig-etcd/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/07/introducing-sig-etcd/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Han Kang (Google), Marek Siarkowicz (Google), Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
Special Interest Groups (SIGs) are a fundamental part of the Kubernetes project, with a substantial share of the community activity happening within them. When the need arises, new SIGs can be created, and that was precisely what happened recently.
SIG etcd is the most recent addition to the list of Kubernetes SIGs. In this article we will get to know it a bit better, understand its origins, scope, and plans.
The critical role of etcd
If we look inside the control plane of a Kubernetes cluster, we will find etcd, a consistent and highly-available key value store used as Kubernetes' backing store for all cluster data -- this description alone highlights the critical role that etcd plays, and the importanc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building In-Video Search]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/936766f0017c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/building-in-video-search-936766f0017c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering video editors with multimodal machine learning to discover perfect moments across the entire Netflix catalog]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault adds 3 new observability integrations and HTTP streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-adds-3-new-observability-integrations-and-http-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-adds-3-new-observability-integrations-and-http-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault gains 3 new observability integrations with AWS Cloudwatch, Elasticsearch, and New Relic, as well as a generic HTTP endpoint for flexible metrics streaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>