<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-10-29T01:58:06.124Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-29T01:58:06.124Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Wins Three PeerSpot 2022 Peer Awards]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=66325</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/camunda-wins-three-peerspot-2022-peer-awards/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T19:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re grateful to our customers and community for selecting Camunda Platform for three 2022 PeerSpot Peer Awards.
The post Camunda Wins Three PeerSpot 2022 Peer Awards appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity spotlight on bug bounty researcher @ahacker1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-28-cybersecurity-spotlight-on-bug-bounty-researcher-ahacker1/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-28-cybersecurity-spotlight-on-bug-bounty-researcher-ahacker1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T18:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we wrap up Cybersecurity Awareness Month, the GitHub bug bounty team is excited to spotlight one of the security researchers who participates in the GitHub Security Bug Bounty Program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · September 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-28-release-radar-sept-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-28-release-radar-sept-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackatoberfest, hackathons, and open source contributions. It&#8217;s been a hectic month with so many community pull requests to all kinds of projects. So many in fact that we had to spend hours going through all the submissions for this blog post. We almost didn&#8217;t get it out before the end of October. Nevertheless, we are [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Named as a Leader in the 2022 Gartner Cloud Infrastructure & Platform Services (CIPS) Magic Quadrant for the 12th Consecutive Year]]></title>
        <id>90f04a9d62650a4739f4d04add932ad4769dc741</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-named-as-a-leader-in-the-2022-gartner-cloud-infrastructure-platform-services-cips-magic-quadrant-for-the-12th-consecutive-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T16:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, and for the twelfth consecutive year, AWS has been named as a Leader in the 2022 Magic Quadrant for Cloud Infrastructure and Platform Services (CIPS). Per Gartner, AWS is the longest-running CIPS Magic Quadrant Leader. AWS was among the first cloud providers when we launched Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) and Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy JavaScript error investigation with source maps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/easy-javascript-error-investigation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/easy-javascript-error-investigation"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying errors in minified JavaScript code is hard! Check out how source maps uploaded to Elastic Observability make error hunting in RUM traces easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy JavaScript error investigation with source maps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/easy-javascript-error-investigation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/easy-javascript-error-investigation"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Hopefully by now you’re taken your first sip of Elastic RUM, or real user monitoring, and see the power of searching through traces and the User Experience metrics to gain insights into how users actually use and experience your application. One issue you may have experienced is the challenge of finding the source of errors for minified JavaScript files. 

Minification is the process of modifying code and markup using techniques such as whitespace and comment removal and variable renaming to reduce the overall filesize. This is intended to improve the user experience by speeding up the page loading time in the browser. Sadly, this can make diagnosing the cause of issues in production applications rather tricky. As you can see from the below stack trace, files are often minified to a sing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handy, cheap and willing]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44078</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/717535794/0/sethsblog~Handy-cheap-and-willing/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The industrial age prized these three attributes. We’ve all been indoctrinated into adopting them through our time in organized schooling, and it’s easy to imagine that the world still wants this. When work is geographically bounded and the assembly line is the dynamic of efficiency, this is precisely what’s sought. Your resume certifies that you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to personalize search experiences using Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-personalize-search-experiences-using-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-personalize-search-experiences-using-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Personalized ecommerce search experiences build loyalty, influence decisions, and increase spend. This post demystifies the steps to get started, so you can prioritize search results according to user profiles and offer relevant recommendations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to personalize search experiences using Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-personalize-search-experiences-using-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-personalize-search-experiences-using-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Creating personalized search experiences can be challenging. In this post, we’ll demystify the steps to get started, so you can prioritize search results according to user profiles, offer relevant recommendations, and accelerate workflows. But before we get to that, let’s address why personalized search matters.
[Download the whitepaper: Ecommerce search personalization on Elastic]
The influence of personalized search
Whether you’re aware of it or not, search powers the personalized digital experiences you encounter everyday. Here are just a few examples:

Search-as-you-type uses your search history to suggest queries.
Knowledge base articles get served up according to your subscription preferences.
Healthcare providers are suggested depending on your medical history and location.
Online…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2022.10: Sakura UI, Improved Integration With Amazon AWS, Out-of-the-Box HTTPS Support, Google OAuth Authentication, and More.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=292021</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2022/10/teamcity-2022-10-sakura-ui-improved-integration-with-amazon-aws-out-of-the-box-https-support-google-oauth-authentication-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T21:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2022.10 comes with the Sakura UI enabled by default, introduces many cloud-related features including the AWS credentials management system and out-of-the-box terminal access to AWS EC2-based build agents, and adds important improvements to VCS integrations. Server administrators will love the new streamlined way to implement HTTPS for on-premises TeamCity installations. Also, a new authentication […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Rassokhin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 212 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65951</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-212-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T19:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In sprint 211 we enabled the “Try the New Boards Hub” banner and popup. This has resulted in a lot of great user feedback, and in turn, a pile of bugs. Our main focus in sprint 212 was fixing these bugs.
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 212 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choose your own GitHub Universe 2022 adventure]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-27-choose-your-own-github-universe-2022-adventure/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-27-choose-your-own-github-universe-2022-adventure/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T18:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now build your agenda on GitHubUniverse.com! Whether you’re just getting started or you’re a seasoned industry professional, there’s a session for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we learned from the Security Lab’s Community Office Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-27-what-we-learned-from-the-security-labs-community-office-hours/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-27-what-we-learned-from-the-security-labs-community-office-hours/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T15:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Security Lab provided office hours for open source projects looking to improve their security posture and reduce the risk of breach. Here’s what we learned and how you can also participate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.3 EAP #5: Package Vulnerability Checker, Vue Import Improvements, and Windows ARM64 Installer]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=291757</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/10/webstorm-2022-3-eap-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T14:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.3 EAP build #5 is now available! To catch up on all the new features, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up-to-date. You can also manually download the EAP builds from our website. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools 2022.10 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=291827</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/10/27/edutools-plugin-2022-10-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T14:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the release of EduTools 2022.10. The new version brings an extended selection of toolchains for Rust users. Additionally, teachers can now review tasks before creating a course archive and modify the names of hints. We also improved the overall quality of the plugin by fixing a variety of bugs. Read […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasiia Pogorelova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diversity, inclusion, and belonging at GitHub in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-27-diversity-inclusion-and-belonging-at-github-in-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-27-diversity-inclusion-and-belonging-at-github-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As GitHub continues to grow, our vision of being the home for all developers continues to materialize, expanding our progress, perspectives, and responsibility to the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar Recording: “How to Build Beautiful Data Apps with Datalore”]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=291802</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2022/10/27/webinar-recording-how-to-build-beautiful-data-apps-with-datalore/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T10:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, 26th October 2022, I gave a webinar about how to build beautiful data apps with Datalore, our collaborative data science and data analytics platform. Here’s the recording for you to watch if you missed the live stream. Description Have you ever struggled to create presentations for your stakeholders with your data science or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With certainty]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43091</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/717361002/0/sethsblog~With-certainty/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T07:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 98% chance is dramatically different than a 100% certainty. Certainty isn’t on the spectrum of chance. It’s a different thing altogether. If the weather report says the chance of precipitation is zero, one should never walk outside into the rain. When you leave yourself a few points of wiggle room, you can build more […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bootiful Podcast: Spring Mad Scientist Andy Clement on SpringOne 2022, AOT, Azure Spring Apps, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/27/bootiful-podcast-spring-mad-scientist-andy-clement-on-springone-2022-aot-azure-spring-apps-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/27/bootiful-podcast-spring-mad-scientist-andy-clement-on-springone-2022-aot-azure-spring-apps-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring mad scientist Andy Clement (@andy_clement) about the new native support in Spring Boot 3, SpringOne 2022, and Azure Spring Apps, among other things]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create a document schema for product variants and SKUs for your ecommerce search experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-create-a-document-schema-for-product-variants-and-skus-for-your-ecommerce-search-experience</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-create-a-document-schema-for-product-variants-and-skus-for-your-ecommerce-search-experience"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Elastic Enterprise Search, explore how to set up, display, and manage product variants and SKUs when modeling data for your ecommerce search experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Stoltzfus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IT leaders are turning data into actionable insights using search technology [Infographic]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/turning-data-into-actionable-insights-using-search-technology</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/turning-data-into-actionable-insights-using-search-technology"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how IT leaders are using search technology to turn unstructured data into insights that improve the customer experience, increase operational resilience, and mitigate security threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Klinger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How moving to the cloud leads to a better customer experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-moving-to-the-cloud-leads-to-a-better-customer-experience</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-moving-to-the-cloud-leads-to-a-better-customer-experience"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to increase loyalty and retention? Move your customer data to the cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create a document schema for product variants and SKUs for your ecommerce search experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-create-a-document-schema-for-product-variants-and-skus-for-your-ecommerce-search-experience</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-create-a-document-schema-for-product-variants-and-skus-for-your-ecommerce-search-experience"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In this article, we'll explore the concepts of variants and SKUs in ecommerce, and how to best handle these when modeling data for your ecommerce search experiences. We're optimizing our models using Elastic Enterprise Search.
Understanding variants and SKUs
In ecommerce, products are not just "products." There can be a hierarchy to products, which generally follows this pattern:
Product → Variant → SKU
Let's explore these terms and how they factor into ecommerce stores and search experiences.
Variants
The term variant in ecommerce refers to a single product that has a number of variations with different attributes. 
For example, a store may sell a Breezy Classic Button Down Shirt, in three different colors: green, red, and blue. Each color variation of the shirt is considered a variant …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Stoltzfus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IT leaders are turning data into actionable insights using search technology [Infographic]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/turning-data-into-actionable-insights-using-search-technology</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/turning-data-into-actionable-insights-using-search-technology"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
More data is being created than ever before. With an expected 181 zettabytes of data created in 2025 (compared to 64.2 zettabytes in 2020), there’s a lot more of it to make use of. Over the next five years, 80% of that data will be unstructured, according to IDC. This data isn’t just applicable to big data projects with hypothetical opportunities, either. It’s the lifeblood for real, concrete, business-critical use cases that are applicable to businesses of all sizes and across all industries.

As an IT leader, you’re tasked with accelerating digital transformation, supercharging scalability, and improving customer experiences (among a plethora of other business priorities). To achieve all of these objectives, you need technologies that can supercharge your decision-making and turn data …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Klinger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How moving to the cloud leads to a better customer experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-moving-to-the-cloud-leads-to-a-better-customer-experience</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-moving-to-the-cloud-leads-to-a-better-customer-experience"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
It was finally time to bite the bullet. 

After years of relying on an aging on-prem version of Elasticsearch, the U.S.-based expense management firm needed to modernize its IT infrastructure. And as it migrated from v 2.3.4 to v 7.9, it seemed like the right time to graduate to the cloud.



It wouldn’t be simple. The firm — a global leader in accounts payable automation — employed a complex installation using 10 custom searches. And the Lucene syntax that drives Elasticsearch had changed a lot in five years.



With the help of Softjourn, a Bay Area-based software development company, they began a year-long migration to AWS.


The key questions: What would happen to the customer experience? Would searches be as fast and accurate? Could the firm maintain the same high level of responsiv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon Neptune Serverless – A Fully Managed Graph Database that Adjusts Capacity for Your Workloads]]></title>
        <id>418c9a7115badfdc4c7fb44c681e774eb70be3b8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-neptune-serverless-a-fully-managed-graph-database-that-adjusts-capacity-for-your-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T22:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Neptune is a fully managed graph database service that makes it easy to build and run applications that work with highly connected datasets. With Neptune, you can use open and popular graph query languages to execute powerful queries that are easy to write and perform well on connected data. You can use Neptune for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.3 EAP: CMake Debugger]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=291573</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/10/clion-2022-3-eap-cmake-debugger/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T17:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new CLion 2022.3 EAP build is available! Download build 223.7255.15 from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package (if you are using Ubuntu). Update via patch if you are using the previous EAP build. DOWNLOAD CLION EAP CMake Debugger CMake is a tricky scripting language that is sometimes hard to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode Bug-Fix Update 2022.2.4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=291719</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/10/appcode-bug-fix-update-2022-2-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T17:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AppCode 2022.2.4 bug-fix update is now available! Build 222.4345.34 is available from our website, from the Toolbox App, or via an update patch from the IDE itself. This build improves AppCode’s compatibility with Xcode 14.1 RC by fixing an exception that was happening on project opening (OC-23248). DOWNLOAD APPCODE If you are interested in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Natural Language Assessment: A New Framework to Promote Education]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/natural-language-assessment-new.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/natural-language-assessment-new.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T17:18:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kedem Snir, Software Engineer, and Gal Elidan, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Research 
Whether it's a professional honing their skills or a child learning to read, coaches and educators play a key role in assessing the learner's answer to a question in a given context and guiding them towards a goal. These interactions have unique characteristics that set them apart from other forms of dialogue, yet are not available when learners practice alone at home. In the field of natural language processing, this type of capability has not received much attention and is technologically challenging. We set out to explore how we can use machine learning to assess answers in a way that facilitates learning. 

In this blog, we introduce an important natural language understanding (NL…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.3 EAP 5: Updated Tips of the Day, Enhanced Bookmarks, Gradle Improvements, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=290845</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/10/intellij-idea-2022-3-eap-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T17:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.3 EAP 5 is out! With this last EAP build before IntelliJ IDEA 2022.3 Beta, we’re introducing some more of the new features and improvements you can expect in the upcoming major release. This build provides a better user experience with tips of the day and bookmarks, includes updates for Gradle, and more. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State of Vault and Kubernetes, and Future Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-state-of-vault-and-kubernetes-and-future-plans</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-state-of-vault-and-kubernetes-and-future-plans"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get an overview of the most common ways to use HashiCorp Vault and Kubernetes together, and get a preview of a new method we're considering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 strategies for consolidating your toolkit and boosting productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-26-3-strategies-for-consolidating-your-toolkit-and-boosting-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-26-3-strategies-for-consolidating-your-toolkit-and-boosting-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T16:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how GitHub Enterprise can help you transform your software engineering organization and practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KotlinConf 2023 Is Going Global. Get on Board With Us!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=291103</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/10/kotlinconf-2023-is-going-global-get-on-board-with-us/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T14:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been three years since we got together for KotlinConf 2019 Global. Since then, we’ve missed it a lot. That’s why we’re more than happy to announce that KotlinConf will be back in 2023, and so will KotlinConf Global! KotlinConf Global During KotlinConf’23 Global, you’ll get a chance to watch the conference keynotes and other […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Krishtal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A technical sneak peek into inbound Connectors alongside Camunda 8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=66235</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/technical-sneak-peek-inbound-connectors-camunda-8-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T14:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how inbound Connectors work in Camunda Platform 8.1, and how you can get started with them today.
The post A technical sneak peek into inbound Connectors alongside Camunda 8.1 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and how GitHub encrypts sensitive database columns using ActiveRecord::Encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-26-why-and-how-github-encrypts-sensitive-database-columns-using-activerecordencryption/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-26-why-and-how-github-encrypts-sensitive-database-columns-using-activerecordencryption/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T14:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may know that GitHub encrypts your source code at rest, but you may not have known that we encrypt sensitive database columns as well. Read about our column encryption strategy and our decision to adopt the Rails column encryption standard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge Automation: A Paradigm Shift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/edge-automation-a-paradigm-shift</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/edge-automation-a-paradigm-shift"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
 
Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform has seen wide-scale adoption in a variety of automation domains, however with edge use cases becoming more mainstream, the thought process around automation must shift from “complete a task immediately” to being able to run automation now and later, and respond to incoming automation requests from devices that are yet unmanaged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chad Ferman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join Our YouTrack Project Management: Essentials for Getting Started Online Webinar]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=youtrack&amp;p=291378</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/youtrack/2022/10/join-our-youtrack-project-management-essentials-for-getting-started-online-webinar/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T12:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sign up for our YouTrack Project Management: Essentials for Getting Started webinar. You’ll get an overview of how to manage your tasks and projects easily, work with your team’s Agile boards, use powerful time tracking, create Gantt charts effectively, and see what’s going on with reports and dashboards. You’ll get to see real examples of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Pishkova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using a PEmicro Multilink Debug Probe With CLion]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=291421</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/10/using-a-pemicro-multilink-debug-probe-with-clion/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T11:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video, we show how to use CLion together with a PEmicro Multilink debug probe in order to develop, build and debug code on an ARM-based microcontroller. For this example, our target device will be a BluePill with a STM32F103 ARM Cortex M3 microcontroller, and we will be implementing “Blinky”, i.e. making an LED […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timur Doumler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started With Space Cloud Dev Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=287898</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2022/10/26/get-started-with-space-dev-environments/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T10:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you thinking about introducing remote development into your team or organization? JetBrains’ remote development workflow allows you to overcome the limits of local machines and slow laptops by keeping your source code safe and secure on a remote server. With the orchestration functionality included in Space, you can create a dev environment, connect it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maarten Balliauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: “New UI for Your IDE: A Glimpse Into the Future”]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=290002</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/10/26/webinar-new-ui-for-your-ide-a-glimpse-into-the-future/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T10:28:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us Monday, October 31, at 5:00 pm UTC (check other timezones) for our live webinar, New UI for Your IDE: A Glimpse Into the Future with JetBrains Developer Advocates. This webinar features GoLand, IntelliJ IDEA, PyCharm, and WebStorm. Please note that the new UI is a work in progress. REGISTER JetBrains released our first […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giving it a second thought]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44070</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/717203466/0/sethsblog~Giving-it-a-second-thought/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T08:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some problems lend themselves to reexamination. A second, third or even fourth thought is productive, because our initial impulses might not reflect our best effort at understanding the nuances of the situation. But many problems simply create more thoughts, without productive output. As we confront something that is unlikely to have a simple or productive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: the road to Spring Boot 3: Spring Framework 6]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/26/spring-tips-the-road-to-spring-boot-3-spring-framework-6</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/26/spring-tips-the-road-to-spring-boot-3-spring-framework-6"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, we begin a journey to Spring Boot 3, due end of November 2022. In this installment, we’ll look - at a very high level - at some of the amazing features in Spring Framework 6, which underpins Spring Boot 3.


Want to learn more about Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3? Join us at SpringOne 2022! use the code S1VM22_Advocate_200 for $200 off the price of admission!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.16.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/26/spring-tools-4-16-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/26/spring-tools-4-16-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.16.1 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
early access builds available for Spring Tools 4 on Eclipse 2022-12 milestones


important note for upgrading from a release prior to 4.16.0 on Eclipse


  
If you are upgrading an existing Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution 4.15.3 or older to 4.16.1, please take a look at the necessary manual steps described for the upgrade to 4.16.0.


fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: Spring XML Config support does not show symbols with scope “File” (#860)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: [open-rewrite] exception when executing quick fix for project (#853)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: [refactoring] quick fix to convert autowired field to constructor param shows up even if the constructor param already exists (#815)

  
(VSCode) fixed: Vscode Spring Boot Tools 1.39.0 prevents Java project from Running/Debugging (#847)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Web Tools Platform (WTP) validation is activated by default (#859)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: ask user to save dirty editors before deploying on docker (#803)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-10-26-4161-release-incl-language-servers-version-1400

Spring Tools 4.17.0 is scheduled to be released in early December 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leading financial institutions hedge risk by focusing on these 5 critical SIEM requirements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/leading-financial-institutions-hedge-risk-by-focusing-on-these-5-critical-siem-requirements</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/leading-financial-institutions-hedge-risk-by-focusing-on-these-5-critical-siem-requirements"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital transformation is expanding the attack surface in financial services. Learn about several essential features that financial security leaders should look out for in their next SIEM investment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leading financial institutions hedge risk by focusing on these 5 critical SIEM requirements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/leading-financial-institutions-hedge-risk-by-focusing-on-these-5-critical-siem-requirements</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/leading-financial-institutions-hedge-risk-by-focusing-on-these-5-critical-siem-requirements"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Digital transformation is expanding the attack surface in financial services. Throughout the pandemic, the accelerated adoption of digital banking, payments, and insurance channels has enabled providers to offer greater levels of service, new financial products, and enhanced journeys to their customers.



However, with growing amounts of data and increasingly complex IT ecosystems, bad actors are finding more creative ways of wreaking havoc. In fact, U.S. Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell warned last year that cyberattacks are the number-one threat to the global financial system.



Cyberattacks in financial services can be exceptionally devastating. Even small problems can lead to substantial money lost, customers exposed, and heavy regulatory fines. Some of the recent drivers beh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cool S]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2690/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2690/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/cool_s.png" title="Although I hear they were caught cheating off of Rosalind, who sat at a desk in front of them." alt="Although I hear they were caught cheating off of Rosalind, who sat at a desk in front of them." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022 RC2 now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65931</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-rc2-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T20:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Azure DevOps Server 2022 RC2. This is our last planned prerelease before our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2022. You can upgrade from Azure DevOps Server 2022 RC1 or previous versions of TFS and Azure DevOps. You can find the full details in our release notes.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022 RC2 now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Images V7 — Now Featuring Point Labels]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/open-images-v7-now-featuring-point.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/open-images-v7-now-featuring-point.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T19:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rodrigo Benenson, Research Scientist, Google Research 
Open Images is a computer vision dataset covering ~9 million images with labels spanning thousands of object categories. Researchers around the world use Open Images to train and evaluate computer vision models. Since the initial release of Open Images in 2016, which included image-level labels covering 6k categories, we have provided multiple updates to enrich annotations and expand the potential use cases of the dataset. Through several releases, we have added image-level labels for over 20k categories on all images and bounding box annotations, visual relations, instance segmentations, and localized narratives (synchronized voice, mouse trace, and text caption) on a subset of 1.9M images.  
  
Today, we are happy to announ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not the last mile]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44072</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/717133428/0/sethsblog~Its-not-the-last-mile/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T18:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the first mile. Big tech likes to talk about the last mile problem–how to get a wire, a system or a concept from where the nodes are easy to plant to where people actually are. As if the hard part is what they’ve already done, and now it’s just the last little bit… None […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration 6.0.0-RC1 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/25/spring-integration-6-0-0-rc1-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/25/spring-integration-6-0-0-rc1-available"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T13:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring community,



I was so eager to find and fix bugs in the latest Spring Integration release, that missed to announce a 6.0 RC1 last week.
But I believe it is still worth to mention it even after Spring Boot 3.0.0-RC1 announcement since there is a number of notable changes and improvements.



So, please, welcome Spring Integration 6.0 first Release Candidate.
It can be obtained from Spring Milestone repository:




dependencyManagement {
    imports {
        mavenBom 'org.springframework.integration:spring-integration-bom:6.0.0-RC1'
    }
}




Here you can find important changes after the previously announced Spring Integration 6.0.0-M5:





spring-integration-amqp has added support for RabbitMQ Streams;



spring-integration-sftp has been migrated from an old unsupported jsch library to more modern Apache MINA;



spring-integration-gemfire was removed according to dropped support for Apache Geode in Spring Data;



spring-integration-scripting has added a GraalVM Polyglot support for JavaScript invocations;



The Apache Groovy DSL for Spring Integration extension project has been migrated to the spring-integration-groovy module code base;



The Spring Integration for Apache Cassandra extension project has been migrated as a spring-integration-cassandra module;



The Kotlin Coroutines support has been added to the @ServiceActivator POJO functions, also messaging gateway methods can now be as suspended functions;



The AOP ChannelSecurityInterceptor in the spring-integration-security module has been deprecated in favor of AuthorizationChannelInterceptor.





Also, see a Migration Guide for breaking changes in the framework and its modules.



It would be great if you give it a chance and come back to us with reports, so it may make it into GA next month.



See you in person this December at SpringOne!



Cheers, 

Artem



Project Page | GitHub Issues | Contributing | Help | Chat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Batch for Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service]]></title>
        <id>ca16621081273a61c85f2eec5a092eca6cc9cf7e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-batch-for-amazon-elastic-kubernetes-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T13:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I’m pleased to announce AWS Batch for Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). AWS Batch for Amazon EKS is ideal for customers who no longer want to shoulder the burden of configuring, fine-tuning, and managing Kubernetes clusters and pods to use with their batch processing workflows. Furthermore, there is no charge for this service. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why we&#8217;re excited about the Sigstore general availability]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-25-why-were-excited-about-the-sigstore-general-availability/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-25-why-were-excited-about-the-sigstore-general-availability/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T13:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sigstore GA means you can protect your software supply chain today with GitHub Actions, and will power new npm security capabilities in the near future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect might be the enemy of good in group dynamics and choice making]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=31602</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/717084466/0/sethsblog~Perfect-might-be-the-enemy-of-good-in-group-dynamics-and-choice-making/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T08:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When one person needs to fix a wall, adjust a cabinet or choose what to serve for dinner, they can optimize their choice. Make appropriate trade-offs. Take responsibility for the path chosen. But when a group of people are asked to do the same thing, it’s easy to err on the side of the pursuit […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 SIEM challenges in multi-cloud environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-3-siem-challenges-in-multi-cloud-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-3-siem-challenges-in-multi-cloud-environments"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be effective, a SIEM needs to provide compatibility with your current environment — including your cloud infrastructure and applications — as well as support future expansion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Buckler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 SIEM challenges in multi-cloud environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-3-siem-challenges-in-multi-cloud-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-3-siem-challenges-in-multi-cloud-environments"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,

What is a SIEM, and why do you need one for cloud?
Security information and event management (SIEM) is designed to combine the best of security information management (SIM) and security event management (SEM) to provide a unified platform for intrusion detection and response. While SIEMs traditionally don’t include prevention capabilities, users are increasingly expecting fulfillment of this use case from a SIEM as part of tool consolidation. We need to move away from reactive security toward proactive security, working to prevent intrusions before they happen (or get worse). A quality SIEM must equip practitioners to spot cyber-threats quickly, and investigate and remediate threats before they can cause damage.
The shift to the cloud exacerbates the visibility challenges of perimeter-b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Buckler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Guide to: Finding a company you can grow with]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-the-elastic-guide-to-finding-a-company-you-can-grow-with</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-the-elastic-guide-to-finding-a-company-you-can-grow-with"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where do you want to be in 5 years? Here's how to find a company that will help you take the next steps in your career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do telecom security teams need from a SIEM?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-do-telecom-security-teams-need-from-a-siem</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-do-telecom-security-teams-need-from-a-siem"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past couple of years, two things stood out for the telecom industry: 5G and cloud adoption. Put together, there is a need for a completely revamped approach to security. And the journey begins with a “modern” SIEM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customer trust relies on building IT systems that scale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/customer-trust-relies-on-building-it-systems-that-scale</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/customer-trust-relies-on-building-it-systems-that-scale"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solving for scale is the key to ensuring your IT organization delivers on its promise to secure and protect data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Weston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Guide to: Finding a company you can grow with]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-the-elastic-guide-to-finding-a-company-you-can-grow-with</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-the-elastic-guide-to-finding-a-company-you-can-grow-with"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Jordyn Short, Services Architect at Elastic, spent seven years in the U.S. Army. She learned many valuable lessons, among them, the path to success isn’t always easy. After leaving the military, she took these learnings to create a fulfilling career. 
As a civilian, the path to success isn’t as defined as it might be in military training, so Jordyn had to learn how to create and pursue the career she wanted. She went from the Army to government contracting work, which she says was a good transition into finding out who she was and what she wanted.
Jordyn spent two years as a Senior Technical Consultant at Elastic before being recently promoted to Services Architect, a common career trajectory. To get promoted, she had to complete her Elastic Engineering certification, show technical comp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do telecom security teams need from a SIEM?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-do-telecom-security-teams-need-from-a-siem</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-do-telecom-security-teams-need-from-a-siem"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Just within the last 30 days, the two largest telecom operators in Australia1 were hit by a data breach impacting millions of customers and compromising sensitive personal information like home addresses, drivers’ licenses, and passport numbers. The situation is not very different in the Americas, where another leading telecom provider2 cited a 13% jump in ransomware attacks in the past year. And in Europe, the latest cybersecurity report from European Union Agency for Cybersecurity (ENISA)3 that lists the major telecom security incidents from 2021 stated that 5,000+ user hours were lost — compared to just over 800 hours in 2020.



So what has changed in the past couple of years? For the telecom industry in particular, two things stand out: 5G and cloud adoption. These technologies prov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customer trust relies on building IT systems that scale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/customer-trust-relies-on-building-it-systems-that-scale</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/customer-trust-relies-on-building-it-systems-that-scale"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Adopting hybrid or public clouds remains IT’s go-to means of achieving scale. While this transformation has improved price performance and advanced tech-driven business capabilities, including faster and deeper data insights, it hasn’t always engendered higher customer trust. 

That’s due in no small part to widely-publicized hacks that have exposed personally identifiable information (PII) and also in part to higher customer dependence upon mobile commerce, wonky inventory systems, and sometimes unreliable online ordering. By some measures, performing at scale is all about improving transactions per second.

According to a 2022 PwC study, “87% of business executives think consumers have a high level of trust in their business. But only 30% of consumers say they do.” One of the biggest t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Weston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – October 24, 2022]]></title>
        <id>b39e23f90151c8cfdcfc226399885b21d1d1045c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-october-24-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T19:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, we announced plans to launch the AWS Asia Pacific (Bangkok) Region, which will become our third AWS Region in Southeast Asia. This Region will have three Availability Zones and will give AWS customers in Thailand the ability to run workloads and store data that must remain in-country. In the Works – AWS Region […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X.509 Certificate Management with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/certificate-management-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/certificate-management-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll look at practical public key certificate management in HashiCorp Vault using dynamic secrets rotation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of Fest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/best-of-fest-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/best-of-fest-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AnsibleFest 2022, the power of automation was on full display. Through sessions, workshops, labs and more, we explored how to transform enterprise and industry through automation. There were a lot of exciting announcements made on both days, and in case you missed it, we are going to dive into what is new!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many good days?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43087</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/716965058/0/sethsblog~How-many-good-days/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decisions and crises and moments of significant effort and risk can be stressful. But the challenge of a stressful day is rarely directly related to today, it’s about tomorrow or years from now. Which means that pushing your way through some critical choices now will probably pay off in far more good days later. How […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - October 25th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/24/this-week-in-spring-october-25th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/24/this-week-in-spring-october-25th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! When last we spoke, I was in Las Vegas, NV, for the JavaOne show. It was amazing! I’m in sunny Singapore, then off to Malaysia and Thailand. It’s the first time I’ve been to any of these places since 2019! How good it is to be back! I’ve so missed it.

The Spring team is busy preparing for both Spring Boot 3 (and the Spring Framework 6 release that underpins it) and SpringOne 2022. Have you booked your ticket for SpringOne 2022 yet? It’s going to be held in sunny San Francisco, and - of course - it’ll be the absolute best place to learn about Spring Framework 6, Spring Boot 3, GraalVM, the new Ahead-of-time compilation engine in Spring Boot 3, and more. Also, it’s a rare chance to hang out with the Spring team proper.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fermat's First Theorem]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2689/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2689/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/fermats_first_theorem.png" title="Mathematicians quickly determined that it spells ANT BNECN, an unusual theoretical dish which was not successfully cooked until Andrew Wiles made it for breakfast in the 1990s." alt="Mathematicians quickly determined that it spells ANT BNECN, an unusual theoretical dish which was not successfully cooked until Andrew Wiles made it for breakfast in the 1990s." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product idea: Talking discs]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44062</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/716846974/0/sethsblog~Product-idea-Talking-discs/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many offices and public settings are putting up clear plexiglas barriers to insulate staff from the spread of disease. While we can easily see through these partitions, it ends up creating a lot of yelling. What if there were a disc, about the size of a hockey puck and the thickness of a few coasters… […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ECCV 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/google-at-eccv-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/google-at-eccv-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T03:30:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shaina Mehta, Program Manager, Google  
Google is proud to be a Platinum Sponsor of the European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV 2022), a premier forum for the dissemination of research in computer vision and machine learning (ML). This year, ECCV 2022 will be held as a hybrid event, in person in Tel Aviv, Israel with virtual attendance as an option. Google has a strong presence at this year’s conference with over 60 accepted publications and active involvement in a number of workshops and tutorials. We look forward to sharing some of our extensive research and expanding our partnership with the broader ML research community. 
  
Registered for ECCV 2022? We hope you’ll visit our on-site or virtual booths to learn more about the research we’re presenting at ECCV 2022, includi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resale value]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43029</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/716687966/0/sethsblog~Resale-value/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T07:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hopeful to believe that the NFT, baseball card or even car that we next purchase is going to go up in value. It probably won’t. The secret is to only acquire things where the resale value doesn’t matter to your overall satisfaction. That’s one reason there’s a huge difference between investing in stocks and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a game this November with Game Off 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-21-build-a-game-this-november-with-game-off-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-21-build-a-game-this-november-with-game-off-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T17:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Save the date! Game Off returns on November 1 for its 10th year! 🎉]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Global 2022: From Zero Trust to No Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-2022-from-zero-trust-to-no-code</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-2022-from-zero-trust-to-no-code"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the highlights from HashiConf Global 2022 and watch the 40+ keynote and session recordings now live on YouTube.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Merge 2022 &#8211; that&#8217;s a wrap! 🎬]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-21-git-merge-2022-mission-report/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-21-git-merge-2022-mission-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T16:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git Merge 2022 just wrapped up bringing the community together for 16 talks, three workshops, one Git Contributor Summit, and lots of great conversations over two days. Read on for more info, photos from the event, and all of the session recordings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Spring Modulith]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/21/introducing-spring-modulith</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/21/introducing-spring-modulith"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing software systems, architects and developers have plenty of architectural options to choose from. Microservice-based systems have become ubiquitous in the last couple of years. However, the idea of monolithic, modular systems has also regained popularity recently.
Independent of the architectural style ultimately selected, the individual applications comprising the overall system need their structure to be evolvable and able to follow changes in business requirements.



Traditionally, application frameworks have provided structural guidance by providing abstractions aligned with technical concepts, such as Spring Framework’s stereotype annotations (@Controller, @Service, @Repository, and so on).
However, shifting the focus to align code structure with the domain has pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dawani’s Law]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44056</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/716500452/0/sethsblog~Dawanis-Law/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The number of people who say that Moore’s Law can’t continue doubles every 24 months.” Even if you don’t understand this at first, it’s worth a second to understand it. Moore’s Law, now nearly sixty years old, describes a simple engineering fact that has changed the life of everyone on the planet. The number of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-RC1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/spring-boot-3-0-0-rc1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/spring-boot-3-0-0-rc1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-RC1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 135 enhancements, documentation improvements, dependency upgrades, and bug fixes. 

This is our first release candidate for Spring Boot 3.0, which we expect to release November 24, 2022. We are not expecting any more features to be added at this point, and we will only be making API changes if we find issues.

This release is the culmination of 11 months of work and is the first release to fully realize the themes that we set out to deliver in Spring Boot 3.0. Most notably, this release builds on the multi-year R&D effort that started with the experimental Spring Native project to pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble Universes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2688/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2688/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/bubble_universes.png" title="The theory finally unifies cosmic inflation and regular inflation." alt="The theory finally unifies cosmic inflation and regular inflation." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PI-ARS: Accelerating Evolution-Learned Visual-Locomotion with Predictive Information Representations]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/pi-ars-accelerating-evolution-learned.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/pi-ars-accelerating-evolution-learned.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T20:39:00.015Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Wenhao Yu, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google, and Kuang-Huei Lee, Research Engineer, Google Research, Brain team 
Evolution strategy (ES) is a family of optimization techniques inspired by the ideas of natural selection: a population of candidate solutions are usually evolved over generations to better adapt to an optimization objective. ES has been applied to a variety of challenging decision making problems, such as legged locomotion, quadcopter control, and even power system control.  

Compared to gradient-based reinforcement learning (RL) methods like proximal policy optimization (PPO) and soft actor-critic (SAC), ES has several advantages. First, ES directly explores in the space of controller parameters, while gradient-based methods often explore within a limited acti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Roadmap update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65894</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-roadmap-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T17:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week we made significant updates to our product roadmap. We published the latest features for 2022, updated the list of features for 2023, and included an initiatives section that provides details about the product strategy and long-term investments.
In addition to including a new list of key features and initiatives,
The post Azure DevOps Roadmap update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MUSIQ: Assessing Image Aesthetic and Technical Quality with Multi-scale Transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/musiq-assessing-image-aesthetic-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/musiq-assessing-image-aesthetic-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T16:58:00.010Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Junjie Ke, Senior Software Engineer, and Feng Yang, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research
Understanding the aesthetic and technical quality of images is important for providing a better user visual experience. Image quality assessment (IQA) uses models to build a bridge between an image and a user's subjective perception of its quality. In the deep learning era, many IQA approaches, such as NIMA, have achieved success by leveraging the power of convolutional neural networks (CNNs). However, CNN-based IQA models are often constrained by the fixed-size input requirement in batch training, i.e., the input images need to be resized or cropped to a fixed size shape. This preprocessing is problematic for IQA because images can have very different aspect ratios and resolutions…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-Plan/Pre-Apply Run Tasks Now Available in Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pre-plan-apply-run-tasks-now-available-in-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pre-plan-apply-run-tasks-now-available-in-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance your Terraform Cloud workflow by adding run tasks before the plan and/or apply stages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Sip of Elastic RUM (Real User Monitoring)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/performing-real-user-monitoring-rum-with-elastic-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/performing-real-user-monitoring-rum-with-elastic-apm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry if I lured you into the mood of having a sip of a wonderful cocktail made with rum and you realized that the RUM I’m talking about is not the rum you are craving. But, be assured that Elastic RUM is equally wonderful! Let’s take a sip! I do want to warn you that it will take a bit of time to go through the amount of detail I will cover in this blog.
What is RUM?
Elastic real user monitoring, or RUM, captures user interactions with the web browser and provides a detailed view of the “real user experience” of your web applications from a performance perspective. Elastic’s RUM Agent is a JavaScript Agent, which means it supports any JavaScript-based application. RUM can provide valuable insight into your applications. Some of the common benefits of RUM include:

RUM performance data can…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Quan,Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Sip of Elastic RUM (Real User Monitoring)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/performing-real-user-monitoring-rum-with-elastic-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/performing-real-user-monitoring-rum-with-elastic-apm"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic APM real user monitoring (RUM) captures user interactions with browsers. We will instrument an application with a React frontend and a Spring Boot backend using the RUM and Java agents. Together, they provide a holistic view of application performance from an end user perspective through distributed tracing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Quan,Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft's Asir Selvasingh on Azure Spring Apps, Java at Microsoft, application security, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-asir-selvasingh-on-azure-spring-apps-java-at-microsoft-application-security-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-asir-selvasingh-on-azure-spring-apps-java-at-microsoft-application-security-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxma) talks to his friend, Microsoft’s Asir Selvasingh (@asirselvasingh), about Azure Spring Apps, Java at Microsoft, Spring, application security, and more. Want to learn more? Join us at SpringOne (6-8 December 2022)!


Want to meet amazing people like Asir? Join us at SpringOne 2022! Register now and get $200 off with this discount code S1VM22_Advocate_200.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/spring-boot-2-7-5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/spring-boot-2-7-5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.5 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 31 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.0-RC2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/spring-framework-6-0-0-rc2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/spring-framework-6-0-0-rc2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.0-RC2 is available now.

Spring Framework 6.0.0-RC2 includes 28 fixes and improvements. Stay tuned for the announcement of Spring Boot 3.0.0-RC1 later today!

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-31684: Reactor Netty HTTP Server may log request headers]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/cve-2022-31684-reactor-netty-http-server-may-log-request-headers</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/cve-2022-31684-reactor-netty-http-server-may-log-request-headers"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Reactor Netty 1.0.24 release on October 11 included fix for CVE-2022-31684 affecting Reactor Netty HTTP Server.
Users are encouraged to update as soon as possible.

Reactor Netty is used internally in many frameworks including Spring WebFlux and its WebClient.
If you have a Spring Boot application, you can upgrade to Reactor BOM 2020.0.24.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.13 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/spring-boot-2-6-13-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/spring-boot-2-6-13-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T10:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.13 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 27 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The obligation of the honest skeptic]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43037</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/716283416/0/sethsblog~The-obligation-of-the-honest-skeptic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Objections are helpful. We object by holding back action or support because we question one or more pieces of data. But the other half of this is the obligation: if the data ends up meeting the standard of proof we set for it, we have to change our minds and spend as much energy supporting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0 RC1 is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/spring-batch-5-0-rc1-is-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/20/spring-batch-5-0-rc1-is-out"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is finally here! The first release candidate of Spring Batch 5 is now available from our milestone repository. In this release, we worked on the following items:


  
Execution context Meta-data improvement

  
GemFire support removal


This blog post walks through these two changes in details. For the complete list of changes, please check the release notes.
Execution context Meta-data improvement

In addition to what Spring Batch already persists in the execution context with regard to runtime information (like the step type, the restart flag, etc), this release adds an important detail in the execution context which is the Spring Batch version that was used to serialize the context.

While this seems a detail, it has a huge added value when debugging upgrade issues with regard to execution context serialization and deserialization.
GemFire support removal

Based on the decision to discontinue the support of Spring Data for Apache Geode, the support for Apache Geode in Spring Batch was removed.

The code was moved to the spring-batch-extensions repository as a community-driven effort.
What’s next?

We are planning to roll out a second release candidate early November and release 5.0.0 GA by the end of November, in time for Spring Boot 3.0.0. We would appreciate your help to try this release candidate out and share your feedback with us on Github, Twitter and StackOverflow. You can find a migration guide here.

I would like to thank all contributors who had a role in this first release candidate!


Spring Batch Home|Source on Github|Reference documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Server Side Apply Is Great And You Should Be Using It]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/20/advanced-server-side-apply/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/20/advanced-server-side-apply/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Daniel Smith (Google)
Server-side apply (SSA) has now
been GA for a few releases, and I
have found myself in a number of conversations, recommending that people / teams
in various situations use it. So I’d like to write down some of those reasons.
Obvious (and not-so-obvious) benefits of SSA
A list of improvements / niceties you get from switching from various things to
Server-side apply!
Versus client-side-apply (that is, plain kubectl apply):

The system gives you conflicts when you accidentally fight with another
actor over the value of a field!
When combined with --dry-run, there’s no chance of accidentally running a
client-side dry run instead of a server side dry run.
Versus hand-rolling patches:

The SSA patch format is extremely natural to write, with no weird syntax.
It’s …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Wins Datadog’s Integration Developer Partner of the Year Award]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-datadog-s-integration-developer-partner-of-the-year-award</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-datadog-s-integration-developer-partner-of-the-year-award"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp has won the 2022 Datadog Partner Network (DPN) Integration Developer Partner of the Year Award.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Modern ImageNet Classifiers Accurately Predict Perceptual Similarity?]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/do-modern-imagenet-classifiers.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/do-modern-imagenet-classifiers.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T17:57:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Manoj Kumar, Research Engineer, and Ekin Dogus Cubuk, Research Scientist, Google Research 
The task of determining the similarity between images is an open problem in computer vision and is crucial for evaluating the realism of machine-generated images. Though there are a number of straightforward methods of estimating image similarity (e.g., low-level metrics that measure pixel differences, such as FSIM and SSIM), in many cases, the measured similarity differences do not match the differences perceived by a person. However, more recent work has demonstrated that intermediate representations of neural network classifiers, such as AlexNet, VGG and SqueezeNet trained on ImageNet, exhibit perceptual similarity as an emergent property. That is, Euclidean distances between encoded rep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Competency Program Validates Systems Integrators’ HashiCorp Expertise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-competency-program-validates-systems-integrators-hashicorp-expertise</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-competency-program-validates-systems-integrators-hashicorp-expertise"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Technical Competency Program for Systems Integrators allows partners to display earned competency badges on both their own website and HashiCorp.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第217話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316112896950049151</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316112896950049151"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Event-Driven Ansible developer preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-event-driven-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-event-driven-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T04:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today at AnsibleFest 2022, Red Hat announced an exciting new developer preview for Event-Driven Ansible. Most customers are on a journey toward full end-to-end automation and there are many paths you take along this journey.  Event-Driven Ansible is a new way to enhance and expand automation. It improves IT speed and agility, while enabling consistency and resilience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Pisciotta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Event-Driven Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-event-driven-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-event-driven-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T04:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As one technology advances, it expands the possibilities for other technologies and offers the solutions of tomorrow for the challenges we face today. AnsibleFest 2022 brings us new advances in Ansible automation that are as bright as they are innovative. I am talking about the Event-Driven Ansible developer preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It takes a community: how partners play a key role in event driven automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-for-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-for-partners"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-driven automation is increasingly being adopted because of the strong benefits it delivers in managing huge amounts of complexity across multi-clouds, a multi-device remote workforce, and growing edge implementations. In a digital world, maintaining resilience and reliability is essential and event driven automation helps teams meet these needs while working around resource and skills gaps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Bock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Division Notation]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2687/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2687/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/division_notation.png" title="Science tip: Scientists hardly ever use the two-dot division sign, and when they do it often doesn't even mean division, but they still get REALLY mad when you repurpose it to write stuff like SALE! ALL SHOES 30÷ OFF!" alt="Science tip: Scientists hardly ever use the two-dot division sign, and when they do it often doesn't even mean division, but they still get REALLY mad when you repurpose it to write stuff like SALE! ALL SHOES 30÷ OFF!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestrating Data/ML Workflows at Scale With Netflix Maestro]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/aaa2b41b800c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/orchestrating-data-ml-workflows-at-scale-with-netflix-maestro-aaa2b41b800c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T20:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - October 18th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/18/this-week-in-spring-october-18th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/18/this-week-in-spring-october-18th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How’re you doin’? I’m doin’ alright! Last week I was in Antwerp, Belgium, for the amazing Devoxx BE show. I did a presentation with my friend and hero James Ward on Spring and Kotlin (that was voted third most-liked talk at a show with more than 250 speakers!) That was a personal career highlight for me - it’s not often you get to win and have fun in life. And, as if that wasn’t awesome enough, this week I am in Las Vegas, NV, for JavaOne! Fingers crossed, this week will go smoothly, too! Both Devoxx and JavaOne are the first such shows since at least before the pandemic. It’s been a very long time in coming and I’m elated, overjoyed, to be able to be here.

And, of course, I’m super excited about SpringOne 2022! Also, the first in-person show of its kind since before the pandemic! It’s going to be amazing. Have you registered? If not, you might consider using this registration code - S1VM22_Advocate_200.

And this week’s busy roundup reflects the usual flurry of activity on the Spring team as we ready releases for our end-of-November timelines for Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3, which means we’ve got a ton of stuff to get into this week, so let’s!


  
Spring Framework 6.0 goes RC1

  
Observability with Spring Boot 3

  
A Bootiful Podcast: Google mad scientist Josh Suereth on Observability with OpenTelemetry, building better build tools, and so much more 

  
Spring Batch 5.0.0-M8 is out!

  
Learn more about Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3 in these two great talks from Devoxx 2022

  
Spring at JavaOne 2022

  
Spring Data 2022.0.0-RC1, 2021.2.5, and 2021.1.8 available

  
Spring Security 6.0.0-RC1 and 5.8.0-RC1 are released

  
Spring Security 5.7.4 and 5.6.8 available now

  
Spring for GraphQL 1.1.0-RC1 released

  
Spring Web Services 4.0.0-RC1 is out!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Web Services 4.0.0-RC1 is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/18/spring-web-services-4-0-0-rc1-is-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/18/spring-web-services-4-0-0-rc1-is-out"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings Spring community,



The Spring Web Services team has released 4.0.0-RC1. This is the last planned release candidate that supports Spring Boot 3.0. The final GA release is coming next month in anticipation of Spring Boot 3.0 going GA.



4.0.x is the generation of Spring Web Services that works with Jakarta EE 9, the version where the enterprise specs (JAX-WS, etc.) migrate from javax. to jakarta.. See Juergen Holler’s blog post for more details about that.



Being based upon Spring Framework 6.0, this is also the generation of Spring Web Services that is rebased on top of Java 17 (LTS). So check it out!



For more details, read the following release notes for each version:



Release Notes - Spring Web Services - Version 4.0.0-RC1



#1284 - Upgrade to Spring…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Table Tennis: A Research Platform for Agile Robotics]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/table-tennis-research-platform-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/table-tennis-research-platform-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T17:50:00.024Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Avi Singh, Research Scientist, and Laura Graesser, Research Engineer, Robotics at Google
Robot learning has been applied to a wide range of challenging real world tasks, including dexterous manipulation, legged locomotion, and grasping. It is less common to see robot learning applied to dynamic, high-acceleration tasks requiring tight-loop human-robot interactions, such as table tennis. There are two complementary properties of the table tennis task that make it interesting for robotic learning research. First, the task requires both speed and precision, which puts significant demands on a learning algorithm. At the same time, the problem is highly-structured (with a fixed, predictable environment) and naturally multi-agent (the robot can play with humans or another robot), makin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65881</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/october-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T16:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Resolve issue with newly added AD identities not appearing in security dialog identity pickers.
The post October patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.1.0-RC1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/18/spring-for-graphql-1-1-0-rc1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/18/spring-for-graphql-1-1-0-rc1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pleased to announce that the first release candidate of Spring for GraphQL 1.1.0 is now available from our Milestone repository. This version will be shipped with Spring Boot 3.0.0-RC1 due for release later this week.

This release candidate is the last stop for shipping new features; from that point, we’ll be focusing on bug fixes and documentation improvements. Our goal is to stabilize the current branch for our GA release scheduled next month.

With RC1, we’re shipping our new Observability support in Spring for GraphQL. Based on the new Micrometer Observation work, this infrastructure replaces the former GraphQL Metrics support in Spring Boot 2.7. GraphQL is a good use case for Observability in general, as the GraphQL engine can distribute the data fetching operations over caches, databases, REST APIs and more. It’s important not only to keep track of performance metrics for your GraphQL API, but also to be able to explore traces and investigate production issues.

We didn’t have time to tackle features like Pagination/Relay or AOT/Native support, but we’re listening to the community. We’re working on our roadmap for the next feature version, so now is the time to vote on existing issues to show your interest!

The annual Spring survey is here, it’s a great way to let us know what you think!
How can you help?

If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-graphql tag.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cockroach Labs, ForgeRock & Palo Alto Networks Highlight New Vault Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cockroach-labs-forgerock-paloalto-networks-highlight-new-vault-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cockroach-labs-forgerock-paloalto-networks-highlight-new-vault-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Vault ecosystem saw multiple integrations from partners Cockroach Labs, ForgeRock, and PaloAlto Networks as part of the 19 integrations completed this past quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Camunda Platform 7 with Prometheus]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63590</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/monitoring-camunda-platform-7-with-prometheus/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring is an essential facet of running applications in a production system. Through this process, organizations collect and analyze data, and determine if a program is performing as expected within set boundaries. When combined with alerting, monitoring allows for detecting unexpected system behavior to mitigate exceptional situations as fast as possible. Furthermore, tracking the performance of a system enables organizations to improve those aspects that have the biggest impact with higher priority. One essential aspect of monitoring is the list of key metrics you want to observe. There are different categories of statistics that can be of interest here. To observe the defined metrics, there are plenty of application monitoring tools on the market today. They differ in many aspects...
The post Monitoring Camunda Platform 7 with Prometheus appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Metzke-Bernstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.4 and 5.6.8 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/18/spring-security-5-7-4-and-5-6-8-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/18/spring-security-5-7-4-and-5-6-8-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T12:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.7.4 and 5.6.8 are available now. In both cases the releases are largely composed of dependency upgrades and minor fixes.



To learn more, please visit the 5.7.4 and
 5.6.8 release summaries.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.0.0-RC1 and 5.8.0-RC1 are released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/18/spring-security-6-0-0-rc1-and-5-8-0-rc1-are-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/18/spring-security-6-0-0-rc1-and-5-8-0-rc1-are-released"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T12:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 6.0.0-RC1 and 5.8.0-RC1 are available now.



See the 6.0.0-RC1 and 5.8.0-RC1 release notes for more details.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – October 17, 2022]]></title>
        <id>f3d6027b89e3960df03f4dc7b386bf38d63c911d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-october-17-2020/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T17:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Monday means it’s time for another Week in Review post, so, without further ado, let’s dive right in! Last Week’s Launches Here’s some launch announcements from last week you may […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2022.0.0-RC1, 2021.2.5, and 2021.1.8 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/17/spring-data-2022-0-0-rc1-2021-2-5-and-2021-1-8-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/17/spring-data-2022-0-0-rc1-2021-2-5-and-2021-1-8-available"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T08:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring community,

On behalf of the Spring Data team and everyone who contributed, it is my pleasure to announce that Spring Data 2022.0.0 has entered its release candidate phase by releasing RC1 today. It is available from the milestone repository. This release ships with several tickets fixed. Along with the release candidate, we shipped 2021.2.5 and 2021.1.8 service releases, to be picked up by corresponding Spring Boot releases.

The release candidate ships with a revised module structure, specifically Spring Data for Apache Geode is no longer part of the release train. Expect a blog post that outlines details soon.

Please give Spring Data 2022.0.0-RC1 a try (for example, as part of the upcoming Spring Boot 3.0.0-RC1 release), which will be available start.spring.io soon, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring at JavaOne 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/16/spring-at-javaone-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/16/spring-at-javaone-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! It’s Sunday the 16th of October as I write this and I’m winging my way to sunny Las Vegas, Nevada, where I’ll be attending (and presenting at) the first JavaOne show in years! It didn’t exist as the JavaOne we know and love for years, even before the pandemic interrupted life as we know it worldwide. So this isn’t just the first JavaOne since 2019, it’s [the first JavaOne since 2017](https://www.infoq.com/news/2018/04/oracle-kills-java-one/_! I can’t wait to be there, to see the amazing community, to soak up the sun and fun with my teammates and friends in the ecosystem. And we want to see you, too.

There are a few of us doing talks from the Spring team and we’d love to see you!

First of all: we have a booth, so join us there.

There are going to be a bunch of great t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2022: Q&A with Bernd and Daniel]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=65420</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/camundacon-2022-qa-bernd-daniel/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T20:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn from Bernd Ruecker, Camunda Co-founder/Chief Technologist, and Daniel Meyer, Camunda CTO, as they tackle questions on connectors, modeling & more.
The post CamundaCon 2022: Q&A with Bernd and Daniel appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UL2 20B: An Open Source Unified Language Learner]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/ul2-20b-open-source-unified-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/ul2-20b-open-source-unified-language.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T18:47:00.009Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yi Tay and Mostafa Dehghani, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team
Building models that understand and generate natural language well is one the grand goals of machine learning (ML) research and has a direct impact on building smart systems for everyday applications. Improving the quality of language models is a key target for researchers to make progress toward such a goal.   

Most common paradigms to build and train language models use either autoregressive decoder-only architectures (e.g., PaLM or GPT-3), where the model is trained to predict the next word for a given prefix phrase, or span corruption-based encoder-decoder architectures (e.g., T5, ST-MoE), where the training objective is to recover the subset of words masked out of the input. On the one hand, T5-li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Two HashiCorp Employees Marked Latinx & Hispanic Heritage Month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-two-hashicorp-employees-marked-latinx-hispanic-heritage-month</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-two-hashicorp-employees-marked-latinx-hispanic-heritage-month"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Karla De La Garza and Abraham Martinez, from HashiCorp’s Unidos Employee Resource Group, share their experiences in Mexico during Latinx & Hispanic Heritage Month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crossmodal-3600 — Multilingual Reference Captions for Geographically Diverse Images]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/crossmodal-3600-multilingual-reference.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/crossmodal-3600-multilingual-reference.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:53:00.014Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ashish Thapliyal, Software Engineer, and Jordi Pont-Tuset, Research Scientist, Google Research
Image captioning is the machine learning task of automatically generating a fluent natural language description for a given image. This task is important for improving accessibility for visually impaired users and is a core task in multimodal research encompassing both vision and language modeling.  
 
However, datasets for image captioning are primarily available in English. Beyond that, there are only a few datasets covering a limited number of languages that represent just a small fraction of the world’s population. Further, these datasets feature images that severely under-represent the richness and diversity of cultures from across the globe. These aspects have hindered research on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.12 Adds New Secrets Engines, ADP Updates, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-12</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-12"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new HashiCorp Vault 1.12 focuses on improving core workflows and making key features production-ready.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Product Teams Can Build Empathy Through Experimentation]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6253603880a6</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/how-product-teams-can-build-empathy-through-experimentation-6253603880a6?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T20:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Camunda 8 self-managed cluster and applications behind a directory]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=64638</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/securing-camunda-8-self-managed-cluster-and-applications-behind-a-directory/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Directory services are an effective way to manage an organization’s users, groups, printers, devices, and more. Most organizations accomplish this using Active Directory, Apache Directory, Oracle Internet Directory, or other similar tools. Recently I worked with a customer who wanted to see how he could secure the Camunda 8 Platform and process applications with such a directory. Their requirements consisted of: Allowing Directory users to access Camunda applications (Tasklist, Operate, Optimize) Accessing secured Tasklist & Operate APIs from our custom project Securing the custom project In this article, I’ll briefly explain the 3 easy steps taken to fulfill their requirements which include: Federate users from the Directory service into Keycloak Declare an application in Identity to access Camunda APIs Configure...
The post Securing Camunda 8 self-managed cluster and applications behind a directory appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christophe Dame</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate security into your developer workflow with GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65846</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/integrate-security-into-your-developer-workflow-with-github-advanced-security-for-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T12:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting things are in store for Azure DevOps in the coming year! We’re planning deep investments in security as well as broad investment across the product. Read on for more information, and then be sure to check out our updated roadmap at https://aka.ms/AzureDevOpsRoadmap.
The post Integrate security into your developer workflow with GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Hallberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verifying distributed systems with Isabelle/HOL]]></title>
        <id>http://martin.kleppmann.com/2022/10/12/verifying-distributed-systems-isabelle.html</id>
        <link href="http://martin.kleppmann.com/2022/10/12/verifying-distributed-systems-isabelle.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post also appears on Larry Paulson’s blog. We use distributed systems every day in the form of internet services. These systems are very useful, but also challenging to implement because networks are unpredictable. Whenever you send a message over the network, it is likely to arrive quite quickly, but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Kleppmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8.1 Released – What’s New]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=64965</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/camunda-platform-8-1-released-whats-new/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re extremely excited to announce the release of Camunda Platform 8.1.  In this post, we will go into the highlights of this release including Web Modeler, Connectors, Zeebe, Operate, Optimize, and more. Here’s the highlights of what’s included in this release: Easier Installation and maintenance for Camunda Platform Self-managed Hot backups for Self-Managed Token-Based authentication Modeler updates Process Templates FEEL Expression Editor Inline Annotations Changes to Camunda forms Connectors updates Workflow engine updates Operate updates Optimize updates Let’s get started! Easier installation and maintenance for Camunda Platform Self-Managed Improved Guides and Support for OpenShift and Amazon EKS (AWS) With this release, we are introducing official support for deploying and running Camunda Platform 8 Self-Managed on OpenShift and Amazon EKS (AWS)....
The post Camunda Platform 8.1 Released – What’s New appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 7.18 Released – What’s New]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=65073</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/camunda-platform-7-18-released-whats-new/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re extremely excited to announce the release of Camunda Platform 7.18 Here are some of the highlights: Cockpit: Improved instance selection to avoid unintended batch operations Cockpit: Easier navigation of high batch operation volumes MDC logging features Camunda Forms in Tasklist: Populate select options via process data Exception error codes Filter and order tasks by last updated WebSphere Liberty New and retired supported environments You can download Camunda Platform or run it with Docker. For a complete list of the changes, please check out the release notes. For patched security vulnerabilities, see our security notices. If you want to dig deeper, check out the source code on GitHub. Cockpit: Improved instance selection to avoid unintended batch operations Previously, when performing...
The post Camunda Platform 7.18 Released – What’s New appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate Connectivity with Camunda Platform 8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=64182</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/accelerate-connectivity-with-camunda-platform-8-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re thrilled to announce Camunda Platform 8.1, the latest release of our process orchestration solution. This new version introduces features that accelerate connectivity to the many different systems and technologies that are required for true digital transformation, including: Create custom Connectors with our Integration Framework to accelerate connectivity New out-of-the-box Connectors for popular services Enhancements to Camunda Modeler that improve productivity Hot backups and official support for Amazon EKS and Red Hat OpenShift Plus, several upgrades requested by Camunda Platform 7 customers Organizations across all industries rely on complex technology stacks to adapt and enhance their operations in response to market dynamics, new disruptive companies, and increasing consumer expectations. Your technology stack likely includes everything from cutting-edge technologies to legacy...
The post Accelerate Connectivity with Camunda Platform 8.1 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 Trn1 Instances for High-Performance Model Training are Now Available]]></title>
        <id>71e7c11b2e368b46b3451452c13a32231a1453a3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-trn1-instances-for-high-performance-model-training-are-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T21:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deep learning (DL) models have been increasing in size and complexity over the last few years, pushing the time to train from days to weeks. Training large language models the size of GPT-3 can take months, leading to an exponential growth in training cost. To reduce model training times and enable machine learning (ML) practitioners […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – October 10, 2022]]></title>
        <id>7c008f7e8cef2812709e94fb9b2a1a09fcd48422</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-october-10-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T20:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I had an amazing start to the week last week as I was speaking at the AWS Community Day NL. This event had 500 attendees and over 70 speakers, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publishing extensions to Marketplace issue resolved]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65675</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/publishing-extensions-to-marketplace-issue-resolved/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T16:08:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have resolved a known issue regarding publishing extensions to the Visual Studio Marketplace. If you’ve run into the error message: “Your ability to create global personal access tokens (PATs) is restricted by your organization.”, this is likely because your administrator has enabled a policy to restrict the creation of global personal access tokens (PATs).
The post Publishing extensions to Marketplace issue resolved appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.13 Significantly Improves Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-13-significantly-improves-performance</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-13-significantly-improves-performance"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform (CDKTF) 0.13 vastly reduces synth time across all supported languages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 211 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65804</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-211-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T14:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sprint 211 was a busy one. We were able to complete a lot of bugs and yet introduce some new exciting features. We also enabled a “Try the New Boards Hub” banner and popup to the legacy boards experience on select organizations.
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 211 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AudioLM: a Language Modeling Approach to Audio Generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/audiolm-language-modeling-approach-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/audiolm-language-modeling-approach-to.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T20:05:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zalán Borsos, Research Software Engineer, and Neil Zeghidour, Research Scientist, Google Research 
Generating realistic audio requires modeling information represented at different scales. For example, just as music builds complex musical phrases from individual notes, speech combines temporally local structures, such as phonemes or syllables, into words and sentences. Creating well-structured and coherent audio sequences at all these scales is a challenge that has been addressed by coupling audio with transcriptions that can guide the generative process, be it text transcripts for speech synthesis or MIDI representations for piano. However, this approach breaks when trying to model untranscribed aspects of audio, such as speaker characteristics necessary to help people with spee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.4 Adds Nomad Variables and Updates Service Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-4-adds-nomad-variables-and-updates-service-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-4-adds-nomad-variables-and-updates-service-discovery"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GA release of HashiCorp Nomad 1.4 enhances native service discovery support with health checks and introduces Nomad Variables, which lets users store configuration values.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Waypoint Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-waypoint-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-waypoint-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint — now available on the HashiCorp Cloud Platform in public beta — lets users standardize application delivery across platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Gains Visibility, Self-Service, and Compliance Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-gains-visibility-self-service-and-compliance-upgrades</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-gains-visibility-self-service-and-compliance-upgrades"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous validation, no-code provisioning, native OPA support for Terraform Cloud, and other new features are key upgrades to HashiCorp Terraform introduced at HashiConf Global 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Local Zones Expansion: Taipei and Delhi]]></title>
        <id>4ed417884c91622d902ab22f2b9f806063ec1a09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-local-zones-expansion-taipei-and-delhi/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T21:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In late 2019 I told you about the AWS Local Zone in Los Angeles, California. In that post I described Local Zones as a new type of AWS infrastructure deployment that brings select AWS services very close to a particular geographic area. A year after that launch, I announced our plans to add 3 more […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Boundary — Now GA — Bolsters HashiCorp's Zero Trust Security Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-boundary-now-ga-bolsters-hashicorp-s-zero-trust-security-solution</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-boundary-now-ga-bolsters-hashicorp-s-zero-trust-security-solution"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of HCP Boundary lets developers access critical systems with fine-grained authorizations — without managing credentials or exposing your network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault on Microsoft Azure Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-on-microsoft-azure-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-on-microsoft-azure-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to its availability on AWS, HCP Vault can now be deployed on Microsoft Azure infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Developer: Your New Experience for Docs and Tutorials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-developer-your-new-experience-for-docs-and-tutorials</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-developer-your-new-experience-for-docs-and-tutorials"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Developer is your one-stop shop for interactive labs, sample code, videos, tutorials, and in-depth documentation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.14 Beta: Announcing Simplified Service Mesh Deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-14-beta-announcing-simplified-service-mesh-deployments</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-14-beta-announcing-simplified-service-mesh-deployments"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul 1.14 enhances traffic management and failover, and adds a new deployment method: Consul dataplane. AWS Lambda updates and beta Windows VM support were also added.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a New HCP-Based Management Plane for Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-a-new-hcp-based-management-plane-for-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-a-new-hcp-based-management-plane-for-consul"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Cloud Platform (HCP) adds new visibility and management controls for self-managed and HCP-managed Consul deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Current State: 2019 Third Party Security Audit of Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/05/current-state-2019-third-party-audit/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/05/current-state-2019-third-party-audit/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors (in alphabetical order): Cailyn Edwards (Shopify), Pushkar Joglekar (VMware), Rey Lejano (SUSE) and Rory McCune (DataDog)
We expect the brand new Third Party Security Audit of Kubernetes will be
published later this month (Oct 2022).
In preparation for that, let's look at the state of findings that were made
public as part of the last third party security audit of
2019
that was based on Kubernetes v1.13.4.
Motivation
Craig Ingram has graciously attempted over the years to keep track of the
status of the findings reported in the last audit in this issue:
kubernetes/kubernetes#81146.
This blog post will attempt to dive deeper into this, address any gaps
in tracking and become a point in time summary of the state of the
findings reported from 2019.
This article should also help reader…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2022 HashiCorp Technology Partner Award Winners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2022-hashicorp-technology-partner-award-winners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2022-hashicorp-technology-partner-award-winners"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 HashiCorp Technology Partner Awards have been announced. Find out who the winners are in our four categories this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large Motion Frame Interpolation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/large-motion-frame-interpolation.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/large-motion-frame-interpolation.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T18:43:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Fitsum Reda and Janne Kontkanen, Google Research 
Frame interpolation is the process of synthesizing in-between images from a given set of images. The technique is often used for temporal up-sampling to increase the refresh rate of videos or to create slow motion effects. Nowadays, with digital cameras and smartphones, we often take several photos within a few seconds to capture the best picture. Interpolating between these “near-duplicate” photos can lead to engaging videos that reveal scene motion, often delivering an even more pleasing sense of the moment than the original photos.  
  
Frame interpolation between consecutive video frames, which often have small motion, has been studied extensively. Unlike videos, however, the temporal spacing between near-duplicate photos can …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing Kueue]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/04/introducing-kueue/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/04/introducing-kueue/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Abdullah Gharaibeh (Google), Aldo Culquicondor (Google)
Whether on-premises or in the cloud, clusters face real constraints for resource usage, quota, and cost management reasons. Regardless of the autoscalling capabilities, clusters have finite capacity. As a result, users want an easy way to fairly and
efficiently share resources.
In this article, we introduce Kueue,
an open source job queueing controller designed to manage batch jobs as a single unit.
Kueue leaves pod-level orchestration to existing stable components of Kubernetes.
Kueue natively supports the Kubernetes Job
API and offers hooks for integrating other custom-built APIs for batch jobs.
Why Kueue?
Job queueing is a key feature to run batch workloads at scale in both on-premises and cloud environments. The main goal…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of Amazon Connect Cases]]></title>
        <id>b52baf93c46bb68d0030598dd7ae15d1a9913d72</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-general-availability-of-amazon-connect-cases/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T20:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June 2022 AWS announced a preview of Amazon Connect Cases, a feature of Amazon Connect that simplifies these customer interactions and reduces the average handle times of issues. Today I am excited to announce the general availability of Amazon Connect Cases. Cases, a feature of Amazon Connect, makes it easy for your contact center […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – October 3, 2022]]></title>
        <id>ae5d0488bf0646507a69e9e761f48098a248df55</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-october-3-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T18:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! A new week and a new month just started. Curious which were the most significant AWS news from the previous seven days? I got you covered with this post. Last […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hands-On Course for Business Analysts – Practical Decision Making using No-Code ML on AWS]]></title>
        <id>732ba82c2e85ba6a2394bf8a29ee95a5e73a4c90</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-hands-on-course-for-business-analysts-practical-decision-making-using-no-code-ml-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T16:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is all around us. AI sends certain emails to our spam folders. It powers autocorrect, which helps us fix typos when we text. And now we can use it to solve business problems. In business, data-driven insights have become increasingly valuable. These insights are often discovered with the help of machine learning […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Ansible and Packer, From Provisioning to Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-and-packer-why-they-are-better-together</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-and-packer-why-they-are-better-together"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform can help you orchestrate, operationalize and govern your hybrid cloud deployments.  In my last public cloud blog, I talked about Two Simple Ways Automation Can Save You Money on Your AWS Bill and similarly to Ashton’s blog Bringing Order to the Cloud: Day 2 Operations in AWS with Ansible, we both wanted to look outside the common public cloud use-case of provisioning and deprovisioning resources and instead look at automating common operational tasks.  For this blog post I want to cover how the Technical Marketing team for Ansible orchestrates a pipeline for demos and workshops with Ansible and how we integrate that with custom AMIs (Amazon Machine Images) created with Packer.  Packer is an open source tool that allows IT operators to standardize and automate the process of building system images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: alpha support for running Pods with user namespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/03/userns-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/03/userns-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Rodrigo Campos (Microsoft), Giuseppe Scrivano (Red Hat)
Kubernetes v1.25 introduces the support for user namespaces.
This is a major improvement for running secure workloads in
Kubernetes. Each pod will have access only to a limited subset of the
available UIDs and GIDs on the system, thus adding a new security
layer to protect from other pods running on the same system.
How does it work?
A process running on Linux can use up to 4294967296 different UIDs and
GIDs.
User namespaces is a Linux feature that allows mapping a set of users
in the container to different users in the host, thus restricting what
IDs a process can effectively use.
Furthermore, the capabilities granted in a new user namespace do not
apply in the host initial namespaces.
Why is it important?
There are mainly t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using FEEL with Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=64132</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/using-feel-with-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T16:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is FEEL As a part of the Decision Model and Notation (DMN) specification, the OMG also defined the Friendly Enough Expression Language (FEEL).  Since DMN is intended to be used by designers and business analysts who would like to build decision tables, FEEL needed to be designed as an uncomplicated and human-readable expression language that would help readers understand the logic being described or executed by the DMN table.  Expression languages are typically used by developers to evaluate data to produce a result based on query parameters or conditions. This means it’s syntactically closer to code than human-readable sentences. Since one of the goals of FEEL is to be “process analyst friendly,” it prioritizes readability more than other expression...
The post Using FEEL with Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon File Cache – A High Performance Cache On AWS For Your On-Premises File Systems]]></title>
        <id>5ab6ca4c7fbca6e707e93106cb015a859442a687</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-file-cache-a-high-performance-cache-on-aws-for-your-on-premises-file-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T14:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce today the availability of Amazon File Cache, a new high-speed cache service on AWS designed for processing file data stored in disparate locations—including on premises. File Cache accelerates and simplifies your most demanding cloud bursting and hybrid workflows by giving your applications access to files using a fast and familiar […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Camunda 8 supports process automation at enterprise scale]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63983</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/how-camunda-8-supports-process-automation-at-enterprise-scale/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling process automation across an enterprise naturally includes a wide array of challenges. To counter these challenges, more and more organizations are evolving their organizational structures accordingly, often creating Centers of Excellence (CoE) and/or communities of practice (CoP). Please note that during this post we will use the term CoE, but keep in mind your organization might call this very differently. That said, in Camunda Platform 8, we included new functionalities that will help companies to scale process automation successfully.  This blog post discusses different aspects of scaling process automation, the role of CoEs, and how new Camunda 8 features support those initiatives.  What does scaling mean? Organizations that want to create a competitive edge through digital transformation (and frankly: which...
The post How Camunda 8 supports process automation at enterprise scale appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon WorkSpaces Introduces Ubuntu Desktops]]></title>
        <id>f345653beefe2e326410b05edcca8bc0fdf98a41</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-workspaces-introduces-ubuntu-desktops/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T16:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS, we love to give our customers choices: the choice of infrastructure to deploy your workloads, to store your most important data, or the operating systems for your virtual desktops. Many of you choose Amazon Workspaces to provision and distribute virtual desktops securely and at scale to your workforce. Our customers choose Workspaces when […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dungeons & Dragons for Team Building]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dungeons-dragons-for-team-building</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dungeons-dragons-for-team-building"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Community team used a custom Dungeons & Dragons campaign as a team building exercise. Check out the highlights and then try it yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>