<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-12-20T00:43:20.791Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-12-20T00:43:20.791Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing 7.16.2 and 6.8.22 releases of Elasticsearch and Logstash to upgrade Apache Log4j2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-elasticsearch-and-logstash-releases-upgrade-apache-log4j2</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-elasticsearch-and-logstash-releases-upgrade-apache-log4j2"/>
        <updated>2021-12-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce new versions of Elasticsearch and Logstash, 7.16.2 and 6.8.22, to upgrade to the latest release of Apache Log4j and address false positive concerns with some vulnerability scanners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Callahan,Quin Hoxie,Rajiv Raghunarayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing 7.16.2 and 6.8.22 releases of Elasticsearch and Logstash to upgrade Apache Log4j2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-elasticsearch-and-logstash-releases-upgrade-apache-log4j2</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-elasticsearch-and-logstash-releases-upgrade-apache-log4j2"/>
        <updated>2021-12-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are pleased to announce new versions of Elasticsearch and Logstash, 7.16.2 and 6.8.22, to upgrade to the latest release of Apache Log4j and address false positive concerns with some vulnerability scanners. Elastic also maintains ongoing updates via our advisory to ensure our Elastic customers and our communities can stay up-to-date on the latest developments. 
December 10th started with the public disclosure of the Apache Log4j vulnerability -  CVE-2021-44228 affecting the popular open source logging framework adopted by several Java based custom and commercial applications. This vulnerability, affecting versions 2.0-beta9 through 2.14.1 of Log4j2, and is already being exploited by nation state attackers and ransomware groups, such as APT35 and Hafnium. Research by Google using Open S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Callahan,Quin Hoxie,Rajiv Raghunarayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with GitHub Actions just got easier!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-17-getting-started-with-github-actions-just-got-easier/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-17-getting-started-with-github-actions-just-got-easier/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T17:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you want to create a workflow in the Actions tab of your repository, the recommendations are now based on an analysis of repo content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better together: How Elastic supports fast-paced growth with empathy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-elastic-supports-fastpaced-growth-with-empathy-culture</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-elastic-supports-fastpaced-growth-with-empathy-culture"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the spirit of our free and open heritage, we’re sharing some of the ways we’ve maintained our culture as we’ve grown, and what we’ve learned along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CISOs can better manage an emerging risk: unfilled roles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-cisos-better-manage-emerging-risk-unfilled-roles-insights-leadership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-cisos-better-manage-emerging-risk-unfilled-roles-insights-leadership"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity leaders are accelerating recruiting efforts to build organizational resilience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Palmquist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better together: How Elastic supports fast-paced growth with empathy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-elastic-supports-fastpaced-growth-with-empathy-culture</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-elastic-supports-fastpaced-growth-with-empathy-culture"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Our ten-year anniversary is just around the corner. As I’m sure you can imagine, a lot has changed since our humble beginnings as a recipe app. For one, we’ve gone from a scrappy startup with our core Elastic Stack to becoming a publicly traded company with a full arsenal of search-powered solutions. 
Since our start, we’ve led with a human-centric approach to our culture and how we grow. It’s so integrated into what we do, it’s a part of our Source Code. 
“At the beginning of defining values for the company, it was difficult to determine what would actually inspire people.” says CEO and founder, Shay Banon when talking about how our Source Code came to be. “We didn’t want our set of values to be bland or common. We wanted it to be multidimensional, so people can find themselves in it. G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CISOs can better manage an emerging risk: unfilled roles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-cisos-better-manage-emerging-risk-unfilled-roles-insights-leadership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-cisos-better-manage-emerging-risk-unfilled-roles-insights-leadership"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
When Colonial Pipeline suffered a massive ransomware attack in early 2021, an internal vulnerability added to the crisis: The company was operating without its top cybersecurity manager. 
The global security workforce needs to grow by 65% to become fully staffed, according to a new study by (ISC)², the world’s largest organization for cybersecurity pros. While modern IT platforms and tools can certainly automate many low-level tasks to help relieve overburdened security teams, chief information security officers must still find better ways to retain existing workers and recruit new ones.  
If they don’t, those unfilled positions represent a significant source of risk, security leaders say. Staff shortages are causing misconfigured systems, oversights in following security procedures, rus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Palmquist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第200話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496654874704</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496654874704"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.12.17]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63015</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-12-17/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T11:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.12.17 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.12.17 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client Side Development with Spring Boot Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/17/client-side-development-with-spring-boot-applications</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/17/client-side-development-with-spring-boot-applications"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores the different options that Spring Boot developers have for using Javascript and CSS on the client (browser) side of their application. Part of the plan is to explore some Javascript libraries that play well in the traditional server-side-rendered world of Spring web applications. Those libraries tend to have a light touch for the application developer, in the sense that they allow you to completely avoid Javascript, but still have nice a progressive "modern" UI. We also look at some more "pure" Javascript tools and frameworks. It’s kind of a spectrum, so as a TL;DR here is a list of the sample apps, in rough order of low to high Javascript content:





htmx: HTMX is a library that allows you to access modern browser features directly from HTML, rather than using…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Ronald Dehuysser, Creator of the Distributed Job Scheduler JobRunr]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/16/a-bootiful-podcast-ronald-dehuysser-creator-of-the-distributed-job-scheduler-jobrunr</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/16/a-bootiful-podcast-ronald-dehuysser-creator-of-the-distributed-job-scheduler-jobrunr"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long talks to JobRunr.io creator Ronald Dehuysser (@rdehuyss) about JobRunr, which is a distributed job scheduling engine that plugs right into Spring Boot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the HashiCorp Partner Hackstravaganza Winners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/meet-the-hashicorp-partner-hackstravaganza-winners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/meet-the-hashicorp-partner-hackstravaganza-winners"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See the results of HashiCorp’s virtual partner hackathon held in the Asia-Pacific region.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turing Complete]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2556/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2556/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/turing_complete.png" title="Thanks to the ForcedEntry exploit, your company's entire tech stack can now be hosted out of a PDF you texted to someone." alt="Thanks to the ForcedEntry exploit, your company's entire tech stack can now be hosted out of a PDF you texted to someone." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Scalable Approach for Partially Local Federated Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/a-scalable-approach-for-partially-local.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/a-scalable-approach-for-partially-local.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T18:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Karan Singhal, Senior Software Engineer, Google Research  
Federated learning enables users to train a model without sending raw data to a central server, thus avoiding the collection of privacy-sensitive data. Often this is done by learning a single global model for all users, even though the users may differ in their data distributions. For example, users of a mobile keyboard application may collaborate to train a suggestion model but have different preferences for the suggestions. This heterogeneity has motivated algorithms that can personalize a global model for each user.  
 However, in some settings privacy considerations may prohibit learning a fully global model. Consider models with user-specific embeddings, such as matrix factorization models for recommender systems. Tr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical interviews via Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-16-technical-interviews-via-codespaces/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-16-technical-interviews-via-codespaces/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T17:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Codespaces is a great tool for technical hiring exercises and helps level the playing field for candidates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 automations every developer should be running]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-16-5-automations-every-developer-should-be-running/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-16-5-automations-every-developer-should-be-running/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T17:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to avoid security vulnerabilities, buttons that don’t work, slow site speeds, or manually writing release notes? This one's for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Consul 1.11 - Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-consul-1-11</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-consul-1-11"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul 1.11 adds important new features: multi-tenancy with administrative partitions, new installation-and-management Consul Kubernetes CLI, and Vault integration on Consul Kubernetes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Cross Cluster Search with Elastic Cloud to improve observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/use-cross-cluster-search-elastic-cloud-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/use-cross-cluster-search-elastic-cloud-observability"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s SRE team has used features and functionality from Elastic Cloud to build and deploy a global observability solution that allows vital visibility into the logs, metrics and traces that are collected across our globally distributed platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neil Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Cross Cluster Search with Elastic Cloud to improve observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/use-cross-cluster-search-elastic-cloud-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/use-cross-cluster-search-elastic-cloud-observability"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Leveraging various tools and pieces of functionality, this blog describes how we have built a scalable cross-region and cross-provider Single Pane of Glass (SPOG) using cross-cluster search (CCS).
This blog will be useful if your Observability data is distributed across deployments, if you have multiple points of entry to view and analyze your data, and if you find yourself hopping from one Kibana instance to another to find the answers you’re looking for.
Supporting customers across multiple providers and regions means we collect and observe data within each region. Technically, we operate each region in a largely stand-alone fashion. Logs, metrics and trace data collected within that region will remain in that region. While this provides the benefits of isolation and security, it can b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neil Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0 M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/16/spring-framework-6-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/16/spring-framework-6-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T16:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring community,

It is my pleasure to announce that the first Spring Framework 6.0 milestone release is available from htts://repo.spring.io/milestone now. This initial milestone covers our baseline upgrade efforts, in particular requiring JDK 17+ and migrating to the Jakarta EE 9 APIs; see my recent baseline blog post for the rationale. At the same time, it removes many long-deprecated classes, including several support packages for outdated third-party infrastructure.

For current upgrade notes, please refer to our Upgrading to Spring Framework 6.0 page which we will keep updating. Follow our main branch on GitHub for the latest changes, as we prepare for 6.0 M2 and the corresponding Spring Boot 3.0 M1 release in January. At that point, you will also be able to consume Spring Framework 6.0 through https://start.spring.io/. For the time being, feel free to grab 6.0 M1 from https://repo.spring.io/ and let us know how it goes.

Cheers,
Juergen]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new: network automation using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-network-automation-using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-network-automation-using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A financial customer explained his first automation priority in the most visual and understandable way: “I want to paint all of my network devices with the color of the company.” What I like about that analogy is that it clearly describes the first rule for automation: customers must define their golden configurations (the color to paint) to be able to automate configurations and later assess compliance, and remediate any issues accordingly. 
A “golden configuration” usually refers to a Day 1 configuration, and covers the minimal settings needed for a network device to be configured after a fresh network operating system installation. This usually includes common services such as NTP, DNS, AAA, Syslog, SNMP, and ACLs for management connectivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advice for CIOs from the IT frontlines: Design training programs for higher impact and retention]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/upskilling-reskilling-it-key-strategies-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/upskilling-reskilling-it-key-strategies-success"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IT talent gap shortage requires CIOs to make savvy investments in upskilling and reskilling. Here are the 4 key strategies IT practitioners recommend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Rabinowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advice for CIOs from the IT frontlines: Design training programs for higher impact and retention]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/upskilling-reskilling-it-key-strategies-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/upskilling-reskilling-it-key-strategies-success"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The shortage of tech skills worsened during the pandemic, and the battle to hire and retain top IT talent is only getting more challenging. To close the IT talent gap, more CIOs are looking to expand the skills of their current workforce, according to a recent McKinsey Global Survey.
But effective upskilling and reskilling isn’t simply a matter of paying for IT practitioners to earn certifications in the latest technology. Leaders must decide what options align best with business objectives, specific skills gaps, and rapidly changing learning styles of knowledge workers.
To get a front-line perspective on these issues, we interviewed a group of seasoned IT pros for their insights into how enterprise leaders should approach employee training and reskilling challenges. Here are highlights …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Rabinowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.14 and 5.2.19 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/16/spring-framework-5-3-14-and-5-2-19-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/16/spring-framework-5-3-14-and-5-2-19-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T10:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.14 and 5.2.19 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.14 includes 36 fixes and improvements. Spring Framework 5.2.19 includes 11 selected fixes and improvements.

Stay tuned for the announcement of Spring Framework 6.0.0-M1 later today!

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2020.0.5 (Ilford) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/16/spring-cloud-2020-0-5-ilford-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/16/spring-cloud-2020-0-5-ilford-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the General Availability (RELEASE) of the Spring Cloud 2020.0.5 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2020.0.5 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2020.0.5 Release Train
Spring Cloud Netflix


  
Upgraded Netflix/Eureka to 1.10.17 issue


Spring Cloud Config


  
Support Using HTTPS proxies for Git Repositories (1965)

  
Support ordering AWS, Redis, and CredHub Repositories (1980)


Spring Cloud Gateway


  
Enhancements for metrics: Netty connections, path as tag, and route definition count


Spring Cloud Kubernetes


  
Specify User Agent for Kubernetes API Client (898)

  
Allow activeProfile not to be appended (508)

  
Upgrade to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How observability drives better customer experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-observability-drives-better-customer-experiences</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-observability-drives-better-customer-experiences"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New software tools can help CIOs identify, fix, and prevent service-impacting glitches in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How observability drives better customer experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-observability-drives-better-customer-experiences</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-observability-drives-better-customer-experiences"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As marketing director of technology for Stanley Black & Decker, it’s no surprise that Colleen Romero is into power tools. But her favorite utility isn’t a jigsaw or cordless drill.
It’s observability technology.
Observability—software that integrates data from various departments and applications —makes it possible to monitor how customers experience the performance of the 350 websites that Romero oversees. On her watch, the tools have spotted some problems before customers notice. 
“We no longer have customers calling us to say our websites are down,” says Romero. “Observability tools let us spot any degradation of performance and identify the root cause so we can address it proactively.”
Observability enables businesses and IT teams to trace customer issues back to an offending applica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: @Controllers and GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/15/spring-tips-controllers-and-graphql</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/15/spring-tips-controllers-and-graphql"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, we continue our tour of all things @Controller by looking at the nascent Spring GraphQL project]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Training Machine Learning Models More Efficiently with Dataset Distillation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/training-machine-learning-models-more.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/training-machine-learning-models-more.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T19:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Timothy Nguyen1, Research Engineer and Jaehoon Lee, Senior Research Scientist, Google Research  
For a machine learning (ML) algorithm to be effective, useful features must be extracted from (often) large amounts of training data. However, this process can be made challenging due to the costs associated with training on such large datasets, both in terms of compute requirements and wall clock time. The idea of distillation plays an important role in these situations by reducing the resources required for the model to be effective. The most widely known form of distillation is model distillation (a.k.a. knowledge distillation), where the predictions of large, complex teacher models are distilled into smaller models.  
 An alternative option to this model-space approach is dataset …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62998</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/december-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T18:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Fix work item macro for queries with “Contains Words”. Previously, queries were returning incorrect results for values that contained a line break.
The post December patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A brief history of code search at GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-15-a-brief-history-of-code-search-at-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-15-a-brief-history-of-code-search-at-github/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T18:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post tells the story of why we built a new search engine optimized for code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysis of Log4Shell vulnerability & CVE-2021-45046]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/analysis-of-log4shell-cve-2021-45046</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/analysis-of-log4shell-cve-2021-45046"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we cover next steps the Elastic Security team is taking for users to continue to protect themselves against CVE-2021-44228, or Log4Shell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysis of Log4Shell vulnerability & CVE-2021-45046]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/analysis-of-log4shell-cve-2021-45046</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/analysis-of-log4shell-cve-2021-45046"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In recent days Log4Shell, or CVE-2021-44228, has dominated the news cycle in the world of information security and beyond. Elastic released an advisory detailing how Elastic products and users are impacted, and a blog post describing how our users can leverage Elastic Security to help defend their networks.
Many readers have further questions as to how we’re tracking this issue within Elastic Security, what our coverage is now, and what we’re expecting to do next. This post outlines a few details for our current status, and provides details regarding a new, related vulnerability: CVE-2021-45046.
Elastic Security response
As you may imagine, the team has worked tirelessly to ensure that we’re developing detections for both active exploitation of the vulnerability, as well as post-compromi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Helm Apps to Kubernetes with Waypoint and GitOps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploying-helm-apps-to-kubernetes-with-waypoint-and-gitops</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploying-helm-apps-to-kubernetes-with-waypoint-and-gitops"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use HashiCorp Waypoint to help simplify and automate your Helm application deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps trend accelerates: CIOs are changing who is responsible for cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/cios-are-changing-who-is-responsible-for-cybersecurity-devsecops-observability-securitytools</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/cios-are-changing-who-is-responsible-for-cybersecurity-devsecops-observability-securitytools"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security tools are becoming used as much by developers as by security specialists, according to data from 451 Research, part of S&P Global Market Intelligence. By recognizing the shared responsibility of protecting organizations, CIOs are remaking IT for the better and delivering improved services to customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps trend accelerates: CIOs are changing who is responsible for cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/cios-are-changing-who-is-responsible-for-cybersecurity-devsecops-observability-securitytools</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/cios-are-changing-who-is-responsible-for-cybersecurity-devsecops-observability-securitytools"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
CIOs are remaking the IT function — no longer will security and developer teams be siloed. 
Recent survey data from 451 Research, part of S&P Global Market Intelligence, and published by Elastic shows a major shift in who is using application security tools, suggesting that DevSecOps is not just an idea, but a growing reality for IT decision makers.
IT decision-makers allocated application security tools to 48% of development teams in 2020, compared to just 29% in 2015. That’s nearly a two-fold jump. 
According to “The New Security Imperative for CIOs” report by 451 Research, “Opportunities abound for security to become more directly integrated into DevOps efforts, with CIOs leading the charge.” The report continues: “Security teams must become better versed in DevOps practices and tools…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Smarter Cities with Process Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=38609</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/12/building-smarter-cities-with-process-automation/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover why Apendo partnered with Camunda to automate citizen services for several municipalities and counting all over Sweden. 
The post Building Smarter Cities with Process Automation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Elastic and Amazon S3 Storage Lens Integration: Simplify management, control costs, and reduce risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-elastic-and-amazon-s3-storage-lens-integration-simplify-management-control-costs-and-reduce-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-elastic-and-amazon-s3-storage-lens-integration-simplify-management-control-costs-and-reduce-risk"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud enables organizations to get a holistic view of operations across Amazon S3 Storage Lens metrics and AWS and on-premises data sets to simplify management, contain costs, and reduce security risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uday Theepireddy,Ravi Kesarwani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Elastic and Amazon S3 Storage Lens Integration: Simplify management, control costs, and reduce risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-elastic-and-amazon-s3-storage-lens-integration-simplify-management-control-costs-and-reduce-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-elastic-and-amazon-s3-storage-lens-integration-simplify-management-control-costs-and-reduce-risk"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As data and applications grow at an exponential rate — they produce logs, metrics and traces at a rapid pace — making storage and management even more complex. The new Elastic and Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) Storage Lens integration provides customers with a complete organization-wide view of Amazon S3 usage and activity metrics alongside their other AWS and on-premises data sets. 
SREs and DevOps engineers can now use the powerful search and analytics capabilities of the Elastic search platform — including dashboarding capabilities, built-in machine learning analysis, and threshold-based alerts — to identify trends and correlate their Amazon S3 Storage Lens data with other performance indicators across their environment. These insights can also be leveraged to optimize sto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uday Theepireddy,Ravi Kesarwani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=38438</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/12/camunda-automation-platform-7170-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T02:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're pleased to announce the second alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17.0. Download Camunda for free or run it with Docker today. 
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps (and Azure DevOps Server) and the log4j vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62991</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-and-azure-devops-server-and-the-log4j-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T02:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the most part, Azure DevOps (and Azure DevOps Server) are built on .NET and do not use the Apache log4j library whose vulnerabilities (CVE-2021-44228, CVE-2021-45046, Microsoft security blog post) have been the focus of so much recent attention. The Search feature in both Azure DevOps and Azure DevOps Server does use this library,
The post Azure DevOps (and Azure DevOps Server) and the log4j vulnerability appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2555/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2555/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/notifications.png" title="It's 10:34 PM for this user. They really need to get going, they have a thing early tomorrow. Are you sure you want to notify?" alt="It's 10:34 PM for this user. They really need to get going, they have a thing early tomorrow. Are you sure you want to notify?" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using GitHub’s security features to help identify Log4j exposure in your codebase]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-14-using-githubs-security-features-identify-log4j-exposure-codebase/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-14-using-githubs-security-features-identify-log4j-exposure-codebase/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T19:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use GitHub’s security features to assess Apache Log4j exposure and, where possible, mitigate this vulnerability within your GitHub repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 14th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/14/this-week-in-spring-december-14th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/14/this-week-in-spring-december-14th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How are you? Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’m doing alright! It’s noon as I write this, and I’ve got GSUG joint presentation with Matt Raible later today. Then, tonight at midnight my time to 5 am or 6 am, I’m kicking off a two-day workshop for GOTO! I look forward to seeing ya there! Anyway, we’ve got a lot to cover so let’s dive into it! 


  
Read this first! If you’ve been living under a rock, you may not have heard of the recent Log4J2 vulnerability. If you’re using the default, out-of-the-box Spring Boot logging support, then this does not apply to you! But, if you are using Log4j2, specifically, then you need to read this post on Log4j2 and Spring Boot!

  
Bruno Borges tweets this very simple workaround for those of you who are using Lo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Square 0.4.0-RC1 is available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/14/spring-cloud-square-0-4-0-rc1-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/14/spring-cloud-square-0-4-0-rc1-is-available"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T18:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Release Candidate 1 (RC1) of the Spring Cloud Square 0.4.0 is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 0.4.0-RC1 release notes for more information.

This is primarily a bugfix release. See all issues included in this release here.
Notable changes in RC1:


  
Spring Cloud Sleuth integration for OkHttpClient #36


The documentation for this milestone can be found here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to define security requirements for your OSS project]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-14-how-to-define-security-requirements-for-your-oss-project/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-14-how-to-define-security-requirements-for-your-oss-project/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T17:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defining your security requirements is the most important proactive control you can implement for your project. Here's how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Adds Support for GKE Autopilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-adds-support-for-gke-autopilot</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-adds-support-for-gke-autopilot"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Cloud Terraform provider now supports deployment of GKE Autopilot clusters. Learn how to use the new feature with a short example.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring GraphQL 1.0.0-M4 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/14/spring-graphql-1-0-0-m4-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/14/spring-graphql-1-0-0-m4-released"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T16:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spring GraphQL team has just released the 4th milestone towards a 1.0.0 release. Thanks to all contributors!

In this milestone, we have further improved the annotation programming model and extended the Spring Data support that were provided in the previous milestones.
Interface Projections for GraphQL Arguments

If you’re familiar with Spring Data’s Interface-based Projections, then this new feature will make perfect sense: you can use a well-defined interface to work with GraphQL arguments, without the need for any Object implementation. 

For example:

@Controller
public class BookController {

    @MutationMapping
    public Book addBook(@Argument BookInputProjection bookInput) {
        // ...
    }
}

@ProjectedPayload
interface BookInputProjection {
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New reference architecture: Deploying Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-deploying-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-deploying-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1, we are proud to deliver the latest reference architecture on the best practices for deploying a highly available Ansible Automation Platform environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.7.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=38581</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/12/camunda-optimize-3-7-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.7.0-alpha2. Use your Camunda Enterprise Platform credentials to get started now.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.7.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.3.0-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=38579</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/12/camunda-cloud-1-3-0-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Cloud 1.3.0-alpha3. Sign up now to get started with Camunda Cloud 1.3.0-alpha3 right away!
The post Camunda Cloud 1.3.0-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Open – AWS Asia Pacific (Jakarta) Region]]></title>
        <id>f2939be25b70e1866f8b4c262cdd3a095b2fe38c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-aws-asia-pacific-jakarta-region/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T05:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Region in Jakarta, Indonesia, is now open and you can start using it today. The official name is Asia Pacific (Jakarta) and the API name is ap-southeast-3. The AWS Asia Pacific (Jakarta) Region is the tenth active AWS Region in Asia Pacific and mainland China along with Beijing, Hong Kong, Mumbai, Ningxia, Osaka, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub’s response to Log4j vulnerability CVE-2021-44228]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-13-githubs-response-to-log4j-vulnerability-cve-2021-44228/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-13-githubs-response-to-log4j-vulnerability-cve-2021-44228/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T19:06:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, December 9, 2021, GitHub was made aware of a vulnerability in the Log4j logging framework, CVE-2021-44228.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new from GitHub Changelog? November 2021 recap]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-13-whats-new-from-github-changelog-november-2021-recap/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-13-whats-new-from-github-changelog-november-2021-recap/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T17:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We shipped a ton of updates in November, from the push notification for PR review activities on the go, to an easy way to create Markdown links.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interpretable Deep Learning for Time Series Forecasting]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/interpretable-deep-learning-for-time.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/interpretable-deep-learning-for-time.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T17:22:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sercan O. Arik, Research Scientist and Tomas Pfister, Engineering Manager, Google Cloud   
Multi-horizon forecasting, i.e. predicting variables-of-interest at multiple future time steps, is a crucial challenge in time series machine learning. Most real-world datasets have a time component, and forecasting the future can unlock great value. For example, retailers can use future sales to optimize their supply chain and promotions, investment managers are interested in forecasting the future prices of financial assets to maximize their performance, and healthcare institutions can use the number of future patient admissions to have sufficient personnel and equipment. 
  
Deep neural networks (DNNs) have increasingly been used in multi-horizon forecasting, demonstrating strong perform…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub at the UN Internet Governance Forum]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-13-github-at-the-un-internet-governance-forum/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-13-github-at-the-un-internet-governance-forum/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T17:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, GitHub joined the Internet Governance Forum to spread awareness of developers’ initiatives and public policy interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes: BT Media and Broadcast Builds A Stronger Media Network with Camunda]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=38461</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/12/behind-the-scenes-bt-media-and-broadcast-builds-a-stronger-media-network-with-camunda/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how the help of our process automation and support, made BT Media and Broadcast fully equipped to adapt for their clients' needs. 
The post Behind the Scenes: BT Media and Broadcast Builds A Stronger Media Network with Camunda appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and how to replace end-to-end tests with synthetic monitors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-and-how-replace-end-to-end-tests-synthetic-monitors</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-and-how-replace-end-to-end-tests-synthetic-monitors"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passing tests on your machine and CI can't ensure your code will work in production. This post explains how synthetics help you write code that "works on your machine" and everyone else's, both before and after your code reaches production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas da Costa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and how to replace end-to-end tests with synthetic monitors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-and-how-replace-end-to-end-tests-synthetic-monitors</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-and-how-replace-end-to-end-tests-synthetic-monitors"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
A thousand tests can't prove your software works. They can only prove it doesn't. When your code reaches production, even the most thorough end-to-end tests can't prevent your users from seeing that "500 - Unexpected Server Error" screen that keeps you awake at night. 
In this blog post, you'll learn why even the most thorough end-to-end tests can't prove your software works and get to know an alternative to these classic end-to-end tests: synthetic monitors. 
The latest version of Kibana is shipping with many improvements to Elastic's Synthetics and this blog post will help you use them.
First, we'll explain what synthetic monitors are and the advantages of writing synthetics tests over traditional end-to-end tests.
Then, we'll describe how you can use Elastic's Synthetic Monitors to he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas da Costa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Bicep files by using GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62942</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-bicep-files-by-using-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T11:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I did a live streaming session for the New York City Microsoft Reactor in which I took concepts from the Quickstart: Deploy Bicep files by using GitHub Actions doc and put them into action.  In this session I create an Azure Kubernetes (AKS) cluster with secrets from Azure Key Vault with Bicep and GitHub Actions.
The post Deploy Bicep files by using GitHub Actions appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gift Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2554/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2554/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/gift_exchange.png" title="In addition to having all their budgets in a spreadsheet with consistent formatting, they just love expressing preferences on a well-calibrated numerical scale." alt="In addition to having all their budgets in a spreadsheet with consistent formatting, they just love expressing preferences on a well-calibrated numerical scale." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Fast WordPiece Tokenization System]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/a-fast-wordpiece-tokenization-system.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/a-fast-wordpiece-tokenization-system.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T20:35:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xinying Song, Staff Software Engineer and Denny Zhou, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Research   
Tokenization is a fundamental pre-processing step for most natural language processing (NLP) applications. It involves splitting text into smaller units called tokens (e.g., words or word segments) in order to turn an unstructured input string into a sequence of discrete elements that is suitable for a machine learning (ML) model. ln deep learning–based models (e.g., BERT), each token is mapped to an embedding vector to be fed into the model.  
   


Tokenization in a typical deep learning model, like BERT.

   
A fundamental tokenization approach is to break text into words. However, using this approach, words that are not included in the vocabulary are treated as “unknown”.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Log4J2 Vulnerability and Spring Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/10/log4j2-vulnerability-and-spring-boot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/10/log4j2-vulnerability-and-spring-boot"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates: Since this blog post has been published, a new logback 1.2.9 version has been published. While this fixes a security issue, prerequisites for exploits are very different as they “requires write access to logback’s configuration file”.
Log4J also released a new 2.17.0 version with fixes for CVE-2021-45046 and CVE-2021-45105
Our upcoming releases will pick up these new versions.


As you may have seen in the news, a new zero-day exploit has been reported against the popular Log4J2 library which can allow an attacker to remotely execute code. The vulnerability has been reported with CVE-2021-44228 against the log4j-core jar and has been fixed in Log4J v2.15.0.

Spring Boot users are only affected by this vulnerability if they have switched the default logging system to Log4J2. The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.12.10]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62964</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-12-10/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T11:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.12.10 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.12.10 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident Report]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2553/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2553/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/incident_report.png" title="Increasing-precision timestamps are the Jaws theme of incident reports." alt="Increasing-precision timestamps are the Jaws theme of incident reports." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Efficient In-Context Learning with GLaM]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/more-efficient-in-context-learning-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/more-efficient-in-context-learning-with.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T20:22:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Andrew M Dai and Nan Du, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team  
Large language models (e.g., GPT-3) have many significant capabilities, such as performing few-shot learning across a wide array of tasks, including reading comprehension and question answering with very few or no training examples. While these models can perform better by simply using more parameters, training and serving these large models can be very computationally intensive. Is it possible to train and use these models more efficiently? 
  
In “GLaM: Efficient Scaling of Language Models with Mixture-of-Experts”, we introduce the Generalist Language Model (GLaM), a trillion weight model that can be trained and served efficiently (in terms of computation and energy use) thanks to sparsity, and achieves…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Transformative leader, brilliant technologist, my friend, Patrick Chanezon]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/09/a-bootiful-podcast-transformative-leader-brilliant-technologist-my-friend-patrick-chanezon</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/09/a-bootiful-podcast-transformative-leader-brilliant-technologist-my-friend-patrick-chanezon"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! This week, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to transformational leader, my old boss, legendary technologist, and friend Patrick Chanezon (@chanezon).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Chapter for HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-new-chapter-for-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-new-chapter-for-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we officially enter the public markets, we plan to continue to do what we think we do best: solving problems for our end users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing stack graphs]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-09-introducing-stack-graphs/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-09-introducing-stack-graphs/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T17:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Precise code navigation is powered by stack graphs, a new open source framework that lets you define the name binding rules for a programming language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AOT Engine Brings Spring Native to the Next Level]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/09/new-aot-engine-brings-spring-native-to-the-next-level</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/09/new-aot-engine-brings-spring-native-to-the-next-level"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the release of Spring Native 0.11, which provides native support for Spring Boot 2.6. This ambitious release is the result of five months of hard work by the Spring team, who have been working on a brand new architecture to bring Spring support for creating native executables with GraalVM to the next level. You can already try it on start.spring.io!



Learn more about Spring Native 0.11 and see it in action in this new Spring Tips video from Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long.




New Ahead-Of-Time Engine



The biggest change is undoubtedly the introduction of a new AOT engine that performs a deep analysis of your Spring application at build-time to transform and optimize your application and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.1 Improves Refactoring and the Cloud CLI Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-1-improves-refactoring-and-the-cloud-cli-experience</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-1-improves-refactoring-and-the-cloud-cli-experience"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now generally available, HashiCorp Terraform 1.1 offers easier and safer refactoring with ‘moved’ statements and improves the CLI for Terraform Cloud and Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General and Scalable Parallelization for Neural Networks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/general-and-scalable-parallelization.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/general-and-scalable-parallelization.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T19:30:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yuanzhong Xu and Yanping Huang, Software Engineers; Google Research, Brain Team  
Scaling neural networks, whether it be the amount of training data used, the model size or the computation being utilized,  has been critical for improving model quality in many real-world machine learning applications, such as computer vision, language understanding and neural machine translation. This, in turn, has motivated recent studies to scrutinize the factors that play a critical role in the success of scaling a neural model. Although increasing model capacity can be a sound approach to improve model quality, doing so presents a number of systems and software engineering challenges that must be overcome. For instance, in order to train large models that exceed the memory capacity of an accel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.13.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/spring-tools-4-13-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/spring-tools-4-13-0-released"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.13.0 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
updated to Eclipse 2021-12 release (including support for Java 17) (new and noteworthy)

  
builds for Apple Silicon platform (ARM M1) are available now from the regular download page


additional changes


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: STS 4.12.0 (for eclipse) *.yml can’t automatic prompt (#690)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: A StackOverFlow error for serializable Kotlin data class for autocompletion in the Eclipse IDE (#693)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Typescript comparison: An internal error occurred during: “LSP4E Linked Editing Highlight” (#700)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: js syntax highlight disabled by STS4 (#702)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Cannot copy/paste from ANSI console without escape sequences (#667) - fixed in ANSI Color Console project thanks to @mihnita


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


If you are updating an existing Spring Tools 4 installation, please make sure you to prepare your installation propertly this time: https://twitter.com/springtools4/status/1468587842838355980

Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2021-12-08-4130-release-incl-language-servers-version-1290

Spring Tools 4.13.1 is scheduled to be released in early Feb 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure communications end-to-end for Spring Boot apps – in Zero Trust environment]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/secure-communications-end-to-end-for-spring-boot-apps-in-zero-trust-environment</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/secure-communications-end-to-end-for-spring-boot-apps-in-zero-trust-environment"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secure communications end-to-end for Spring Boot apps - in a Zero Trust environment

Hi, Spring fans! Today, we are excited to announce the general availability of all the features to secure communications end-to-end for Spring Boot apps – in a Zero Trust environment. You can secure communications end-to-end or terminate transport level security at any communication point for Spring Boot apps. You can also automate the provisioning and configuration for all the Azure resources needed for securing communications.

Implementing secure communications as part of your solution architecture can be challenging. Many customers manually rotate their certificates or create their own solutions to automate provisioning and configuration. Even then, there is still data exfiltration risk – say unautho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snaring the Bad Folks]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/66726a1f4c80</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/snaring-the-bad-folks-66726a1f4c80?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T17:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project by Netflix’s Cloud Infrastructure Security team (Alex Bainbridge, Mike Grima, Nick Siow)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Gateway and gRPC]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/spring-cloud-gateway-and-grpc</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/spring-cloud-gateway-and-grpc"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting from version 3.1.0 as part of the Spring Cloud 2021.0.0 (aka Jubilee) release train, Spring Cloud Gateway included support for gRPC and HTTP/2.



We will introduce the basic concepts behind gRPC and how to configure it with two examples:





One that showcases how Spring Cloud Gateway can transparently re-route gRPC traffic without needing to know the proto definition and without having to modify our existing gRPC servers.



Another that showcases how we can create a custom filter in Spring Cloud Gateway to transform a JSON payload to a gRPC message.





Introduction to gRPC and HTTP/2



HTTP/2 makes our applications faster, simpler, and more robust. Reducing latency by enabling request and response
multiplexing, adding efficient compression of HTTP header…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Camunda Holiday Reading List 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=38076</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/12/the-camunda-holiday-reading-list-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T02:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a moment sit back and browse these interesting holiday reading recommendations from Camunda colleagues and our community.
The post The Camunda Holiday Reading List 2021 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Quick AKS Cluster the Easy Way with Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/build-a-quick-aks-cluster-the-easy-way-with-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/build-a-quick-aks-cluster-the-easy-way-with-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Find providers in HashiCorp Terraform Cloud to help quickly spin up Kubernetes containers in Microsoft’s Azure Kubernetes Service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 7th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/07/this-week-in-spring-december-7th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/07/this-week-in-spring-december-7th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We’ve got a ton of stuff to dive into so let’s get goin’! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: DataStax’s Christopher Bradford on the Apache Cassandra operator for Kubernetes, K8ssandra

  
Accelerate Spring Apps to Cloud at Scale - Discussion with Azure Spring Cloud Customers

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.2.1 available now

  
Spring Cloud 2021.0.0 (codename Jubilee) Has Been Released

  
Spring Cloud Function 3.2 is out!

  
Spring Cloud Sleuth 3.1.0 is out!

  
Spring Tips: @Controllers and RSocket

  
JSON:API for Spring HATEOAS

  
Living with Kubernetes: 12 Commands to Debug Your Workloads

  
Hmm. I wonder what Mark Paluch’s cooking something awesome with the R2DBC SPI. I wonder what…?

  
Nice job, Github Actions! There’s now integrated sigstore support! Safeguard your containers with new container signing capability in GitHub Actions

  
Pull Request #762 adds Knative for incubation at CNCF - hurray!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Vision Transformer Efficiency and Accuracy by Learning to Tokenize]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/improving-vision-transformer-efficiency.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/improving-vision-transformer-efficiency.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T17:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Michael Ryoo, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google and Anurag Arnab, Research Scientist, Google Research 
Transformer models consistently obtain state-of-the-art results in computer vision tasks, including object detection and video classification. In contrast to standard convolutional approaches that process images pixel-by-pixel, the Vision Transformers (ViT) treat an image as a sequence of patch tokens (i.e., a smaller part, or “patch”, of an image made up of multiple pixels). This means that at every layer, a ViT model recombines and processes patch tokens based on relations between each pair of tokens, using multi-head self-attention. In doing so, ViT models have the capability to construct a global representation of the entire image. 
At the input-level, the tokens are fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Sleuth 3.1.0 is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/07/spring-cloud-sleuth-3-1-0-is-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/07/spring-cloud-sleuth-3-1-0-is-out"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of the Spring Cloud 2021.0.0 (aka Jubilee) release train we’re more than happy to announce the general availability of Spring Cloud Sleuth 3.1.0. In this blog post we’ll describe the most notable released features.

Here is the list of most notable features, we’ll elaborate on them in the subsequent parts of this post.


  
JDBC #1930

  
Tomcat Valve #1329

  
Spring Vault #1952

  
Automatic tag table generation for documentation #1950

  
Spring Cloud Deployer #1947

  
R2DBC #1524

  
Kafka #2013 and Reactor Kafka #1708

  
Spring TX #1941

  
Spring Batch #1904

  
RSocket #1677

  
Spring Cloud Task #1903

  
Spring Cloud Config #1915

  
Spring Cloud CircuitBreaker Reactive #1910

  
Cassandra #1974

  
Spring Session #1961

  
Spring Security #201…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new: an introduction to automation mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.1-automation-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.1-automation-mesh"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the most recent Ansible Automation Platform 2.1 release announced December 2, 2021, we are excited to debut one of the most long-awaited features of the release: automation mesh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at NeurIPS 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/google-at-neurips-2021.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/google-at-neurips-2021.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T19:38:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jaqui Herman and Cat Armato, Program Managers 
This week marks the beginning of the 35th annual Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS 2021), the biggest machine learning conference of the year. NeurIPS 2021 will be held virtually and includes invited talks, demonstrations and presentations of some of the latest in machine learning research. This year, NeurIPS also announced a new Datasets and Benchmarks track, which will include publications, talks, posters, and discussions related to this research area.   
 Google will have a strong presence with more than 170 accepted papers, additionally contributing to and learning from the broader academic research community via talks, posters, workshops, and tutorials. You can learn more about our work being presented…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confluent, JFrog, and ServiceNow Integrations Highlight Additions to the Vault Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/confluent-jfrog-servicenow-integrations-highlight-additions-vault-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/confluent-jfrog-servicenow-integrations-highlight-additions-vault-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A pair of new HCP Vault verified integrations and ten new self-managed HashiCorp Vault integrations add to the existing list of more than 100 partner Vault integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.12.03]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62907</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-12-03/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T11:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! I am Jay Gordon and every week I try to bring you the latest updates from around the DevOps on Azure community. If you have a post you’d like to have me include, I am always listening. You can reach out on Twitter or LinkedIn and I will be sure to share your latest post with the community.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.12.03 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第199話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496631846058</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496631846058"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: DataStax's Christopher Bradford on the Apache Cassandra operator for Kubernetes, K8ssandra]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/a-bootiful-podcast-datastax-s-christopher-bradford-on-the-apache-cassandra-operator-for-kubernetes-k8ssandra</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/a-bootiful-podcast-datastax-s-christopher-bradford-on-the-apache-cassandra-operator-for-kubernetes-k8ssandra"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to DataStax’s Christopher Bradford on the Apache Cassandra operator for Kubernetes, K8ssandra.


  
KubeCon Talk blogpost part 1

  
KubeCon Talk blogpost part 2

  
We Pushed Helm to the Limit, then Built a Kubernetes Operator 

  
A Case for Databases on Kubernetes from a Former Skeptic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.0 (codename Jubilee) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-codename-jubilee-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-codename-jubilee-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce the General Availability of the Spring Cloud 2021.0 Release Train, codename Jubilee, is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2021.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0 Release Train

2021.0.0 is compatible with Spring Boot 2.6.1

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Support for per LoadBalancer configuration properties (added as well to Gateway, Contract and OpenFeign).


Spring Cloud Config


  
Integration with AWS Secrets Manager, AWS Parameter Store and GCP Secret Manager.


Spring Cloud Function


  
Support for gRPC, FunctionCatalog via actuator endpoint, AWS improvements, Clo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Function 3.2 is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/spring-cloud-function-3-2-is-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/spring-cloud-function-3-2-is-out"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.0 is finally out and with it you have Spring Cloud Function 3.2

While the full list of features, enhancements and bug fixes is available here, I’d like to call out few of them in this post and provide some details.
gRPC Support

In addition to an already existing support for invoking function via AWS Lambda, RSocket, Spring Cloud Stream etc., Spring Cloud Function now allows you to invoke function via gRPC.
Two ways to benefit from it. 
Spring Message

Given the wide adaption of Spring Messaging, one way of benefiting from gRPC support is by embracing Spring’s Message.
Spring Cloud Function provides GrpcSpringMessage schema modeled after Spring’s Message. It is internally converted to Spring Message to benefit from all of the existing support for Spring Messaging. 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluating Syntactic Abilities of Language Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/evaluating-syntactic-abilities-of.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/evaluating-syntactic-abilities-of.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jason Wei, AI Resident and Dan Garrette, Research Scientist, Google Research  
In recent years, pre-trained language models, such as BERT and GPT-3, have seen widespread use in natural language processing (NLP). By training on large volumes of text, language models acquire broad knowledge about the world, achieving strong performance on various NLP benchmarks. These models, however, are often opaque in that it may not be clear why they perform so well, which limits further hypothesis-driven improvement of the models. Hence, a new line of scientific inquiry has arisen: what linguistic knowledge is contained in these models? 
 While there are many types of linguistic knowledge that one may want to investigate, a topic that provides a strong basis for analysis is the subject–verb ag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – FreeRTOS Extended Maintenance Plan for Up to 10 Years]]></title>
        <id>7d40e463227e81077de707dea4aea2845e47e6b2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-freertos-extended-maintenance-plan-for-up-to-10-years/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last AWS re:Invent 2020, we announced FreeRTOS Long Term Support (LTS) that offers a more stable foundation than standard releases, as manufacturers deploy and later update devices in the field. FreeRTOS is an open source, real-time operating system for microcontrollers that makes small, low-power edge devices easy to program, deploy, secure, connect, and manage. In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS re:Post – A Reimagined Q&A Experience for the AWS Community]]></title>
        <id>52c5a244baa151c58d56f8df62c2df1d96c3c3b5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-repost-a-reimagined-qa-experience-for-the-aws-community/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet is an excellent resource for well-intentioned guidance and answers. However, it can sometimes be hard to tell if what you’re reading is, in fact, advice you should follow. Also, some users have a preference toward using a single, trusted online community rather than the open internet to provide them with reliable, vetted, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Sustainability Pillar for AWS Well-Architected Framework]]></title>
        <id>f1fac23aefd780d5623728bb3569f0b331f5fa54</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/sustainability-pillar-well-architected-framework/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Well-Architected Framework has been helping AWS customers improve their cloud architectures since 2015. The framework consists of design principles, questions, and best practices across multiple pillars: Operational Excellence, Security, Reliability, Performance Efficiency, and Cost Optimization. Today we are introducing a new Sustainability Pillar to help organizations learn, measure, and improve their workloads using […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Casalboni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of Construct Hub and AWS Cloud Development Kit Version 2]]></title>
        <id>baeea21fcb7d874432a757c3ba44fce9acd8b91b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-general-availability-of-construct-hub-and-aws-cloud-development-kit-version-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T17:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to announce that both the Construct Hub and AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) version 2 are now generally available (GA). The AWS CDK is an open-source framework that simplifies working with cloud resources using familiar programming languages: C#, TypeScript, Java, Python, and Go (in developer preview). Within their applications, developers create […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Azure Static Web Apps in Azure Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62906</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/automating-azure-static-web-apps-in-azure-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T16:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Static Web Apps were launched earlier in 2021 and out of the box they had the capability to integrate your existing repository and deploy your Static Web App from Azure DevOps. You can reference the full getting started guide for the end-to-end deployment setup.
The post Automating Azure Static Web Apps in Azure Pipelines appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use New Amazon EC2 M1 Mac Instances to Build & Test Apps for iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple Watch, and Apple TV]]></title>
        <id>699ccea03204f481929c95c6a5aa2c90f42d3171</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-amazon-ec2-m1-mac-instances-to-build-test-macos-ios-ipados-tvos-and-watchos-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T16:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year at AWS re:Invent, Jeff Barr wrote about the exciting availability of Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) Mac instances. Today, we’re announcing the preview of a new EC2 M1 Mac instance. The introduction of EC2 Mac instances brought the flexibility, scalability, and cost benefits of AWS to all Apple developers. EC2 Mac instances […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Behind the IT Transformation of Covéa Insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=37914</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/12/the-secret-behind-the-it-transformation-of-covea-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get details on how solutions built with Camunda enabled Covea to organize data more effectively and create an even-stronger user experience.
The post The Secret Behind the IT Transformation of Covéa Insurance appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce the general availability of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1. This is the follow-on to the Ansible Automation Platform 2.0 Early Access released this summer, and announced at AnsibleFest 2021. Red Ansible Automation Platform 2.1 introduces major features that allow customers to onboard more easily with even more flexible automation architectures and use cases. Ansible Automation Platform 2.1 is the culmination of many years of reimagining how enterprise automators automate for today and tomorrow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 62 – Supercharge your Java Apps on Azure with @rorypreddy]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62880</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-62-supercharge-your-java-apps-on-azure-with-rorypreddy/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T10:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a short break for some Microsoft streaming events, AzureFunBytes returns to LearnTV for another fun conversation about the products, people, and services that make for a delightful Azure experience.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 62 – Supercharge your Java Apps on Azure with @rorypreddy appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Site-to-Site Connectivity with AWS Direct Connect SiteLink]]></title>
        <id>55ab2625372c8e72c8276741e6a5057f4a9040ab</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-site-to-site-connectivity-with-aws-direct-connect-sitelink/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are launching AWS Direct Connect SiteLink, a new capability of AWS Direct Connect that lets you create connections between your on-premises networks through the AWS global network backbone. Until today, when you needed direct connectivity between your data centers or branch offices, you had to rely on public internet or expensive and hard-to-deploy fixed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Enhanced Dead-letter Queue Management Experience for Amazon SQS Standard Queues]]></title>
        <id>8644204a7230b8ce822a50054999a4a95a9027bb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/enhanced-dlq-management-sqs/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:29:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hundreds of thousands of customers use Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS) to build message-based applications to decouple and scale microservices, distributed systems, and serverless apps. When a message cannot be successfully processed by the queue consumer, you can configure SQS to store it in a dead-letter queue (DLQ). As a software developer or architect, you’d […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Casalboni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Address Management and Auditing at Scale with Amazon VPC IP Address Manager]]></title>
        <id>91077886bb96f2e3b9a037e2c2d884a56171b3cb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/network-address-management-and-auditing-at-scale-with-amazon-vpc-ip-address-manager/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:25:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing, monitoring, and auditing IP address allocation for at-scale networks, as the growth in cloud workloads and connected devices continues at a rapid pace, is a complex, time-consuming, and potentially error-prone task. Traditionally, network administrators have resorted to using combinations of spreadsheets, home-grown tools, and scripts to track address assignments across multiple accounts, virtual private […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon VPC Network Access Analyzer]]></title>
        <id>82f2efc595c375405b34fa67c8fc70587c4a2d27</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-vpc-network-access-analyzer/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a member of your organization’s networking, cloud operations, or security teams, you are going to love this new feature. The new Amazon VPC Network Access Analyzer helps you identify network configurations that lead to unintended network access. As you will see in a moment, it will point out ways that you can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Shield Advanced Update – Automatic Application Layer DDoS Mitigation]]></title>
        <id>25af4ed6c26e6c324812d06b1d417d07416f6636</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-shield-advanced-update-automatic-application-layer-ddos-mitigation/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2016, we launched AWS Shield, a managed Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection service that safeguards applications running on AWS. AWS Shield provides always-on detection and automatic inline mitigations that minimize application downtime and latency without needing to contact AWS Support. There are two tiers of AWS Shield: Standard and Advanced. All AWS customers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RLDS: An Ecosystem to Generate, Share, and Use Datasets in Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/rlds-ecosystem-to-generate-share-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/rlds-ecosystem-to-generate-share-and.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sabela Ramos, Software Engineer and Léonard Hussenot, Student Researcher, Google Research, Brain Team 
Most reinforcement learning (RL) and sequential decision making algorithms require an agent to generate training data through large amounts of interactions with their environment to achieve optimal performance. This is highly inefficient, especially when generating those interactions is difficult, such as collecting data with a real robot or by interacting with a human expert. This issue can be mitigated by reusing external sources of knowledge, for example, the RL Unplugged Atari dataset, which includes data of a synthetic agent playing Atari games.  
 However, there are very few of these datasets and a variety of tasks and ways of generating data in sequential decision making …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Scholarship Program Helps Underrepresented and Underserved Students Prep for Careers in AI and ML]]></title>
        <id>36dd9d3bf20f530368ca29c6cf90d04d91dc31f4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-scholarship-program-helps-underrepresented-and-underserved-students-prep-for-careers-in-ai-and-ml/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a woman working in information technology (IT) for many years, it has always been close to my heart to challenge long-standing gender stereotypes and inspire more young learners to consider a career in tech. With artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) defining the future of technology, this future also depends on diverse representation. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now in Preview – Amazon SageMaker Studio Lab, a Free Service to Learn and Experiment with ML]]></title>
        <id>1927d6ce6648e935cc728859b8d14b9d628b7745</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-in-preview-amazon-sagemaker-studio-lab-a-free-service-to-learn-and-experiment-with-ml/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our mission at AWS is to make machine learning (ML) more accessible. Through many conversations over the past years, I learned about barriers that many ML beginners face. Existing ML environments are often too complex for beginners, or too limited to support modern ML experimentation. Beginners want to quickly start learning and not worry about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon SageMaker Inference Recommender]]></title>
        <id>57696c6a1a2c6cfda41e948287037f5b21ead2e8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-sagemaker-inference-recommender/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re pleased to announce Amazon SageMaker Inference Recommender — a brand-new Amazon SageMaker Studio capability that automates load testing and optimizes model performance across machine learning (ML) instances. Ultimately, it reduces the time it takes to get ML models from development to production and optimizes the costs associated with their operation. Until now, no […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean M. Tracey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Introducing SageMaker Training Compiler]]></title>
        <id>9062a6f94e60c2751154482eb447547bf95806bb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-introducing-sagemaker-training-compiler/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re pleased to announce Amazon SageMaker Training Compiler, a new Amazon SageMaker capability that can accelerate the training of deep learning (DL) models by up to 50%. As DL models grow in complexity, so too does the time it can take to optimize and train them. For example, it can take 25,000 GPU-hours to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean M. Tracey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Create and Manage EMR Clusters and Spark Jobs with Amazon SageMaker Studio]]></title>
        <id>15e2986b6ad7e2ed810c28b51458fd55c9ec0c01</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-create-and-manage-emr-clusters-and-spark-jobs-with-amazon-sagemaker-studio/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re very excited to offer three new enhancements to our Amazon SageMaker Studio service. As of now, users of SageMaker Studio can create, terminate, manage, discover, and connect to Amazon EMR clusters running within a single AWS account and in shared accounts across an organization—all directly from SageMaker Studio. Furthermore, SageMaker Studio Notebook users […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean M. Tracey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth Plus – Create Training Datasets Without Code or In-house Resources]]></title>
        <id>90908fa995f0be9abc2109eedc874cd9fc8553ef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-sagemaker-ground-truth-plus/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re pleased to announce the latest service in the Amazon SageMaker suite that will make labeling datasets easier than ever before. Ground Truth Plus is a turn-key service that uses an expert workforce to deliver high-quality training datasets fast, and reduces costs by up to 40 percent. The Challenges of Machine Learning Model Creation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean M. Tracey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New DynamoDB Table Class – Save Up To 60% in Your DynamoDB Costs]]></title>
        <id>0ca1e66606cb25277f37424382ba8f4fc650c532</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-dynamodb-table-class-save-up-to-60-in-your-dynamodb-costs/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing Amazon DynamoDB Standard-Infrequent Access (DynamoDB Standard-IA). A new table class for DynamoDB that reduces storage costs by 60 percent compared to existing DynamoDB Standard tables, and that delivers the same performance, durability, and scaling. Nowadays, many customers are moving their infrequently accessed data between DynamoDB and Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon RDS Custom for SQL Server Is Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>0a304ebf551106001072e05ee8faa86c88be77c3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-rds-custom-for-sql-server-is-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 26, 2021, we launched Amazon RDS Custom for Oracle, a managed database service for applications that require customization of the underlying operating system and database environment. RDS Custom lets you access and customize your database server host and operating system, for example, by applying special patches and changing the database software settings to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon DevOps Guru for RDS to Detect, Diagnose, and Resolve Amazon Aurora-Related Issues using ML]]></title>
        <id>0babac98dfd335531b1699c60e9d6bf5ef545aec</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-devops-guru-for-rds-to-detect-diagnose-and-resolve-amazon-aurora-related-issues-using-ml/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing Amazon DevOps Guru for RDS, a new capability for Amazon DevOps Guru. It allows developers to easily detect, diagnose, and resolve performance and operational issues in Amazon Aurora. Hundreds of thousands of customers nowadays are using Amazon Aurora because it is highly available, scalable, and durable. But as applications grow in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MURAL: Multimodal, Multi-task Retrieval Across Languages]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/mural-multimodal-multi-task-retrieval.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/mural-multimodal-multi-task-retrieval.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T21:03:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Aashi Jain, AI Resident and Yinfei Yang, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research    
For many concepts, there is no direct one-to-one translation from one language to another, and even when there is, such translations often carry different associations and connotations that are easily lost for a non-native speaker. In such cases, however, the meaning may be more obvious when grounded in visual examples. Take, for instance, the word "wedding". In English, one often associates a bride in a white dress and a groom in a tuxedo, but when translated into Hindi (शादी), a more appropriate association may be a bride wearing vibrant colors and a groom wearing a sherwani. What each person associates with the word may vary considerably, but if they are shown an image of the intended concep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecating weak cryptographic standards (TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1) in Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62891</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deprecating-weak-cryptographic-standards-tls-1-0-and-tls-1-1-in-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T19:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to the potential for future protocol downgrade attacks and other Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocol versions 1.0 and 1.1 vulnerabilities not specific to Microsoft’s implementation, it is required that dependencies on all security protocols older than TLS 1.2 be removed wherever possible.
The post Deprecating weak cryptographic standards (TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1) in Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Ramamurthy (MSFT)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Teams with AWS on New Control Tower Account Factory for Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-teams-with-aws-on-new-control-tower-account-factory-for-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-teams-with-aws-on-new-control-tower-account-factory-for-terraform"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T23:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Control Tower Account Factory for HashiCorp Terraform (AFT), the evolution of Terraform Landing Zones, offers an easy way to set up and govern a secure, multi-account AWS environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AWS Provider Continues to Expand Coverage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-aws-provider-continues-to-expand-coverage</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-aws-provider-continues-to-expand-coverage"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During 2021, HashiCorp and Amazon Web Services have partnered to bring hundreds of new services and features to the Terraform providers for AWS and AWS Cloud Control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Boards Ux Modernization – Public Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62857</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-boards-ux-modernization-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T16:41:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team is excited to release the public preview of the Ux modernization for Azure Boards! The web platform has been updated to provide a faster Ux, consistency with other parts of the product, and accessibility compliance.
The post Azure Boards Ux Modernization – Public Preview appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第198話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496620290741</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496620290741"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Developing Java Apps is Easier with a Process Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=37672</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/how-developing-java-apps-is-easier-with-a-process-engine/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how using Camunda’s process engine in your Java application will make development easier and save you time. 
The post How Developing Java Apps is Easier with a Process Engine appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DiscoverDev - curated engineering articles for Wed, 24 Nov 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://discoverdev.io/archive/2021-11-24.html</id>
        <link href="http://discoverdev.io/archive/2021-11-24.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CarbonJ: A high performance, high-scale, drop-in replacement for carbon-cache and carbon-relay 
 
          
            
 Mobile Performance @ Lyft 
 
          
            
 Presentation: eBPF - Superpowers for Cloud Native Operations 
 
          
            
 How do CRDTs solve distributed data consistency challenges? 
 
          
            
 Grammar Correction as You Type, on Pixel 6]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at AWS re:Invent: Breakouts, Experts, Demos, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-breakouts-experts-demos-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-breakouts-experts-demos-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit us at AWS re:Invent 2021 in Las Vegas, Nov. 29 - Dec. 3 for breakout sessions, expert talks, and product demos to accelerate your cloud strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Superpowers for Next Level Microservices Orchestration Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=37690</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/3-superpowers-for-next-level-microservices-orchestration-recap/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the questions we didn't have time to answer at the recent 3 Superpowers for Next Level Microservices Orchestration webinar 
The post 3 Superpowers for Next Level Microservices Orchestration Recap appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 2022 will be the year for edge automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/2022-the-year-for-edge-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/2022-the-year-for-edge-automation"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T19:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seamlessly, every single day, we wake up and check our health statistics in smart watches, scan QR codes to validate information, pay using credit cards in different locations, use surveillance cameras to record our neighborhoods, and connect our smartphones to distributed WiFi access points in our restaurants or coffee shops. According to the Statista, in the Forecast number of mobile users worldwide 2020-2025[1] report, the number of mobile users worldwide reached 7.1 billion in 2021, and this number is projected to grow. This initiates a new set of use cases for edge devices due to the explosive growth of network-connected entry points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predicting Text Selections with Federated Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/predicting-text-selections-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/predicting-text-selections-with.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:21:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Florian Hartmann, Software Engineer, Google Research 
Smart Text Selection, launched in 2017 as part of Android O, is one of Android’s most frequently used features, helping users select, copy, and use text easily and quickly by predicting the desired word or set of words around a user’s tap, and automatically expanding the selection appropriately. Through this feature, selections are automatically expanded, and for selections with defined classification types, e.g., addresses and phone numbers, users are offered an app with which to open the selection, saving users even more time. 

  Today we describe how we have improved the performance of Smart Text Selection by using federated learning to train the neural network model on user interactions responsibly while preserving user p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.7 Brings New Automated Host Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-7</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary 0.7 adds support for partner plugins, dynamic host catalogs, UI support for managed groups and resource filtering, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>