<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-01-03T01:23:16.731Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-03T01:23:16.731Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtually no one]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43488</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723385438/0/sethsblog~Virtually-no-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compared to the overall population, virtually no one built Wikipedia, virtually no one voted for that senator and virtually no one starts a business. Virtually no one cares enough to help a stranger in need, and virtually no one leads the way. And that’s okay. Because virtually no one is enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: Alpha support for cross-namespace storage data sources]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/02/cross-namespace-data-sources-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/02/cross-namespace-data-sources-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Takafumi Takahashi (Hitachi Vantara)
Kubernetes v1.26, released last month, introduced an alpha feature that
lets you specify a data source for a PersistentVolumeClaim, even where the source
data belong to a different namespace.
With the new feature enabled, you specify a namespace in the dataSourceRef field of
a new PersistentVolumeClaim. Once Kubernetes checks that access is OK, the new
PersistentVolume can populate its data from the storage source specified in that other
namespace.
Before Kubernetes v1.26, provided your cluster had the AnyVolumeDataSource feature enabled,
you could already provision new volumes from a data source in the same
namespace.
However, that only worked for the data source in the same namespace,
therefore users couldn't provision a PersistentVolume with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arguing for inaction]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43422</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723339578/0/sethsblog~Arguing-for-inaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[…is surprisingly easy. “We’ve done all this work and things haven’t gotten better,” so, apparently, we should stop trying and go back to what we were doing. “We’ve done all this work and things are getting better,” so that means that there’s no need to keep trying and we can go back to what we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[年賀イラスト] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190247049337281</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190247049337281"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The world as it is]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43643</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723296176/0/sethsblog~The-world-as-it-is/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one sees reality. It’s worth repeating: No one accurately sees the world as it is. A person with hearing loss doesn’t experience the world the same way a synesthete does. A rock climber doesn’t see a steep slope the same way an elderly person does. And an optimist and a pessimist rarely experience opportunities […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning in the new year]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44501</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723268578/0/sethsblog~Learning-in-the-new-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T19:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[86,000 people have taken my Udemy courses over the last few years, and the first week of January is always a good time to lean in and learn. These are self-paced, video lectures. Udemy is offering the Modern Marketing course at 25% off for the next few weeks. The course for freelancers is my most […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub and the Ekoparty 2022 Capture the Flag]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-30-github-and-the-ekoparty-2022-capture-the-flag/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-30-github-and-the-ekoparty-2022-capture-the-flag/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T17:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the design behind, and solutions to, several of GitHub’s CTF challenge for Ekoparty’s 2022 event!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logic is a special case]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44286</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723243042/0/sethsblog~Logic-is-a-special-case/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T09:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We agree on so many things. Productive arguments are scarce, because they depend on shared constructs of reality. And arguments are a luxury, because they allow people to engage around ideas without resorting to external forces or authorities for resolution. An argument might be flawed because it relies on facts that aren’t in evidence. If […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Year's Eve Party]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2718/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2718/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/new_years_eve_party.png" title="[Earlier, at the eye doctor] 'No, for the last time, the numerals on the paper aren't my prescription, it's the shape I want you to make with the laser.'" alt="[Earlier, at the eye doctor] 'No, for the last time, the numerals on the paper aren't my prescription, it's the shape I want you to make with the laser.'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: Advancements in Kubernetes Traffic Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/30/advancements-in-kubernetes-traffic-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/30/advancements-in-kubernetes-traffic-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Andrew Sy Kim (Google)
Kubernetes v1.26 includes significant advancements in network traffic engineering with the graduation of
two features (Service internal traffic policy support, and EndpointSlice terminating conditions) to GA,
and a third feature (Proxy terminating endpoints) to beta. The combination of these enhancements aims
to address short-comings in traffic engineering that people face today, and unlock new capabilities for the future.
Traffic Loss from Load Balancers During Rolling Updates
Prior to Kubernetes v1.26, clusters could experience loss of traffic
from Service load balancers during rolling updates when setting the externalTrafficPolicy field to Local.
There are a lot of moving parts at play here so a quick overview of how Kubernetes manages load balancers migh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub’s top 10 blog posts of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-29-githubs-top-10-blog-posts-of-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-29-githubs-top-10-blog-posts-of-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-29T17:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the year winds down, we're highlighting some of the incredible work from GitHub’s engineers, product teams, and security researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insightful data is called information]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44466</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723184500/0/sethsblog~Insightful-data-is-called-information/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-29T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is everywhere around us, and most of it is simply noise. The purpose of information is to inform, to help us change our minds. Information has a point of view, it’s useful. It turns data into actionable truth. Getting more data isn’t the hard part. Turning it into information is. About a year ago, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: DaShaun Carter: amazing human being, father, friend, engineer, and fellow Spring Developer Advocate]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/29/a-bootiful-podcast-dashaun-carter-amazing-human-being-father-friend-engineer-and-fellow-spring-developer-advocate</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/29/a-bootiful-podcast-dashaun-carter-amazing-human-being-father-friend-engineer-and-fellow-spring-developer-advocate"/>
        <updated>2022-12-29T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! this episode, we turn it to 11 and ring in the new year with a fantastic human being, father, friend, engineer, and fellow Spring Developer Advocate: DaShaun Carter (@dashaun). 

Happy new year!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Job Tracking, to Support Massively Parallel Batch Workloads, Is Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/29/scalable-job-tracking-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/29/scalable-job-tracking-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Aldo Culquicondor (Google)
The Kubernetes 1.26 release includes a stable implementation of the Job
controller that can reliably track a large amount of Jobs with high levels of
parallelism. SIG Apps
and WG Batch
have worked on this foundational improvement since Kubernetes 1.22. After
multiple iterations and scale verifications, this is now the default
implementation of the Job controller.
Paired with the Indexed completion mode,
the Job controller can handle massively parallel batch Jobs, supporting up to
100k concurrent Pods.
The new implementation also made possible the development of Pod failure policy,
which is in beta in the 1.26 release.
How do I use this feature?
To use Job tracking with finalizers, upgrade to Kubernetes 1.25 or newer and
create new Jobs. You can also use …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2022.3.1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=310298</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/12/2022-3-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T22:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can get the latest version from our website, via the Toolbox App, from inside the IDE, or by using snaps if you’re a Ubuntu user. Here are the most notable improvements in the new version: The option to display editor tabs on multiple rows is available in the new UI. [IDEA-295095] Actions on Save […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.3.1 is released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=310266</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/12/phpstorm-2022-3-1-is-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T17:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first bug-fix update for PhpStorm 2022.3 is now available. You can update to it using the Toolbox App or right from inside the IDE. You can also download PhpStorm 2022.3.1 from the website. Notable changes in this update: The option to display editor tabs on multiple rows is available in the new UI [IDEA-295095]. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda community values]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=70025&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=70025</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/camunda-community-values/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the values that represent the culture and beliefs of our Camunda community. Thank you for being a part of it!
The post Camunda community values appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Alcantara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All jokes are inside jokes]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43484</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723122678/0/sethsblog~All-jokes-are-inside-jokes/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone’s not going to get it. That doesn’t mean it wasn’t funny to you. It simply means that culture works because, for a moment, a group of people share a history, an understanding and a point of view. When a design or a song or a riff fails, it might be because there weren’t enough […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[L6 Lagrange Point]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2717/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2717/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/l6_lagrange_point.png" title="It's difficult to orbit L6 stably due to gravitational perturbation from Akron and Toledo." alt="It's difficult to orbit L6 stably due to gravitational perturbation from Akron and Toledo." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scale and the small business (freelancer grid)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43477</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723068082/0/sethsblog~Scale-and-the-small-business-freelancer-grid/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T10:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The industry giants want tonnage. Undifferentiated, commodity-priced, regularly delivered, consistent work for hire. They’re not going out of their way for freelancers that are bespoke, artisanal or even ‘better.’ They simply want to meet spec at the best price. They can keep you very busy, and they might even pay on time. There are a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring  - Happy New Year 2023 edition - December 27th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/27/this-week-in-spring-happy-new-year-2023-edition-december-27th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/27/this-week-in-spring-happy-new-year-2023-edition-december-27th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! It’s 27 December as I write this and - being honest - I couldn’t be happier. It’s raining outside. I’m in a warm cozy office. Good music is playing. People are asleep in my home. I can hear the raindrops and wind outside the window. I’m at peace as I code. And code I have. I’ve been updating my blog, and a half dozen little side projects, to the new Spring Boot 3. This has given me a chance to do a little, shall we say, Spring cleaning, and also update my Github Actions to the latest and greatest. I’m pleasantly surprised by how many builds I’ve switched over to 3.0 and then used the AOT engine to build a GraalVM native image and it just worked! 

How were or are your holidays going? My family and I had a lovely Chris…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.3.1 is released!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=309923</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2022/12/rubymine-2022-3-1-is-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.3 is out! You can get the new build from our website or via the free Toolbox App. The new version includes some important updates, and here are the highlights you need to know about. Find usages of let variables in RSpec shared contexts Find Usages can now help you search for all usages […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iryna Pisklyarova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perf8: Performance metrics for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/perf8-performance-metrics-for-python</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/perf8-performance-metrics-for-python"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perf8 is a tool Enterprise Search has started to develop to standardize the creation of performance reports for its Python applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarek Ziadé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perf8: Performance metrics for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/perf8-performance-metrics-for-python</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/perf8-performance-metrics-for-python"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We're building this neat service in Python to ingest data in Elasticsearch from various sources (MySQL, Network Drive, AWS, etc.) for Enterprise Search.
Sucking data from a third-party service to Elasticsearch is usually an I/O-bound activity. Your code sits on opened sockets and passes data from one end to the other. That's a great use case for an asynchronous application in Python, but it needs to be carefully crafted.
When data flows through that pipeline, we want to ensure we don't blow the available resources (RAM/CPU/FDs). We also want to maximize the output without killing Elasticsearch or the backend service.
So it's all about implementing the right throttling and backpressure safeguards and surfacing the right settings, so you can properly size how aggressive the service will be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarek Ziadé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: CPUManager goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/27/cpumanager-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/27/cpumanager-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author:
Francesco Romani (Red Hat)
The CPU Manager is a part of the kubelet, the Kubernetes node agent, which enables the user to allocate exclusive CPUs to containers.
Since Kubernetes v1.10, where it graduated to Beta, the CPU Manager proved itself reliable and
fulfilled its role of allocating exclusive CPUs to containers, so adoption has steadily grown making it a staple component of performance-critical
and low-latency setups. Over time, most changes were about bugfixes or internal refactoring, with the following noteworthy user-visible changes:
support explicit reservation of CPUs: it was already possible to request to reserve a given
number of CPUs for system resources, including the kubelet itself, which will not be used for exclusive CPU allocation. Now it is possible to also
expli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long is forever?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43583</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723006286/0/sethsblog~How-long-is-forever/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-26T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And how soon is never? Most organizations are fundamentally incapable of planning ten years out. When a company promises to be carbon neutral by 2030, they’re actually saying that they may never be. That’s because almost all the pressures on them are short-term pressures. And it doesn’t help that few people expect to be in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Night Ordering]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2716/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2716/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/game_night_ordering.png" title="One good trick, if you get called on a fake service, is to build a working version of it and mention it again the next week." alt="One good trick, if you get called on a fake service, is to build a working version of it and mention it again the next week." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Pod Scheduling Readiness]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/26/pod-scheduling-readiness-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/26/pod-scheduling-readiness-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Wei Huang (Apple), Abdullah Gharaibeh (Google)
Kubernetes 1.26 introduced a new Pod feature: scheduling gates. In Kubernetes, scheduling gates
are keys that tell the scheduler when a Pod is ready to be considered for scheduling.
What problem does it solve?
When a Pod is created, the scheduler will continuously attempt to find a node that fits it. This
infinite loop continues until the scheduler either finds a node for the Pod, or the Pod gets deleted.
Pods that remain unschedulable for long periods of time (e.g., ones that are blocked on some external event)
waste scheduling cycles. A scheduling cycle may take ≅20ms or more depending on the complexity of
the Pod's scheduling constraints. Therefore, at scale, those wasted cycles significantly impact the
scheduler's performance. See …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our dreaming opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43495</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/722940656/0/sethsblog~Our-dreaming-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-25T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[School and work push us to avoid real dreams. Dreamers are dangerous, impatient and unwilling to tolerate the status quo. Existing systems would prefer we simply fit in. The dreams we need to teach are the dreams of self-reliance and generosity. The only way for us to move forward is to encourage and amplify the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make 2023 the Year of Process Improvement [Recap]]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=70032&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=70032</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/how-to-make-2023-the-year-of-process-improvement-recap/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T21:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what you need to know to make 2023 the year of process improvement. We look back at 2022 and ahead at the key trends coming next year.
The post How to Make 2023 the Year of Process Improvement [Recap] appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What&#8217;s with all the ducks?]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-23-whats-with-all-the-ducks/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-23-whats-with-all-the-ducks/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T17:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What in the world do rubber ducks have to do with programming? And why were they everywhere at GitHub Universe? A lot of you asked, so I’m here to help explain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 0.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/23/spring-modulith-0-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/23/spring-modulith-0-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce the availability of Spring Modulith 0.2. The release adds the following features:


  
We introduced @ApplicationModuleListener to ease the declaration of asynchronous, transactional event listeners that run in a transaction themselves. A model that we recommend as default to integration application modules. (#80, reference documentation)

  
The application module dependency structure is now also exposed as Spring Boot actuator. This allows operating infrastructure to visualize insights it provides to operations teams to be aligned with the application module structure (HTTP traces by module etc.) (#87, reference documentation

  
The Postgres event publication registry schema now follows Postgres best practices. (#81)


The release also contains the obligatory upgrade to Spring Boot 3.0.1. Find more information on the release page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/spring-boot-3-0-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/spring-boot-3-0-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.1 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 54 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pando]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2715/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2715/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/pando.png" title="The presents under the tree are actually a single gift connected by an underground ribbon system." alt="The presents under the tree are actually a single gift connected by an underground ribbon system." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Support for Passing Pod fsGroup to CSI Drivers At Mount Time]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/23/kubernetes-12-06-fsgroup-on-mount/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/23/kubernetes-12-06-fsgroup-on-mount/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Fabio Bertinatto (Red Hat), Hemant Kumar (Red Hat)
Delegation of fsGroup to CSI drivers was first introduced as alpha in Kubernetes 1.22,
and graduated to beta in Kubernetes 1.25.
For Kubernetes 1.26, we are happy to announce that this feature has graduated to
General Availability (GA).
In this release, if you specify a fsGroup in the
security context,
for a (Linux) Pod, all processes in the pod's containers are part of the additional group
that you specified.
In previous Kubernetes releases, the kubelet would always apply the
fsGroup ownership and permission changes to files in the volume according to the policy
you specified in the Pod's .spec.securityContext.fsGroupChangePolicy field.
Starting with Kubernetes 1.26, CSI drivers have the option to apply the fsGroup settings durin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Field CTO and Chief Evangelist at Gradle Justin Reock]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/a-bootiful-podcast-field-cto-and-chief-evangelist-at-gradle-justin-reock</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/a-bootiful-podcast-field-cto-and-chief-evangelist-at-gradle-justin-reock"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans and happy holidays!! In this installment, Josh Long talks to Field CTO and Chief Evangelist at Gradle Justin Reock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.7 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/spring-boot-2-7-7-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/spring-boot-2-7-7-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T18:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.7 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 24 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Ambassador Call for Submissions 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-ambassador-call-for-submissions-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-ambassador-call-for-submissions-2023"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The submission window for HashiCorp Ambassador — our program to recognize individuals for knowledge sharing, mentorship, and kindness in the community — is now open.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.3.2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=309876</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/12/22/datagrip-2022-3-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T14:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! We’ve released the second bug-fix update for DataGrip 2022.3. Here’s what’s been improved: DBE-16825: The default name for created objects is selected so that it’s easy to replace it. DBE-16899: Virtual views are correctly refreshed. DBE-16824: Virtual views can be found via the Search dialog. DBE-15968: [PostgreSQL] Database names with slashes are supported. DBE-16862: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maksim Sobolevskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletproofing Zeebe against concurrency bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69968&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69968</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/bulletproofing-zeebe-concurrency-bugs/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how we test and identify hard-to-find critical bugs in Zeebe, the workflow engine powering Camunda Platform 8, using property-based testing.
The post Bulletproofing Zeebe against concurrency bugs appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepthi Akkoorath</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.3.1 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=309556</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/12/webstorm-2022-3-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T10:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.3.1, the first bug-fix update for WebStorm 2022.3, is now available! It’s packed with improvements, including the fix for the disturbing regression bug with Actions on Save (IDEA-307368). We’ve also fixed several issues with Vue, Vitest, and Angular and added Prisma ORM support. You can update to v2022.3.1 by using the Toolbox App, installing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Ryabukha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The PyCharm 2022.3.1 Release Candidate is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=309777</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/12/2022-3-1-rc/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T08:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This build contains important bug fixes for PyCharm 2022.3. Look through the list of improvements and update to the latest version for a better experience. Download PyCharm 2022.3.1 RC Packaging: PyCharm no longer uses excessive disk space caching PyPI. [PY-57156] HTTP client: Setting a proxy no longer breaks package inspection. [PY-57612] Python console: Code that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2022.3.1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=309746</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2022/12/2022-3-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T08:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2022.3.1 brings you a fix for interpreter widget woes, an uninterrupted onboarding tour, simplified settings sync and code completion for column names in Python scripts.  Download the new version from our website, update directly from the IDE, via the free Toolbox App, or use snaps for Ubuntu. Download DataSpell 2022.3.1 Simplified Settings Sync  Want […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ciara Byrne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: GA Support for Kubelet Credential Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/22/kubelet-credential-providers/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/22/kubelet-credential-providers/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Andrew Sy Kim (Google), Dixita Narang (Google)
Kubernetes v1.26 introduced generally available (GA) support for kubelet credential
provider plugins,
offering an extensible plugin framework to dynamically fetch credentials
for any container image registry.
Background
Kubernetes supports the ability to dynamically fetch credentials for a container registry service.
Prior to Kubernetes v1.20, this capability was compiled into the kubelet and only available for
Amazon Elastic Container Registry, Azure Container Registry, and Google Cloud Container Registry.
 
Figure 1: Kubelet built-in credential provider support for Amazon Elastic Container Registry, Azure Container Registry, and Google Cloud Container Registry.
Kubernetes v1.20 introduced alpha support for kubelet credential provide…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EHR-Safe: Generating High-Fidelity and Privacy-Preserving Synthetic Electronic Health Records]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/ehr-safe-generating-high-fidelity-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/ehr-safe-generating-high-fidelity-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T18:57:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jinsung Yoon and Sercan O. Arik, Research Scientists, Google Research, Cloud AI Team  
Analysis of Electronic Health Records (EHR) has a tremendous potential for enhancing patient care, quantitatively measuring performance of clinical practices, and facilitating clinical research. Statistical estimation and machine learning (ML) models trained on EHR data can be used to predict the probability of various diseases (such as diabetes), track patient wellness, and predict how patients respond to specific drugs. For such models, researchers and practitioners need access to EHR data. However, it can be challenging to leverage EHR data while ensuring data privacy and conforming to patient confidentiality regulations (such as HIPAA).  

Conventional methods to anonymize data (e.g., de-id…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking Forward to 2023 in CLion]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=309719</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/12/looking-forward-towards-2023-in-clion/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T17:40:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has only been a few weeks since the CLion 2022.3 release, which brought a better user experience across the board, from projects with only a couple of C/C++ files to complex CMake-based applications. Today, we are ready to share our product plans for 2023, and especially the upcoming 2023.1 release. This blog post will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Gives 2022: Creating positive, lasting contributions in our communities]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-21-github-gives-2022-creating-positive-lasting-contributions-in-our-communities/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-21-github-gives-2022-creating-positive-lasting-contributions-in-our-communities/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T16:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, we took GitHub Gives, our company-wide giving campaign, to new heights and wanted to share our learnings to provide best practices in programming a successful hybrid giving campaign for employees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.3.1 RC]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=309653</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/12/phpstorm-2022-3-1-rc/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T15:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release candidate build for PhpStorm 2022.3.1 is available. Notable updates since preview build: Editor tabs: return multiple rows [IDEA-295095] Fixed: Vue 3 Setup: Vue TypeScript Service false errors not suppressed in Problems > Project Errors tab [WEB-56403] Vue.js: support type inference for v-slot scope variable [WEB-41084] Fixed: Angular: image paths are incorrectly resolved in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper and Rider 2022.3.1 Bug Fixes Are Here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=309623</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/12/21/resharper-and-rider-2022-3-1-bug-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T15:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, The ReSharper and Rider 2022.3.1 bug-fix releases are now available! Let’s go over the most important updates. ReSharper Here’s a list of the top bug fixes:  Fixed an issue with the screen blinking while typing before and after hints appear (RSRP-490593). Fixed a bug causing a false positive error when using C# 11 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Guest Users in Space]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=309411</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2022/12/21/guest-users/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T15:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Space, a complete software development platform, simplifies team collaboration to help make development more enjoyable. However, development often does not take place exclusively within a single team, or even organization.  To provide more opportunities for collaboration, we’re introducing guest users in Space. You can now invite clients, freelancers, and other external partners to collaborate on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgenia Verbina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best WebStorm Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=308912</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/12/best-webstorm-themes/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T14:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s important you feel comfortable in your IDE. Fortunately, WebStorm is very customizable, so you can configure it how you like. One way to do this is to change the theme you’re using, which will alter the look and feel of the IDE. In this blog post, we’ve put together some of our team’s favorite […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Santa drives his sleigh using Kibana Dashboards!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/santa-drives-his-sleigh-using-kibana-dashboards</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/santa-drives-his-sleigh-using-kibana-dashboards"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how Santa keeps track of his journey to deliver presents across the world? He uses Kibana! In this festive post, learn how Lens, TSVB, and Vega controls can be used to make Santa’s sleigh dashboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Each Elastic office has its own locally-designed mural. See them all.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-each-elastic-office-has-its-own-locally-designed-mural</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-each-elastic-office-has-its-own-locally-designed-mural"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building community is one of our top priorities. We want our employees to feel at home in their local office, so we hired local designers to create murals on the walls of each office to bring to life the essence of each Elastic city.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Santa drives his sleigh using Kibana Dashboards!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/santa-drives-his-sleigh-using-kibana-dashboards</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/santa-drives-his-sleigh-using-kibana-dashboards"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
It’s the festive season. Regardless of whether you believe in Santa or celebrate Christmas or another holiday in December, we can all appreciate the speed at which good ol’ St. Nick flies around the world with his trusty reindeer delivering presents to all the good children.

He’s been doing this job for a long time. But in 2022, his sleigh got an upgrade thanks to Kibana dashboards! He is now able to track the cities he’s visited along the way, the state of his journey, and his cool Christmas playlist.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt710d158fc999aff7/63a1fc518f1f170dcb413236/blog-elastic-dashboard.png,blog-elastic-dashboard.png,
This blog post shares details of building some of the key controls Santa uses to drive his sleigh and track his journey across th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Each Elastic office has its own locally-designed mural. See them all.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-each-elastic-office-has-its-own-locally-designed-mural</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-each-elastic-office-has-its-own-locally-designed-mural"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re a distributed, global company (and proud of it), but we do want to give Elasticisians a place to connect face-to-face should they choose. In fact, building community is one of our top priorities here at Elastic. That’s why we have offices in 15 cities around the world. While some Elasticians use them to work and connect, we also use them to host in-person events, like this summer’s Elasticamp. 

Currently, we have offices in: Amsterdam, Arlington, Austin, Bangalore, Berlin, Chicago, Copenhagen, London, Munich, New York, Paris, San Francisco, Singapore, Sydney, and Tokyo. 

What makes our offices special is that each one is designed with its location in mind. We want our employees to feel at home in their local office, so we hired local designers to create murals on the walls of eac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Awarded the Palo Alto Networks 2022 Global Technology Partner of the Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-awarded-palo-alto-networks-2022-global-technology-partner-of-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-awarded-palo-alto-networks-2022-global-technology-partner-of-year"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp wins the 2022 Palo Alto Networks Global Technology Partner of the Year Award.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differential Privacy Accounting by Connecting the Dots]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/differential-privacy-accounting-by.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/differential-privacy-accounting-by.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T18:29:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Pritish Kamath and Pasin Manurangsi, Research Scientists, Google Research  
Differential privacy (DP) is an approach that enables data analytics and machine learning (ML) with a mathematical guarantee on the privacy of user data.  DP quantifies the “privacy cost” of an algorithm, i.e., the level of guarantee that the algorithm’s output distribution for a given dataset will not change significantly if a single user’s data is added to or removed from it. The algorithm is characterized by two parameters, ε and δ, where smaller values of both indicate “more private”. There is a natural tension between the privacy budget (ε, δ) and the utility of the algorithm: a smaller privacy budget requires the output to be more “noisy”, often leading to less utility. Thus, a fundamental goal of D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase developer productivity, save time on developer onboarding, and drive ROI in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-20-increase-developer-productivity-save-time-on-developer-onboarding-and-drive-roi-in-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-20-increase-developer-productivity-save-time-on-developer-onboarding-and-drive-roi-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forrester's Total Economic Impact™ study dives into how GitHub Enterprise Cloud and GitHub Advanced Security help businesses drive ROI, increase developer productivity, and save time on developer onboarding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not just flightless birds: How EMUs secure and scale identity and access management for your GitHub Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-20-emus-more-than-just-flightless-birds/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-20-emus-more-than-just-flightless-birds/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T18:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise has evolved to support the needs of enterprise administrators, corporate security teams, and individual developers who contribute to open source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contributing to Camunda’s Connector ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69911&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69911</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/contributing-to-camunda-connector-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T17:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can contribute a Connector to Camunda’s Community Hub, either as another partner of ours or as a community member. 
The post Contributing to Camunda’s Connector ecosystem appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we use GitHub to be more productive, collaborative, and secure]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-20-how-we-use-github-to-be-more-productive-collaborative-and-secure/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-20-how-we-use-github-to-be-more-productive-collaborative-and-secure/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our engineering and security teams have done some incredible work in 2022. Let’s take a look at how we use GitHub to be more productive, build collaboratively, and shift security left.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp 2022 Year in Review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2022-year-in-review</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2022-year-in-review"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before we ring in the new year, here’s a look back at some of the most important moments in 2022 for HashiCorp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top 10 Ansible Blogs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/top-10-ansible-blogs-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/top-10-ansible-blogs-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
 
If you're looking to brush up on the most popular Ansible information from 2022 (or just grasping at any excuse to break away from your relatives for a few minutes during the holidays), you've come to the right place. What follows are the top 10 blogs that have captured the most attention from Ansible.com readers in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>trmcconn@redhat.com (Tricia McConnell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 20th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/20/this-week-in-spring-december-20th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/20/this-week-in-spring-december-20th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! It’s the 20th of December, 2022 as I write this, which means that by the time we meet again, here on this humble blog, Tuesday next week, Christmas will already have come and gone. Chanukah is already here! Time is sure flying! So, to those of you who celebrate: Happy Chanukah, Merry Christmas, and happy holidays! 

There’s arguably nothing better than the gift of knowledge, so let’s dive right into this week’s roundup:


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft’s Brian Benz on the state of Java, Microsoft, Azure, and so much more

  
Spring Framework 6.0.3 available now

  
Spring Security 6.0.1, 5.8.1, 5.7.6 and 5.6.10 available now

  
Spring for Apache Pulsar 0.1.0 available now

  
Spring for GraphQL 1.1.1 released

  
Fixing the No Main Manifest Attribute in Spring Boot

  
Oracle has a nice post: Go Native with Spring Boot 3 and GraalVM

  
Baeldung has an interesting tutorial on Pinpoint, which looks to be a large APM suite with some interesting capabilities.

  
[Stream Large Byte[] to File With WebClient](https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/722459996/0/baeldung~Stream-Large-Byte-to-File-With-WebClient)

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Alpha API For Dynamic Resource Allocation

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Device Manager graduates to GA

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Introducing Validating Admission Policies

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Non-Graceful Node Shutdown Moves to Beta

  
Running Multiple Thread Groups in JMeter

  
Extract Values using AssertJ in Java

  
Interesting, and well worth bookmarking: how to build a statically linked or mostly-statically linked native executable with GraalVM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.1.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/20/spring-for-graphql-1-1-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/20/spring-for-graphql-1-1-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T10:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pleased to announce that Spring for GraphQL 1.1.1 is now available on Maven Central.

This first maintenance release in the 1.1.x generation includes 19 fixes and documentation improvements. This version will be shipped with Spring Boot 3.0.1, to be released later this week.
How can you help?

If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-graphql tag.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing search to advance equity in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/harnessing-search-to-advance-equity-in-healthcare</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/harnessing-search-to-advance-equity-in-healthcare"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores how Elastic’s search capabilities can help address potential barriers to health equity, specifically by utilizing NLP and search analytics to support Medicare beneficiaries with limited English proficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isra Sunhachawi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Log monitoring and unstructured log data, moving beyond tail -f]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-monitoring-management-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-monitoring-management-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Log data and system logs can be a treasure trove of information and insights for SREs and DevOps team with the right tools. Take a dive into the Elastic Platform, a leader in log management and monitoring capabilities, based on the proven ELK stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Wintergerst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing search to advance equity in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/harnessing-search-to-advance-equity-in-healthcare</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/harnessing-search-to-advance-equity-in-healthcare"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As more productive and healthy populations live longer, healthcare will be one of the most important aspects of society. The COVID-19 pandemic has accelerated adoption of modern technologies and shined a light on the importance of patient experiences. As more consumers are taking control of their data, healthcare systems are getting stretched. According to a study published by Deloitte and the Scottsdale Institute, 92% of healthcare technology leaders see digital capabilities as a path to achieve better patient experience.

In this blog post, we’ll explore how Elastic’s search capabilities can help address potential barriers to health equity, as outlined in the Center for Medicare & Medicaid Services (CMS) strategic pillars — specifically, how to deliver relevant results for healthcare i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isra Sunhachawi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Log monitoring and unstructured log data, moving beyond tail -f]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-monitoring-management-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-monitoring-management-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Log files and system logs have been a treasure trove of information for administrators and developers for decades. But with more moving parts and ever more options on where to run modern cloud applications, keeping an eye on logs and troubleshooting problems have become increasingly difficult. 

While it’s often possible to ssh into a server and run commands like tail -f, this approach doesn’t scale for most developers and administrators. Even if you’re good on the command line, you might be able to find what you’re looking for in a log file using awk and grep and could even calculate some simple statistics around how often certain errors occur. But what if the applications are running across hundreds of servers or Kubernetes pods? Or even worse, what if the applications are split across…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Wintergerst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Introducing Validating Admission Policies]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/20/validating-admission-policies-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/20/validating-admission-policies-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Joe Betz (Google), Cici Huang (Google)
In Kubernetes 1.26, the 1st alpha release of validating admission policies is
available!
Validating admission policies use the Common Expression
Language (CEL) to offer a declarative,
in-process alternative to validating admission
webhooks.
CEL was first introduced to Kubernetes for the Validation rules for
CustomResourceDefinitions.
This enhancement expands the use of CEL in Kubernetes to support a far wider
range of admission use cases.
Admission webhooks can be burdensome to develop and operate. Webhook developers
must implement and maintain a webhook binary to handle admission requests. Also,
admission webhooks are complex to operate. Each webhook must be deployed,
monitored and have a well defined upgrade and rollback plan. To make matte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do you create and grow a Center of Excellence?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69868&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69868</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/how-to-create-grow-center-of-excellence/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T21:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering how to get your CoE started and how to run one effectively? Check out this extended Q&A and our live CamundaCon panel for the answers.
The post How do you create and grow a Center of Excellence? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Strauch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – December 19, 2022]]></title>
        <id>352365395483907fe0b79316529e5f6a73acb358</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-december-19-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T19:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are half way between the re:Invent conference and the end-of-year holidays, and I did expect the cadence of releases and news to slow down a bit, but nothing is further away from reality. Our teams continue to listen to your feedback and release new capabilities and incremental improvements. This week, many items caught my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.0.1, 5.8.1, 5.7.6 and 5.6.10 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/19/spring-security-6-0-1-5-8-1-5-7-6-and-5-6-10-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/19/spring-security-6-0-1-5-8-1-5-7-6-and-5-6-10-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 6.0.1, 5.8.1, 5.7.6 and 5.6.10 are available now. In all cases, the releases are mostly composed of bug fixes and documentation improvements.



To learn more, please visit the 6.0.1, 5.8.1, 5.7.6 and
 5.6.10 release summaries.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Celebrates 10 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-celebrates-10-years</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-celebrates-10-years"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-Founders Armon Dadgar and Mitchell Hashimoto share their thoughts on HashiCorp’s 10th Anniversary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Video] How has open source changed in the last 10 years?]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-19-video-how-has-open-source-changed-in-the-last-10-years/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-19-video-how-has-open-source-changed-in-the-last-10-years/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T15:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of open source and how has it changed over the last decade? GitHub’s VP of Developer Relations, Martin Woodward, tackles that question and more in a 2022 keynote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern observability and security on Kubernetes with Elastic and OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/implementing-kubernetes-observability-security-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/implementing-kubernetes-observability-security-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a deep-dive into deploying Elastic for Kubernetes observability and security. Understand why managing Kubernetes can be a challenge and how to leverage OpenTelemetry with the power of the Elastic search and analytics platform to ensure success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ty Bekiares</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern observability and security on Kubernetes with Elastic and OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/implementing-kubernetes-observability-security-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/implementing-kubernetes-observability-security-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The structured nature of Kubernetes enables a repeatable and scalable means of deploying and managing services and applications. This has led to widespread adoption across market verticals for both on-premises and cloud deployment models. The autonomous nature of Kubernetes operation, however, demands comprehensive, fully-converged observability and security. This is uniquely possible today using the Elastic platform.
In this article, we discuss best practices for observing and securing application and service workflows on Kubernetes using Elasticsearch and OpenTelemetry. You will learn how to:

Deploy and configure Elastic Agent in your Kubernetes cluster
Ingest OpenTelemetry application traces, metrics, and events using Elastic Agent
Ingest Kubernetes container logs, cluster metrics, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ty Bekiares</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Device Manager graduates to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/19/devicemanager-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/19/devicemanager-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Swati Sehgal (Red Hat)
The Device Plugin framework was introduced in the Kubernetes v1.8 release as a vendor
independent framework to enable discovery, advertisement and allocation of external
devices without modifying core Kubernetes. The feature graduated to Beta in v1.10.
With the recent release of Kubernetes v1.26, Device Manager is now generally
available (GA).
Within the kubelet, the Device Manager facilitates communication with device plugins
using gRPC through Unix sockets. Device Manager and Device plugins both act as gRPC
servers and clients by serving and connecting to the exposed gRPC services respectively.
Device plugins serve a gRPC service that kubelet connects to for device discovery,
advertisement (as extended resources) and allocation. Device Manager connects to
t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.0  (codename Kilburn) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/16/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-codename-kilburn-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/16/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-codename-kilburn-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-17T01:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the General Availability (RELEASE) of the Spring Cloud 2022.0 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2022.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2022.0.0 Release Train

Spring Cloud 2022.0.0 is a major release that builds upon Spring Framework 6.x and Spring Boot 3.x. This includes compatibility with Jakarta EE and requires a Java 17 baseline. See here for the issues included in this release. Below are highlights from all of the 2022.0.0 milestone, release candidate and GA releases.
Spring Cloud OpenFeign feature complete announcement

Since Spring now provides its own interface HTTP clients solution, starting with 2022.0.0, we’re going to treat Spri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · November 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-16-release-radar-nov-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-16-release-radar-nov-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T19:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We promised we&#8217;d be back soon and here we are! There has been an incredible amount of open source projects shipping major version releases before the year wraps up. I can&#8217;t believe we are all saying that now. &#8220;When the year wraps up!&#8221; or &#8220;See you next year!&#8221; What happened to 2022? Well, we know [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating Text Generation with Confident Adaptive Language Modeling (CALM)]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/accelerating-text-generation-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/accelerating-text-generation-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tal Schuster, Research Scientist, Google Research    
Language models (LMs) are the driving force behind many recent breakthroughs in natural language processing. Models like T5, LaMDA, GPT-3, and PaLM have demonstrated impressive performance on various language tasks. While multiple factors can contribute to improving the performance of LMs, some recent studies suggest that scaling up the model’s size is crucial for revealing emergent capabilities. In other words, some instances can be solved by small models, while others seem to benefit from increased scale. 

Despite recent efforts that enabled the efficient training of LMs over large amounts of data, trained models can still be slow and costly for practical use. When generating text at inference time, most autoregressive LMs …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Non-Graceful Node Shutdown Moves to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/16/kubernetes-1-26-non-graceful-node-shutdown-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/16/kubernetes-1-26-non-graceful-node-shutdown-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Xing Yang (VMware), Ashutosh Kumar (VMware)
Kubernetes v1.24 introduced an alpha quality implementation of improvements
for handling a non-graceful node shutdown.
In Kubernetes v1.26, this feature moves to beta. This feature allows stateful workloads to failover to a different node after the original node is shut down or in a non-recoverable state, such as the hardware failure or broken OS.
What is a node shutdown in Kubernetes?
In a Kubernetes cluster, it is possible for a node to shut down. This could happen either in a planned way or it could happen unexpectedly. You may plan for a security patch, or a kernel upgrade and need to reboot the node, or it may shut down due to preemption of VM instances. A node may also shut down due to a hardware failure or a software problem.
To tr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Run Tasks From Checkpoint, Rapid7, ZScaler and Others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-run-tasks-from-checkpoint-rapid7-zscaler-and-others</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-run-tasks-from-checkpoint-rapid7-zscaler-and-others"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Cloud Run Tasks partners provide more options to ensure security and compliance for cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many shards should I have in my Elasticsearch cluster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T15:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch is a very versatile platform that supports a variety of use cases and provides great flexibility around data organisation and replication strategies. This flexibility can, however, sometimes make it hard to determine up-front how to best organize your data into indices and shards, especially if you are new to the Elastic Stack. While suboptimal choices will not necessarily cause problems when first starting out, they have the potential to cause performance problems as data volumes grow over time. The more data the cluster holds, the more difficult it also becomes to correct the problem, as reindexing of large amounts of data can sometimes be required.
When we come across users that are experiencing performance problems, it is not uncommon that this can be traced back to issue…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Dahlqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many shards should I have in my Elasticsearch cluster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T15:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Dahlqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized as a Leader in the 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Insight Engines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-recognized-as-a-leader-in-the-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-insight-engines</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-recognized-as-a-leader-in-the-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-insight-engines"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic is delighted to be named a Leader in the 2022 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Insight Engines. Download the complimentary report today, and see why we believe Elastic Enterprise Search gives developers the best solution for creating ML-powered search and discovery experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Riley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized as a Leader in the 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Insight Engines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-recognized-as-a-leader-in-the-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-insight-engines</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-recognized-as-a-leader-in-the-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-insight-engines"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,

We’re pleased to announce that Elastic has been named a Leader in the 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Insight Engines. This is our second year of inclusion in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for this category, and this year’s evaluation places Elastic as the furthest entry on the "Completeness of Vision" axis. We believe this placement, our market momentum, and the strength of our vision are outcomes driven by two fundamentals:

Our unwavering focus on search and the expanding toolkit of search capabilities we deliver to developers, search operators, and data analysts.
The Elastic platform’s ability to address a broad range of search application needs – from standalone applications like internal workplace search, to new search-powered applications built to deliver specific functionalities …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Riley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Pulsar 0.1.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/spring-for-apache-pulsar-0-1-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/spring-for-apache-pulsar-0-1-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring for Apache Pulsar 0.1.0 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This is the initial GA minor release of the framework. The full 1.0.0 GA release is expected mid Q12023 and will contain many more features. Although it still lives in the experimental Spring projects it is expected to move into the main Spring projects as part of the full release.
Notable Changes

We have been busy adding features since our last blog. Notable new features include:


  
Reactive support

  
GraalVM Native Image Support


Please see the release notes for more detail.

A great place to get started is the Quick Tour in the reference docs.
Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on GitHub.

GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Predicts: What to Expect in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-predicts-what-to-expect-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-predicts-what-to-expect-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leaders from around HashiCorp share their predictions for the coming year on everything from Kubernetes to AI to zero trust security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaked a secret? Check your GitHub alerts&#8230;for free]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-15-leaked-a-secret-check-your-github-alerts-for-free/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-15-leaked-a-secret-check-your-github-alerts-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T17:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub now allows you to track any leaked secrets in your public repository, for free. With secret scanning alerts, you can track and action on leaked secrets directly within GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security maintains Product Approved status for AV-Comparatives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-maintains-product-approved-status-for-av-comparatives</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-maintains-product-approved-status-for-av-comparatives"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AV-Comparatives offers a comparison as an independent organization performing systematic testing that checks whether security software lives up to its promises. Elastic Security performed better than ever on the real-world protection test.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samantha Zeitlin,Mark Dufresne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security maintains Product Approved status for AV-Comparatives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-maintains-product-approved-status-for-av-comparatives</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-maintains-product-approved-status-for-av-comparatives"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Organizations need real-world protection from malware, but how do you know what you’ll get for security coverage in advance of purchasing a product? AV-Comparatives offers a comparison as an independent organization performing systematic testing that checks whether security software lives up to its promises. They create a real-world environment for accurate testing.
The testing is well-regarded in the industry, assessing malware prevention, real-world protection, and performance of antivirus products. Elastic has performed well consistently on malware protection testing since 2017, starting with our legacy Endgame product and achieving Approved Business Security Product each test cycle. Now, we’re performing better than ever on the real-world protection test. 
Security software testing o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samantha Zeitlin,Mark Dufresne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Custom Rules for Ansible Lint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-custom-rules-for-ansible-lint</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-custom-rules-for-ansible-lint"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Ansible Lint? 
 
Ansible Lint is a command-line tool (part of the ansible-lint upstream community project) for linting of Ansible Playbooks, Roles, and Collections. Ok, so what exactly is “linting?” Its fundamental objective is to promote proven behaviors, patterns, and practices while avoiding typical traps that can quickly result in errors or make code more difficult to maintain. That is - leverage community recommendations and opinions in writing Ansible content by means of a tool to help ensure what you’re writing is generally valid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vineeth Reddy Katuru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft's Brian Benz on the state of Java, Microsoft, Azure, and so much more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-brian-benz-on-the-state-of-java-microsoft-azure-and-so-much-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-brian-benz-on-the-state-of-java-microsoft-azure-and-so-much-more"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Microsoft’s Brian Benz (@bbenz)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/spring-framework-6-0-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/spring-framework-6-0-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T09:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.3 is available now.

Spring Framework 6.0.3 includes 48 fixes and documentation improvements. This version will be shipped with Spring Boot 3.0.1, to be released next week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notice of Permissions Changes to repo.spring.io, January 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/14/notice-of-permissions-changes-to-repo-spring-io-january-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/14/notice-of-permissions-changes-to-repo-spring-io-january-2023"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T06:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical piece of infrastructure, the Spring Artifactory instance lies at the heart of the Spring portfolio development work. Since 2013, JFrog, Inc., has generously sponsored the instance for the Spring developer community.

In October 2020, we announced some permissions changes to our Artifactory instance to restrict anonymous access to the platform for third-party dependencies.

At that time, we asked the Community to source Spring releases from Maven Central. Today, we are announcing some changes to our infrastructure in alignment with that request so that we can better position repo.spring.io for the long term.
How to use repo.spring.io

repo.spring.io is intended for the download of snapshots and milestone artifacts that are not available from Maven Central. All other artifacts …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized as a Strong Performer in The Forrester Wave™: Artificial Intelligence for IT Operations (AIOps), Q4 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/2022-forrester-aiops-wave-it-operations-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/2022-forrester-aiops-wave-it-operations-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AIOps has become increasingly important in observability for managing complex, cloud-native applications and technologies. Learn how Elastic Observability earned top scores for multiple criteria in the new Forrester Wave, AI for IT Operations!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized as a Strong Performer in The Forrester Wave™: Artificial Intelligence for IT Operations (AIOps), Q4 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/2022-forrester-aiops-wave-it-operations-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/2022-forrester-aiops-wave-it-operations-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are excited to announce that Elastic has been recognized as a Strong Performer in The Forrester Wave™: Artificial Intelligence for IT Operations (AIOps), Q4 2022 in our first year participating! 

As organizations modernize their infrastructure and applications, operations and development teams are faced with an exponential growth in data. With the increased complexity and faster release cycles in hybrid and cloud environments, teams are overwhelmed when trying to detect and find the root cause of issues. In today’s digital world, application performance dictates business success and downtime and poor customer experience negatively impacts company revenue. 

Elastic Observability is built on Elasticsearch, with powerful search and machine learning capabilities to provide customers wit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Alpha API For Dynamic Resource Allocation]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/15/dynamic-resource-allocation/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/15/dynamic-resource-allocation/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Patrick Ohly (Intel), Kevin Klues (NVIDIA)
Dynamic resource allocation is a new API for requesting resources. It is a
generalization of the persistent volumes API for generic resources, making it possible to:
access the same resource instance in different pods and containers,
attach arbitrary constraints to a resource request to get the exact resource
you are looking for,
initialize a resource according to parameters provided by the user.
Third-party resource drivers are responsible for interpreting these parameters
as well as tracking and allocating resources as requests come in.
Dynamic resource allocation is an alpha feature and only enabled when the
DynamicResourceAllocation feature
gate and the
resource.k8s.io/v1alpha1 API group are enabled. For details, see the
--feature-gat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Said What? Recorder's On-device Solution for Labeling Speakers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/who-said-what-recorders-on-device.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/who-said-what-recorders-on-device.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T17:03:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Quan Wang, Senior Staff Software Engineer, and Fan Zhang, Staff Software Engineer, Google  
In 2019 we launched Recorder, an audio recording app for Pixel phones that helps users create, manage, and edit audio recordings. It leverages recent developments in on-device machine learning to transcribe speech, recognize audio events, suggest tags for titles, and help users navigate transcripts. 
 
Nonetheless, some Recorder users found it difficult to navigate long recordings that have multiple speakers because it's not clear who said what. During the Made By Google event this year, we announced the "speaker labels" feature for the Recorder app. This opt-in feature annotates a recording transcript with unique and anonymous labels for each speaker (e.g., "Speaker 1", "Speaker 2", etc.)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Plugin Framework Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-plugin-framework-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-plugin-framework-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform Plugin Framework 1.0 is now generally available to provide a modern and extensible way for developers to create Terraform providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Security Analytics Platforms, Q4 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-for-siem-recognized-by-leading-industry-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-for-siem-recognized-by-leading-industry-analysts"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic named a Leader in the 2022 in Forrester Wave™: Security Analytics, Q4 2022. Forrester remarks that “Far and above, Elastic’s data visualizations steal the show.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols,Mike Paquette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Security Analytics Platforms, Q4 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-for-siem-recognized-by-leading-industry-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-for-siem-recognized-by-leading-industry-analysts"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
It’s that time of the year… and we’re not talking about the holidays. That’s right, it’s analyst report season.
Elastic continues to be recognized by leading industry analyst firms. Today, Forrester Research recognized Elastic as a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Security Analytics Platforms, Q4 2022. Elastic had the highest score in the Wave in the strategy category. 


https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt34f5a352b1a55049/639a0584f8b8d66898be5451/2022Q4_Security_Analytics_Platforms_176427.png,2022Q4_Security_Analytics_Platforms_176427.png,
Forrester remarks that “Far and away, Elastic’s data visualizations steal the show” and “Elastic is cloud-agnostic, providing flexibility to customers to use the CSP that they prefer.”
Elastic SIEM unifies security analytics,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols,Mike Paquette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Bring ML Models Built Anywhere into Amazon SageMaker Canvas and Generate Predictions]]></title>
        <id>3f44cecf80edbc14ee966c9c46596ccede484f1f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-bring-ml-models-built-anywhere-into-amazon-sagemaker-canvas-and-generate-predictions/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T16:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Canvas provides business analysts with a visual interface to solve business problems using machine learning (ML) without writing a single line of code. Since we introduced SageMaker Canvas in 2021, many users have asked us for an enhanced, seamless collaboration experience that enables data scientists to share trained models with their business analysts […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第221話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190247031398461</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190247031398461"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform now available in AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-now-available-in-aws-marketplace</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-now-available-in-aws-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AnsibleFest 2022 in the “windy city” Chicago, Red Hat announced Ansible Automation Platform’s upcoming availability in AWS Marketplace. That day is here!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hicham Mourad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heads-Up: Amazon S3 Security Changes Are Coming in April of 2023]]></title>
        <id>f76cf7ff0047a1af2e03a6a49905cd0af60accb7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/heads-up-amazon-s3-security-changes-are-coming-in-april-of-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T21:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting in April of 2023 we will be making two changes to Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) to put our latest best practices for bucket security into effect automatically. The changes will begin to go into effect in April and will be rolled out to all AWS Regions within weeks. Once the changes are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66150</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/december-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T18:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Failures in the “Account Parallelism Sync Analytics Job”.
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2 Patch 4
The post December patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RT-1: Robotics Transformer for Real-World Control at Scale]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/rt-1-robotics-transformer-for-real.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/rt-1-robotics-transformer-for-real.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T16:48:00.016Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted Keerthana Gopalakrishnan and Kanishka Rao, Google Research, Robotics at Google    
Major recent advances in multiple subfields of machine learning (ML) research, such as computer vision and natural language processing, have been enabled by a shared common approach that leverages large, diverse datasets and expressive models that can absorb all of the data effectively. Although there have been various attempts to apply this approach to robotics, robots have not yet leveraged highly-capable models as well as other subfields. 

Several factors contribute to this challenge. First, there’s the lack of large-scale and diverse robotic data, which limits a model’s ability to absorb a broad set of robotic experiences. Data collection is particularly expensive and challenging for robotics bec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69517&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69517</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/camunda-modeler-5-6-release-blog-post/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the release of Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.6, which ships with broader BPMN support and some key UI improvements.
The post Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.6 released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maciej Barelkowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.10 alpha2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69519&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69519</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/optimize-3-10-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See what's new in Camunda Optimize. Camunda Optimize provides business activity monitoring for workflows, supporting continuous process improvement.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.10 alpha2 released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.19.0-alpha2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69518&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69518</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/camunda-automation-platform-7-19-0-alpha2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7, including new REST docs, support for PostgreSQL 15 and more.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.19.0-alpha2 released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 13th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/13/this-week-in-spring-december-13th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/13/this-week-in-spring-december-13th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I truly, absolutely, can not believe that we’re nearly done with the year already! Have you made your new years’ resolutions? Submitted your expense reports? It’s that time of the year when I’m going to start focusing on staying warm and avoiding undue work for a while :-) I hope you do too. This is why I’m glad I write these roundups: I hope they save people from extra, undue work! So, with that… let’s dive into the roundup!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Vaadin’s Marcus Hellberg on rich UIs, Spring Boot 3, GraalVM native images, and more

  
A Guide to Spring CredHub

  
Do more with Azure Spring Apps – scale to zero and enhance productivity

  
Form Login and Basic Authentication in springdoc-openapi

  
Getting Started with Blaze Persistence

  
Guide to Java PriorityQueue

  
Java Generics PECS – Producer Extends Consumer Super

  
RSocket Security with Spring Boot via Spring Security | VMware Tanzu Developer Center

  
Rate Limiting With Client IP in Spring Cloud Gateway

  
Reinitialize Singleton Bean in Spring Context

  
a very important release - v3.0.0 - of the rickroll-security-spring-boot-starter  · TomCools/rickroll-security-spring-boot-starter!

  
Running Spring Boot Applications with the Embedded Camunda Engine

  
Securing RSocket TCP with TLS | VMware Tanzu Developer Center

  
Spring Cloud Data Flow version 2.10.0 released

  
Spring Dependency Injection | VMware Tanzu Developer Center

  
Spring Tools 4.17.0 released

  
Tracing a Reactive Kotlin App with Spring Cloud Sleuth | VMware Tanzu Developer Center]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Windows HostProcess Containers Are Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/13/windows-host-process-containers-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/13/windows-host-process-containers-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Brandon Smith (Microsoft) and Mark Rossetti (Microsoft)
The long-awaited day has arrived: HostProcess containers, the Windows equivalent to Linux privileged
containers, has finally made it to GA in Kubernetes 1.26!
What are HostProcess containers and why are they useful?
Cluster operators are often faced with the need to configure their nodes upon provisioning such as
installing Windows services, configuring registry keys, managing TLS certificates,
making network configuration changes, or even deploying monitoring tools such as a Prometheus's node-exporter.
Previously, performing these actions on Windows nodes was usually done by running PowerShell scripts
over SSH or WinRM sessions and/or working with your cloud provider's virtual machine management tooling.
HostProcess containe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – December 12, 2022]]></title>
        <id>38646395c7ef57fef2041e8de74e54446ae45793</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-december-12-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T22:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! The world is asynchronous, is what Werner Vogels, Amazon CTO, reminded us during his keynote last week at AWS re:Invent. At the beginning of the keynote, he showed us how […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crank up your automation with Ansible validated content]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/crank-up-your-automation-with-ansible-validated-content</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/crank-up-your-automation-with-ansible-validated-content"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible validated content is expert-built automation content packaged as Collections that contain Ansible roles and playbooks that you can use “out-the-box” through Ansible Automation Platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Data Flow version 2.10.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/12/spring-cloud-data-flow-version-2-10-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/12/spring-cloud-data-flow-version-2-10-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, we are very excited to announce the 2.10.0 release of Spring Cloud Data Flow is now available from Maven Central.
Spring updates

Updates to the following versions:


  
Spring Boot 2.7.6

  
Spring Framework 5.3.24

  
Spring Cloud 2021.0.5


Spring Shell

Spring Shell has been updated to 2.1.4.
Documentation Updates
Container images for ARM.

Spring Cloud Data Flow and Skipper, and Stream Application projects contain scripts to use in creating containers when running on an ARM platform. The Reference Guide has a section describing the use of the scripts.
Scripts for local Kuberenetes Development

We have added a collection of scripts to the Spring Cloud Data Flow that makes it easy to launch a local Kuberenetes cluster and install SCDF with MariaDB and RabbitMQ or Kafka. See the Reference Guide for more info.

The detailed release notes contain more info.
Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on Stackoverflow or GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 214 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66155</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-214-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T15:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[List of New Boards Hub bugs fixed in sprint 214. We enabled the “Try New Boards Hub” message across another ring of accounts. The process continues to go slower than originally expected. Every time we enable the message, we receive more feedback on issues that need to be fixed.
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 214 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest 2022 recap]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69423&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69423</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/hacktoberfest-2022-recap/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T13:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn all about our Hacktoberfest 2022 challenge. We hope you all had a great time participating in it and Hacktoberfest as a whole! 
The post Hacktoberfest 2022 recap appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mia Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: We're now signing our binary release artifacts!]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/12/kubernetes-release-artifact-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/12/kubernetes-release-artifact-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
The Kubernetes Special Interest Group (SIG) Release is proud to announce that we
are digitally signing all release artifacts, and that this aspect of Kubernetes
has now reached beta.
Signing artifacts provides end users a chance to verify the integrity of the
downloaded resource. It allows to mitigate man-in-the-middle attacks directly on
the client side and therefore ensures the trustfulness of the remote serving the
artifacts. The overall goal of out past work was to define the used tooling for
signing all Kubernetes related artifacts as well as providing a standard signing
process for related projects (for example for those in kubernetes-sigs).
We already signed all officially released container images (from Kubernetes v1.24 onwards).
Image signing was alpha for v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: Electrifying]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/09/kubernetes-v1-26-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/09/kubernetes-v1-26-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes 1.26 Release Team
It's with immense joy that we announce the release of Kubernetes v1.26!
This release includes a total of 37 enhancements: eleven of them are graduating to Stable, ten are
graduating to Beta, and sixteen of them are entering Alpha. We also have twelve features being
deprecated or removed, three of which we better detail in this announcement.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes 1.26: Electrifying
The theme for Kubernetes v1.26 is Electrifying.
Each Kubernetes release is the result of the coordinated effort of dedicated volunteers, and only
made possible due to the use of a diverse and complex set of computing resources, spread out through
multiple datacenters and regions worldwide. The end result of a release - the binaries, the image
containers, the docum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formation of Robust Bound States of Interacting Photons]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/formation-of-robust-bound-states-of.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/formation-of-robust-bound-states-of.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T17:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alexis Morvan and Trond Andersen, Research Scientists, Google Quantum AI  
When quantum computers were first proposed, they were hoped to be a way to better understand the quantum world. With a so-called “quantum simulator,” one could engineer a quantum computer to investigate how various quantum phenomena arise, including those that are intractable to simulate with a classical computer.  
    
But making a useful quantum simulator has been a challenge. Until now, quantum simulations with superconducting qubits have predominantly been used to verify pre-existing theoretical predictions and have rarely explored or discovered new phenomena. Only a few experiments with trapped ions or cold atoms have revealed new insights. Superconducting qubits, even though they are one of the main…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Secrets for Waypoint with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dynamic-secrets-for-waypoint-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dynamic-secrets-for-waypoint-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to source dynamic secrets from HashiCorp Vault in your Waypoint deployments using dynamic configuration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting your microservice architecture with message broker Connectors]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69131&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69131</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/boosting-microservice-architecture-message-broker-connectors/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Amazon SQS, SNS, and Lambda Connectors, as well as Kafka and RabbitMQ Connectors, microservice choreography and orchestration get even closer together.
The post Boosting your microservice architecture with message broker Connectors appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Vaadin's Marcus Hellberg on rich UIs, Spring Boot 3, GraalVM native images, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/08/a-bootiful-podcast-vaadin-s-marcus-hellberg-on-rich-uis-spring-boot-3-graalvm-native-images-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/08/a-bootiful-podcast-vaadin-s-marcus-hellberg-on-rich-uis-spring-boot-3-graalvm-native-images-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Vaadin’s Marcus Hellberg (@marcushellberg) about rich UIs, Vaadin Flow, the new Hilla Framework, GraalVM native image compilation, and so much more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private Ads Prediction with DP-SGD]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/private-ads-prediction-with-dp-sgd.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/private-ads-prediction-with-dp-sgd.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T19:17:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Krishna Giri Narra, Software Engineer, Google, and Chiyuan Zhang, Research Scientist, Google Research     
Ad technology providers widely use machine learning (ML) models to predict and present users with the most relevant ads, and to measure the effectiveness of those ads. With increasing focus on online privacy, there’s an opportunity to identify ML algorithms that have better privacy-utility trade-offs. Differential privacy (DP) has emerged as a popular framework for developing ML algorithms responsibly with provable privacy guarantees. It has been extensively studied in the privacy literature, deployed in industrial applications and employed by the U.S. Census. Intuitively, the DP framework enables ML models to learn population-wide properties, while protecting user-level inf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do more with Azure Spring Apps – scale to zero and enhance productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/07/do-more-with-azure-spring-apps-scale-to-zero-and-enhance-productivity</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/07/do-more-with-azure-spring-apps-scale-to-zero-and-enhance-productivity"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2020, Spotify coined the term "Golden Path” to refer to a supported approach and set of components to build and deploy software. Having these paths simplifies the development process, lets developers focus on their applications instead of infrastructure and speeds time to production. Microsoft and VMware have partnered to make Azure Spring Apps a golden path for deploying and scaling Spring applications in the cloud. And with new capabilities like the scale to zero and developer productivity enhancements, Azure Spring Apps now offers an even more economical and optimized route to get your Spring applications into production.
1. Start from zero and scale to zero – consumption plan

We are introducing a new consumption pricing plan for Azure Spring Apps – you can start from zero and scal…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.17.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/07/spring-tools-4-17-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/07/spring-tools-4-17-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.17.0 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
updated to Eclipse 2022-12 release (new and noteworthy)


early access to new experimental features

Among a number of bug fixes and minor improvements, this release introduces experimental support for:


  
Spring Boot version validations: The IDE will tell you when there is a newer major, minor, or patch version available for your Spring Boot project

  
Spring Boot upgrade support: The tooling will help you upgrading your existing projects to newer Spring Boot versions, including upgrades to newer patch and minor versions, as well as newer major versions (e.g. upgrading to Spring Boot 3)

  
Spring specific validations and refactorings: The tooling will indicate whether something can or should be changed in your source code to keep your Spring project up-to-date with the latest recommendations or advancements in Spring


To learn more about these new experimental features, please take a look at the user guide: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/
And we would like to hear from you. Please let us know if you come across any issues or have thoughts and wishes for further improvements in this space: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/issues
fixes and improvements

Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-12-07-4170-release-incl-language-servers-version-1410
downloads

To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Spring Tools 4.17.1 is scheduled to be released in early Febuary 2023.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at EMNLP 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/google-at-emnlp-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/google-at-emnlp-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T08:41:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Malaya Jules, Program Manager, Google  
This week, the premier conference on Empirical Methods in Natural Language Processing (EMNLP 2022) is being held in Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates. We are proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of EMNLP 2022, with Google researchers contributing at all levels. This year we are presenting over 50 papers and are actively involved in 10 different workshops and tutorials.
    
If you’re registered for EMNLP 2022, we hope you’ll visit the Google booth to learn more about the exciting work across various topics, including language interactions, causal inference, question answering and more. Take a look below to learn more about the Google research being presented at EMNLP 2022 (Google affiliations in bold). 
    

Committees
  
Organizing Committee inclu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will You Find These Shortcuts?]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/will-you-find-these-shortcuts.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/will-you-find-these-shortcuts.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T20:56:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Katja Filippova, Research Scientist, and Sebastian Ebert, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain team    
Modern machine learning models that learn to solve a task by going through many examples can achieve stellar performance when evaluated on a test set, but sometimes they are right for the “wrong” reasons: they make correct predictions but use information that appears irrelevant to the task. How can that be? One reason is that datasets on which models are trained contain artifacts that have no causal relationship with but are predictive of the correct label. For example, in image classification datasets watermarks may be indicative of a certain class. Or it can happen that all the pictures of dogs happen to be taken outside, against green grass, so a green background become…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updated: Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2022 RTW]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66134</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/now-available-azure-devops-server-2022-rtw/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T20:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[12/16 Update: There is an additional step that you will have to follow while upgrading to Azure DevOps Server 2022. This applies to Azure DevOps Server/Team Foundation Server and Elasticsearch installations on the same and in different machines.
Upgrade Elasticsearch 2.x and 5.x to 7.x
You will have to select Install New Search while configuring search post Azure DevOps Server upgrade.
The post Updated: Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2022 RTW appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project signing and verification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/project-signing-and-verification</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/project-signing-and-verification"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project signing is a new feature developed for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform that came out in the latest 2.3 release. It enables users to sign project-based content (think playbooks, workflows, inventories, etc.) and verify whether or not that content has remained secure. It also features a new CLI tool, ansible-sign. This blog post will explain how it works, illustrate how to implement it, and highlight a few scenarios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lila Yasin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 6th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/06/this-week-in-spring-december-6th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/06/this-week-in-spring-december-6th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you? You know what I’ve wanted to do? See my friends on the Spring team in person since the pandemic descended. And, I’m overjoyed to relate, I’ve just had the privilege of a nice meeting with several of them last night. And I’m going to see more of them today! Seriously. I feel like I won the lottery. I’ve missed my friends. Hug your friends and family, friends. You never know when the next pandemic (or life in general) will put distance between you and them. So, in order to close that distance, I’m going to go back to meetings with them, and I’ll leave you with yet another week’s curated list of content. (Can you believe we’re like four weeks away from 2023?)


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Java Champion Gunnar Mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep the learning pace! A Holiday recap about network automation sessions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/keep-the-learning-pace-a-holiday-recap-about-network-automation-sessions</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/keep-the-learning-pace-a-holiday-recap-about-network-automation-sessions"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In case you want to review the most relevant sessions, here is a summary on the abridged network automation related sessions that you can check on-demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Forensic container checkpointing in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/05/forensic-container-checkpointing-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/05/forensic-container-checkpointing-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Adrian Reber (Red Hat)
Forensic container checkpointing is based on Checkpoint/Restore In
Userspace (CRIU) and allows the creation of stateful copies
of a running container without the container knowing that it is being
checkpointed. The copy of the container can be analyzed and restored in a
sandbox environment multiple times without the original container being aware
of it. Forensic container checkpointing was introduced as an alpha feature in
Kubernetes v1.25.
How does it work?
With the help of CRIU it is possible to checkpoint and restore containers.
CRIU is integrated in runc, crun, CRI-O and containerd and forensic container
checkpointing as implemented in Kubernetes uses these existing CRIU
integrations.
Why is it important?
With the help of CRIU and the corresponding integ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>