<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-08-10T00:22:40.008Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-08-10T00:22:40.008Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DTC: Content Creation with Daniel Snow]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11402</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/09/dtc-content-creation-with-daniel-snow/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dtc-content-creation-with-daniel-snow"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T19:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Direct-to-Consumer companies sell their products without going through a traditional middleman like an outlet store or wholesaler. By posting content on platforms like TikTok, Facebook, and YouTube, companies can reach millions of users.TikTok, for example, has an estimated 1 billion monthly active users (wallaroomedia). The company Kindred Studios helps direct-to-consumer companies create consistent, beautiful content
The post DTC: Content Creation with Daniel Snow appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Temperature Over My Lifetime]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2500/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2500/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/global_temperature_over_my_lifetime.png" title="I was really impressed by the accuracy of some of the report's predictions about fossil fuel consumption. Then I realized, oh, right, of course." alt="I was really impressed by the accuracy of some of the report's predictions about fossil fuel consumption. Then I realized, oh, right, of course." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.08.06]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62155</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-08-06/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T13:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday, and every Friday we try to bring you the latest and greatest in content about DevOps. This week we dedicate this list of community posts to our lost friend, Abel Wang. Abel was always about elevating the community and helping others do their best.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.08.06 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Material Security with Ryan Noon]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11347</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/06/material-security-with-ryan-noon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=material-security-with-ryan-noon"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T09:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Noon is the CEO of Material Security.   This interview was also recorded as a video podcast. Check out the video on the Software Daily YouTube channel.   Sponsorship inquiries: sponsor@softwareengineeringdaily.com
The post Material Security with Ryan Noon appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abandonment Function]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2499/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2499/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/abandonment_function.png" title="Remember to only adopt domesticated drones that specifically request it. It's illegal to collect wild ones under the Migratory Drone Treaty Act." alt="Remember to only adopt domesticated drones that specifically request it. It's illegal to collect wild ones under the Migratory Drone Treaty Act." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wasp-Lang: Boilerplate Code with Matija Sosic]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11340</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/05/wasp-lang-boilerplate-code-with-matija-sosic/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wasp-lang-boilerplate-code-with-matija-sosic"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T19:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “boilerplate code” refers to code sections that are repeated across many projects with little to no variation. Every developer is familiar with boilerplate code, whether it be pom.xml files in Java or setting up React.js applications, tweaking boilerplate code for every project is inevitable. Actually, the company Wasp believes writing boilerplate code doesn’t
The post Wasp-Lang: Boilerplate Code with Matija Sosic appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft's Sean Li on Azure, Spring Boot, Azure Spring Cloud, Spring integrations and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/05/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-sean-li-on-azure-spring-boot-azure-spring-cloud-spring-integrations-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/05/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-sean-li-on-azure-spring-boot-azure-spring-cloud-spring-integrations-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long talks to Microsoft’s Sean Li on Azure, Spring Boot, Azure Spring Cloud, Spring integrations and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application Observability with HCP Consul and Datadog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/application-observability-with-hcp-consul-and-datadog</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/application-observability-with-hcp-consul-and-datadog"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spend more time improving observability rather than maintaining infrastructure with HCP Consul and Datadog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Presents: Migrating Your Data – Migrate your MongoDB data to Cosmos DB]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61981</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-presents-migrating-your-data-migrate-your-mongodb-data-to-cosmos-db/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T15:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last time, I showed you how to create a Cosmos DB account for your MongoDB data using an ARM template. This time, we’ll use the Azure Database Migration Service (DBMS) to migrate my data I have on a Virtual Machine into Cosmos DB.
The post AzureFunBytes Presents: Migrating Your Data – Migrate your MongoDB data to Cosmos DB appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four unexpected benefits of working in a distributed engineering org]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-four-unexpected-benefits-of-working-in-a-distributed-engineering-org</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-four-unexpected-benefits-of-working-in-a-distributed-engineering-org"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software engineers cite constant distractions, long commute times, and a lack of flexibility as the biggest challenges of working in an office setting, according to an internal employee survey conducted by the Elastic Culture team. But the survey also revealed that the biggest benefits of a distributed environment could be the new opportunities it opens for employees — for example, the freedom to catch some waves during the workday.

As Elastic offices slowly begin to reopen worldwide in accordance with local guidelines, we asked our Engineering and Product teams why they value being able to work for a company that’s distributed by intention — whether they work in an office, a shared workspace, or from home. 

You can improve your physical and mental health
Of the Elasticians we surveyed, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extract Insights From Customer Conversations with Amazon Transcribe Call Analytics]]></title>
        <id>2e1848a3c16dd182412ffc24ea189f3aa5a05a7c</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/u3VRBOAMpCM/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T18:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2017, we launched Amazon Transcribe, an automatic speech recognition (ASR) service that makes it easy to add speech-to-text capabilities to any application. Today, I’m very happy to announce the availability of Amazon Transcribe Call Analytics, a new feature that lets you easily extract valuable insights from customer conversations with a single API call. Each […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault Secrets in a Browser Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-browser-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-browser-plugin"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to fetch secrets from Vault with a custom Chrome extension in the latest HashiCorp Learn tutorial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Managed Identities with the HashiCorp Stack: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/azure-managed-identities-with-the-hashicorp-stack-part-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/azure-managed-identities-with-the-hashicorp-stack-part-2"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets management with HashiCorp Vault can use Microsoft Azure managed identities to ease the operational burden of Vault cluster availability: Part 2 in a series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized for innovation by Google Cloud and Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-recognized-for-innovation-by-google-cloud-and-microsoft</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-recognized-for-innovation-by-google-cloud-and-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic received honors from two key partners, Microsoft and Google — a recognition of our efforts to ensure that customers can easily find and use Elastic products in the environments that best suit their needs.

Elastic was named the 2021 Microsoft US Partner Award Winner in Business Excellence in the Commercial Marketplace. In addition, for the second year in a row, Elastic was selected by Google Cloud as the 2020 Technology Partner of the Year for Data Management.

We understand that more organizations are procuring software via marketplaces to ease compliance, cost, and operational complexity within their technology landscape. Through our cloud partnerships with Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure, and others, including Amazon Web Services, our customers can gain access to both free and pai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurent Mechain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okteto: Cloud-Native Applications on Kubernetes with Ramiro Berreleza]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11338</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/04/okteto-with-ramiro-berreleza/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=okteto-with-ramiro-berreleza"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T09:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is an open-source container orchestration system. It makes managing container clusters possible as well as deploying code changes to these containers. Microservice architecture is widely used today in large part because of Kubernetes. However, using it can require a large time commitment due to its learning curve. The company Okteto empowers developers to innovate
The post Okteto: Cloud-Native Applications on Kubernetes with Ramiro Berreleza appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Compelling ROI Case for Camunda]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=25892</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/08/a-compelling-roi-case-for-camunda/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T08:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Forrester Consulting spoke to six longtime Camunda Platform users, they learned how they’re delivering process automation projects faster, driving organizational efficiency and better customer service with massive, multi-million dollar impact to the business. Download the Total Economic Impact study commissioned by Camunda. 
The post A Compelling ROI Case for Camunda appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Rogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Better Data-Driven Applications with Spring Boot and Redis]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/04/spring-tips-better-data-driven-applications-with-spring-boot-and-redis</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/04/spring-tips-better-data-driven-applications-with-spring-boot-and-redis"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Redis is the swiss-army knife of databases and it integrates into Spring-based workloads with ease. In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) and special guest star Brian Sam-Bodden (@bsbodden) look at just a few of the bootiful possibilities for Redis and Spring Boot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forest Walk]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2498/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2498/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/forest_walk.png" title="The only other person to walk by was a linguist back in the 80s, but she just spent a while dissecting the phrase 'help me down' before getting distracted by a squirrel and wandering off." alt="The only other person to walk by was a linguist back in the 80s, but she just spent a while dissecting the phrase 'help me down' before getting distracted by a squirrel and wandering off." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beta Support for CRDs in the Terraform Provider for Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/beta-support-for-crds-in-the-terraform-provider-for-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/beta-support-for-crds-in-the-terraform-provider-for-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kubernetes_manifest resource has now graduated into the official Kubernetes provider as a beta, bringing support for CRDs and custom resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 7.14.0 introduces the industry’s first free and open Limitless XDR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the general availability (GA) of Elastic 7.14, including our Elastic Enterprise Search, Observability, and Security solutions, which are built into the Elastic Stack — Elasticsearch and Kibana. 

Elastic 7.14 empowers organizations with the first free and open Limitless XDR, which delivers unified SIEM and endpoint security capabilities in one platform. 

The latest release makes it even easier to manage and monitor data from a growing volume of diverse sources. With Elastic Agent, security practitioners benefit from integrated ransomware and malware prevention as well as remediation on all of their hosts. Users of Elastic Observability can get better visibility across their applications and infrastructure, as well as secure centralized agent management, with Ela…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kearns,Angelos Kottas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Security 7.14: Protect your company with Limitless XDR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 7.14 introduces the industry’s first free and open Limitless XDR solution, unifying the capabilities of SIEM and endpoint security. It is made possible by the general availability of Elastic Agent, which helps equip it to prevent, detect, and respond to threats before adversaries can steal sensitive information or sabotage operations. Let’s dig into the best of what it brings.
Quickly quarantine and inspect endpoints
Elastic Security 7.14 accelerates response by enabling analysts to invoke response actions with Elastic Agent. With the first native response action for Elastic Agent, host isolation, analysts can address malicious activity by quarantining a host from a network, containing the attack and preventing lateral movement to other hosts. Try it out with the Endpoint …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 7.14: Unified telemetry and accelerated application root cause analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 7.14 introduces the general availability of unified telemetry and centralized agent management with Elastic Agent and Fleet, enabling faster and simpler data onboarding, and reduced security risk, in addition to enhanced correlations for accelerated root cause analysis in Elastic APM. 

These new features allow customers to:

Collect all forms of data from anywhere with a single unified agent per host, with just one agent to install, configure, and scale
Deploy endpoint security seamlessly across their infrastructure, bringing DevOps and security teams into greater convergence
Quickly surface factors that have the most significant impact on service performance
Elastic Observability 7.14 is available now on Elastic Cloud — the only hosted Elasticsearch offering to incl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Elastic Enterprise Search 7.14: Kibana integration and precision tuning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 7.14 now lets you manage all your Elastic products from a single management interface, so you can navigate to App Search and Workplace Search from Kibana without losing your way.

We’re also delivering more flexibility and configurability with precision tuning in App Search and content source flexibility and synonym support in Workplace Search. With all these enhancements, you can set up your teams and customers to find what they’re looking for faster than ever:

Generate more search experience insights with Kibana’s powerful visualizations
Gain tighter customization over your search results with adjustable precision and recall
Configure how you want to ingest data with our out-of-the-box content sources
Create synonyms so teams can find information faster
Elastic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Enterprise Search team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Cloud for 7.14: Connect securely to your public cloud environments with Azure Private Link]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-cloud-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-cloud-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest updates to Elastic Cloud make it even easier for our customers to protect their data using Microsoft Azure Private Link, and offer new options for deployment location and hardware configuration in Google Cloud. 
 
Network security enhancements

We’re excited to announce that support for Microsoft Azure Private Link is now generally available. Private Link provides private connectivity from your Azure virtual network to your Elastic Cloud deployments. The traffic between your virtual network and your Elastic Cloud deployment on Azure travels only within the Azure network, utilizing Private Link endpoints and ensuring that your data stays off the Internet. Soon, you will also be able to leverage Google Cloud Private Service Connect to secure the network connection between your Goo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Kibana 7.14: Formulas and time shifts for richer ad hoc analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-kibana-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-kibana-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kibana 7.14 introduces more capabilities for ad hoc analytics to enable users to cut through the noise and discover insights faster and more easily. 

These new features include custom formulas and time-shifted metrics in Kibana Lens and a time slider in Elastic Maps–all without compromising speed. In addition:

Time-shifted metrics and a time slider in Kibana Lens and Elastic Maps allow users to compare data from different time periods at a glance.
Custom formulas in Kibana Lens and edit tools in Elastic Maps give users the creative freedom to author metrics and add to geo indices.
Elastic Agent, a unified agent for collecting data from multiple sources and protecting your data and hosts, is generally available. Users can choose from 100+ out-of-the-box integrations that are pre-loaded wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeline Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 7.14 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce Elasticsearch 7.14.0, based on Apache Lucene 8.9.0. 

Version 7.14 is the latest stable release of Elasticsearch and is now available for deployment via Elasticsearch Service on Elastic Cloud or via download for use in your own environment(s).

Ready to roll up your sleeves and get started? We have the links you need:

Start Elasticsearch on Elastic Cloud 
Download Elasticsearch
Elasticsearch 7.14.0 release notes
Elasticsearch 7.14.0 breaking changes

Swing for the geofences with Elasticsearch 7.14 
When searching data, “where” is a common and important question. Whether you’re trying to identify whether an outage is a local or global issue, locating adversaries attacking your network, or simply tracking where your food delivery is, Elasticsearch and the Elastic S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Consul Plus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-consul-plus</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-consul-plus"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul Plus allows users to federate Consul clusters across multiple regions for improved redundancy and resiliency of applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 6.8.18 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-6-8-18-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-6-8-18-released"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 6.8.18 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Kibana, Elasticsearch, Beats, Logstash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Jaramillo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Limitless XDR defined: Ingest, retain, and analyze security data freely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-limitless-xdr</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-limitless-xdr"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security's newest features define the potential of XDR for cybersecurity teams. Our single platform brings together SIEM and endpoint security, allowing users to ingest and retain large volumes of data from diverse sources, store and search data for longer, and augment threat hunting with detections and machine learning.
Security vendors are using the term “XDR” with increasing frequency, applying varied definitions to suit their respective technologies. The term began as an evolution of EDR (endpoint detection and response), and tried to encapsulate the need for varied data sources in the investigative process by using “X” for “eXtended.” Through all the varying definitions, the core concepts remain:

Visibility: The exponential growth of data makes a security practitioner’s job i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 10% disk space on your logging datasets with match_only_text]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/save-10-percent-disk-space-on-your-logging-datasets-with-match-only-text</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/save-10-percent-disk-space-on-your-logging-datasets-with-match-only-text"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 7.14 introduces match_only_text, a new field type that can be used as a drop-in replacement for the text field type in logging use cases with a much lower disk footprint, leading to lower costs.

Elasticsearch is attractive for log analysis thanks to its ability to index log messages. Want to count how many log messages contain access denied in the last 24 hours? Elasticsearch can give you the answer in milliseconds thanks to its index structures — but index structures take CPU time to build and need disk space. You could save this CPU and disk space by not indexing your message fields, but then you would also lose the ability to query your logging data in an interactive way.

In order to reduce disk space requirements, match_only_text only indexes a subset of the information…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrien Grand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Agent and Fleet make it easier to integrate your systems with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-and-fleet-make-it-easier-to-integrate-your-systems-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-and-fleet-make-it-easier-to-integrate-your-systems-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are happy to announce three major improvements that will make it easier to integrate your systems and applications with the Elastic Stack. First, we are launching the generally available (GA) release of our Elastic Agent, which is a single, unified agent for both observability and security. A unified agent will simplify data onboarding with fewer things to configure and install.

Second, we are launching the GA release of Fleet, a new Kibana app that lets you centrally manage an entire fleet of Elastic Agents at scale. It acts as a control plane, giving you a real-time view into agent status, remotely upgrade agents, execute queries on each host, and contain security threats.

Third, we are launching our new Integrations app in Kibana along with our first set of GA integrations. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Skowronski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 49 – Intro to @Azure SQL with @StevenMurawski]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62072</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-49-intro-to-azure-sql-with-stevenmurawski/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T14:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 49 – Intro to @Azure SQL with @StevenMurawski appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audit your VMware vCenter Server using Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/audit-your-vmware-vcenter-server-using-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/audit-your-vmware-vcenter-server-using-ansible"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How you can use the modules available in Red Hat supported vmware.vmware_rest Ansible Content Collection to audit your vCenter Servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gonéri Le Bouder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera Hashgraph: Proof-of-Stake Public Networks with Leemon Baird]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11339</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/03/hedera-hashgraph-with-leemon-baird/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hedera-hashgraph-with-leemon-baird"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T09:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain protocols like Bitcoin and Ethereum have changed the cyber world dramatically in the last decade. They’ve created communities of like-minded developers, generated new financial markets, and popularized “decentralization” in computer networks. However, they require large resources to operate which makes scaling difficult and transactions expensive. Hedera is a decentralized public network that takes the
The post Hedera Hashgraph: Proof-of-Stake Public Networks with Leemon Baird appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 3rd, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/03/this-week-in-spring-august-3rd-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/03/this-week-in-spring-august-3rd-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! Can you believe it’s already August, 2021! We’re nearly to 2022! And I am, for better or for worse, back from vacation! I am so happy to be back, but I do miss the sunkissed beaches of Hawai’i. Sigh. Anyway, let’s get into it! We’ve got a ton of things to get into, so without further ado…


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft’s Asir V. Selvasingh on Spring Boot, Spring Cloud, Microsoft Azure, and Azure Spring Cloud

  
Blog: Roorkee robots, releases and racing: the Kubernetes 1.21 release interview

  
Join Pure Storage at VMworld 2021

  
Cassandre is an open-source framework that makes it easy to create your crypto trading bot in Java. Our Spring boot starter takes care of exchange connections, accounts, orders, trades, and positions so you can focus 

  
Check out this Spring Security Authorization Server example

  
Join Confluent Developer advocate Viktor Gamov for this look at Spring and Apache Kafka 101

  
Here’s another interesting look at using Spring Boot with Swagger

  
Did y’all see the latest installment of the SpringOne Tour. This was my favorite installment yet!

  
Flight Status: Oracle Cloud VMware Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Vault Starter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-starter</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-starter"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Starter — now generally available on AWS — offers a production-grade 3-node cluster at a reduced price point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Named as a Leader for the 11th Consecutive Year in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud Infrastructure & Platform Services (CIPS)]]></title>
        <id>446271ecb9bf93846c19f7d2d60e450dedd2456a</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/GuZ2U5msR-8/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T15:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my job at AWS I have the privilege of working with many different teams, all focused to help our customers lower costs, become more agile, and innovate faster. It’s greatly rewarding to see these efforts recognized by our customers and by leading analysts. Last year Gartner introduced a new Magic Quadrant for Cloud Infrastructure […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse ETL: Operationalizing Data Warehouses with Tejas Manohar]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11237</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/02/reverse-etl-operationalizing-data-warehouses-with-tejas-manojar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=reverse-etl-operationalizing-data-warehouses-with-tejas-manojar"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T09:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise data warehouses store all company data in a single place to be accessed, queried, and analyzed. They’re essential for business operations because they support managing data from multiple sources, providing context, and have built-in analytics tools. While keeping a single source of truth is important, easily moving data from the warehouse to other applications
The post Reverse ETL: Operationalizing Data Warehouses with Tejas Manohar appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logic Gates]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2497/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2497/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/logic_gates.png" title="In C, the multiocular O represents the bitwise norxondor gorgonax." alt="In C, the multiocular O represents the bitwise norxondor gorgonax." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.0-M1 (aka Jubilee) Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/30/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-m1-aka-jubilee-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/30/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-m1-aka-jubilee-is-available"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T06:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Milestone 1 (M1) of the Spring Cloud 2021 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2021 release notes for more information.

This release is compatible with Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1.

The GitHub Project for this release can be found here.
Notable Changes in the 2021 Release Train
Spring Cloud Gateway


  
StripPrefixFilter now defaults to 1 instead of 0 #2033

  
Add new CacheRequestBodyFilter #1943

  
Share Routes across Gateway instances with Redis #1390


Spring Cloud Sleuth


  
Added JDBC support #1930

  
Instruments Tomcat Valve #1329

  
Support for Spring Vault #1952

  
Automatic tag table generation documentation #1950

  
Spring Cloud D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating the New HashiCorp Enterprise License Deployment Process]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/navigating-the-new-hashicorp-enterprise-license-deployment-process</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/navigating-the-new-hashicorp-enterprise-license-deployment-process"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get helpful resources on a recent change to product license deployments and learn how to navigate this change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Azure by using Grafana dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62089</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/monitoring-azure-by-using-grafana-dashboards/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T16:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By using Azure Monitor, Azure Log Analytics and Application Insights, Azure cloud teams have access to a collection of end-to-end monitoring solutions, directly from the Azure Portal, allowing for Azure Services monitoring, as well as hybrid.
The post Monitoring Azure by using Grafana dashboards appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter De Tender</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.30]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62066</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-07-30/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T14:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.07.30 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.30 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DMN-Powered Sorting Hat]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=25669</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/the-dmn-powered-sorting-hat/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T12:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was painfully reminded of the Dark Lord’s failure when I discovered Harry Potter (the person, not the books) turns 40 tomorrow. To help get my mind off of it, I built a Sorting Hat.
The post The DMN-Powered Sorting Hat appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preface with Farooq Abbasi]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11285</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/30/preface-with-farooq-abbasi/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=preface-with-farooq-abbasi"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T09:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode we discuss venture capital and more with Preface Ventures Founder and General Partner Farooq Abbasi. This interview was also recorded as a video podcast. Check out the video on the Software Daily YouTube channel. Sponsorship inquiries: sponsor@softwareengineeringdaily.com
The post Preface with Farooq Abbasi appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heads-Up: AWS Support for Internet Explorer 11 is Ending]]></title>
        <id>c04a29ab1caa1aa963ed25c0ec3f0fe14e12ecef</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/k3NiY2L_p9s/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T21:31:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are using Internet Explorer 11 (IE 11) to access the AWS Management Console, web-based services such as Amazon Chime or Amazon Honeycode, or other parts of the AWS web site (AWS Documentation, AWS Marketing, AWS Marketplace, or AWS Support), it is time to upgrade to a more modern & secure browser such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IoT SiteWise Edge Is Now Generally Available for Processing Industrial Equipment Data on Premises]]></title>
        <id>80f41b2ee1153fdf2a0cce514f2564d85b05a2e5</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/Z1B7j0oz-TY/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T18:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2020, we announced the preview of AWS IoT SiteWise Edge, a new feature of AWS IoT SiteWise that provides software that runs on premises at industrial sites and makes it easy to collect, process, and monitor equipment data locally before sending the data to AWS Cloud destinations. AWS IoT SiteWise Edge software […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting unusual network activity with Elastic Security and machine learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-unusual-network-activity-with-elastic-security-and-machine-learning</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-unusual-network-activity-with-elastic-security-and-machine-learning"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we’ve shown in a previous blog, search-based detection rules and Elastic’s machine learning-based anomaly detection can be a powerful way to identify rare and unusual activity in cloud API logs. Now, as of Elastic Security 7.13, we’ve introduced a new set of unsupervised machine learning jobs for network data, and accompanying alert rules, several of which look for geographic anomalies. In this blog post, we’ll explore a case study demonstrating how network data can yield important detections. 

Before the advent of endpoint detection and response (EDR) tools, security teams relied heavily on network instrumentation like firewall logs and intrusion detection (IDS) alerts. Given the lack of process information or user context, in network logs, the false positive rate for network events c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Chamberlain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing CDK for Terraform 0.5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-cdk-for-terraform-0-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-cdk-for-terraform-0-5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CDK for Terraform 0.5 introduces code generation from HCL and a new cdktf watch workflow for serverless workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting Elasticsearch ILM: Common issues and fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-elasticsearch-ilm-common-issues-and-fixes</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-elasticsearch-ilm-common-issues-and-fixes"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hiya! Our Elasticsearch team is continually improving our index Lifecycle Management (ILM) feature. When I first joined Elastic Support, I quickly got up to speed via our Automate rollover with ILM tutorial. I noticed after helping multiple users set up ILM that escalations mainly emerge from a handful of configuration issues. 

In the following sections, I’d like to cover frequent tickets, diagnostic flow, and common error recoveries. All commands shown can be run via Kibana’s Dev Tools.
 
Configure

The ILM backend process runs by default but requires user configuration to affect indices. You can verify ILM is running via ILM status returning operation_mode:RUNNING.

Common issue 1: ILM is not running 
ILM runs by default. If you’ve previously stopped ILM, you’ll want to start up ILM aga…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stef Nestor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Azure Static Web Apps vs Azure WebApps vs Azure Blob Storage Static Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62071</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/comparing-azure-static-web-apps-vs-azure-webapps-vs-azure-blob-storage-static-sites/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T15:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Static Web Apps Comparison
The post Comparing Azure Static Web Apps vs Azure WebApps vs Azure Blob Storage Static Sites appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five tips for growing your career in tech sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-five-tips-for-growing-your-career-in-tech-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-five-tips-for-growing-your-career-in-tech-sales"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Rain Hu's favorite moments of the day is her early morning run. "I run six kilometers minimum daily, rain or shine," she says. "I enjoy the time alone because it allows me to have time for self-reflection and self-conversation."

The discipline that it takes to maintain a healthy lifestyle is carried throughout her life. As a wife, mother of two young boys, and sales leader, Rain optimizes her time so that she can show up fully and authentically in all aspects of her life.

We sat down with Rain, Regional Vice President of Sales (ASEAN and Hong Kong) at Elastic, to learn how she has built a career she loves. Read on to learn about how she grew her career in tech sales and what advice she has for others looking to do the same.


Launching a career in tech sales
Shortly after graduati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mara Gates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shoreline: Fleet Automation with Anurag Gupta]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11302</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/29/shoreline-fleet-automation-with-anurag-gupta/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shoreline-fleet-automation-with-anurag-gupta"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T09:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s containerized world, it’s common to encounter similar issues with known solutions across multiple pods. For most people there are 2 solutions: go pod-by-pod finding and fixing the problem, or do that while also spending months trying to automate that process. This is significant time and manual labor. The company Shoreline orchestrates real-time debugging
The post Shoreline: Fleet Automation with Anurag Gupta appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate any Process on Micronaut]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=24764</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/automate-any-process-on-micronaut/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T07:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Camunda can be run as an embedded engine inside a Micronaut application, with the use of our open source integration project.
The post Automate any Process on Micronaut appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft's Asir V. Selvasingh on Spring Boot, Spring Cloud, Microsoft Azure, and Azure Spring Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/29/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-asir-v-selvasingh-on-spring-boot-spring-cloud-microsoft-azure-and-azure-spring-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/29/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-asir-v-selvasingh-on-spring-boot-spring-cloud-microsoft-azure-and-azure-spring-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Microsoft’s Asir V. Selvasingh (@asirselvasingh) about Azure Spring Cloud, Spring Boot, Microsoft Azure and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo – People & Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62043</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-people-teams/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T21:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our 2nd blog DevOps Dojo – Experiential Learning, we shared with you that we couldn’t find a better example than showcasing how our Aspires leverage all the methods listed in the blog to advance their careers and learnings. Their way of learning is disruptive,
The post DevOps Dojo – People & Teams appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EC2-Classic Networking is Retiring – Here’s How to Prepare]]></title>
        <id>f59bc7fc5b869bffbdb77f894f6c9a89aa5e26b2</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/3IaLs3ny3aU/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T19:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (July 29, 2021) – Added link to the Support Automation Workflow document & clarified link to AWS MGN pricing. Also updated the list of recommended instance types to favor those built on AWS Nitro System, and added “Networking” to the title. Let’s go back to the summer of 2006 and the launch of EC2. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Kubernetes the Elastic way using Filebeat and Metricbeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-kubernetes-the-elastic-way-using-filebeat-and-metricbeat</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-kubernetes-the-elastic-way-using-filebeat-and-metricbeat"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous blog post, I demonstrated how to use Prometheus and Fluentd with the Elastic Stack to monitor Kubernetes. That’s a good option if you’re already using those open source-based monitoring tools in your organization. But, if you’re new to Kubernetes monitoring, or want to take full advantage of Elastic Observability, there is an easier and more comprehensive way. In this blog, we will explore how to monitor Kubernetes the Elastic way: using Filebeat and Metricbeat.
Using Filebeat and Metricbeat
Beats, as you know, is a free and open platform dedicated to data shipping. Using Beats, you can transfer data from hundreds or thousands of machines to Logstash or Elasticsearch.
Filebeat, which is known as a lightweight log shipper, also supports containerized architecture. Filebeat ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yukiya Shimizu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prophecy: Apple of Data Engineering with Raj Bains]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11313</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/28/prophecy-apple-of-data-engineering-with-raj-bains/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=prophecy-apple-of-data-engineering-with-raj-bains"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T16:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prophecy is a complete Low-Code Data Engineering Platform for the Enterprise. Prophecy enables all your teams on Apache Spark with a unique low-code designer. While you visually build your Dataflows – Prophecy generates high-quality Spark code on Git. Then, you can schedule Spark workflows with Prophecy’s low-code Airflow. Not only that, Prophecy provides end-to-end visibility
The post Prophecy: Apple of Data Engineering with Raj Bains appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Vault 1.8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-8</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-8"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.8 offers a new Vault Diagnose command, Key Management secrets engine AWS GA support, updates to Integrated Storage Autopilot, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon Route 53 Application Recovery Controller]]></title>
        <id>4dd26d69ade9053b95b2204f25c1aed35d499bcf</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/tSAJ8u0H0bg/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T21:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce the availability today of Amazon Route 53 Application Recovery Controller, a Amazon Route 53 set of capabilities that continuously monitors an application’s ability to recover from failures and controls application recovery across multiple AWS Availability Zones, AWS Regions, and on premises environments to help you to build applications that must […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HashiCorp Consul with Kong Ingress Controller for Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-hashicorp-consul-with-kong-ingress-controller-for-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-hashicorp-consul-with-kong-ingress-controller-for-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure Kong Ingress Controller for Kubernetes with transparent proxy on HashiCorp Consul service mesh to manage traffic to and between your Kubernetes services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Current Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11310</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/27/our-current-strategy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=our-current-strategy"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T18:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve been running Software Daily for 6 years.  When we started it back in 2015, the goal was to create a software engineering podcast that was 60% as good as Software Engineering Radio, but aired with 5x the frequency.  5 shows per week, 50 weeks per year, 5 ads per show, means 1,250 advertising spots.
The post Our Current Strategy appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collecting and operationalizing threat data from the Mozi botnet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/collecting-and-operationalizing-threat-data-from-the-mozi-botnet</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/collecting-and-operationalizing-threat-data-from-the-mozi-botnet"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting and preventing malicious activity such as botnet attacks is a critical area of focus for threat intel analysts, security operators, and threat hunters. Taking up the Mozi botnet as a case study, this blog post demonstrates how to use open source tools, analytical processes, and the Elastic Stack to perform analysis and enrichment of collected data irrespective of the campaign. This will allow you to take the lessons and processes outlined below to your organization and apply them to your specific use cases.

The Mozi botnet has been leveraging vulnerable Internet of Things (IoT) devices to launch campaigns that can take advantage of the force multiplication provided by a botnet (Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS), email spam, brute-force, password spraying, etc.). Mozi was firs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes – @Azure Arc Enabled Data Services with @sqldbawithbeard]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61952</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-azure-arc-enabled-data-services-with-sqldbawithbeard/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T16:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes – @Azure Arc Enabled Data Services with @sqldbawithbeard appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending the Internet of Things from hackers and viruses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/defending-the-internet-of-things-from-hackers-and-viruses</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/defending-the-internet-of-things-from-hackers-and-viruses"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leon Gubbels is a Security Business Developer at ENGIE, an Elastic MSP. Remco Sprooten is the Product Owner for the security team. Together they describe how their team expanded their security-as-a-service offer to address operational technology (OT) as well as traditional IT systems. ENGIE is based in the Netherlands and active in 50+ countries across Europe, the Americas, and Asia-Pacific.
The 2010 Stuxnet malicious software attack on a uranium enrichment plant in Iran had all the twists and turns of a spy thriller. The plant was air gapped (not connected to the internet) so it couldn’t be targeted directly by an outsider. Instead, the attackers infected five of the plant’s partner organizations, hoping that an engineer from one of them would unknowingly introduce the malware to the netw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Gubbels,Remco Sprooten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With BGP Address Family Resource Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-bgp-address-family-resource-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-bgp-address-family-resource-modules"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern enterprise networks have grown a lot in size and complexity, making them more difficult to manage than ever before. Working on these complex networks manually can be tedious, time-consuming, costly, and more prone to error.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2021: Get with the Program]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=25406</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/camundacon-2021-get-with-the-program/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T12:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The countdown has officially begun for CamundaCon 2021. Our agenda is now live, and registration is open for you to reserve your spot and join us September 22–23. 
The post CamundaCon 2021: Get with the Program appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charley Mann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 27th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/27/this-week-in-spring-july-27th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/27/this-week-in-spring-july-27th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, Spring fans, from the beautiful island of Oahu, Hawaii. How’re you doing? We’ve got a ton of stuff to look at so let’s get to it! 


  
In last week’s A Bootiful Podcast, I talk to industry analyst, fascinating person, strategist, and storyteller Michael Coté

  
I love this look at building a first application with RabbitMQ streams

  
I loved this infographic by Dormain Drewitz on modernizing the mainframe

  
Premiering Now: SpringOne Tour - July 2021: Do or Do Not, There is no try{} in Production

  
Spring Boot 2.4.9 is now available

  
Spring Boot 2.5.3 is now available

  
Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1 is now available

  
Spring Data is a 10 years old today the 23rd of July 2021!

  
This Week in Spring - July 20th, 2021

  
Using Java 16 records with Thymeleaf

  
Spring Cloud scales Spring Boot apps to billions of requests per day without the hassle of managing infrastructure. See it in action and hear how Swiss Re is acceleratin

  
Register for @SpringOne today]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an Event-Based HA Architecture with Nomad and Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-an-event-based-ha-architecture-with-nomad-and-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-an-event-based-ha-architecture-with-nomad-and-consul"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how content moderation service Chatsight uses HashiCorp Nomad and Consul to speed deployment and maximize uptime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud is now available on Google Cloud in Asia Pacific Northeast 3 (Seoul)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-available-on-google-cloud-in-asia-pacific-northeast-3-seoul</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-available-on-google-cloud-in-asia-pacific-northeast-3-seoul"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce you can now run Elastic Cloud on Google Cloud in the Asia Pacific Northeast 3 (Seoul) region.  
  
Elastic Cloud gives you the power of enterprise search, observability, and security in the Asia Pacific Northeast 3 (Seoul) region of Google Cloud. Easily search applications, websites, and workplace content platforms for information. Quickly gain deep insights into your environment by monitoring applications and uptime as well as analyzing centralized logs and metrics. You can also help protect your technology investment by layering endpoint security with security event monitoring (SIEM).  
  
Deploy your own way 
 Elastic Cloud gives you the flexibility to run where and how you want. Deploy in the cloud on Amazon Web Services, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure, or all the above. You can choose between our managed service offering, or manage the service yourself with built-in automation and orchestration tools. 
  
When you log in to the Elastic Cloud console, simply select your preferred region and cloud service provider and choose how you want to optimize your deployment based on the compute, memory, or I/O requirements of your specific use case. Once you click “Create deployment,” your Elastic Cloud workload is provisioned in minutes.  
  
Visit our documentation to learn more. 
  
Elastic Cloud and marketplace integration 
 If you are a Google Cloud customer, you can also subscribe to Elastic Cloud (Elasticsearch managed service) via the Google Cloud Marketplace. You can select between usage plans and integrated billing consolidates your Elastic Cloud usage charges into your existing Google Cloud bill. Your Elastic Cloud spend accrues towards your Google Cloud spending commitments. 
  
Getting started is easy: Log in to the Elastic Cloud console or sign up for a free 14-day trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controlling Processes in a Smart Factory with the Camunda Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=24939</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/controlling-processes-in-a-smart-factory-with-the-camunda-platform/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T14:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how a novel software stack can reduce the gap between the production shop floor and enterprise-level management systems in Industry 4.0
The post Controlling Processes in a Smart Factory with the Camunda Platform appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charley Mann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pulsar Rerevisted with Enrico Olivelli]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11299</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/26/pulsar-rerevisted-with-enrico-olivelli/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pulsar-rerevisted-with-enrico-olivelli"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T09:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous episode, Pulsar Revisited, we discussed how the company DataStax has added to their product stack Astra Streaming, their cloud-native messaging and event streaming service that’s built on top of Apache Pulsar. We discussed Apache Pulsar and the added features DataStax offers like injecting machine learning into your data streams and viewing real-time
The post Pulsar Rerevisted with Enrico Olivelli appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pulsar Revisited with Jonathan Ellis]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11289</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/23/pulsar-revisited-with-jonathan-ellis/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pulsar-revisited-with-jonathan-ellis"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T23:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Pulsar is a cloud-native, distributed messaging and streaming platform originally created at Yahoo! and now a top-level Apache Software Foundation project (pulsar.apache.org). Pulsar is used by many large companies like Yahoo!, Verizon media, Tencent, and Splunk. The company DataStax, an open, multi-cloud stack for modern data apps, has added to their product stack Astra
The post Pulsar Revisited with Jonathan Ellis appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.23]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62012</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-07-23/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T17:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Friday! With Jay out of the office this week, I’m back with some great community content to keep you going until he’s back.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.23 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Murawski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premiering Now: SpringOne Tour - July 2021: Do or Do Not, There is no try{} in Production]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/23/premiering-now-springone-tour-july-2021-do-or-do-not-there-is-no-try-in-production</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/23/premiering-now-springone-tour-july-2021-do-or-do-not-there-is-no-try-in-production"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this July 2021 installment of SpringOne Tour, Josh Long, Cora Iberkleid, Angie Jones, Madhura Bhave, Bella Bai, Olga Maciaszek-Sharma, Whitney Lee, and Nate Schutta look at the wide and wonderful world of testing, continuous integration, and continuous delivery. 

This event - a mini-conference if you will - is two hours and some change long and features dedicated segments from the industry’s best, so grab a drink, a note pad, and let’s get to it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-6-0-m1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-6-0-m1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 120 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Auto-configuration for Spring Data Envers

  
More metrics support (including task execution and scheduling export and support for the Dynatrace v2 API)

  
Auto-configured Spring Web Service Server Tests

  
Improved Configuration of the Maven Plugin’s Start Goal


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests. Our next set of releases are due August 19, 2021.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitchell's New Role at HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mitchell-s-new-role-at-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mitchell-s-new-role-at-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mitchell Hashimoto takes on a new individual contributor role at HashiCorp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.3 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-5-3-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-5-3-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T14:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.3 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 58 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.4.9 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-4-9-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-4-9-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T10:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.4.9 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 35 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stack Overflow for Teams: A Centralized Knowledge Sharing and Collaboration Platform with Tom Limoncelli]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11280</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/22/stack-overflow-for-teams-a-centralized-knowledge-sharing-and-collaboration-platform-with-tom-limoncelli/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=stack-overflow-for-teams-a-centralized-knowledge-sharing-and-collaboration-platform-with-tom-limoncelli"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T09:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever googled a CS or programming question, you likely found an answer (or many) on Stack Overflow. Founded in 2008 and named after a common computing error, Stack Overflow empowers the world to develop technology through collective knowledge. More than 100 million people visit Stack Overflow every month making it one of the
The post Stack Overflow for Teams: A Centralized Knowledge Sharing and Collaboration Platform with Tom Limoncelli appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: industry analyst, fascinating person, strategist, and storyteller Michael Coté]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/a-bootiful-podcast-industry-analyst-fascinating-person-strategist-and-storyteller-michael-cot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/a-bootiful-podcast-industry-analyst-fascinating-person-strategist-and-storyteller-michael-cot"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to industry analyst, fascinating person, strategist, and storyteller Michael Coté (@cote).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Duplicate Batch Jobs in HashiCorp Nomad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-duplicate-batch-jobs-in-hashicorp-nomad</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-duplicate-batch-jobs-in-hashicorp-nomad"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two approaches to injecting variability into your Nomad batch job template without having to modify the template in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Contact Center Day – July 2021]]></title>
        <id>00b7c611ad2f6105489605e59f50390273ecc710</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/9-I5Zf71gm0/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T15:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, I ordered from Amazon.fr a box of four toothpaste tubes, but only one was in the box. I called Amazon’s customer center. The agent immediately found my order without me having to share the long order number. She issued a refund and told me I even can keep the one tube I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CockroachDB: Distributed Databases and Containerization with Spencer Kimball]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11275</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/21/cockroachdb-distributed-databases-and-containerization-with-spencer-kimball/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cockroachdb-distributed-databases-and-containerization-with-spencer-kimball"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T09:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2003, Google developed a robust cluster management system called Borg. This enabled them to manage clusters with tens of thousands of machines, moving them away from virtual machines and firmly into container management. Then, in 2014, they open sourced a version of Borg called Kubernetes, or K8s.  Now, in 2021, CockroachDB is a distributed
The post CockroachDB: Distributed Databases and Containerization with Spencer Kimball appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Herding (Apache) Camels with HashiCorp Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/herding-apache-camels-with-hashicorp-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/herding-apache-camels-with-hashicorp-consul"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how to keep track of your Apache Camel services running throughout a deployment, and enable them to communicate with one another in a multi-cloud or hybrid cloud environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes – @Azure Logic Apps with @ChloeCondon]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61948</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-azure-logic-apps-with-chloecondon/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T16:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes – @Azure Logic Apps with @ChloeCondon appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 20th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/20/this-week-in-spring-july-20th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/20/this-week-in-spring-july-20th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T14:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, my friends, from Hawai’i, where I’m currently on vacation! And, because I’m on vacation, I’ll cut to the chase: there’s a lot of great stuff to get to this week (surprise!) 

But first, a friendly turtle I met the other day:


You’re welcome. Now then, where were we? Oh right! 


  
In last week’s installment of A Bootiful Podcast, I talk about visualizing software architecture with the C4 model with architect Simon Brown. Don’t miss this one!

  
Spring Tips: Some cool features possible with Spring Integration 5.5

  
Have you checked out the speakers in this year’s SpringOne, on September 1st to 2nd, 2021? I’ll be there and so will many amazing others!

  
Spring Data 2021.0.3 and 2020.0.11 released

  
Spring Data 2021.1.0-M1 released

  
Spring Framework 5.3.9 and 5.2.16 available now

  
I love this blog looking at Spring GraphQL Milestone One

  
Spring Security 5.6.0-M1 released

  
The State of Spring Survey is back and we want to hear from you!

  
I love to see this, finally, Building applications with RabbitMQ streams

  
Blog: Kubernetes Release Cadence Change: Here’s What You Need To Know]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fun with private Automation Hub - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/fun-with-private-automation-hub-part-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/fun-with-private-automation-hub-part-2"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous blog post, I provided a brief history on Ansible Content Collections and demonstrated how to upload a Collection to a private Automation Hub. We ended the blog by synchronizing content from Ansible Galaxy and Automation Hub. Today, we will configure Ansible Tower to communicate with private Automation Hub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Leroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sust Global: Taking Action Against Climate Change with Josh Gilbert]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11270</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/20/sust-global-taking-action-against-climate-change-with-josh-gilbert/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sust-global-taking-action-against-climate-change-with-josh-gilbert"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T09:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments, consumers, and companies across the world are becoming more aware and attentive to the risks and causes of climate change. From recycling to using solar power, people are looking for ways to reduce their carbon footprint. Markets like the financial sector, governments, and consulting are looking for ways to understand climate data to make
The post Sust Global: Taking Action Against Climate Change with Josh Gilbert appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EBS io2 Block Express Volumes with Amazon EC2 R5b Instances Are Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>4f26815f4609dfa07968fe11baa5223ab8c8533c</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/o7h88XQ3T_Y/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T20:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2020, we previewed Amazon EBS io2 Block Express volumes, the next-generation server storage architecture that delivers the first SAN built for the cloud. Block Express is designed to meet the requirements of the largest, most I/O-intensive, mission-critical deployments of Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle, SAP HANA, and SAS Analytics on AWS. Today, I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imply Infra: Big Data Analysis and Real-World Examples with Jad Naous]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11265</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/19/imply-infra-big-data-analysis-and-real-world-examples-with-jad-naous/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=imply-infra-big-data-analysis-and-real-world-examples-with-jad-naous"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T18:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big data analytics is the process of collecting data, processing and cleaning it, then analyzing it with techniques like data mining, predictive analytics, and deep learning. This process requires a suite of tools to operate efficiently. Data analytics can save companies money, drive product development, and give insight into the market and customers. The company
The post Imply Infra: Big Data Analysis and Real-World Examples with Jad Naous appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.6.0-M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/19/spring-security-5-6-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/19/spring-security-5-6-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Security 5.6.0-M1!



In addition to dependency upgrades, bug fixes, and minor enhancements, the milestone contains a few noteworthy changes:





An AuthorizationManager for method security



Support for any data type in Access Token Response



A separate repository for Spring Security samples





You can find the complete details in the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convince Ashmeet Sidana to Invest in Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11262</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/18/how-to-convince-ashmeet-sidana-to-invest-in-your-business/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-convince-ashmeet-sidana-to-invest-in-your-business"/>
        <updated>2021-07-18T17:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ashmeet Sidana is the founder of Engineering Capital.
The post How to Convince Ashmeet Sidana to Invest in Your Business appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HashiCorp Does Developer Advocacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-does-developer-advocacy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-does-developer-advocacy"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about our approach to developer advocacy, from choosing Developer Advocates to represent and engage our community, to how we approach the work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.0.3 and 2020.0.11 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/16/spring-data-2021-0-3-and-2020-0-11-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/16/spring-data-2021-0-3-and-2020-0-11-released"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data2021.0.2 and 2020.0.10 service releases.

Both releases are built on top of Spring Framework 5.3.9. For your convenience, you can consume these releases through Spring Boot 2.5.3 and 2.4.9, respectively. Our teammates on the Boot team will release those in about a week.

The service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.

To round things off, here are the links to the artifacts, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.0.3


  
Spring Data Commons 2.5.3 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.2.3 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.5.3 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data KeyValue 2.5.3 -…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.1.0-M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/16/spring-data-2021-1-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/16/spring-data-2021-1-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data 2021.1.0-M1 milestone release.

Both releases are built on top of Spring Framework 5.3.9. For your convenience, you can consume this release through Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1, which our team mates on the Boot team will release in about a week.

The 2021.1 release train ships a set of features and dependency upgrades.
The most important changes are:


  
Upgrade to Querydsl 5.

  
Support for a wide range of Redis 6.2 commands.

  
Support for dialect-dependent custom conversions in Spring Data JDBC. This was used to improve the support of java.time types across multiple databases.

  
Support for streaming large result sets in Spring Data JDBC.

  
Support for AggregateReference in query derivation.

  
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design for the future: Improving the Camunda Optimize Report builder experience]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=21705</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/06/design-for-the-future-improving-the-camunda-optimize-report-builder-experience/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T10:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize is maturing. New features and a better understanding of user needs required a refinement of the tool's UI and provided Camunda’s design team with an opportunity to improve the user experience.
The post Design for the future: Improving the Camunda Optimize Report builder experience appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid Threat Protection with Sumo Logic Cloud SIEM Powered by AWS]]></title>
        <id>372e69aca051cae4f4c1b6a43259e8a84c0f5a51</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/aTcqLe6p0cY/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT security teams need to have a real-time understanding of what’s happening with their infrastructure and applications. They need to be able to find and correlate data in this continuous flood of information to identify unexpected behaviors or patterns that can lead to a security breach. To simplify and automate this process, many solutions have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Stack: A New DevOps Experience with Juraj Masar]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11238</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/15/better-stack-a-new-devops-experience-with-juraj-masar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=better-stack-a-new-devops-experience-with-juraj-masar"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T21:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps has shortened the development life cycle for countless applications and is embraced by companies around the world. But managing and monitoring multiple environments is still a major pain point, particularly when companies need to mix cloud and legacy systems. Knowing when services go down and quickly pinpointing the cause is essential for continuous development. 
The post Better Stack: A New DevOps Experience with Juraj Masar appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Visualizing software architecture with the C4 model with architect Simon Brown]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/15/a-bootiful-podcast-visualizing-software-architecture-with-the-c4-model-with-architect-simon-brown</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/15/a-bootiful-podcast-visualizing-software-architecture-with-the-c4-model-with-architect-simon-brown"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, I talk to author, prolific public speaker, an architect’s architect, and one of the most interesting people I get to bump into, and learn from, in this wacky, wild, and wonderful ecosystem of ours: Simon Brown (@simonbrown).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of Spring Survey is back!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/15/state-of-spring-survey-is-back</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/15/state-of-spring-survey-is-back"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR - head over to spring.io/survey to take the State of Spring 2021 survey! You can also RT this tweet and help spread the word! Thank you <3


We ran the State of Spring survey last year, and it was a huge success. Spring community members across the globe, like you, shared their views and experiences, and it all made for fantastic reading.

The survey is back this year, and we want to hear from you! How can Spring help you build new apps and experiences this year? What would you like us to change? This year, we have new sections on Spring Native, building & sharing APIs internally/externally, and a deeper dive on Data.

In exchange for 15 minutes of your time taking the survey, you’ll be among the first to receive our report and the insights included in it. 

Sounds good? Head over to spring.io/survey now! The survey will close at the end of July. 

Do consider helping us share the survey by retweeting this post on Spring Central twitter, and thank you for sharing your thoughts and experiences with us! 

The Spring Team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Your Summer Spotify Playlist with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/build-your-summer-spotify-playlist-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/build-your-summer-spotify-playlist-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow our new tutorial to build your summer playlist with Terraform using a community-authored Spotify provider. Hear from the author and share your playlist for a chance to win a free HashiCorp T-shirt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paging Doctor Cloud! Amazon HealthLake Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>57587dfa2c2661bbc68cad661a38c942328e95e6</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/DuRcp2g2t04/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2020, we previewed Amazon HealthLake, a fully managed, HIPAA-eligible service that allows healthcare and life sciences customers to aggregate their health information from different silos and formats into a structured, centralized AWS data lake, and extract insights from that data with analytics and machine learning (ML). Today, I’m very happy to announce […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Some cool features possible with Spring Integration 5.5]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/14/spring-tips-some-cool-features-possible-with-spring-integration-5-5</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/14/spring-tips-some-cool-features-possible-with-spring-integration-5-5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, I look at some key features made possible by the new Spring Integration 5.5 release, including the new Spring .zip archive support and the new Spring Native hints supporting GraalVM native images]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation Savings Planner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-savings-planner</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-savings-planner"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-plan your automation savings with Red Hat Insights for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Science on AWS: Implementing AI and ML Pipelines on AWS with Chris Fregly]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11236</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/14/data-science-on-aws-implementing-ai-and-ml-pipelines-on-aws-with-chris-fregly/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-science-on-aws-implementing-ai-and-ml-pipelines-on-aws-with-chris-fregly"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T09:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data science is an interdisciplinary field that combines strong technical skills with industry knowledge to perform a large range of jobs. Data scientists solve business questions with hands-on work cleaning and analyzing data, building machine learning models and applying algorithms, and generating dynamic visuals and tools to understand the world from the data it generates.
The post Data Science on AWS: Implementing AI and ML Pipelines on AWS with Chris Fregly appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.9 and 5.2.16 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/14/spring-framework-5-3-9-and-5-2-16-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/14/spring-framework-5-3-9-and-5-2-16-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T08:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.9 and 5.2.16 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.9 includes 45 fixes and improvements. Spring Framework 5.2.16 includes 12 selected fixes and improvements.

Stay tuned for follow-up Spring Boot releases next week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 13th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/13/this-week-in-spring-july-13th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/13/this-week-in-spring-july-13th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How’re you doing? I’m heads-down, hurriedly making final preparations for tomorrow’s SpringOne Tour episode installment. This is going to be SO MUCH FUN. Do NOT miss this show tomorrow morning, 10AM California time. I’ll be there, along with my friends Madhura Bhave, Olga Maciaszek-Sharma, Bella Bai, Whitney Lee, Core Iberkleid, Nate Schutta, and special guest star Angie Jones. 

We look forward to seeing you there and we’ll explore the wide and wonderful world of continuous delivery, testing and more together. 


  
JOOQ 3.15.0 Release  is out, and includes support for R2DBC (and much more)

  
Neat! The JRE will be UTF-8 by default instead of dangerously assuming the host operating system’s default: openjdk/jdk

  
A Bootiful Podcast: Matt Raible Last week, I talked to Matt Raible, and you can too! I love that guy. So happy he was able to join the show again.

  
Spring Tips: Spring Cloud Square

  
This is neat: you can run TestNG tests with JUnit 5 now

  
Piotr Mińkowski on Twitter: JPAstreamer is a library for expressing JPA/Hibernate queries as Java streams. It can be also integrated with Spring. 

  
Apress’ R2DBC Revealed book is available for order

  
Scaling Spring Boot Microservices

  
Have you seen the lineup for our annual tentpole conference, SpringOne, this  Sep 1–2, 2021? I’ll be there and so will a ton of other amazing people.

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.1.2 available now

  
Spring Cloud Hoxton.SR12 has been released

  
Check out this cool Spring GraphQL demo project]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Move Fast with Jeff Meyerson]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11231</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/13/move-fast-with-jeff-meyerson/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=move-fast-with-jeff-meyerson"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T16:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode we discuss the new Move Fast book, as well as many aspects of the current state of software engineering. Daliana Liu interviews Jeff Meyerson, host of Software Daily and author of Move Fast. This interview was also recorded as a video podcast. Check out the video on the Software Daily YouTube channel.
The post Move Fast with Jeff Meyerson appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS) – 15 Years and Still Queueing!]]></title>
        <id>2c8d960c80b46e817beea8943dac6c1c391c0232</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/yQjvDBuBwoA/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time sure does fly! I wrote about the production launch of Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS) back in 2006, with no inkling that I would still be blogging fifteen years later, or that this service would still be growing rapidly while remaining fundamental to the architecture of so many different types of web-scale applications. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.1.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=24420</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/camunda-cloud-110-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T10:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.1.0, the next version of our innovative process automation SaaS offering, is here. 
The post Camunda Cloud 1.1.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Mueller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16.0-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=23929</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/camunda-platform-runtime-7160-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T07:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16.0-alpha3 is here, featuring support for Java 15 & GraalVM JavaScript, and a new create deployment REST API. 
The post Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16.0-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda BPM Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Modeler 4.9 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=23565</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/camunda-modeler-49-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Camunda Modeler 4.9 release ships with support for Camunda Cloud 1.1, improvements to the core editor UI, BPMN and DMN editor enhancements, and bug fixes.
The post Camunda Modeler 4.9 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nico Rehwaldt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.5.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=24143</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/camunda-optimize-350-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T07:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.5.0. which ships with new capabilities including Multi Process Reports and an Elasticsearch headers plugin.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.5.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Mueller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Lineage: Understanding Data Lineage at Scale with Julien Le Dem]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11210</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/12/data-lineage-understanding-data-lineage-at-scale-with-julien-le-dem/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-lineage-understanding-data-lineage-at-scale-with-julien-le-dem"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T18:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big Data has exploded the past decade as cloud computing and more efficient hardware made scaling essentially limitless. Products like Uber revolve entirely around analyzing data to provide rides. According to an EMC/IDC study, there was approximately 5.2TB of data for every person in 2020. That estimate was made before the transition to remote work,
The post Data Lineage: Understanding Data Lineage at Scale with Julien Le Dem appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>