<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-09-19T02:32:51.024Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-19T02:32:51.024Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The last 1%]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41964</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/712009696/0/sethsblog~The-last/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T09:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you apply for something with a 99% rejection rate (which is more common than it sounds–job openings, sales pitches, fellowships, journals, etc.) that’s pretty close to 100%. Something with a 99% certainty is generally considered a sure thing. Hence this Journal, which promises to reject every single person who submits an article. The absurdity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at Interspeech 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/google-at-interspeech-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/google-at-interspeech-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T02:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cat Armato, Program Manager, Google 
This week, the 23rd Annual Conference of the International Speech Communication Association (INTERSPEECH 2022) is being held in Incheon, South Korea, representing one of the world’s most extensive conferences on research and technology of spoken language understanding and processing. Over 2,000 experts in speech-related research fields gather to take part in oral presentations and poster sessions and to collaborate with streamed events across the globe. 
We are excited to be a Diamond Sponsor of INTERSPEECH 2022, where we will be showcasing nearly 50 research publications and supporting a number of workshops, special sessions and tutorials. We welcome in-person attendees to drop by the Google booth to meet our researchers and participate in Q&…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust Online Allocation with Dual Mirror Descent]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/robust-online-allocation-with-dual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/robust-online-allocation-with-dual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Santiago Balseiro, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research, and Associate Professor at Columbia University, and Vahab Mirrokni, Distinguished Scientist, Google Research 
The emergence of digital technologies has transformed decision making across commercial sectors such as airlines, online retailing, and internet advertising. Today, real-time decisions need to be repeatedly made in highly uncertain and rapidly changing environments. Moreover, organizations usually have limited resources, which need to be efficiently allocated across decisions. Such problems are referred to as online allocation problems with resource constraints, and applications abound. Some examples include: 
 
Bidding with Budget Constraints: Advertisers increasingly purchase ad slots using auction-based mark…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Drift Detection Helps Maintain a Secure Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-drift-detection-helps-maintain-a-secure-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-drift-detection-helps-maintain-a-secure-infrastructure"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drift detection is essential to maintaining efficiency while minimizing risk and giving teams confidence in your infrastructure as code (IaC) provisioning workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we tripled max concurrent jobs to boost performance of GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-16-how-we-tripled-max-concurrent-jobs-to-boost-performance-of-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-16-how-we-tripled-max-concurrent-jobs-to-boost-performance-of-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T15:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Actions team has done lots of work to improve the performance and resource consumption of Actions on GHES in the past year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin News: 1.7.20-RC, kotlinx.serialization 1.4.0, KotlinConf Call for Speakers, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=279329</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/09/kotlin-news-august/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T13:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin 1.7.20-RC Released Here are some highlights from this preview version of Kotlin: K2 now supports several new plugins. A preview of the ..< operator for open-ended ranges has been added. The K/N memory manager is enabled by default. Inline classes with generic underlying type (experimental) have been added. Read about all the updates kotlinx.serialization […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ksenia Shneyveys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2.2 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=276342</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/09/webstorm-2022-2-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T10:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2.2, the second bug-fix update for WebStorm 2022.2, is now available! You can update to v2022.2.2 using the Toolbox App, installing it right from the IDE, or by downloading it from our website. Here are some of the fixes available in v2022.2.2: We’ve fixed the bug with ESLint 8.23.0 where WebStorm was failing with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“And we also”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43001</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/711887411/0/sethsblog~And-we-also/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T10:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The simplest way to run a business is to have no also. We maximize profit, period. At least you’re being honest about it. If you say, “and we also care about the environment,” or “we also care about our people and treat them like family,” or even, “we’re here to serve our customers…” now you’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.16.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/16/spring-tools-4-16-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/16/spring-tools-4-16-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.16.0 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
updated to Eclipse 2022-09 release (new and noteworthy)

  
new distribution build for Linux on ARM included now (experimental) - downloads are here

  
m2e 2.0.5 release included in distribution builds for Eclipse


important note for upgrading from a previous installation on Eclipse


  
Due to the major update to m2e 2.0 that comes with the Eclipse 2022-09 release, several additional third-party m2e connector extensions that the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution had installed in the past are no longer compatible. This prevents the automatic update of installations of Spring Tool…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workflow diagram and pattern examples using BPMN models]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=62079</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/workflow-diagram-and-pattern-examples-using-bpmn-models/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are multiple angles to look at workflows one of which is patterns. The Workflow Patterns initiative differentiates between control, data, and resource perspectives. They are not just focusing on the modeling language as such but have workflow systems in mind too. It’s valuable to have a closer look at those patterns and discuss which parts of it can be shown and even automated in BPMN, and which parts are taken care of in the technical implementation. I have seen BPMN diagrams that try to include every aspect in the diagram itself. This often leads to overloaded BPMN models with a lack of clear transparency of the business flow. Therefore, it is important to focus on all aspects of workflow...
The post Workflow diagram and pattern examples using BPMN models appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nele Uhlemann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The grassroots]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42756</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/711696621/0/sethsblog~The-grassroots/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting at the top seems like great advice. Deal with the people with power and authority. Except… Power and authority aren’t often in the same place. The real power is usually foundational. What happens when humans interact. The way things are around here. Often, the people who are ostensibly in charge are simply choosing from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Sleuth OpenTelemetry (OTel) 1.1.0 Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/16/spring-cloud-sleuth-opentelemetry-otel-1-1-0-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/16/spring-cloud-sleuth-opentelemetry-otel-1-1-0-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the first General Availability (RELEASE) of the Spring Cloud Sletuh OTel 1.1.0 project is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the reference documentation for more information.
What is this?

Spring Cloud Sleuth OTel is an extension project to Spring Cloud Sleuth that comes with an OpenTelemetry tracer.

As always, we welcome feedback on GitHub, on Gitter, on Stack Overflow, or on Twitter.

To get started with Maven with a BOM (dependency management only):


<dependencyManagement>
    <dependencies>
        <dependency>
            <groupId>org.springframework.cloud</groupId>
            <artifactId>spring-cloud-dependencies</artifactId>
            <version>2021.0.4</version>…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IT leaders build more proactive organizations using observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-it-leaders-build-more-proactive-organizations-using-observability-APM-MTTR</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-it-leaders-build-more-proactive-organizations-using-observability-APM-MTTR"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mining performance data for insights can be the difference-maker in positive business outcomes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Weston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IT leaders build more proactive organizations using observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-it-leaders-build-more-proactive-organizations-using-observability-APM-MTTR</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-it-leaders-build-more-proactive-organizations-using-observability-APM-MTTR"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In the lingua franca of modern IT architecture, latency is the perfect metaphor for an unresponsive business. If an organization’s latency is problematic, operations teams are always a step behind — reacting to events rather than anticipating them. 

But it doesn’t have to stay that way. 

For instance, Wells Fargo, a multinational financial services company headquartered in San Francisco, CA, realized that in order to measure performance of their myriad applications, they had to have a modern observability and APM solution in place. Eric Chho, vice president of engineering at Wells Fargo, is responsible for providing observability to the many application teams across Wells’ wide-ranging IT organization. Chho says, “being able to measure golden signals [of improving application availabil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Weston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cursed mRNA Cocktail]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2673/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2673/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/cursed_mrna_cocktail.png" title="Serve one each to guests whose last cursed cocktail was more than 2 months ago." alt="Serve one each to guests whose last cursed cocktail was more than 2 months ago." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2022 preview – A conference for all things process orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=62651</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/camunda-con-2022-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T21:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our annual process orchestration conference, CamundaCon, is back this October 5-6 with a new hybrid format. Join us online from the comfort of your desk or meet us in person in Berlin, Germany. No matter how you CamundaCon, it will be a fun and insightful event! This year’s agenda is jam-packed with an all-star line-up of experts who will share their experience automating, orchestrating, and improving core business processes. You’ll hear real-world use cases and best practices from companies across all industries that have found innovative ways to deliver better customer experiences through orchestration. Here’s a sneak peek at a few of the sessions you won’t want to miss: Navdeep Singh of Walmart will share how they manage customer experiences...
The post CamundaCon 2022 preview – A conference for all things process orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2022.2.2 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=279206</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/09/2022-2-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T20:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released the second bug-fix update for PyCharm 2022.2. You can update to this version from inside the IDE, by using the Toolbox App, or by using snaps for Ubuntu. You can also download it from our website. In this minor release, we’ve included major improvements for Python dataclass support.  For the attrs package, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PaLI: Scaling Language-Image Learning in 100+ Languages]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/pali-scaling-language-image-learning-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/pali-scaling-language-image-learning-in.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T19:16:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xi Chen and Xiao Wang, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Advanced language models (e.g., GPT, GLaM, PaLM and T5) have demonstrated diverse capabilities and achieved impressive results across tasks and languages by scaling up their number of parameters. Vision-language (VL) models can benefit from similar scaling to address many tasks, such as image captioning, visual question answering (VQA), object recognition, and in-context optical-character-recognition (OCR). Increasing the success rates for these practical tasks is important for everyday interactions and applications. Furthermore, for a truly universal system, vision-language models should be able to operate in many languages, not just one. 
In “PaLI: A Jointly-Scaled Multilingual Language-Image Model”, we introduce a uni…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.4 Beta Adds Nomad Variables and Updates Service Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-4-adds-nomad-variables-and-updates-service-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-4-adds-nomad-variables-and-updates-service-discovery"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The beta release of HashiCorp Nomad 1.4 enhances native service discovery support with health checks and introduces Nomad Variables, which lets users store configuration values.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 210 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65737</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-210-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T17:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We spent most of sprint 210 focusing on accessibility issues and bug fixes. Here is a list of the items that have been resolved.
Issue
Unable to create a branch from card
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 210 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2.2 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=279016</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/09/phpstorm-2022-2-2-is-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T17:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve released PhpStorm 2022.2.2, the second minor release for PhpStorm 2022.2 You can update by using the Toolbox App or from right inside the IDE. You can also download PhpStorm 2022.2.2 from our website. These are the most notable changes and bug fixes: Added: support for remote interpreters for Rector (WI-66504) Fixed: ESLint 8.23 fatal […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical CLion Bug-Fix Update 2022.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=279148</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/09/critical-clion-bug-fix-update-2022-2-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T17:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The urgent CLion bug-fix update 2022.2.3 is now available. In CLion 2022.2.2 we unfortunately introduced an issue that caused the IDE to crash when Python interpreters were configured (PY-56176). As the source code for the issue is located in a plugin bundled into CLion, simply updating the plugin doesn’t solve the problem. Thus, we’ve prepared […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode Bug-Fix Update 2022.2.2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=279175</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/09/appcode-bug-fix-update-2022-2-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T17:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AppCode 2022.2.2 bug-fix update is now available! Build 222.4167.29 is available from our website, from the Toolbox App, or via update patch from the IDE itself. DOWNLOAD APPCODE Here are the main highlights: Quick Documentation: The Quick Documentation popup for Swift code no longer scrambles the order of the access modifiers and keywords (OC-22712). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: big data legend, former Pivot, and friend to the Spring community, Tim Spann]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/15/a-bootiful-podcast-big-data-legend-former-pivot-and-friend-to-the-spring-community-tim-spann</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/15/a-bootiful-podcast-big-data-legend-former-pivot-and-friend-to-the-spring-community-tim-spann"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to big data legend, former Pivot, and friend to the Spring community, Tim Spann (@PaaSDev), about big data, StreamNative, and Apache Pulsar, and Spring for Apache Pulsar. Get your notebooks ready for this one, class!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Tools Explained Using a Minecraft World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-tools-explained-using-a-minecraft-world</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-tools-explained-using-a-minecraft-world"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit our Minecraft world and learn how HashiCorp Vault, Consul, Nomad, and Boundary all work through fun analogies. Join us at HashiConf Global 2022 — in Los Angeles or online Oct. 4-6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2022.3 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=279041</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/09/15/resharper-2022-3-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T13:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a few weeks since ReSharper 2022.2 was released, bringing you extended support for C# 11 features, memory-optimized solution-wide analysis, and a brand-new Virtual Formatter, among other exciting additions and improvements.  While we’re unpacking your feedback in preparation for the next Early Access Program (EAP) cycle, we thought it would be the perfect time […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2022.3 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=279081</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/09/15/rider-2022-3-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T13:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the start of a new release cycle of our Early Access Program (EAP) just around the corner, we think it’s time to share our plans for Rider 2022.3.  Keep in mind that plans are always subject to change, and some features and fixes may have to be postponed to a later release. Also, you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase your resilience with new regions in Camunda Platform 8 SaaS]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=62542</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/increase-your-resilience-with-new-regions-in-camunda-platform-8-saas/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce new regions for Camunda Platform 8 SaaS that further strengthen the resilience, performance, and data requirements for our SaaS customers. Enterprise customers can now choose to create their clusters in a number of regions including Europe West, US Central, US East, and the most recent addition, Australia South East. This provides multiple benefits, such as increasing availability, allowing to set up fail-safes, adhering to regulatory requirements for regional data storage, and reduced latency due to closer physical proximity. Resilience and redundancy in technology are important for all modern organizations and are top of mind for many. Across industries, organizations need a solution that scales effectively and is resilient to provide a good base for process orchestration....
The post Increase your resilience with new regions in Camunda Platform 8 SaaS appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annie Talvasto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL for Backend Developers on JetBrains Academy]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=278768</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/09/15/sql-for-backend-developers-on-jetbrains-academy/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T09:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to work with data is one of the most in-demand skills in tech. Especially so if you want to work in backend development. For example, almost every website or software application nowadays has a registration and login form. Behind the simple two-field window, there is a complex process of storing, retrieving, and changing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.0-M6 and 5.3.23 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/15/spring-framework-6-0-0-m6-and-5-3-23-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/15/spring-framework-6-0-0-m6-and-5-3-23-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T09:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.0-M6 and 5.3.23 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.23 includes 32 fixes and improvements and is a recommended upgrade for all Spring production scenarios.

Spring Framework 6.0.0-M6 includes 123 additional fixes and improvements specific to the 6.0 branch. This milestone wraps up most of our AOT efforts, in preparation for our release candidate phase. Stay tuned for the announcement of Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5 next week!

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talking about money]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42289</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/711560403/0/sethsblog~Talking-about-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T08:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who benefits when we hesitate to look at money clearly? When we avoid doing a P&L, thinking about pricing, or creating a budget, we’re avoiding the fear that comes with these choices. And we’re also decreasing our odds of success. Good cooks talk about salt. Successful athletes talk about training. Money isn’t the point. But […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.9.6 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/14/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-9-6-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/14/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-9-6-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.9.6 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release updates to Postgres SQL driver 42.2.26 to address CVE-2022-31197. See the release notes for more information.
Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on Stackoverflow or GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Elasticians Unidos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elasticians-unidos</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elasticians-unidos"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 15 through October 15 is Hispanic Heritage month—or as we like to call it, Elasticians Unidos Month. Learn more about how we're celebrating the month with our Elasticians Unidos ERG.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key to reducing cybersecurity risk: search-powered technology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/key-to-reducing-cybersecurity-risk-search-powered-technology</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/key-to-reducing-cybersecurity-risk-search-powered-technology"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity was the top business priority organizations used search-powered technology for today, according to a study conducted by Forrester Consulting, commissioned by Elastic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Radogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is AIOps? A beginner's guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-aiops-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-aiops-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AIOps has become an increasingly important consideration for operations teams. With the rapidly increasing volume of metrics, logs, and traces, operations teams are increasingly relying on machine learning driven AI to analyze data and reduce noise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinay Chandrasekhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Elasticians Unidos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elasticians-unidos</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elasticians-unidos"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Employee resource groups, or Elastician resource groups as we like to call them, are formal groups within Elastic that are aligned with shared identities, experiences, interests, affinities, and allyships. 

We formalized these groups in 2021, but they’ve been a part of our culture since 2016. The formalization means that they are now ensured structure, budget, and a voice based on any dimension of diversity, identity, allyship, and advocacy. This was an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy. 

Each ERG has their own mission and goals, but as a whole they want to create community and belonging around shared interests and experiences. 
Our Core ERGs
We have seven formal ERGs: The Accessibles, Blasticians, ElastAsians, Elasticians Unidos, Rainbow Stack, Mil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key to reducing cybersecurity risk: search-powered technology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/key-to-reducing-cybersecurity-risk-search-powered-technology</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/key-to-reducing-cybersecurity-risk-search-powered-technology"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
It’s time to re-evaluate how we define the term “search.” Today, search has far broader applications than those of a standard search engine query. That’s especially true when it comes to cybersecurity. 

In fact, in a recent survey of 832 data leaders, cybersecurity was named as the top business priority that organizations use search-powered technology for today. The survey, conducted by Forrester Consulting and commissioned by Elastic, defines search-powered technology as tools that enable the search of data across multiple sources, such as websites, applications, databases, and hybrid cloud environments. 

Search capabilities can assist security analysts in detection and response processes such as:

Facilitating real-time detection and protection from endpoints to data centers
Enabling…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Radogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is AIOps? A beginner's guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-aiops-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-aiops-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Understanding AIOps for observability 
Artificial Intelligence for IT Operations (or AIOps for short) continues to be a hot topic among developers, SREs, and DevOps professionals. The case for AIOps is especially crucial given the expansive nature of today’s observability efforts across hybrid and multi-cloud environments. As with most observability platforms, it all starts with your telemetry data: metrics, logs, traces, and events. 

Once IT operations teams collect and begin analyzing that data, the benefit of AIOps becomes rapidly clear. AIOps aims to accurately and proactively identify areas that need attention and assist IT teams in solving issues faster. As human beings, we cannot keep up with analyzing petabytes of raw observability data. Adding AIOps delivers a layer of intellig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinay Chandrasekhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: Two Features for Apps Rollouts Graduate to Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/15/app-rollout-features-reach-stable/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/15/app-rollout-features-reach-stable/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Ravi Gudimetla (Apple), Filip Křepinský (Red Hat), Maciej Szulik (Red Hat)
This blog describes the two features namely minReadySeconds for StatefulSets and maxSurge for DaemonSets that SIG Apps is happy to graduate to stable in Kubernetes 1.25.
Specifying minReadySeconds slows down a rollout of a StatefulSet, when using a RollingUpdate value in .spec.updateStrategy field, by waiting for each pod for a desired time.
This time can be used for initializing the pod (e.g. warming up the cache) or as a delay before acknowledging the pod.
maxSurge allows a DaemonSet workload to run multiple instances of the same pod on a node during a rollout when using a RollingUpdate value in .spec.updateStrategy field.
This helps to minimize the downtime of the DaemonSet for consumers.
These features …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Direct VPC Routing Between On-Premises Networks and AWS Outposts Rack]]></title>
        <id>6d089016af02ca1b0fdb9d5d59d86f2aae0f62a3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-direct-vpc-routing-between-on-premises-networks-and-aws-outposts-rack/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T22:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we announced direct VPC routing for AWS Outposts rack. This enables you to connect Outposts racks and on-premises networks using simplified IP address management. Direct VPC routing automatically advertises Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) subnet CIDR addresses to on-premises networks. This enables you to use the private IP addresses of resources in your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 things you didn’t know you could do with GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-14-8-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-14-8-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T16:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers all over the world are using GitHub Copilot to help speed up their development and increase developer productivity. With GitHub Copilot available to developers everywhere, we’ve found some fun and useful examples of how developers can use GitHub Copilot for things you may not be thinking about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Annotated June-August 2022: C++23 and C23 News, Language Tips and Tricks, and New Tools Releases]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=278925</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/09/cpp-annotated-jun-aug-23/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T12:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve returned with all of the news from June, July, and August 2022 in our latest C++ Annotated digest. We’ve kept silent for a while, and despite these three months being less busy than the rest of the year for many, they were still jam-packed full of awesome news. So, expect today’s digest to be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2.2 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=278763</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/09/intellij-idea-2022-2-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T11:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released the second bug-fix update for v2022.2. You can update to this version from inside the IDE, using the Toolbox App, or using snaps if you are a Ubuntu user. You can also download it from our website. This latest release includes the following fixes and improvements: The Markdown auto-formatting action now correctly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion Bug-Fix Update 2022.2.2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=278894</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/09/clion-bug-fix-update-2022-2-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T11:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CLion 2022.2.2 bug-fix update has been released. Build 222.4167.25 is available from our website, via the Toolbox App, as a snap for Ubuntu, or via patch from the IDE itself. DOWNLOAD CLION Below are the highlights of this update: Refactoring: We fixed a bug that was causing a duplicate name to appear when performing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CAM project in JIRA is moving to GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=61700</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/the-cam-project-in-jira-is-moving-to-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T07:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For almost 10 years, JIRA has been our development issue tracker for the core components of Camunda Platform 7. About 15,000 tickets later, Camunda’s engineering has grown from one team to a team of teams. Many new projects have used GitHub exclusively as a code repository and an issue tracker from the start. In October, we will move the CAM project to GitHub issues. With this change we are reducing the gap: our community can participate in our development processes with a single account. We achieve a unified approach for managing development issues, making it easier for everyone to participate. We thank everyone who has contributed to our CAM issue tracker and hope that the collaboration continues in our new...
The post The CAM project in JIRA is moving to GitHub appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thorben Lindhauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feature creep]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43775</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/711427701/0/sethsblog~Feature-creep/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T07:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding another feature is cheap compared to the benefits it offers to new users or existing ones. Once a feature is added, it is almost never removed. When enough features are added, the system breaks down and fails. This isn’t just software. It’s the menu at the diner. It’s the buttons on the dashboard of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A cyber summer: Students experience Elastic during IU OmniSOC Cybersecurity Summer Internship Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-cyber-summer-students-experience-elastic-during-iu-omnisoc-cybersecurity-summer-internship-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-cyber-summer-students-experience-elastic-during-iu-omnisoc-cybersecurity-summer-internship-program"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a proud sponsor of the Indiana University OmniSOC Cyber Security Summer Internship program, read about how Elastic helps students not only learn about Elastic Security but experience it through interactive training and workshops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Raiguel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing a new streamlined sign-up experience for Elastic Cloud on AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/announcing-a-new-streamlined-sign-up-experience-for-elastic-cloud-on-aws-marketplace</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/announcing-a-new-streamlined-sign-up-experience-for-elastic-cloud-on-aws-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and AWS have collaborated to accelerate results that matter through a streamlined sign-up experience for Elastic on AWS Marketplace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy,Osman Ishaq,Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A cyber summer: Students experience Elastic during IU OmniSOC Cybersecurity Summer Internship Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-cyber-summer-students-experience-elastic-during-iu-omnisoc-cybersecurity-summer-internship-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-cyber-summer-students-experience-elastic-during-iu-omnisoc-cybersecurity-summer-internship-program"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Launched in 2019, the Indiana University (IU) OmniSOC Cybersecurity Summer Internship Program provides students with an opportunity to experience a “day in the life” of a security analyst. The interns learn about the day-to-day operations and the technology used to power a security operations center (SOC). As a proud sponsor of the program since its inception, Elastic leads students through various hands-on training sessions and workshops throughout the program. 
Going beyond the classroom
Unlike the previous two years when in-person participation was not an option, this year’s six-week paid program was conducted in a hybrid setting. Students spent the first three weeks in-person at the OmniSOC in Bloomington, IN. At the conclusion of the three-week training, interns traveled back home t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Raiguel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing a new streamlined sign-up experience for Elastic Cloud on AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/announcing-a-new-streamlined-sign-up-experience-for-elastic-cloud-on-aws-marketplace</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/announcing-a-new-streamlined-sign-up-experience-for-elastic-cloud-on-aws-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Now it's easier than ever for you to get the most value out of your data with Elastic on Amazon Web Services (AWS). We’re pleased to announce a new improvement to help you easily get set up with Elastic on AWS in just a few minutes.
Simplified onboarding: Get set up with Elastic on AWS with just a few clicks
Elastic and AWS have collaborated to build a streamlined UX that greatly simplifies onboarding. Beginning today, you can subscribe to Elastic Cloud with an easier signup and setup experience directly through the AWS Marketplace console. This simplified experience reduces the need to navigate between multiple applications and lets you easily set up Elastic in just a few clicks. The new UX allows you to:

Subscribe to Elastic
Deploy the Elastic Stack in any of Elastic’s supported AWS r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy,Osman Ishaq,Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: PodHasNetwork Condition for Pods]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/14/pod-has-network-condition/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/14/pod-has-network-condition/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author:
Deep Debroy (Apple)
Kubernetes 1.25 introduces Alpha support for a new kubelet-managed pod condition
in the status field of a pod: PodHasNetwork. The kubelet, for a worker node,
will use the PodHasNetwork condition to accurately surface the initialization
state of a pod from the perspective of pod sandbox creation and network
configuration by a container runtime (typically in coordination with CNI
plugins). The kubelet starts to pull container images and start individual
containers (including init containers) after the status of the PodHasNetwork
condition is set to "True". Metrics collection services that report latency of
pod initialization from a cluster infrastructural perspective (i.e. agnostic of
per container characteristics like image size or payload) can utilize the
PodHas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOLNeRF: Learn from One Look]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/lolnerf-learn-from-one-look.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/lolnerf-learn-from-one-look.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T21:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Daniel Rebain, Student Researcher, and Mark Matthews, Senior Software Engineer, Google Research, Perception Team 
An important aspect of human vision is our ability to comprehend 3D shape from the 2D images we observe. Achieving this kind of understanding with computer vision systems has been a fundamental challenge in the field. Many successful approaches rely on multi-view data, where two or more images of the same scene are available from different perspectives, which makes it much easier to infer the 3D shape of objects in the images. 
There are, however, many situations where it would be useful to know 3D structure from a single image, but this problem is generally difficult or impossible to solve. For example, it isn’t necessarily possible to tell the difference between an …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.10 Brings Custom Pipelines and Nomad Plugin Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-10-brings-custom-pipelines-and-nomad-plugin-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-10-brings-custom-pipelines-and-nomad-plugin-updates"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint 0.10 — now generally available — introduces the tech preview of custom pipelines and improvements to the Nomad integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Git’s garbage collection]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-13-scaling-gits-garbage-collection/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-13-scaling-gits-garbage-collection/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T16:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tour of recent work to re-engineer Git’s garbage collection process to scale to our largest and most active repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join GitHub at the Grace Hopper Celebration 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-13-join-github-at-the-grace-hopper-celebration-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-13-join-github-at-the-grace-hopper-celebration-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T13:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re thrilled to be back at the Grace Hopper Celebration at Open Source Day, the largest celebration of women in open source. Stop by and say hi at one of our workshops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible vs. Terraform Demystified]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-vs.-terraform-demystified</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-vs.-terraform-demystified"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing and contrasting Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform and Hashicorp Terraform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F5, New Relic, and Sophos Highlight New Consul Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/f5-new-relic-and-sophos-among-new-consul-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/f5-new-relic-and-sophos-among-new-consul-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Consul ecosystem continues its growth with the addition of 15 new self-managed, enterprise, and HCP Consul integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0 alpha4 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=62210</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-alpha4-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T07:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce a new release of Camunda Optimize. Camunda Optimize provides business activity monitoring for workflows, supporting continuous process improvement by providing transparency into your automated workflows and decisions. Business-friendly reports, dashboards, and alerts make it possible to identify process bottlenecks, improve end-to-end processes, and evaluate the success of your process automation initiative. In the rest of this post, we’ll highlight some of the new capabilities introduced in Optimize 3.9.0 alpha4. What’s new? Process Onboarding UX Whenever the first process instance of a new process definition is deployed, the user will receive an email with an invitation to create a first default dashboard in Optimize. Restrict report and dashboard creation to collections Optimize is structured with entities like...
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0 alpha4 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha5 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=61925</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/camunda-automation-platform-7180-alpha5-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.18. This release features the following improvements: Logging: Engine name parameter in mapped diagnostic context Exception Error Codes now available in the External Task Clients IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty support New Supported Environments 7 Bug Fixes You can download Camunda for free or run it with Docker. For a complete list of all improvements, take a look at the release notes. Please also see the list of known issues. If you want to dig in deeper, you can find the source code on GitHub. Logging: Engine Name Parameter in Mapped Diagnostic Context As an addition to the already present list of parameters for the logging context,...
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha5 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 13th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/13/this-week-in-spring-september-13th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/13/this-week-in-spring-september-13th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We’ve got a lot of good stuff to get to so let’s dive right into it! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Hashicorp’s Rosemary Wang on securing the intersection of apps and ops with Hashicorp Vault

  
a nice video by my colleague Dan Vega: Spring Security JWT

  
I also loved Dan’s video on Spring Security without the WebSecurityConfigurerAdapter 

  
Dispatching Queries in Axon Framework

  
Guide to Find the Java .class Version

  
Spring Cloud 2021.0.4 (codename Jubilee) Has Been Released

  
Static Fields and Garbage Collection

  
Blog: Announcing the Auto-refreshing Official Kubernetes CVE Feed

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: KMS V2 Improvements

  
Blog: Kubernetes’s IPTables Chains Are Not API

  
this is an interesting post looking at how to use JUnit with Spring Boot. The only thing I didn’t quite understand is why the author declares Mockito explicitly. I’m pretty sure it’s brought in transitively in spring-boot-starter-test, but either way: good post!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The proximity hack]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42746</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/711206332/0/sethsblog~The-proximity-hack/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T06:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We evolved to care about things that were close by or in the near future. That makes sense. It’s a useful survival skill in a primitive world. Today, though, our instinct for the close and the imminent is being used against us. Media and those in search of our money or attention bring the far […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic provides the foundation for the DoD’s pillars of Zero Trust Networking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-provides-the-foundation-for-the-dods-pillars-of-zero-trust-networking</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-provides-the-foundation-for-the-dods-pillars-of-zero-trust-networking"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For most public sector organizations, especially the U.S. Department of Defense, enacting a strong Zero Trust security strategy is critical. Learn how Elastic Security provides the foundation for the fundamental pillars of a Zero Trust architecture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Woody Walton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic provides the foundation for the DoD’s pillars of Zero Trust Networking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-provides-the-foundation-for-the-dods-pillars-of-zero-trust-networking</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-provides-the-foundation-for-the-dods-pillars-of-zero-trust-networking"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The whole point of IT systems, whether deployed via traditional methods or via modern practices (such as Agile methodologies, DevSecOps, and orchestration platforms like Kubernetes) is to make data available for business operations — whether those operations are making business decisions, identifying or troubleshooting system performance and efficiency issues, detecting bad actors, or protecting organizational assets. Unfortunately, the result is a large array of disparate data silos that were never designed to interact with each other.

What’s needed is the ability to collect and ingest data from multiple disparate sources and bring them together within a common access layer, in a format that allows cross-correlation and analysis, at scale and in near real-time. Elastic provides a uniqu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Woody Walton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What If? 2 Flowchart]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2672/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2672/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/what_if_2_flowchart.png" title="Don't worry, the dogs are all fine. That's actually kind of the problem." alt="Don't worry, the dogs are all fine. That's actually kind of the problem." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – September 12, 2022]]></title>
        <id>e12120d49afe56b0cb9f9b01c88fc4cb655ae305</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-september-12-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T23:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am working from London, UK, this week to record sessions for the upcoming Innovate EMEA online conference—more about this in a future Week In Review. While I was crossing the channel, I took the time to review what happened on AWS last week. Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my attention: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gear-up and unlock the newest GitHub Global Campus features]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-12-gear-up-and-unlock-the-newest-github-global-campus-features/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-12-gear-up-and-unlock-the-newest-github-global-campus-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T19:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calling all students and teachers!  With semester change coming soon, now is the time to start using the latest features within GitHub Education and Global Campus!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul-Terraform-Sync 0.7 Adds High Availability and Redundancy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-terraform-sync-0-7-adds-high-availability-and-redundancy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-terraform-sync-0-7-adds-high-availability-and-redundancy"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of HashiCorp Consul-Terraform-Sync 0.7 represents a key step in the maturity of our Network Infrastructure Automation solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drift Detection for Terraform Cloud is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/drift-detection-for-terraform-cloud-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/drift-detection-for-terraform-cloud-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drift Detection for Terraform Cloud continuously checks infrastructure state to detect and notify operators of any changes, minimizing risk, downtime, and costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The anatomy of automation execution environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-anatomy-of-automation-execution-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-anatomy-of-automation-execution-environments"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 introduced  major architectural changes, like automation mesh and automation execution environments, that help extend Ansible automation across your organization in a flexible manner, providing a single solution to all your organizational and hybrid cloud automation needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who cares?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41853</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/710931810/0/sethsblog~Who-cares/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one cares. That happens rarely. Someone cares. That happens all the time, and it’s at the heart of our work. Everyone cares. Almost never. Someone is enough. In fact, someone is the entire point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet our 7 ERGs who are building communities at Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-our-7-ergs-who-are-building-communities-at-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-our-7-ergs-who-are-building-communities-at-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Employee resource groups build a sense of community and belonging, provide an inclusive space for people with similar experiences, empower employees to share their voice, and amplify our DEI initiatives. Here’s a bit about each one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to custom machine learning models and maps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introduction-to-custom-machine-learning-models-and-maps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introduction-to-custom-machine-learning-models-and-maps"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to run custom machine learning models to extract location information from text-based datasets and plot it on a map.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Elastic Security capabilities in the cloud — and how do they drive results?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-are-elastic-security-capabilities-in-the-cloud-and-how-do-they-drive-results</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-are-elastic-security-capabilities-in-the-cloud-and-how-do-they-drive-results"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many benefits to conducting security operations on a cloud-based platform. In this post, we’ll cover a few of the benefits Elastic Security for Cloud users experience, and how you can take advantage of an Elastic Cloud deployment yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet our 7 ERGs who are building communities at Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-our-7-ergs-who-are-building-communities-at-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-our-7-ergs-who-are-building-communities-at-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Employee resource groups, or as we like to call them, Elastician resource groups, have been a part of Elastic’s culture since 2016. They started as organic Slack channels that Elasticians could join to connect with others from similar backgrounds or experiences.
In 2021, we formalized these ERGs to ensure that the members would have structure, budget, and ultimately, a voice based on any dimension of diversity, allyship, and advocacy. Formalizing these ERGs was an important step in broadening the impact of our collective diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI) initiatives.
ERGs are aligned to shared identities, interests, affinities, or allyships and have visions and goals they are working towards. They allow Elasticians to build a sense of community and belonging outside of their immediat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to custom machine learning models and maps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introduction-to-custom-machine-learning-models-and-maps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introduction-to-custom-machine-learning-models-and-maps"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In Elasticsearch 8.0, we introduced the ability to run custom machine learning models, such as the ones based on BERT (Bidirectional Encoder Representations from Transformers), to perform natural language processing (NLP). This feature makes it easier to work with text-based datasets.

In this blog, I will put this concept into practice by showing how to extract location information from CNN articles and plot it on a map!

[Related article: How to use Elastic Maps to make public datasets observable]
Step 1. Gather the data
The first step is to gather a publicly available dataset. I have chosen the CNN dataset provided by Kaggle. You can download that and just import the CSV file as it is through Kibana, using the file upload feature inside machine learning.
Step 2. Import the machine lea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Elastic Security capabilities in the cloud — and how do they drive results?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-are-elastic-security-capabilities-in-the-cloud-and-how-do-they-drive-results</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-are-elastic-security-capabilities-in-the-cloud-and-how-do-they-drive-results"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Cloud-based SIEM, long a forward-looking topic, is here and now. In fact, advanced organizations will spend 27% more on cloud cybersecurity as a percentage of IT spending in 2022 vs. 2021 as they expand their use of cloud providers, services, and integrations with other technologies.

There are a myriad of benefits to conducting security operations on a cloud-based platform. In this post, we’ll cover a few of the benefits that users of Elastic Security for Cloud are experiencing, and how you can take advantage of an Elastic Cloud deployment yourself.
Scalability
One of the leading advantages of cloud-deployed Elastic is the ability to scale easily and efficiently with your workload. Whether you’re operating a small-scale test cluster, or instantaneously deploying a large fleet of Elastic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rotation]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2671/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2671/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/rotation.png" title="It's okay, we can just feed the one-pixel image into an AI upscaler and recover the original image, or at least one that's just as cool." alt="It's okay, we can just feed the one-pixel image into an AI upscaler and recover the original image, or at least one that's just as cool." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Announcing the Auto-refreshing Official Kubernetes CVE Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/12/k8s-cve-feed-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/12/k8s-cve-feed-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Pushkar Joglekar (VMware)
A long-standing request from the Kubernetes community has been to have a
programmatic way for end users to keep track of Kubernetes security issues
(also called "CVEs", after the database that tracks public security issues across
different products and vendors). Accompanying the release of Kubernetes v1.25,
we are excited to announce availability of such
a feed as an alpha
feature. This blog will cover the background and scope of this new service.
Motivation
With the growing number of eyes on Kubernetes, the number of CVEs related to
Kubernetes have increased. Although most CVEs that directly, indirectly, or
transitively impact Kubernetes are regularly fixed, there is no single place for
the end users of Kubernetes to programmatically subscribe or pull the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A reallocation of respect]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43771</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/710623784/0/sethsblog~A-reallocation-of-respect/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-11T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who gets the benefit of the doubt? Who is treated with dignity? You would think that this shouldn’t be scarce. When the pool of respect is widened, no one is harmed. And yet, cultural status roles have ingrained biases all around us. We’re now seeing a long overdue evaluation of unexamined norms, which aren’t, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does it mean to be smart?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43760</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/710398298/0/sethsblog~What-does-it-mean-to-be-smart/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-10T08:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You probably know that Bruce Wayne is actually Batman. That’s a secret identity that most of us are aware of. And if you’re up on pop culture, you know that the best Batman was played by the late actor Adam West. Visit the visual search engine Lexica, though, and you’ll see that it knows that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Walk in the Wild from Terrain Semantics]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/learning-to-walk-in-wild-from-terrain.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/learning-to-walk-in-wild-from-terrain.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yuxiang Yang, Student Researcher, Robotics at Google 
An important promise for quadrupedal robots is their potential to operate in complex outdoor environments that are difficult or inaccessible for humans. Whether it’s to find natural resources deep in the mountains, or to search for life signals in heavily-damaged earthquake sites, a robust and versatile quadrupedal robot could be very helpful. To achieve that, a robot needs to perceive the environment, understand its locomotion challenges, and adapt its locomotion skill accordingly. While recent advances in perceptive locomotion have greatly enhanced the capability of quadrupedal robots, most works focus on indoor or urban environments, thus they cannot effectively handle the complexity of off-road terrains. In these environme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Make Interns a Dynamic Part of Your Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-make-interns-a-dynamic-part-of-your-team</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-make-interns-a-dynamic-part-of-your-team"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figuring out where interns fit into larger team goals can be tough. One HashiCorp manager shares three essential tips to encourage success for everyone involved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCA vs SAST: what are they and which one is right for you?]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-09-sca-vs-sast-what-are-they-and-which-one-is-right-for-you/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-09-sca-vs-sast-what-are-they-and-which-one-is-right-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T15:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re taking a look at two commonly-used security tools and detailing how they can help secure your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your process communication with the new Slack Connector]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=61972</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/level-up-your-process-communication-with-the-new-slack-connector/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce an out-of-the-box Slack Connector.
The post Level up your process communication with the new Slack Connector appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake-aceuticals]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43734</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/710290176/0/sethsblog~Fakeaceuticals/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T08:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of course, we’ve always had snake oil salesmen. We’ve always had patent medicines, odd electric probes and copper bracelets. That’s partly because placebos work, and partly because when someone isn’t feeling well, it’s tempting to seek relief and belief. In the last fifty years, peer-reviewed and tested medicine has gotten dramatically more effective at the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interruption]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2670/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2670/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/interruption.png" title="It's been extra bad ever since my GPS got stuck on Phoebe Judge mode." alt="It's been extra bad ever since my GPS got stuck on Phoebe Judge mode." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: KMS V2 Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/09/kms-v2-improvements/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/09/kms-v2-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Anish Ramasekar, Rita Zhang, Mo Khan, and Xander Grzywinski (Microsoft)
With Kubernetes v1.25, SIG Auth is introducing a new v2alpha1 version of the Key Management Service (KMS) API. There are a lot of improvements in the works, and we're excited to be able to start down the path of a new and improved KMS!
What is KMS?
One of the first things to consider when securing a Kubernetes cluster is encrypting persisted API data at rest. KMS provides an interface for a provider to utilize a key stored in an external key service to perform this encryption.
Encryption at rest using KMS v1 has been a feature of Kubernetes since version v1.10, and is currently in beta as of version v1.12.
What’s new in v2alpha1?
While the original v1 implementation has been successful in helping Kubernetes us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot now available for teachers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-08-github-copilot-now-available-for-teachers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-08-github-copilot-now-available-for-teachers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a year in technical preview, GitHub Copilot, an AI pair programmer, is now free for all teachers verified on GitHub Global Campus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Multi-Axis Approach for Vision Transformer and MLP Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/a-multi-axis-approach-for-vision.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/a-multi-axis-approach-for-vision.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T17:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zhengzhong Tu and Yinxiao Li, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Convolutional neural networks have been the dominant machine learning architecture for computer vision since the introduction of AlexNet in 2012. Recently, inspired by the evolution of Transformers in natural language processing, attention mechanisms have been prominently incorporated into vision models. These attention methods boost some parts of the input data while minimizing other parts so that the network can focus on small but important parts of the data. The Vision Transformer (ViT) has created a new landscape of model designs for computer vision that is completely free of convolution. ViT regards image patches as a sequence of words, and applies a Transformer encoder on top. When trained on sufficiently la…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changes to the Terraform Partner Integration Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-partner-integration-program-changes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-partner-integration-program-changes"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are making some changes to the way that we tag modules and providers in the Terraform Registry for better consistency, clarity, and scalability in the Registry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research: open source software in India, Kenya, Egypt, and Mexico]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-08-research-open-source-software-in-india-kenya-egypt-and-mexico/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-08-research-open-source-software-in-india-kenya-egypt-and-mexico/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T07:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read the new GitHub report on OSS in India, Kenya, Egypt, and Mexico. Available now in English, and in Spanish and Arabic later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Hashicorp's Rosemary Wang on securing the intersection of apps and ops with Hashicorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/08/a-bootiful-podcast-hashicorp-s-rosemary-wang-on-securing-the-intersection-of-apps-and-ops-with-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/08/a-bootiful-podcast-hashicorp-s-rosemary-wang-on-securing-the-intersection-of-apps-and-ops-with-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Hashicorp Developer Advocate Rosemary Wang (@joatmon08) about a few Hashicorp technologies and their integrations with Spring Boot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.4 (codename Jubilee) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/07/spring-cloud-2021-0-4-codename-jubilee-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/07/spring-cloud-2021-0-4-codename-jubilee-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T22:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the General Availability (RELEASE) of the Spring Cloud 2021.0.4 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2021.0.4 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0.4 Release Train

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.
Spring Cloud Config


  
Replace JSCH with Apache MINA to resolve a number of SSH issues (#1901)


Spring Cloud Gateway


  
Added native JSON to gRPC filter (#2657)

  
Support ‘use-insecure-trust-manager’ & ‘trustedX509Certificates’ for GRPC Filter (2699)


Spring Cloud Openfeign


  
Allow overriding binary content types list ([#734]https://github.com/spring-cloud/spring-cloud-openfeign/…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: August 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-07-github-availability-report-august-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-07-github-availability-report-august-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T18:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In August, we experienced one incident resulting in significant impact to Codespaces. We’re still investigating that incident and will include it in next month’s report. This report also sheds light into an incident that impacted Codespaces in July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Automation Experience: AnsibleFest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-automation-experience-ansiblefest-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-automation-experience-ansiblefest-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is almost time for our favorite event of the year! AnsibleFest is back as an in-person event, and it’s the only place to feel the full power of automation. Join us October 18 and 19 in Chicago, and immerse yourself in the movement that’s made Ansible an industry-leading automation technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research: quantifying GitHub Copilot’s impact on developer productivity and happiness]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-07-research-quantifying-github-copilots-impact-on-developer-productivity-and-happiness/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-07-research-quantifying-github-copilots-impact-on-developer-productivity-and-happiness/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the GitHub Copilot Technical Preview launched just over one year ago, we wanted to know one thing: Is this tool helping developers? The GitHub Next team conducted research using a combination of surveys and experiments, which led us to expected and unexpected answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Global Preview: Evolving Your Cloud Operating Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-preview-evolving-your-cloud-operating-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-preview-evolving-your-cloud-operating-model"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Find out about the 13 most interesting HashiConf Global sessions for enterprise cloud platform teams. Join us October 4 - 6, 2022 in Los Angeles and virtual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes’s IPTables Chains Are Not API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/07/iptables-chains-not-api/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/07/iptables-chains-not-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Dan Winship (Red Hat)
Some Kubernetes components (such as kubelet and kube-proxy) create
iptables chains and rules as part of their operation. These chains
were never intended to be part of any Kubernetes API/ABI guarantees,
but some external components nonetheless make use of some of them (in
particular, using KUBE-MARK-MASQ to mark packets as needing to be
masqueraded).
As a part of the v1.25 release, SIG Network made this declaration
explicit: that (with one exception), the iptables chains that
Kubernetes creates are intended only for Kubernetes’s own internal
use, and third-party components should not assume that Kubernetes will
create any specific iptables chains, or that those chains will contain
any specific rules if they do exist.
Then, in future releases, as part of KEP-31…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Graph connectors for Microsoft Search]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65671</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-graph-connectors-for-microsoft-search/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T23:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Search is the workplace search solution offered with Microsoft 365. Microsoft Search lets you find the information you need by unlocking knowledge and expertise. It helps you find what you need to complete what you’re working on. Whether you’re searching for people,
The post Azure DevOps Graph connectors for Microsoft Search appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digitizing Smell: Using Molecular Maps to Understand Odor]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/digitizing-smell-using-molecular-maps.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/digitizing-smell-using-molecular-maps.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T17:35:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Richard C. Gerkin, Google Research, and Alexander B. Wiltschko, Google 


Did you ever try to measure a smell? …Until you can measure their likenesses and differences you can have no science of odor. If you are ambitious to found a new science, measure a smell.
  
— Alexander Graham Bell, 1914.

 How can we measure a smell? Smells are produced by molecules that waft through the air, enter our noses, and bind to sensory receptors. Potentially billions of molecules can produce a smell, so figuring out which ones produce which smells is difficult to catalog or predict. Sensory maps can help us solve this problem.  Color vision has the most familiar examples of these maps, from the color wheel we each learn in primary school to more sophisticated variants used to perform color correc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault, Kubernetes, and the Graduation of vault-k8s to Version 1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-kubernetes-and-the-graduation-of-vault-k8s-to-version-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-kubernetes-and-the-graduation-of-vault-k8s-to-version-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of vault-k8s 1.0 marks a great time to learn how HashiCorp Vault has integrated with Kubernetes in the past and what to look forward to in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 5th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/06/this-week-in-spring-september-5th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/06/this-week-in-spring-september-5th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How are you? It’s a fantastic Tuesday, the 5th of September, 2022, and I couldn’t be happier. It’s also Labor Day weekend here in the US. It marks the unofficial end of summer, which is a bit sad. But, on the upside, it’s a four-day weekend for me! I’m technically off today. So, you’ll forgive me, but I won’t spend too much time here. Let’s dive right into this week’s roundup!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Dr. Kris De Volder on Spring Tools, VS Code, and so much more

  
Connect to Multiple Databases Using Spring Data Mongodb

  
End-to-end tracing with OpenTelemetry

  
I love this article by Hashicorp’s Rosemary Wang on refreshable secrets for Kubernetes Applications with Vault Agent

  
Microsoft is committed to the success of Java developers

  
Price Reduction - Azure Spring Apps does more, costs less!

  
The Second Best Way to Fetch a Spring Data JPA DTO Projection – Java, SQL and jOOQ.

  
The best way to fetch a Spring Data JPA DTO Projection - Vlad Mihalcea

  
Speaking of JOOQ, did you know there’s good reactive API support included? Check it out: 3.15.0 Release with Support for R2DBC, Nested ROW, ARRAY, and MULTISET types, 5 new SQL dialects, CREATE PROCEDURE, FUNCTION, and TRIGGER support and Much More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – September 5, 2022]]></title>
        <id>8f3c0923bae1a075227962f5ea6ebbfc45ae02a5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-september-5-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T18:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! As a new week begins, let’s quickly look back at the most significant AWS news from the previous seven days. Last Week’s Launches Here are the launches that got my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing COSI: Object Storage Management using Kubernetes APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/02/cosi-kubernetes-object-storage-management/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/02/cosi-kubernetes-object-storage-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Sidhartha Mani (Minio, Inc)
This article introduces the Container Object Storage Interface (COSI), a standard for provisioning and consuming object storage in Kubernetes. It is an alpha feature in Kubernetes v1.25.
File and block storage are treated as first class citizens in the Kubernetes ecosystem via Container Storage Interface (CSI). Workloads using CSI volumes enjoy the benefits of portability across vendors and across Kubernetes clusters without the need to change application manifests. An equivalent standard does not exist for Object storage.
Object storage has been rising in popularity in recent years as an alternative form of storage to filesystems and block devices. Object storage paradigm promotes disaggregation of compute and storage. This is done by making data avail…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Standardize Cryptography in the Enterprise with HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-standardize-cryptography-in-the-enterprise-with-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-standardize-cryptography-in-the-enterprise-with-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how centralizing encryption tools in a self-service platform for developers lowers the cost of ownership, centralizes best practices, and makes auditing easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Dr. Kris De Volder on Spring Tools, VS Code, and so much more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/01/a-bootiful-podcast-dr-kris-de-volder-on-spring-tools-vs-code-and-so-much-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/01/a-bootiful-podcast-dr-kris-de-volder-on-spring-tools-vs-code-and-so-much-more"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode Josh Long (@starbuxman)  talks to Dr. Kris De Volder, a longtime member of the Spring Tools team, about all the cool stuff he’s worked on and is going to work on. And then we get knee deep into a discussion around building IDE integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Patent Phrase Similarity Dataset]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/announcing-patent-phrase-similarity.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/announcing-patent-phrase-similarity.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted Grigor Aslanyan, Software Engineer, Google 
Patent documents typically use legal and highly technical language, with context-dependent terms that may have meanings quite different from colloquial usage and even between different documents. The process of using traditional patent search methods (e.g., keyword searching) to search through the corpus of over one hundred million patent documents can be tedious and result in many missed results due to the broad and non-standard language used. For example, a "soccer ball" may be described as a "spherical recreation device", "inflatable sportsball" or "ball for ball game". Additionally, the language used in some patent documents may obfuscate terms to their advantage, so more powerful natural language processing (NLP) and semantic similari…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 209 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65658</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-209-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T16:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We fixed a bunch more issues for New Boards Hub in sprint 209. Here is a list of the items that have been resolved.
Issue
OnBlur instead of onChange
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 209 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation in banking: 6 considerations for digital transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60932</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/automation-in-banking-6-considerations-for-digital-transformation/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation and banking have been two peas in a technological pod since the 1934 introduction of the IBM ® 801 Bank Proof machine, a check sorting machine. Later innovations like the automated teller machine and the debit card continued the banking automation trend of digitizing analog processes. With the advent of the internet, machine learning, and cloud computing, there are still so many automation opportunities to explore.  For instance, using AI for risk assessment, automating the classification of unstructured data, or reducing manual work can help you increase the agility of the overall organization, improve the customer experience, and get new features and products to market much more rapidly. We’re going to explore six concepts to keep in mind for...
The post Automation in banking: 6 considerations for digital transformation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price Reduction - Azure Spring Apps does more, costs less!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/31/price-reduction-azure-spring-apps-does-more-costs-less</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/31/price-reduction-azure-spring-apps-does-more-costs-less"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We believe in providing the most innovative cloud offerings at incredibly competitive prices. As we operate Azure Spring Apps, we continue to build efficiencies and economies of scale. We are passing those efficiencies to you. 

Many customers have asked us to lower the size of the base unit to make it easier to get started and accommodate smaller projects. 
Announcing Price and Base Unit Reduction

Effective September 1st, we are reducing the base unit of Azure Spring Apps Standard and Enterprise to 6 vCPUs and 12 GB of Memory. And reducing the overage prices for vCPU and Memory. 


New Monthly FREE Grants

Furthermore, to help you get started, effective mid-September, we are offering monthly FREE grants – 50 vCPU hours and 100 Memory GB hours. 

Let’s look at a few examples: 

Note…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: cgroup v2 graduates to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/31/cgroupv2-ga-1-25/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/31/cgroupv2-ga-1-25/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors:: David Porter (Google), Mrunal Patel (Red Hat)
Kubernetes 1.25 brings cgroup v2 to GA (general availability), letting the
kubelet use the latest container resource
management capabilities.
What are cgroups?
Effective resource management is a
critical aspect of Kubernetes. This involves managing the finite resources in
your nodes, such as CPU, memory, and storage.
cgroups are a Linux kernel capability that establish resource management
functionality like limiting CPU usage or setting memory limits for running
processes.
When you use the resource management capabilities in Kubernetes, such as configuring
requests and limits for Pods and containers,
Kubernetes uses cgroups to enforce your resource requests and limits.
The Linux kernel offers two versions of cgroups: cgroup v1 and cgr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and VMware Announce VMware Cloud on AWS integration with Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP]]></title>
        <id>fdb3e5851333d5a35feee69841bc3b0de7ed14eb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-and-vmware-announce-vmware-cloud-on-aws-integration-with-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our customers are looking for cost-effective ways to continue to migrate their applications to the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is a fully managed, jointly engineered service that brings VMware’s enterprise-class, software-defined data center architecture to the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS offers our customers the ability to run applications across operationally consistent VMware vSphere-based […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can a Service Mesh Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-can-a-service-mesh-do</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-can-a-service-mesh-do"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A service mesh is a force multiplier that can do everything from service discovery to zero trust security, load balancing, multi-cloud connectivity, automation, and north-south traffic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is committed to the success of Java developers]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/microsoft-is-committed-to-the-success-of-java-developers</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/microsoft-is-committed-to-the-success-of-java-developers"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! This is a guest post from our friend Julia Liuson, President, Developer Division, Microsoft

As a company, we are committed to making Java developers as efficient and productive as possible. This commitment means empowering you to use any tool, framework, and application server on any operating system. Wherever you are with Java, Microsoft supports your workload with an abundance of choices and with a wide range of developer tools and services. 
Code, Deploy, and Scale Java Your Way

Today, more and more Java developers are looking at how they can bring their existing Java applications to the cloud—or how to build new cloud-native applications. We have been working to make it easier for you to bring your Java applications to the cloud using the tools and frameworks you l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BPMN and DMN Modeler for Atlassian Confluence]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60833</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/bpmn-and-dmn-modeler-for-atlassian-confluence/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Document business processes with the BPMN and DMN Modeler for Confluence - two plugins available for free on the Atlassian Marketplace.
The post BPMN and DMN Modeler for Atlassian Confluence appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 30th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/this-week-in-spring-august-30th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/this-week-in-spring-august-30th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How are you? How’re you doin’ this fine tuesday morning? I’m doing well, of course, because this week VMware’s tentpole show - VMware Explore - is happening not even a mile from my home, here in San Francisco! And this is just the first one - there’ll be another show, my favorite show, in December: SpringOne 2022! I sure hope you’ve registered and that we’ll see you there! 

Indeed, I’ve got a lunch to get to, so let’s get this this week’s wrapup done a little more quickly: without further ado….


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert

  
Creating a custom Spring Cloud Gateway Filter

  
Feign Client Exception Handling

  
Kai Tödter has just announced version 1.6.0 of JSON:API for Spring HATEOAS

  
Multitenancy With Spring Data JPA

  
PKCE Support for Secret Clients with Spring Security

  
Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is available now!

  
Swagger: Specify Two Responses with the Same Response Code

  
Are you building Spring Apps? Join us to learn how to build, deploy and operate Spring Apps at scale.

  
So, here is VMware’s stack for building a platform on the platform as kubernetes, the Tanzu Application Platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Open–AWS Region in the United Arab Emirates (UAE)]]></title>
        <id>abade96b96022cbe9580a09867b67fafe3511c48</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-aws-region-in-the-united-arab-emirates-uae/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T06:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Region in the United Arab Emirates is now open. The official name is Middle East (UAE), and the API name is me-central-1. You can start using it today to deploy workloads and store your data in the United Arab Emirates. The AWS Middle East (UAE) Region is the second Region in the Middle […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 29, 2022]]></title>
        <id>d79ee60a7a83272276a7f3bd52c297b82f87c603</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-29-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T19:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve just returned from data and machine learning (ML) conferences in Los Angeles and San Francisco, California. It’s been great to chat with customers and developers about the latest technology trends and use cases. This past week has also been packed with launches at AWS. Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refresh Secrets for Kubernetes Applications with Vault Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/refresh-secrets-for-kubernetes-applications-with-vault-agent</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/refresh-secrets-for-kubernetes-applications-with-vault-agent"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the system signal and live reload methods for updating Kubernetes applications when secrets change. See an example via a Spring Boot application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Red Hat OpenShift - The Easy Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/monitoring-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-red-hat-openshift-the-easy-way</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/monitoring-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-red-hat-openshift-the-easy-way"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform enables teams and organizations to drive their automation from across the cloud and on-premise, keeping Ansible Automation Platform healthy with the ability to monitor key metrics becomes paramount.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: CSI Inline Volumes have graduated to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/29/csi-inline-volumes-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/29/csi-inline-volumes-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jonathan Dobson (Red Hat)
CSI Inline Volumes were introduced as an alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.15 and have been beta since 1.16. We are happy to announce that this feature has graduated to General Availability (GA) status in Kubernetes 1.25.
CSI Inline Volumes are similar to other ephemeral volume types, such as configMap, downwardAPI and secret. The important difference is that the storage is provided by a CSI driver, which allows the use of ephemeral storage provided by third-party vendors. The volume is defined as part of the pod spec and follows the lifecycle of the pod, meaning the volume is created once the pod is scheduled and destroyed when the pod is destroyed.
What's new in 1.25?
There are a couple of new bug fixes related to this feature in 1.25, and the CSIInlineVolum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a custom Spring Cloud Gateway Filter]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/26/creating-a-custom-spring-cloud-gateway-filter</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/26/creating-a-custom-spring-cloud-gateway-filter"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we look into writing a custom extension for Spring Cloud Gateway. Before we get started, let’s go over how Spring Cloud Gateway works:




  
First, a client makes a network request to the Gateway

  
The Gateway is defined with a number of routes, each with Predicates to match the request to the route. For example, you can match on the path segment of the URL or the HTTP method of the request.

  
Once matched, the Gateway executes pre-request logic on each of the filters applied to the route. For example, you might want to add query parameters to your request

  
A proxy filter routes the request to the proxied service

  
The service executes and returns a response

  
The gateway receives the response and executes post-request logic on each filter before return…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What HashiCorp Interns Learned This Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-hashicorp-interns-learned-this-summer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-hashicorp-interns-learned-this-summer"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10 interns in HashiCorp’s Early Career Program share what they learned during their summer with the company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways to involve your community to improve your programs]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60542</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/3-ways-to-involve-your-community-to-improve-your-programs/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community programs are valuable tools for organizations. But enabling engagement in these programs can be challenging.
The post 3 ways to involve your community to improve your programs appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danielle Andrist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the latest AWS Heroes – August 2022]]></title>
        <id>f94b7ec2837a44f904bb188f134e48c449671094</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-latest-aws-heroes-august-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T18:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global AWS community is filled with passionate builders, eager to learn and explore ways to build better and faster on AWS. Within the AWS community, a select few individuals truly go above and beyond to share their knowledge and inspire others through content creation, event organization, open source contributions, and more. These community leaders […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-Definition Segmentation in Google Meet]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/high-definition-segmentation-in-google.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/high-definition-segmentation-in-google.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tingbo Hou and Juhyun Lee, Software Engineers, Google 
In recent years video conferencing has played an increasingly important role in both work and personal communication for many users. Over the past two years, we have enhanced this experience in Google Meet by introducing privacy-preserving machine learning (ML) powered background features, also known as “virtual green screen”, which allows users to blur their backgrounds or replace them with other images. What is unique about this solution is that it runs directly in the browser without the need to install additional software.  
So far, these ML-powered features have relied on CPU inference made possible by leveraging neural network sparsity, a common solution that works across devices, from entry level computers to high-end …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Fine-Grained Visual Embedding Powered by Amazon QuickSight]]></title>
        <id>a1501b50fea420ead40fcf160e7a0bea82b5b85f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-fine-grained-visual-embedding-powered-by-amazon-quicksight/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T16:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing a new feature, Fine-Grained Visual Embedding Powered by Amazon QuickSight. With this feature, individual visualizations from Amazon QuickSight dashboards can now be embedded in high-traffic webpages and applications. Additionally, this feature enables you to provide rich insights for your end-users where they need them the most, without server or software setup […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-fellow-java-champion-and-timescaledb-developer-advocate-christoph-engelbert</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-fellow-java-champion-and-timescaledb-developer-advocate-christoph-engelbert"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert (@noctarius2k) about PostgreSQL, Java, time series databases, observability, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Run Tasks Ecosystem Continues to Grow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-run-tasks-ecosystem-continues-to-grow</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-run-tasks-ecosystem-continues-to-grow"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teams can now integrate oak9 and Torq into the Terraform Cloud workflow via run tasks. Plus: A list of integrations now validated to work with Terraform Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.25: Pod Security Admission Controller in Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/25/pod-security-admission-stable/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/25/pod-security-admission-stable/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Tim Allclair (Google), Sam Stoelinga (Google)
The release of Kubernetes v1.25 marks a major milestone for Kubernetes out-of-the-box pod security
controls: Pod Security admission (PSA) graduated to stable, and Pod Security Policy (PSP) has been
removed.
PSP was deprecated in Kubernetes v1.21,
and no longer functions in Kubernetes v1.25 and later.
The Pod Security admission controller replaces PodSecurityPolicy, making it easier to enforce predefined
Pod Security Standards by
simply adding a label to a namespace. The Pod Security Standards are maintained by the K8s
community, which means you automatically get updated security policies whenever new
security-impacting Kubernetes features are introduced.
What’s new since Beta?
Pod Security Admission hasn’t changed much since the Beta i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using ML to Boost Engagement with a Maternal and Child Health Program in India]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/using-ml-to-boost-engagement-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/using-ml-to-boost-engagement-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Aparna Taneja, Software Engineer, and Milind Tambe, Principal Scientist, Google Research, India Research Lab 
The widespread availability of mobile phones has enabled non-profits to deliver critical health information to their beneficiaries in a timely manner. While advanced applications on smartphones allow for richer multimedia content and two-way communication between beneficiaries and health coaches, simpler text and voice messaging services can be effective in disseminating information to large communities, particularly those that are underserved with limited access to information and smartphones. ARMMAN1, one non-profit doing just this, is based in India with the mission of improving maternal and child health outcomes in underserved communities. 
    


Overview of ARMMAN

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning for Budget Constrained Recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6cbc5263a32a</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/reinforcement-learning-for-budget-constrained-recommendations-6cbc5263a32a?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Ehtsham Elahi
with James McInerney, Nathan Kallus, Dario Garcia Garcia and Justin Basilico]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS Support App in Slack to Manage Support Cases]]></title>
        <id>7987abd39e83187889bce5fb0aa7f7f73557375e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-support-app-in-slack-to-manage-support-cases/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatOps speeds up software development and operations by enabling DevOps teams to use chat clients and chatbots to communicate and run tasks. DevOps engineers have increasingly moved their monitoring, system management, continuous integration (CI), and continuous delivery (CD) workflows to chat applications in order to streamline activities in a single place and enable better collaboration […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is available now!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/24/spring-batch-5-0-0-m5-is-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/24/spring-batch-5-0-0-m5-is-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is now available from our milestone repository. The main theme of this milestone is improving testing support in Spring Batch. This post walks through the major changes in this area as well as other changes introduced in this milestone release. For the complete list of changes, see the release notes.
Test utilities configuration updates

Up to version 4.3, the JobLauncherTestUtils used to autowire the job under test with the goal of facilitating the test setup. But what if multiple jobs are defined in the test context? And what if no Job beans are defined at all? So while this autowiring was convenient for most cases, it turned out to cause several issues in the aforementioned situations. In this release, and based on community feedback,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps and CI/CD with automation controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/devops-and-ci/cd-with-automation-controller</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/devops-and-ci/cd-with-automation-controller"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog shares practical examples of using Ansible Automation Platform to accelerate your DevOps journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: PodSecurityPolicy: The Historical Context]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/podsecuritypolicy-the-historical-context/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/podsecuritypolicy-the-historical-context/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mahé Tardy (Quarkslab)
The PodSecurityPolicy (PSP) admission controller has been removed, as of
Kubernetes v1.25. Its deprecation was announced and detailed in the blog post
PodSecurityPolicy Deprecation: Past, Present, and Future,
published for the Kubernetes v1.21 release.
This article aims to provide historical context on the birth and evolution of
PSP, explain why the feature never made it to stable, and show why it was
removed and replaced by Pod Security admission control.
PodSecurityPolicy, like other specialized admission control plugins, provided
fine-grained permissions on specific fields concerning the pod security settings
as a built-in policy API. It acknowledged that cluster administrators and
cluster users are usually not the same people, and that creating workloads …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UVQ: Measuring YouTube's Perceptual Video Quality]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/uvq-measuring-youtubes-perceptual-video.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/uvq-measuring-youtubes-perceptual-video.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T17:02:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yilin Wang, Staff Software Engineer, YouTube and Feng Yang, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research 
Online video sharing platforms, like YouTube, need to understand perceptual video quality (i.e., a user's subjective perception of video quality) in order to better optimize and improve user experience. Video quality assessment (VQA) attempts to build a bridge between video signals and perceptual quality by using objective mathematical models to approximate the subjective opinions of users. Traditional video quality metrics, like peak signal-to-noise ratio (PSNR) and Video Multi-Method Assessment Fusion (VMAF), are reference-based and focus on the relative difference between the target and reference videos. Such metrics, which work best on professionally generated content …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 23rd, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/23/this-week-in-spring-august-23rd-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/23/this-week-in-spring-august-23rd-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We’ve got a ton to cover, so let’s dive right into it!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Flowable founder Joram Barrez on a Bootiful Podcast on workflow, business process management, and more

  
Building IoT Applications Using Fauna and Spring

  
Cosmos DB for Spring Developers, Part I: Using Cosmos DB as a SQL Database

  
How to Build Web Servers with Paketo Buildpacks - Paketo Buildpacks

  
Introducing Experimental Spring Support for Apache Pulsar

  
Propagating Exceptions With OpenFeign and Spring

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M1 available now

  
Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M1 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.6.11 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.7.3 available now

  
Spring Boot Actuator

  
Spring Boot Native image builds with 22.2.0 are failing · Issue #176 paketo-buildpacks/native-image - this is in regards to an issue related to Buildpacks that just appeared last week. There’s a workaround that’s been recently deployed.

  
Spring Boot and Spring Security with JWT including Access and Refresh Tokens 🔑

  
Spring JDBC Batch Inserts

  
Spring Security 5.8.0-M2 is released

  
Spring Shell 2.1.1 is now available

  
Spring for GraphQL with Querydsl.

  
Testcontainers and Spring Boot for local development and integration testing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.25: Combiner]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/kubernetes-v1-25-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/kubernetes-v1-25-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes 1.25 Release Team
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.25!
This release includes a total of 40 enhancements. Fifteen of those enhancements are entering Alpha, ten are graduating to Beta, and thirteen are graduating to Stable. We also have two features being deprecated or removed.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes 1.25: Combiner
The theme for Kubernetes v1.25 is Combiner.
The Kubernetes project itself is made up of many, many individual components that, when combined, take the form of the project you see today. It is also built and maintained by many individuals, all of them with different skills, experiences, histories, and interests, who join forces not just as the release team but as the many SIGs that support the project and the community year-round.
With this rel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 22, 2022]]></title>
        <id>cd57561ca684dacfdb5a73e1204fff6a6bfa1214</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-22-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T18:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I’m back from my summer holidays and ready to get up to date with the latest AWS news from last week! Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Cloud Skills Shortage Is Affecting Multi-Cloud Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-a-cloud-skills-shortage-is-affecting-multi-cloud-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-a-cloud-skills-shortage-is-affecting-multi-cloud-adoption"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 State of Cloud Strategy survey reveals that IT organizations are turning to platform teams and automated tools to bridge a growing skills shortage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 10th Anniversary, Amazon S3 Glacier – A Decade of Cold Storage in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>2d8c2df87af9a66f78fc7d7776db8517bedf54f4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-10th-anniversary-amazon-s3-glacier-a-decade-of-cold-storage-in-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T15:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten years ago, on August 20, 2012, AWS announced the general availability of Amazon Glacier, secure, reliable, and extremely low-cost storage designed for data archiving and backup. At the time, I was working as an AWS customer and it felt like an April Fools’ joke, offering long-term, secure, and durable cloud storage that allowed me […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing a VMware Template Lifecycle with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/managing-a-vmware-template-lifecycle-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/managing-a-vmware-template-lifecycle-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we manage a large number of virtual machines (VMs), we want to reduce the differences between them and create a standard template. By using a standard template, it becomes easier to manage and propagate the same operation on the different nodes. When using VMware vSphere, it is a common practice to share a standardized VM template and use it to create new VMs. This template is often called a golden image. Its creation involves a series of steps that can be automated with Ansible. In this blog, we will see how one can create and use a new golden image.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gonéri Le Bouder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad Service Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-service-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-service-discovery"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad’s addition of native service discovery offers a new option for simple service registration, plus integration with Consul for more complex service mesh use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/22/sig-storage-spotlight/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/22/sig-storage-spotlight/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS)
Since the very beginning of Kubernetes, the topic of persistent data and how to address the requirement of stateful applications has been an important topic. Support for stateless deployments was natural, present from the start, and garnered attention, becoming very well-known. Work on better support for stateful applications was also present from early on, with each release increasing the scope of what could be run on Kubernetes.
Message queues, databases, clustered filesystems: these are some examples of the solutions that have different storage requirements and that are, today, increasingly deployed in Kubernetes. Dealing with ephemeral and persistent storage, local or remote, file or block, from many different vendors, while considering how to provide the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>