<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-03T01:09:32.258Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-10-03T01:09:32.258Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – Amazon Bedrock Is Now Generally Available, Attend AWS Innovate Online, and More – Oct 2, 2023]]></title>
        <id>53a22c5fc2a3360eecf4437ddff15bbd97bbb343</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-bedrock-is-now-generally-available-attend-aws-innovate-online-and-more-oct-2-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T20:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week I attended the AWS Summit Johannesburg. This was the first summit to be hosted in my own country and my own city since 2019 so it was very special to have the opportunity to attend. It was great to get to meet with so many of our customers and hear how they are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity spotlight on bug bounty researcher @inspector-ambitious]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-02-cybersecurity-spotlight-on-bug-bounty-researcher-inspector-ambitious/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-02-cybersecurity-spotlight-on-bug-bounty-researcher-inspector-ambitious/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T17:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For this year’s Cybersecurity Awareness Month, the GitHub bug bounty team is excited to feature another spotlight on a talented security researcher who participates in the GitHub Security Bug Bounty Program—@inspector-ambitious!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-02-cybersecurity-spotlight-on-bug-bounty-researcher-inspector-ambitious/">Cybersecurity spotlight on bug bounty researcher @inspector-ambitious</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team Work Item Automation Rules (Private Preview)]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67716</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/team-backlog-automation-rules-private-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T16:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers have been requesting to automate state transitions for a while. Take this request from 2018:
The post Team Work Item Automation Rules (Private Preview) appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.15 adopts Microsoft Workload Identity Federation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-1-15-adopts-microsoft-workload-identity-federation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-1-15-adopts-microsoft-workload-identity-federation"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.15  improves security by adopting Microsoft Workload Identity Federation for applications and services in Azure, Google Cloud, and GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the new, Apple silicon powered M1 macOS larger runner for GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-02-introducing-the-new-apple-silicon-powered-m1-macos-larger-runner-for-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-02-introducing-the-new-apple-silicon-powered-m1-macos-larger-runner-for-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T15:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Speed up your GitHub Actions jobs on macOS with all new, faster Apple silicon powered M1 macOS larger runner for arm64.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-02-introducing-the-new-apple-silicon-powered-m1-macos-larger-runner-for-github-actions/">Introducing the new, Apple silicon powered M1 macOS larger runner for GitHub Actions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recordings from JetBrains .NET Day Online ’23 are available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=393425</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/10/02/recordings-jetbrains-dotnet-day-online-23/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T14:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 26, we hosted a free virtual event – .NET Day Online ’23. This was the fifth annual edition of the conference, and we were absolutely amazed at how lively the conversation was! We’d like to extend a huge thank you to the wonderful speakers who joined us to share their passion for the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Kolesova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now serving: Event-Driven Ansible with a dash of durability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/now-serving-event-driven-ansible-with-a-dash-of-durability</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/now-serving-event-driven-ansible-with-a-dash-of-durability"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of automation, the ability to respond to events in real-time is a game-changer. At Red Hat, we've been pioneering in this space with Event-Driven Ansible, which can consume messages from various sources like AWS Simple Queue Service (SQS), Azure Service Bus, and Kafka to trigger automated actions. Today, we're excited to delve into a powerful integration pattern involving AWS Lambda, AWS SQS, and Event-Driven Ansible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MPS 2021.3.4 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=mps&amp;p=392031</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/mps/2023/10/mps-2021-3-4-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T12:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MPS 2021.3.4 has just arrived with a batch of useful backported improvements. Parallel model checker The model checker can now effectively utilize parallel hardware, thereby speeding up the process of model checking. Depending on the settings in Settings | Tools | Model Checker, it can spawn multiple threads when starting this process. This option is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaclav Pech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The PhpStorm 2023.3 Early Access Program Is Now Open]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=391243</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/10/the-phpstorm-2023-3-early-access-program-is-now-open/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T11:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re opening the Early Access Program (EAP) for the next version of PhpStorm! In this EAP, we’ve included part of the latest improvements provided in PHP 8.3, which is due to be released at the end of November, a New Project wizard for Symfony, and support for the conversion of Doctrine annotations to attributes. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tania Goral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[But it matters a lot to them…]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47398</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/797112998/0/sethsblog~But-it-matters-a-lot-to-them/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To get to the Kebab House Cafe, you’ll need to drive past a dozen fast food restaurants, restaurants you can find off just about any interstate. It’s certainly less convenient to go a few blocks off the beaten path, but the food and service and vibe might be worth it. The thing is, it matters […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ICCV 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/google-at-iccv-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/google-at-iccv-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T07:51:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shaina Mehta, Program Manager, Google




Google is proud to be a Platinum Sponsor of the International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV 2023), a premier annual conference, which is being held this week in Paris, France. As a leader in computer vision research, Google has a strong presence at this year’s conference with 60 accepted papers and active involvement in 27 workshops and tutorials. Google is also proud to be a Platinum Sponsor for the LatinX in CV workshop. We look forward to sharing some of our extensive computer vision research and expanding our partnership with the broader research community. 



Attending ICCV 2023? We hope you’ll visit the Google booth to chat with researchers who are actively pursuing the latest innovations in computer vision, and check out som…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy a Hello World web app with Elastic Observability on AWS App Runner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/deploy-hello-world-web-app-elastic-observability-aws-app-runner</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/deploy-hello-world-web-app-elastic-observability-aws-app-runner"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow the step-by-step process of instrumenting Elastic Observability for a Hello World web app running on AWS App Runner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy a Hello World web app with Elastic Observability on AWS App Runner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/deploy-hello-world-web-app-elastic-observability-aws-app-runner</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/deploy-hello-world-web-app-elastic-observability-aws-app-runner"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Observability is the premiere tool to provide visibility into web apps running in your environment. AWS App Runner is the serverless platform of choice to run your web apps that need to scale up and down massively to meet demand or minimize costs. Elastic Observability combined with AWS App Runner is the perfect solution for developers to deploy web apps that are auto-scaled with fully observable operations, in a way that’s straightforward to implement and manage. 
This blog post will show you how to deploy a simple Hello World web app to App Runner and then walk you through the steps to instrument the Hello World web app to enable observation of the application’s operations with Elastic Cloud.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt110c7427eb172a17/651a46…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Halloween Carol]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2836/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2836/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/a_halloween_carol.png" title="[after a minute] &quot;Okay, I think I've got it, thanks. Can I--&quot; &quot;oOOOooOOooo!&quot;" alt="[after a minute] &quot;Okay, I think I've got it, thanks. Can I--&quot; &quot;oOOOooOOooo!&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning from the Amazon gift card snafu]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47390</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/797042708/0/sethsblog~Learning-from-the-Amazon-gift-card-snafu/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Millions of people got this email last night: It’s legitimate, but it’s a mistake. A mistake because: We can learn a lot about what not to do from this. First, if you make a mistake by email, fix it. Fix it by email AND fix it on your site. Let everyone who got the wrong […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confusion and certainty]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47371</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/797019347/0/sethsblog~Confusion-and-certainty/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When facing a complex problem, it’s easy to become confused. Lately, it’s become socially acceptable to express your confusion with certainty. Untrained in the field, make a pronouncement that makes it clear that you have not just an understanding of what’s going on, but also that you’ve figured out the causes and the next steps. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving invented problems]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47208</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/796885115/0/sethsblog~Solving-invented-problems/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some problems, when well solved, lead to making things better. Some problems give us a chance to get back on course. And some problems are opportunities to be generous. But many of the problems that we seek to solve are actually invented, and maybe we could benefit by simply walking away. There are two interesting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds streamlined run task reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-streamlined-run-task-reviews</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-streamlined-run-task-reviews"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlined run task reviews provide meaningful context on run task evaluations to help practitioners resolve issues faster without having to leave Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · September 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-29-game-bytes/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-29-game-bytes/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T14:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-29-game-bytes/">Game Bytes · September 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freedom of attitude]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45660</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/796702271/0/sethsblog~Freedom-of-attitude/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two franchised pack-and-ship shops about equidistant from my home. One has a 4.5 rating and is reliably busy. The other has an astonishingly low 1.5 out of 5 rating. The physical plant is virtually identical, and the marketing and promo are the same. The only difference is the owner running the second shop. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2023.0.0-M2 (aka Leyton) has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/29/spring-cloud-2023-0-0-m2-aka-leyton-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/29/spring-cloud-2023-0-0-m2-aka-leyton-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Maciaszek-Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customize your data ingestion with Elastic input packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/customize-data-ingestion-elastic-input-packages</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/customize-data-ingestion-elastic-input-packages"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, learn about input packages and how they can provide a flexible solution to advanced users for customizing their ingestion experience in Elastic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishleen Kaur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customize your data ingestion with Elastic input packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/customize-data-ingestion-elastic-input-packages</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/customize-data-ingestion-elastic-input-packages"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic® has enabled the collection, transformation, and analysis of data flowing between the external data sources and Elastic Observability Solution through integrations. Integration packages achieve this by encapsulating several components, including agent configuration, inputs for data collection, and assets like ingest pipelines, data streams, index templates, and visualizations. The breadth of these assets supported in the Elastic Stack increases day by day. 
This blog dives into how input packages provide an extremely generic and flexible solution to the advanced users for customizing their ingestion experience in Elastic.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt1e9826a298a33a1d/65131d1e90c094c11eef472f/elastic-blog-1-config-parameters.png,elastic-blog-1-con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishleen Kaur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Factorial Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2835/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2835/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/factorial_numbers.png" title="So what do we do when we get to base 10? Do we use A, B, C, etc? No: Numbers larger than about 3.6 million are simply illegal." alt="So what do we do when we get to base 10? Do we use A, B, C, etc? No: Numbers larger than about 3.6 million are simply illegal." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A small shopping list (floss and more)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47363</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/796614728/0/sethsblog~A-small-shopping-list-floss-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T20:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are some books and household items that I wanted to share. I’m mostly into audiobooks these days–a good narrator combined with a good author is pretty rare and wonderful… It turns out that a breakthrough rice cooker is a bargain, even if it seems expensive at first. The Cuckoo is an extraordinary device. It […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DynIBaR: Space-time view synthesis from videos of dynamic scenes]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/dynibar-space-time-view-synthesis-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/dynibar-space-time-view-synthesis-from.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zhengqi Li and Noah Snavely, Research Scientists, Google Research







A mobile phone’s camera is a powerful tool for capturing everyday moments. However, capturing a dynamic scene using a single camera is fundamentally limited. For instance, if we wanted to adjust the camera motion or timing of a recorded video (e.g., to freeze time while sweeping the camera around to highlight a dramatic moment), we would typically need an expensive Hollywood setup with a synchronized camera rig. Would it be possible to achieve similar effects solely from a video captured using a mobile phone’s camera, without a Hollywood budget?



In “DynIBaR: Neural Dynamic Image-Based Rendering”, a best paper honorable mention at CVPR 2023, we describe a new method that generates photorealistic free-viewp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 EAP 2: All-in-One Diff Viewer, Run to Cursor Inlay Option, And More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=391141</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/09/intellij-idea-2023-3-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T19:44:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second EAP build for IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 is now available. It introduces enhancements designed to streamline code reviews, simplify the debugging workflow, and accelerate the startup process for both Maven and Gradle projects. You can get the latest build from our website, the free Toolbox App, or via snaps for Ubuntu. If you’d like […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-weighted gradient descent via distributionally robust optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/re-weighted-gradient-descent-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/re-weighted-gradient-descent-via.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T18:16:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ramnath Kumar, Pre-Doctoral Researcher, and Arun Sai Suggala, Research Scientist, Google Research





Deep neural networks (DNNs) have become essential for solving a wide range of tasks, from standard supervised learning (image classification using ViT) to meta-learning. The most commonly-used paradigm for learning DNNs is empirical risk minimization (ERM), which aims to identify a network that minimizes the average loss on training data points. Several algorithms, including stochastic gradient descent (SGD), Adam, and Adagrad, have been proposed for solving ERM. However, a drawback of ERM is that it weights all the samples equally, often ignoring the rare and more difficult samples, and focusing on the easier and abundant samples. This leads to suboptimal performance on unseen data, espe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Learning Pathways: Learn from the best]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-28-github-learning-pathways-learn-from-the-best/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-28-github-learning-pathways-learn-from-the-best/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T17:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Gain expertise and insights from top organizations through guided tutorials, boosting productivity, enhancing security, and enabling seamless collaboration.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-28-github-learning-pathways-learn-from-the-best/">GitHub Learning Pathways: Learn from the best</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.15 brings UI updates, PKI enhancements, new betas, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-15-brings-ui-updates-pki-enhancements-new-betas-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-15-brings-ui-updates-pki-enhancements-new-betas-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.15 contains a range of updates from UI updates and PKI enhancements to betas for Enterprise secrets sync, Enterprise seal high availability, and event monitoring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Ready for JetBrains JavaScript Day 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=392207</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/09/get-ready-for-jetbrains-javascript-day-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T16:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calling all JavaScript enthusiasts! Registration for JetBrains JavaScript Day 2023 is now open, and you can be sure that this year’s event is going to be a special one! We know how hard it is to keep up with the ever-changing world of JavaScript – we sometimes find it challenging to stay on top of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Aganezova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud no-code provisioning adds module version upgrades in beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-no-code-provisioning-adds-module-version-upgrades-in-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-no-code-provisioning-adds-module-version-upgrades-in-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No-code provisioning adds more Day 2 operations. Users can now update the module version used in their no-code workspaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Azure DevOps scopes now available for Microsoft Identity OAuth delegated flow apps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67699</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-azure-devops-scopes-now-available-for-microsoft-identity-oauth-delegated-flow-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T14:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have added new Azure DevOps scopes for delegated OAuth apps on the Microsoft Identity platform, also colloquially known as Azure Active Directory OAuth apps. These new scopes will enable app developers to announce specifically which permissions they are hoping to request from the user in order to perform app duties.
The post New Azure DevOps scopes now available for Microsoft Identity OAuth delegated flow apps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock Is Now Generally Available – Build and Scale Generative AI Applications with Foundation Models]]></title>
        <id>87d4f2587de031cfb55e02ce3038009a4561c184</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-bedrock-is-now-generally-available-build-and-scale-generative-ai-applications-with-foundation-models/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T13:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This April, we announced Amazon Bedrock as part of a set of new tools for building with generative AI on AWS. Amazon Bedrock is a fully managed service that offers a choice of high-performing foundation models (FMs) from leading AI companies, including AI21 Labs, Anthropic, Cohere, Stability AI, and Amazon, along with a broad set […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Containerized Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/announcing-containerized-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/announcing-containerized-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you know and love about Ansible Automation Platform in containerized form
 
We’re excited to announce something that we’ve been working on for a while now, the technical preview of a containerized Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building APIs With Django REST Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=389613</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/09/building-apis-with-django-rest-framework/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T12:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Django REST framework tutorial, you will create a rental platform API. The tutorial demonstrates how to use Python and Django REST framework in PyCharm to develop APIs. By the time you complete the tutorial, you will be able to answer the following questions: Prerequisites To successfully complete the Django REST framework tutorial, you’ll […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denis Mashutin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet 1.24 Comes With Project-Specific Code Reformatting, Git Integration Enhancements, and Other Improvements.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=fleet&amp;p=392367</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/fleet/2023/09/fleet-1-24-comes-with-project-specific-code-reformatting-git-integration-enhancements-and-other-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T12:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet 1.24 is now available! This latest release comes packed with a variety of new features and enhancements designed to elevate your development experience. Dive into the following overview to discover this update’s most notable changes: New features Improvements Bugfixes These are the most important updates for Fleet 1.24. See the full release notes for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Prokashev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-42793 Vulnerability in TeamCity: Post-Mortem]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=392576</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/09/cve-2023-42793-vulnerability-post-mortem/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T11:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Actions taken by the TeamCity team On September 6, 2023, we received a report from Sonar regarding a critical vulnerability issue identified in TeamCity On-Premises. If abused, the flaw could enable an unauthenticated attacker with HTTP(S) access to a TeamCity server to perform a remote code execution (RCE) attack and gain administrative control of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2023 Day 2 Live Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=90979</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/camundacon-2023-day-2-live-blog/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get all the latest updates and recaps of what's happening in this live blog of CamundaCon 2023.
The post CamundaCon 2023 Day 2 Live Blog appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thoughts on the manual]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47332</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/796525661/0/sethsblog~Thoughts-on-the-manual/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T08:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have more ways to offer instructions than ever before, but it’s not obvious that we’re getting better at it. Not just the operator’s manual, but every way we have to teach and offer instructions… Some (uncategorized) things to consider: The first manual I created, in 1983, was for eight year old kids. I was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Producer Initiated Transactions in Spring Cloud Stream Kafka Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/28/producer-initiated-transactions-in-spring-cloud-stream-kafka-applications</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/28/producer-initiated-transactions-in-spring-cloud-stream-kafka-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soby Chacko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring AI lead Dr. Mark Pollack]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/28/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-ai-lead-dr-mark-pollack</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/28/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-ai-lead-dr-mark-pollack"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elasticians celebrate their culture this Elasticians Unidos month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-celebrate-elasticians-unidos-month</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-celebrate-elasticians-unidos-month"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hispanic Heritage month—or as we like to call it, Elasticians Unidos Month is a month to celebrate the culture and impact of Latinx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic SQL inputs: A generic solution for database metrics observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-sql-inputs-generic-solution-database-metrics-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-sql-inputs-generic-solution-database-metrics-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog dives into the functionality of generic SQL and provides various use cases for advanced users to ingest custom metrics to Elastic for database observability. We also introduce the fetch from all database new capability released in 8.10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lalit Satapathy,Ishleen Kaur,Muthukumar Paramasivam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elasticians celebrate their culture this Elasticians Unidos month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-celebrate-elasticians-unidos-month</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-celebrate-elasticians-unidos-month"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Hispanic Heritage month — or as we like to call it, Elasticians Unidos month to align with our Elasiticans Unidos ERG — is celebrated every year from September 15 through October 15 in the United States. We’re taking that celebration global and honoring the impact Hispanic Americans have had on the world. 
As a global company, we celebrate cultural diversity and its positive impact on our Elasticians, teams, and business. Where someone comes from is a big part of who they are and personal experiences shape so much of who we are.
We have a few different events scheduled for Elasticians to participate in throughout Elasticians Unidos month, including a fireside chat with Latinitas, an organization that empowers girls to innovate through media and technology, an interactive event that showc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic SQL inputs: A generic solution for database metrics observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-sql-inputs-generic-solution-database-metrics-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-sql-inputs-generic-solution-database-metrics-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic® SQL inputs (metricbeat module and input package) allows the user to execute SQL queries against many supported databases in a flexible way and ingest the resulting metrics to Elasticsearch®. This blog dives into the functionality of generic SQL and provides various use cases for advanced users to ingest custom metrics to Elastic®, for database observability. The blog also introduces the fetch from all database new capability, released in 8.10.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt59cb255469f677f2/64ff40a220c4f96b016fc63d/elastic-blog-1-genericSQL.png,elastic-blog-1-genericSQL.pngFunctionalities details,
This section covers some of the features that would help with the metrics extraction. We provide a brief description of the response format configuratio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lalit Satapathy,Ishleen Kaur,Muthukumar Paramasivam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon MSK Introduces Managed Data Delivery from Apache Kafka to Your Data Lake]]></title>
        <id>20db51bf42eed2d350d691f7fe9c14057c7b658d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-msk-introduces-managed-data-delivery-from-apache-kafka-to-your-data-lake/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T21:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m excited to announce today a new capability of Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka (Amazon MSK) that allows you to continuously load data from an Apache Kafka cluster to Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3). We use Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose—an extract, transform, and load (ETL) service—to read data from a Kafka topic, transform […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.3 EAP2: Support for Device Tree Files and Meson]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=392318</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/09/clion-2023-3-eap2-support-for-device-tree-files-and-meson/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T16:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CLion 2023.3 Early Access Program has just started, featuring assembly view for files, enhanced C++ data flow analysis, and other updates. The CLion 2023.3 EAP2 build is ready for you to try! With it, you can finally start working on Meson projects in CLion and benefit from device tree format support. Build 233.8264.3 is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I used GitHub Copilot Chat to build a ReactJS gallery prototype]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-27-how-i-used-github-copilot-chat-to-build-a-reactjs-gallery-prototype/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-27-how-i-used-github-copilot-chat-to-build-a-reactjs-gallery-prototype/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T16:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub Copilot Chat can help developers create prototypes, understand code, make UI changes, troubleshoot errors, make code more accessible, and generate unit tests. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-27-how-i-used-github-copilot-chat-to-build-a-reactjs-gallery-prototype/">How I used GitHub Copilot Chat to build a ReactJS gallery prototype</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2023 Day 1 Live Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=90977</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/camundacon-2023-day-1-live-blog/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get all the latest updates and recaps of what's happening in this live blog of CamundaCon 2023.
The post CamundaCon 2023 Day 1 Live Blog appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managed identity and service principal support for Azure DevOps now in General Availability (GA)]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67669</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/managed-identity-and-service-principal-support-for-azure-devops-now-in-general-availability-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T11:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After announcing the release of Managed Identity and Service Principal support in public preview last March, we were overcome by the positive response many of you had. We’re grateful to those who have taken the time to implement a managed identity within your apps and tools.
The post Managed identity and service principal support for Azure DevOps now in General Availability (GA) appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Annotated – September 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=392127</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/09/php-annotated-september-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T10:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the September edition of PHP Annotated! We’ll recap the most interesting developments in the PHP community over the past month, featuring handpicked news, articles, tools, and videos. Highlights PHP 8.0.30, PHP 8.1.22, and PHP 8.2.9 have been released ❗These are security releases and include fixes for GHSA-3qrf-m4j2-pcrr (external entity loading in XML without […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.3 Early Access Program Is Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=391622</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/09/2023-3-eap-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T09:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UI/UX Enhancements, Support for PEP 647, and More The Early Access Program for PyCharm 2023.3 kicks off today, offering you a sneak peek of the exciting new features and improvements we expect to include in the next major release. If you’re not familiar with how the EAP works, please read this blog post for an introduction to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Jenga situation]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47214</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/796072964/0/sethsblog~The-Jenga-situation/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T09:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When an organization first sets out to have an impact, it discovers that it has no customers, no clients, no constituents. So it shows up, it makes an offer and it listens. The early days are exciting. Customers are seen and heard and served. Variations are created and value is produced as problems are solved. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Transactions in Spring Cloud Stream Kafka Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/27/introduction-to-transactions-in-spring-cloud-stream-kafka-applications</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/27/introduction-to-transactions-in-spring-cloud-stream-kafka-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soby Chacko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionizing big data management: Unveiling the power of Amazon EMR and Elastic integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-data-management-amazon-emr-elastic-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-data-management-amazon-emr-elastic-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EMR allows you to easily run and scale big data workloads. With Elastic’s native integration, you'll find the confidence to monitor, analyze, and optimize your EMR clusters, opening up exciting opportunities for your data-driven initiatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy (Uday),Subhrata Kulshrestha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionizing big data management: Unveiling the power of Amazon EMR and Elastic integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-data-management-amazon-emr-elastic-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-data-management-amazon-emr-elastic-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In the dynamic realm of data processing, Amazon EMR takes center stage as an AWS-provided big data service, offering a cost-effective conduit for running Apache Spark and a plethora of other open-source applications. While the capabilities of EMR are impressive, the art of vigilant monitoring holds the key to unlocking its full potential. This blog post explains the pivotal role of monitoring Amazon EMR clusters, accentuating the transformative integration with Elastic®.
Elastic can make it easier for organizations to transform data into actionable insights and stop threats quickly with unified visibility across your environment — so mission-critical applications can keep running smoothly no matter what. From a free trial and fast deployment to sending logs to Elastic securely and fricti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy (Uday),Subhrata Kulshrestha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book Podcasts]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2834/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2834/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/book_podcasts.png" title="I've been working my way through this 1950s podcast by someone named John Tolkien called 'Lord of the Rings'--it's a deep dive into this fictional world he created. Good stuff, really bingeable!" alt="I've been working my way through this 1950s podcast by someone named John Tolkien called 'Lord of the Rings'--it's a deep dive into this fictional world he created. Good stuff, really bingeable!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting the Dots: How Camunda Connectors and RPA Simplify Process Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=91276</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/how-camunda-connectors-and-rpa-simplify-process-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T18:12:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Connectors from a process orchestration solution like Camunda can pair with RPA tools to make automation easier.
The post Connecting the Dots: How Camunda Connectors and RPA Simplify Process Automation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Arroyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub uses GitHub Actions and Actions larger runners to build and test GitHub.com]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-26-how-github-uses-github-actions-and-actions-larger-runners-to-build-and-test-github-com/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-26-how-github-uses-github-actions-and-actions-larger-runners-to-build-and-test-github-com/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T17:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently, we’ve been working to make our CI experience better by leveraging the newly released GitHub feature, Actions larger runners, to run our CI. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-26-how-github-uses-github-actions-and-actions-larger-runners-to-build-and-test-github-com/">How GitHub uses GitHub Actions and Actions larger runners to build and test GitHub.com</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your ultimate guide to the GitHub Universe ‘23 agenda]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-26-your-ultimate-guide-to-the-github-universe-23-agenda/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-26-your-ultimate-guide-to-the-github-universe-23-agenda/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T16:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Get a sneak peek into the must-attend sessions, speakers, workshops, and GitHub certifications available at our global developer event.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-26-your-ultimate-guide-to-the-github-universe-23-agenda/">Your ultimate guide to the GitHub Universe ‘23 agenda</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTrack Now With Improved Knowledge Base Collaboration]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=youtrack&amp;p=384706</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/youtrack/2023/09/youtrack-now-with-improved-knowledge-base-collaboration/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T15:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The YouTrack 2023.2 release brings powerful updates to article collaboration in the Knowledge Base, improves the experience of both support teams and customers within helpdesk projects, adds Turkish language support, and supercharges YouTrack’s performance for everyone working with tasks. YouTrack’s Knowledge Base has become even more collaborative and informative for internal teams and external readers. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Pishkova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting RCE in Chrome with incorrect side effect in the JIT compiler]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-26-getting-rce-in-chrome-with-incorrect-side-effect-in-the-jit-compiler/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-26-getting-rce-in-chrome-with-incorrect-side-effect-in-the-jit-compiler/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T15:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In this post, I'll exploit CVE-2023-3420, a type confusion in Chrome that allows remote code execution (RCE) in the renderer sandbox of Chrome by a single visit to a malicious site.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-26-getting-rce-in-chrome-with-incorrect-side-effect-in-the-jit-compiler/">Getting RCE in Chrome with incorrect side effect in the JIT compiler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research embarks on effort to map a mouse brain]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/google-research-embarks-on-effort-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/google-research-embarks-on-effort-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Michał Januszewski, Research Scientist, Google Research






The human brain is perhaps the most computationally complex machine in existence, consisting of networks of billions of cells. Researchers currently don’t understand the full picture of how glitches in its network machinery contribute to mental illnesses and other diseases, such as dementia. However, the emerging connectomics field, which aims to precisely map the connections between every cell in the brain, could help solve that problem. While maps have only been created for simpler organisms, technological advances for mapping even larger brains can enable us to understand how the human brain works, and how to treat brain diseases.



Today, we're excited to announce that the Connectomics team at Google Research and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Ansible Galaxy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-ansible-galaxy</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-ansible-galaxy"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For awhile, the Red Hat Ansible team behind the components Ansible automation hub and Ansible cloud automation hub at console.redhat.com have been on a special ops mission to enhance the galaxy_ng code base that serves the aforementioned components to also serve galaxy.ansible.com, with the intention of replacing galaxy.ansible.com with a fresh code base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toward stickiness]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47315</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/795419141/0/sethsblog~Toward-stickiness/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting the word out is easy to measure and exciting as well. Focusing on this misses the point. You might be able to get a song played on the radio, but will the song motivate listeners to show up at the concert? The math is simple: You can’t build a freelance career or a restaurant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 26th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/26/this-week-in-spring-september-26th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/26/this-week-in-spring-september-26th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Filestream fingerprint mode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-filestream-fingerprint-mode</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-filestream-fingerprint-mode"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Filebeat 8.10.0 and 7.17.12 we introduced a new fingerprint mode. This article covers the problem this new mode solves, what changes have been made to implement it, and details on how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denis Rechkunov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking whole-system visibility with Elastic Universal Profiling™]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whole-system-visibility-elastic-universal-profiling</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whole-system-visibility-elastic-universal-profiling"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual profiling data can be overwhelming. This blog post aims to demystify continuous profiling and guide you through its unique visualizations. We will equip you with the knowledge to derive quick, actionable insights from Universal Profiling™.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Ogbole,Francesco Gualazzi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Filestream fingerprint mode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-filestream-fingerprint-mode</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-filestream-fingerprint-mode"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In Filebeat 8.10.0 and 7.17.12, we introduced a new fingerprint mode that gives our users an option to use hashing of the files’ content for identifying them instead of relying on file system metadata. This change is available in Filestream inputs.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt65f62324bd9ac6bd/6512334a69060a0304fc1d72/elastic-blog-1-Filestream-architecture.png,elastic-blog-1-Filestream-architecture.png,
Peeling the onion of the top components:
File Scanner collects information about all files that match paths of the input.
File Watcher scans the file system every few seconds, as specified in the prospector.scanner.check_interval setting, and then compares the file system states between checks. If something changes, it emits an event describing the change…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denis Rechkunov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking whole-system visibility with Elastic Universal Profiling™]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whole-system-visibility-elastic-universal-profiling</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whole-system-visibility-elastic-universal-profiling"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identify, optimize, measure, repeat! ,
SREs and developers who want to maintain robust, efficient systems and achieve optimal code performance need effective tools to measure and improve code performance. Profilers are invaluable for these tasks, as they can help you boost your app's throughput, ensure consistent system reliability, and gain a deeper understanding of your code's behavior at runtime. However, traditional profilers can be cumbersome to use, as they often require code recompilation and are limited to specific languages. Additionally, they can also have a high overhead that negatively affects performance and makes them less suitable for quick, real-time debugging in production environments.
To address the limitations of traditional profilers, Elastic® recently announced the ge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Ogbole,Francesco Gualazzi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Happy 7th Birthday kubeadm!]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/26/happy-7th-birthday-kubeadm/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/26/happy-7th-birthday-kubeadm/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fabrizio Pandini (VMware)
What a journey so far!
Starting from the initial blog post “How we made Kubernetes insanely easy to install” in September 2016, followed by an exciting growth that lead to general availability / “Production-Ready Kubernetes Cluster Creation with kubeadm” two years later.
And later on a continuous, steady and reliable flow of small improvements that is still going on as of today.
What is kubeadm? (quick refresher)
kubeadm is focused on bootstrapping Kubernetes clusters on existing infrastructure and performing an essential set of maintenance tasks. The core of the kubeadm interface is quite simple: new control plane nodes
are created by running kubeadm init and
worker nodes are joined to the control plane by running
kubeadm join.
Also included are utilities…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon EC2 M2 Pro Mac, Amazon Coretto 21, Amazon CloudWatch Synthetics, and more (Sept. 25, 2023)]]></title>
        <id>e6ef9c7dfd44aa0831944f8c5ff466f0d1a2fd30</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-ec2-m2-pro-mac-amazon-coretto-21-amazon-cloudwatch-synthetics-and-more-sept-25-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T21:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I’m in Jakarta to support AWS User Group Indonesia and AWS Cloud Day Indonesia. Yesterday, I attended a community event – a collaboration between AWS User Group Indonesia and Hacktiv8 with “Innovating Yourself as Early-Stage Developers” as the main theme. We had a blast and I had a wonderful time connecting with speakers and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Rollout Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67655</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-rollout-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T18:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July, we provided an overview on the steps for New Boards hub to go GA. In this blog post, we wanted to provide a short update on where things are at and what you can expect over the next couple of months.
The post New Boards Hub Rollout Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calling all teachers! Learn how to build new commands on the GitHub Classroom CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-25-calling-all-teachers-learn-how-to-build-new-commands-on-the-github-classroom-cli/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-25-calling-all-teachers-learn-how-to-build-new-commands-on-the-github-classroom-cli/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T16:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In this step-by-step tutorial, we’ll dive into how you can become the next open source contributor to the GitHub Classroom CLI, building commands that you can use to improve your workflow as an educator!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-25-calling-all-teachers-learn-how-to-build-new-commands-on-the-github-classroom-cli/">Calling all teachers! Learn how to build new commands on the GitHub Classroom CLI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Consul on Kubernetes with Argo CD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploy-consul-on-kubernetes-with-argo-cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploy-consul-on-kubernetes-with-argo-cd"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use GitOps to deploy and synchronize a Consul cluster on Kubernetes with Argo CD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Heimstaden chose Camunda for Their Tenant Ticketing System]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=91192</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/why-camunda-platform-8-heimstaden/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T14:54:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why Camunda? Learn how real estate invester Heimstaden utilizes Camunda to orchestrate their tenant support ticketing system.
The post Why Heimstaden chose Camunda for Their Tenant Ticketing System appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kickstart Your Next Automation Project with the New Camunda Starter Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=91087</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/camunda-starter/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've relaunched our Professional plan as the Starter plan with an updated offering and a new monthly price to help you get started faster.
The post Kickstart Your Next Automation Project with the New Camunda Starter Plan appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joao Oliveira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More vs. better]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47304</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/795053633/0/sethsblog~More-vs-better/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T08:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If every building in the shopping district in a big city was owned by one landlord, rents would go up. So would the prices of everything sold. The landlord would keep a significant percentage of each store’s profits and innovation would suffer as well. Google’s monopoly is real. They pay Apple more than a million […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking seamless API management: Introducing AWS API Gateway integration with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/api-management-aws-api-gateway-integration-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/api-management-aws-api-gateway-integration-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Elastic's AWS API Gateway integration, application owners and developers unlock the capability to proactively identify and resolve problems, fine-tune resource utilization, and provide extraordinary digital experiences to their users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy (Uday),Subhrata Kulshrestha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking seamless API management: Introducing AWS API Gateway integration with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/api-management-aws-api-gateway-integration-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/api-management-aws-api-gateway-integration-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
AWS API Gateway is a powerful service that redefines API management. It serves as a gateway for creating, deploying, and managing APIs, enabling businesses to establish seamless connections between different applications and services. With features like authentication, authorization, and traffic control, API Gateway ensures the security and reliability of API interactions. 
In an era where APIs serve as the backbone of modern applications, having the means to maintain visibility and control over these vital components is absolutely essential. In this blog post, we dive deep into the comprehensive observability solution offered by Elastic®, ensuring real-time visibility, advanced analytics, and actionable insights, empowering you to fine-tune your API Gateway for optimal performance.
For …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy (Uday),Subhrata Kulshrestha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lying]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2833/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2833/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/lying.png" title="I was, at least at the start of this disastrous game night, your friend." alt="I was, at least at the start of this disastrous game night, your friend." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: kubeadm: Use etcd Learner to Join a Control Plane Node Safely]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/25/kubeadm-use-etcd-learner-mode/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/25/kubeadm-use-etcd-learner-mode/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Paco Xu (DaoCloud)
The kubeadm tool now supports etcd learner mode, which
allows you to enhance the resilience and stability
of your Kubernetes clusters by leveraging the learner mode
feature introduced in etcd version 3.4.
This guide will walk you through using etcd learner mode with kubeadm. By default, kubeadm runs
a local etcd instance on each control plane node.
In v1.27, kubeadm introduced a new feature gate EtcdLearnerMode. With this feature gate enabled,
when joining a new control plane node, a new etcd member will be created as a learner and
promoted to a voting member only after the etcd data are fully aligned.
What are the advantages of using etcd learner mode?
etcd learner mode offers several compelling reasons to consider its adoption
in Kubernetes clusters:
Enhanced R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resolving Process Incidents and Exceptions with Operate]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=90999</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/resolving-process-incidents-exceptions-operate/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that you can keep your process instances moving with Operate? Learn how in this tutorial.
The post Resolving Process Incidents and Exceptions with Operate appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Contributor Summit, Durham 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-contributor-summit-durham-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-contributor-summit-durham-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Ansible Contributor Summit in Durham, as well as how to register and propose topics for the event. This is a full day working session especially for community contributors to interact with one another, as well as with Ansible development teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Ansible Community Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paketo Buildpacks Bionic End Of Support]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/22/paketo-buildpacks-bionic-end-of-support</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/22/paketo-buildpacks-bionic-end-of-support"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Frederick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplified Event Externalization with Spring Modulith]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/22/simplified-event-externalization-with-spring-modulith</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/22/simplified-event-externalization-with-spring-modulith"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your Elastic Cloud deployment with AWS PrivateLink traffic filter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-elastic-cloud-deployment-aws-privatelink-traffic-filter</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-elastic-cloud-deployment-aws-privatelink-traffic-filter"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your Elastic Cloud deployment using Elasticsearch AWS PrivateLink traffic filter. It improves security by establishing private connectivity between customer AWS VPC and customer Elastic Cloud deployments in the respective AWS region.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemendra Singh Lodhi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic launches new Verified Designation for Managed Service Provider partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-verified-designation-managed-service-provider-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-verified-designation-managed-service-provider-partners"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic invests in new partner programs designed to empower Managed Service Provider partners to sell, support, and embed Elastic solutions as part of your global portfolio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kosman,Isabelle Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your Elastic Cloud deployment with AWS PrivateLink traffic filter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-elastic-cloud-deployment-aws-privatelink-traffic-filter</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-elastic-cloud-deployment-aws-privatelink-traffic-filter"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
One of the security features available in Elasticsearch® Service (Elastic® Cloud) is traffic filtering. Traffic filtering enables network layer security by limiting access to the deployment from configured networks only. In addition to the security policies consisting of role based access control (RBAC) employing principle of least privilege, using traffic filtering in conjunction provides greater security.

Elasticsearch Service (Elastic Cloud) supports CIDR (Classless Inter-Domain Routing) or IP address based traffic filtering in the form of 199.226.244.0/24 or 82.102.25.74. It also integrates traffic from major cloud providers: Amazon Web Services (AWS) VPC over AWS PrivateLink, Azure Virtual Network (VNets), and Google Cloud (GCP) Private Service Connect, for their respective cloud p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemendra Singh Lodhi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic launches new Verified Designation for Managed Service Provider partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-verified-designation-managed-service-provider-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-verified-designation-managed-service-provider-partners"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic® understands the need for quality, reliability, innovation, and support to foster strong relationships and partnerships. As such, Elastic is committed to investing in new partner programs designed to empower you to sell, support, and embed Elastic solutions as part of your global portfolio. 

As part of our evolving partner strategy, we are focusing on helping our Managed Service Provider (MSP) partners better represent and differentiate themselves to new and prospective end customers. As such, we have designed a number of new program benefits, which include: Guided Support, Enablement, Service co-creation workshops, and go-to-market support. 

In addition, Elastic is happy to announce a new special designation available to all of our MSPs: the Verified Managed Services Provider (MSP) designation. By capitalizing on exclusive benefits for our Verified MSP partners, you can further strengthen your partnership with Elastic, engage with your customers, and distinguish yourself in the market.
How to get started,
If you are interested in becoming a Verified MSP, simply sign up to be evaluated. To fill out the form, you need these three items:


Two Elastic certified engineers

One existing reference architecture or design document 

A list of your third-party vendors 


For more information on the benefits of becoming Elastic Verified, visit our MSP partners page.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kosman,Isabelle Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distilling step-by-step: Outperforming larger language models with less training data and smaller model sizes]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/distilling-step-by-step-outperforming.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/distilling-step-by-step-outperforming.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cheng-Yu Hsieh, Student Researcher, and Chen-Yu Lee, Research Scientist, Cloud AI Team





Large language models (LLMs) have enabled a new data-efficient learning paradigm wherein they can be used to solve unseen new tasks via zero-shot or few-shot prompting. However, LLMs are challenging to deploy for real-world applications due to their sheer size. For instance, serving a single 175 billion LLM requires at least 350GB of GPU memory using specialized infrastructure, not to mention that today's state-of-the-art LLMs are composed of over 500 billion parameters. Such computational requirements are inaccessible for many research teams, especially for applications that require low latency performance.




To circumvent these deployment challenges, practitioners often choose to deplo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 6 Benefits of Event-Driven Business Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=90875</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/top-benefits-event-driven-business-process-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T21:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-streaming technology has many advantages. Learn how your business processes can benefit from using it for process orchestration.
The post Top 6 Benefits of Event-Driven Business Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Security Lab’s journey to disclosing 500 CVEs in open source projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-21-the-github-security-labs-journey-to-disclosing-500-cves-in-open-source-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-21-the-github-security-labs-journey-to-disclosing-500-cves-in-open-source-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T20:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The GitHub Security Lab audits open source projects for security vulnerabilities and helps maintainers fix them. Recently, we passed the milestone of 500 CVEs disclosed. Let’s take a trip down memory lane with a review of some noteworthy CVEs!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-21-the-github-security-labs-journey-to-disclosing-500-cves-in-open-source-projects/">The GitHub Security Lab’s journey to disclosing 500 CVEs in open source projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet HashiCorp’s boomerang interns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/meet-hashicorp-s-boomerang-interns</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/meet-hashicorp-s-boomerang-interns"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hear from four Hashi-interns who have spent more than one summer with the company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.1 M1 and 1.0.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-modulith-1-1-m1-and-1-0-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-modulith-1-1-m1-and-1-0-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Java community legend Sharat Chander]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/a-bootiful-podcast-java-community-legend-sharat-chander</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/a-bootiful-podcast-java-community-legend-sharat-chander"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.0-M3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-boot-3-2-0-m3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-boot-3-2-0-m3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Add Your Swift Packages to AWS CodeArtifact]]></title>
        <id>416cc344dd4464df6f6cae5418f4a7665bdcd4a2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-add-your-swift-packages-to-aws-codeartifact/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T22:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, Swift developers who write code for Apple platforms (iOS, iPadOS, macOS, tvOS, watchOS, or visionOS) or for Swift applications running on the server side can use AWS CodeArtifact to securely store and retrieve their package dependencies. CodeArtifact integrates with standard developer tools such as Xcode, xcodebuild, and the Swift Package Manager (the swift […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is ACME PKI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-is-acme-pki</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-is-acme-pki"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the ACME protocol for PKI, the common problems it solves, and why it should be part of your certificate management roadmap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observing Camunda Environments with IBM Instana Business Monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=90552</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/observing-camunda-environments-ibm-instana-business-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T19:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Combining a process orchestration solution like Camunda with an observability solution like Instana can break down silos and help teams better understand their systems.
The post Observing Camunda Environments with IBM Instana Business Monitoring appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cross Ganaway</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise adds new flexible deployment options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-new-flexible-deployment-options</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-new-flexible-deployment-options"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise now supports more flexible deployment options for self-hosted environments, including cloud-managed Kubernetes services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Generally Available: GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps is ready for you to use]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67480</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/now-generally-available-github-advanced-security-for-azure-devops-is-ready-for-you-to-use/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T15:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps is now generally available and is ready for you to use in your own Azure DevOps repos! You can now enable code, secret, and dependency scanning within Azure Repos and take advantage of the new product updates.
The post Now Generally Available: GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps is ready for you to use appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第237話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755225457808</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755225457808"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor Process Instance Progress on a BPMN diagram via the Operate API]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=90560</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/monitor-process-instance-progress-bpmn-diagram-operate-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to provide the status of running and completed instances in your own custom UIs.
The post Monitor Process Instance Progress on a BPMN diagram via the Operate API appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M2 Pro Mac Instances Built on Apple Silicon M2 Pro Mac Mini Computers]]></title>
        <id>44c35de4f6bf0c5b6f008dc79b434a3de65444cd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-m2-pro-mac-instances-built-on-apple-silicon-m2-pro-mac-mini-computers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T20:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the general availability of Amazon EC2 M2 Pro Mac instances. These instances deliver up to 35 percent faster performance over the existing M1 Mac instances when building and testing applications for Apple platforms. New EC2 M2 Pro Mac instances are powered by Apple M2 Pro Mac Mini computers featuring 12 core […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Azure DevOps Server 2022 Update 1 RC1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67633</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-azure-devops-server-2022-update-1-rc1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T19:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re very excited to announce the first release candidate (RC1) of Azure DevOps Server 2022.1!
Last Accessed column on Delivery Plans page
There are many more features with this release,
The post Introducing Azure DevOps Server 2022 Update 1 RC1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – NVMe Reservations for Amazon Elastic Block Store io2 Volumes]]></title>
        <id>8a8dbf5c7083cca1519f0502d44702094c90f6a1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-nvme-reservations-for-amazon-elastic-block-store-io2-volumes/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T18:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) io2 and io2 Block Express volumes now support storage fencing using NVMe reservations. As I learned while writing this post, storage fencing is used to regulate access to storage for a compute or database cluster, ensuring that just one host in the cluster has permission to write to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the removal of bundled plugins in HashiCorp Packer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-removal-of-bundled-plugins-in-hashicorp-packer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-removal-of-bundled-plugins-in-hashicorp-packer"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the final step in moving towards external plugins, HashiCorp Packer will stop bundling official plugins within its binary releases. Here’s what that means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud now supports assigning agent pools at the organization level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-now-supports-assigning-agent-pools-at-the-organization-level</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-now-supports-assigning-agent-pools-at-the-organization-level"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assigning agents at the organization level provides a faster, more consistent, and scalable approach to agent pool configuration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: C7i Instances, Knowledge Base for Amazon Bedrock, and More (Sept. 18, 2023)]]></title>
        <id>d1bcf2bd9f720f4423af24b67cf619a2cbec257c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-c7i-instances-knowledge-base-for-amazon-bedrock-and-more-sept-18-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While daylight is getting shorter in the Northern hemisphere, we’ve got two new EC2 instance types optimized for compute and memory and many new capabilities for other services. Last week there was also the EMEA AWS Heroes Summit in Munich, an amazing day full of insights and passion. Here’s a nice picture of the participants! […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a multi-cloud golden image pipeline with Terraform Cloud and HCP Packer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multicloud-golden-image-pipeline-terraform-cloud-hcp-packer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multicloud-golden-image-pipeline-terraform-cloud-hcp-packer"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how creating a golden image pipeline can help unify and streamline your imaging and provisioning workflows throughout your infrastructure estate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MediaPipe FaceStylizer: On-device real-time few-shot face stylization]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/mediapipe-facestylizer-on-device-real.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/mediapipe-facestylizer-on-device-real.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T17:39:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Haolin Jia, Software Engineer, and Qifei Wang, Senior Software Engineer, Core ML



In recent years, we have witnessed rising interest across consumers and researchers in integrated augmented reality (AR) experiences using real-time face feature generation and editing functions in mobile applications, including short videos, virtual reality, and gaming. As a result, there is a growing demand for lightweight, yet high-quality face generation and editing models, which are often based on generative adversarial network (GAN) techniques. However, the majority of GAN models suffer from high computational complexity and the need for a large training dataset. In addition, it is also important to employ GAN models responsibly. 



In this post, we introduce MediaPipe FaceStylizer, an effi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating AI adoption on Azure with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerating-ai-adoption-on-azure-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerating-ai-adoption-on-azure-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use Terraform to scale the adoption of artificial intelligence in a Microsoft Azure environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-device content distillation with graph neural networks]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/on-device-content-distillation-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/on-device-content-distillation-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:39:00.035Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Gabriel Barcik and Duc-Hieu Tran, Research Engineers, Google Research




In today's digital age, smartphones and desktop web browsers serve as the primary tools for accessing news and information. However, the proliferation of website clutter — encompassing complex layouts, navigation elements, and extraneous links — significantly impairs both the reading experience and article navigation. This issue is particularly acute for individuals with accessibility requirements.



To improve the user experience and make reading more accessible, Android and Chrome users may leverage the Reading Mode feature, which enhances accessibility by processing webpages to allow customizable contrast, adjustable text size, more legible fonts, and to enable text-to-speech utilities. Additionally, An…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a Camunda Champion?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89980</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/are-you-a-camunda-champion/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T19:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to become a Camunda Champion? Join our community and get some great benefits.
The post Are you a Camunda Champion? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Alcantara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp extends security use cases with new Vault integrations including Oracle, Veeam, and Venafi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-extends-security-use-cases-with-new-vault-integrations-including-oracle</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-extends-security-use-cases-with-new-vault-integrations-including-oracle"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New HashiCorp Vault ecosystem integrations extend security use cases for customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview – Connect Foundation Models to Your Company Data Sources with Agents for Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>1364088e6dfe688a2aef712ce4bd05603087a126</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/preview-connect-foundation-models-to-your-company-data-sources-with-agents-for-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T14:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July, we announced the preview of agents for Amazon Bedrock, a new capability for developers to create generative AI applications that complete tasks. Today, I’m happy to introduce a new capability to securely connect foundation models (FMs) to your company data sources using agents. With a knowledge base, you can use agents to give […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: User Namespaces: Now Supports Running Stateful Pods in Alpha!]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/13/userns-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/13/userns-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Rodrigo Campos Catelin (Microsoft), Giuseppe Scrivano (Red Hat), Sascha Grunert (Red Hat)
Kubernetes v1.25 introduced support for user namespaces for only stateless
pods. Kubernetes 1.28 lifted that restriction, after some design changes were
done in 1.27.
The beauty of this feature is that:
it is trivial to adopt (you just need to set a bool in the pod spec)
doesn't need any changes for most applications
improves security by drastically enhancing the isolation of containers and
mitigating CVEs rated HIGH and CRITICAL.
This post explains the basics of user namespaces and also shows:
the changes that arrived in the recent Kubernetes v1.28 release
a demo of a vulnerability rated as HIGH that is not exploitable with user namespaces
the runtime requirements to use this feature
what yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World scale inverse reinforcement learning in Google Maps]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/world-scale-inverse-reinforcement.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/world-scale-inverse-reinforcement.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T21:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Matt Barnes, Software Engineer, Google Research




Routing in Google Maps remains one of our most helpful and frequently used features. Determining the best route from A to B requires making complex trade-offs between factors including the estimated time of arrival (ETA), tolls, directness, surface conditions (e.g., paved, unpaved roads), and user preferences, which vary across transportation mode and local geography. Often, the most natural visibility we have into travelers' preferences is by analyzing real-world travel patterns.



Learning preferences from observed sequential decision making behavior is a classic application of inverse reinforcement learning (IRL). Given a Markov decision process (MDP) — a formalization of the road network — and a set of demonstration traject…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[September patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67525</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/september-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T19:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.0.1
Team Foundation Server 2018.3.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 Patch 3
Note: If you have Azure DevOps Server 2022,
The post September patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Comparing Local Kubernetes Development Tools: Telepresence, Gefyra, and mirrord]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/12/local-k8s-development-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/12/local-k8s-development-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Eyal Bukchin (MetalBear)
The Kubernetes development cycle is an evolving landscape with a myriad of tools seeking to streamline the process. Each tool has its unique approach, and the choice often comes down to individual project requirements, the team's expertise, and the preferred workflow.
Among the various solutions, a category we dubbed “Local K8S Development tools” has emerged, which seeks to enhance the Kubernetes development experience by connecting locally running components to the Kubernetes cluster. This facilitates rapid testing of new code in cloud conditions, circumventing the traditional cycle of Dockerization, CI, and deployment.
In this post, we compare three solutions in this category: Telepresence, Gefyra, and our own contender, mirrord.
Telepresence
The oldest a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 R7a Instances Powered By 4th Gen AMD EPYC Processors for Memory Optimized Workloads]]></title>
        <id>64de4acd73459b1274a4808233a3fb07d4637598</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-r7a-instances-powered-by-4th-gen-amd-epyc-processors-for-memory-optimized-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T23:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched the memory optimized Amazon EC2 R6a instances in July 2022 powered by 3rd Gen AMD EPYC (Milan) processors, running at frequencies up to 3.6 GHz. Many customers who run workloads that are dependent on x86 instructions, such as SAP, are looking for ways to optimize their cloud utilization. They’re taking advantage of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: R7iz Instances, Amazon Connect, CloudWatch Logs, and Lots More (Sept. 11, 2023)]]></title>
        <id>e1de18a127682dd7c4d5fdc0b14ca2c6dd79e1b2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-r7iz-instances-amazon-connect-cloudwatch-logs-and-lots-more-sept-11-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T18:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like it is my turn once again to write the AWS Weekly Roundup. I wrote and published the first one on April 16, 2012 — just 4,165 short day ago! Last Week’s Launches Here are some of the launches that caught my eye last week: R7iz Instances – Optimized for high CPU performance and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp enters Gartner PAM MQ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-enters-gartner-pam-mq</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-enters-gartner-pam-mq"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Vault and Boundary, HashiCorp makes its debut in Gartner’s Magic Quadrant for privileged access management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the new Ansible Community Forum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/welcome-to-the-new-ansible-community-forum</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/welcome-to-the-new-ansible-community-forum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we're delighted to announce the launch of the new Ansible Community Forum - a single starting point for questions and help, development discussions, events, and much more. Everyone is invited, whether you are an Ansible user, contributor or developer, we are all community! Register here to join us!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Ansible Community Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public preview of Workload identity federation for Azure Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67467</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/public-preview-of-workload-identity-federation-for-azure-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T08:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to stop storing secrets and certificates in Azure service connections? Are you tired rotating these secrets whenever they expire? We are now announcing a public preview of workload identity federation for Azure service connections. Workload identity federation uses an industry-standard technology,
The post Public preview of Workload identity federation for Azure Pipelines appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differentially private median and more]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/differentially-private-median-and-more.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/differentially-private-median-and-more.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T22:59:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Edith Cohen and Uri Stemmer, Research Scientists, Google Research





Differential privacy (DP) is a rigorous mathematical definition of privacy. DP algorithms are randomized to protect user data by ensuring that the probability of any particular output is nearly unchanged when a data point is added or removed. Therefore, the output of a DP algorithm does not disclose the presence of any one data point. There has been significant progress in both foundational research and adoption of differential privacy with contributions such as the Privacy Sandbox and Google Open Source Library.


ML and data analytics algorithms can often be described as performing multiple basic computation steps on the same dataset. When each such step is differentially private, so is the output, but with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New version of ServiceNow Terraform Catalog enables resource updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-of-servicenow-terraform-catalog-enables-resource-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-of-servicenow-terraform-catalog-enables-resource-updates"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ServiceNow Service Catalog for Terraform now lets you update existing Terraform workspaces and reprovision resources with new variables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A novel computational fluid dynamics framework for turbulent flow research]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/a-novel-computational-fluid-dynamics.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/a-novel-computational-fluid-dynamics.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shantanu Shahane, Software Engineer, and Matthias Ihme, Research Scientist, Athena Team




Turbulence is ubiquitous in environmental and engineering fluid flows, and is encountered routinely in everyday life. A better understanding of these turbulent processes could provide valuable insights across a variety of research areas — improving the prediction of cloud formation by atmospheric transport and the spreading of wildfires by turbulent energy exchange, understanding sedimentation of deposits in rivers, and improving the efficiency of combustion in aircraft engines to reduce emissions, to name a few. However, despite its importance, our current understanding and our ability to reliably predict such flows remains limited. This is mainly attributed to the highly chaotic nature a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon EC2 R7iz Instances are Optimized for High CPU Performance, Memory-Intensive Workloads]]></title>
        <id>8ba74cddc223f444061c3b940056b7e5bf430c07</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-r7iz-instances-memory-optimized-for-high-cpu-performance-memory-intensive-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re announcing general availability of the Amazon EC2 R7iz instances. R7iz instances are the fastest 4th Generation Intel Xeon Scalable-based (Sapphire Rapids) instances in the cloud with 3.9 GHz sustained all-core turbo frequency. R7iz instances are suitable for workloads where there’s a requirement for more memory to process additional data, larger sizes of instances […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2 of the Packer Azure plugin is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/version-2-packer-azure-plugin-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/version-2-packer-azure-plugin-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Packer Azure plugin has migrated to the HashiCorp Go Azure SDK to address known Azure SDK deprecations and provide a consistent foundation for managing Azure infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TSMixer: An all-MLP architecture for time series forecasting]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/tsmixer-all-mlp-architecture-for-time.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/tsmixer-all-mlp-architecture-for-time.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:47:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Si-An Chen, Student Researcher, Cloud AI Team, and Chun-Liang Li, Research Scientist, Cloud AI Team



  
Update — 2023/09/12: This post has been updated as the work described is now published in Transactions on Machine Learning Research. 
Time series forecasting is critical to various real-world applications, from demand forecasting to pandemic spread prediction. In multivariate time series forecasting (forecasting multiple variants at the same time), one can split existing methods into two categories: univariate models and multivariate models. Univariate models focus on inter-series interactions or temporal patterns that encompass trends and seasonal patterns on a time series with a single variable. Examples of such trends and seasonal patterns might be the way mortgage rates i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The newest AWS Heroes are here – September 2023]]></title>
        <id>191318f95fbfcb42c00d05fc4648b0a473270294</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/the-newest-aws-heroes-are-here-september-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each quarter, the AWS Heroes program recognizes technical enthusiasts who lift up the greater AWS community through various approaches. While these inspirational individuals are driven to knowledge share, they sometimes discover novel and fun ways of using technology, such as leveraging LEDs to create a magical display of holiday lights. Many are also contributing heavily […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第236話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755178180638</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755178180638"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate OpenShift with Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automate-openshift-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automate-openshift-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy an application to OpenShift and configure it with Ansible Automation Platform using the Red Hat Certified Collection for OpenShift.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachna Dodia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS End User Computing Innovation Day 2023:  Architecting End User Computing for Change and Agility]]></title>
        <id>bbcc0023eaa53f35fd89db9349acde25fa3f6254</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-end-user-computing-innovation-day-2023-architecting-end-user-computing-for-change-and-agility/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on Wednesday, September 13, for a free-to-attend online event, AWS End User Computing Innovation Day 2023. AWS will stream the event simultaneously across multiple platforms, including LinkedIn Live, Twitter, YouTube, and Twitch. Adapting to a complex landscape shaped by return-to-oﬃce mandates, pressure to migrate out of self-operated data centers, escalating security concerns, scarcity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vercel Shipped Cron Jobs in 2 Months Using Amazon EventBridge Scheduler]]></title>
        <id>b17a63568d9769bf55a6e0e7bf657f0b4f373478</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-vercel-shipped-cron-jobs-in-2-months-using-amazon-eventbridge-scheduler/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vercel implemented Cron Jobs using Amazon EventBridge Scheduler, enabling their customers to create, manage, and run scheduled tasks at scale. The adoption of this feature was rapid, reaching over 7 million weekly cron invocations within a few months of release. This article shows how they did it and how they handle the massive scale they’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Farewell EC2-Classic, EBS at 15 Years, and More (Sept. 4, 2023)]]></title>
        <id>1a569d832e6d0012825fad5a9dbc82223bec7711</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-farewell-ec2-classic-ebs-at-15-years-and-more-sept-4-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, there was some great reading about Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) and Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) written by AWS tech leaders. Dr. Werner Vogels wrote Farewell EC2-Classic, it’s been swell, celebrating the 17 years of loyal duty of the original version that started what we now know as cloud computing. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>