<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-01-10T01:35:48.140Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-10T01:35:48.140Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Discussions just got better with Category Forms!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-01-09-github-discussions-just-got-better-with-category-forms/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-01-09-github-discussions-just-got-better-with-category-forms/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T21:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Category Forms allow maintainers to create templates for their GitHub Discussions, which means that users can start new discussions with all the necessary information already included.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Default setup: A new way to enable GitHub code scanning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-01-09-default-setup-a-new-way-to-enable-github-code-scanning/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-01-09-default-setup-a-new-way-to-enable-github-code-scanning/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T18:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Default setup is a new way to automatically set up code scanning on your repository, without the use of a .yaml file.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! AWS Week in Review – January 9, 2023]]></title>
        <id>29642ee7bf4126983375f8ea67a5256cd124b778</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-new-year-aws-week-in-review-january-9-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T17:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! As we kick off 2023, I wanted to take a moment to remind you of some 2023 predictions by AWS leaders for you to help prepare for the new year. Five Tech Predictions for 2023 and Beyond by Dr. Wener Vogels, CTO of Amazon.com – Read how these technologies and trends will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Resources To Help You Upgrade Your Data Science Career In 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=311279</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2023/01/09/5-resources-to-help-you-upgrade-your-data-science-career-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T11:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings from the Datalore team! In our first newsletter of the new year, we’ve brought together 5 inspiring pieces of content that will help you plan your data science career for 2023. [Video + Notebook] Full Stack Data Science Roadmap Continuous learning is one of the key habits that makes you resilient in any crisis […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The myth of luxury goods]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43541</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723792968/0/sethsblog~The-myth-of-luxury-goods/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T10:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury goods are items that are worth more (to some) because they cost more. The cost itself is the benefit that is being sold. There used to be a correlation between superior performance and price. In 1900, an Hermes saddle or a Louis Vuitton trunk was arguably better built for the work it was put […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etymonline]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2722/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2722/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/etymonline.png" title="NOTE TO FUTURE ETYMONLINGUISTS: Our best guess is that 'blimp' is onomatopoeia. The 'B-Limp' thing is a folk etymology." alt="NOTE TO FUTURE ETYMONLINGUISTS: Our best guess is that 'blimp' is onomatopoeia. The 'B-Limp' thing is a folk etymology." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a new one]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44546</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723736496/0/sethsblog~Build-a-new-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-08T09:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entrenched cultural organizations and icons feel more permanent than they are. Network effects, brand power and the status quo can seduce us into believing that we’re stuck with what we have, but things are rarely as permanent as they appear. James Bond is bloated and dated. Idris Elba deserves the role, but that’s unlikely to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just in time]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=39560</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723683012/0/sethsblog~Just-in-time/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-07T09:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have noticed that when you eventually find something, it’s in the last place you looked. Mostly because after that, you stop looking. And when a long-awaited moment finally arrives, the respite comes just in time, when we’re at the end of our rope. That’s largely because if we give up before then, it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node runner update guidance for Azure Pipelines task authors]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66225</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/node-runner-update-guidance-for-azure-pipelines-task-authors/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T15:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
The post Node runner update guidance for Azure Pipelines task authors appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – January 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=310999</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/01/java-annotated-monthly-january-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T13:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Start the year by cultivating a good habit – reading JAM at the beginning of the month! Welcome to the January edition of Java Annotated Monthly, your update on all things Java! We’ll cover the latest news, updates, and developments in the Java ecosystem and highlight some of the best technologies for developers. Whether you’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Maryasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patterns, culture and theft]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44539</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723622994/0/sethsblog~Patterns-culture-and-theft/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is here, and it can (or soon will) be able to draw, code, or write with more skill than most of us. It’s tireless, very fast and very cheap. Understandably, some creators are up in arms. They say that if an AI is trained on their photographs, their architectural designs or their cartoons, it’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euler Diagrams]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2721/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2721/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/euler_diagrams.png" title="Things Leonhard Euler created ( most of math ( overlapping circle diagrams ) a cricket bowling machine ) Things John Venn created" alt="Things Leonhard Euler created ( most of math ( overlapping circle diagrams ) a cricket bowling machine ) Things John Venn created" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Eviction policy for unhealthy pods guarded by PodDisruptionBudgets]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/06/unhealthy-pod-eviction-policy-for-pdbs/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/06/unhealthy-pod-eviction-policy-for-pdbs/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Filip Křepinský (Red Hat), Morten Torkildsen (Google), Ravi Gudimetla (Apple)
Ensuring the disruptions to your applications do not affect its availability isn't a simple
task. Last month's release of Kubernetes v1.26 lets you specify an unhealthy pod eviction policy
for PodDisruptionBudgets (PDBs)
to help you maintain that availability during node management operations.
In this article, we will dive deeper into what modifications were introduced for PDBs to
give application owners greater flexibility in managing disruptions.
What problems does this solve?
API-initiated eviction of pods respects PodDisruptionBudgets (PDBs). This means that a requested voluntary disruption
via an eviction to a Pod, should not disrupt a guarded application and .status.currentHealthy of a PDB should n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 Encrypts New Objects By Default]]></title>
        <id>6a490327f42a0b08871eb4843fc22e2b6a07f127</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-encrypts-new-objects-by-default/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T21:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS, security is the top priority. Starting today, Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) encrypts all new objects by default. Now, S3 automatically applies server-side encryption (SSE-S3) for each new object, unless you specify a different encryption option. SSE-S3 was first launched in 2011. As Jeff wrote at the time: “Amazon S3 server-side encryption […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet Preview update 1.13 improves code completion and much more]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=fleet&amp;p=310898</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/fleet/2023/01/fleet-preview-1-13-is-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T18:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! The first Fleet Preview update in 2023 is available for download. Here’s a brief overview of the most notable changes and bug fixes in 1.13: ​ ‘Git Sync’ was renamed to ‘Git Pull & Push’, so it is more transparent and predictable what to expect when using this action. Now when hovering over an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Prokashev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View the Current State of Variables in Zeppelin Notebooks]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=big-data-tools&amp;p=310569</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/big-data-tools/2023/01/05/view-the-current-state-of-variables-in-zeppelin-notebooks/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you remember a long time ago when we introduced a feature in the Big Data Tools plugin called ZTools that allows you to view the current state of variables in a Zeppelin notebook? Do you remember that we made significant changes to ZTools implementation almost a year ago? It’s our tradition to make big […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pasha Finkelshteyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Road to Out-of-Process ReSharper: Asynchronous Typing]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=310895</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/01/05/resharper-out-of-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T15:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking ReSharper out of process is a monumental undertaking. We covered the magnitude of this in a previous blog post and posted some updates on YouTrack along the way.   In the simplest terms, we’re tasked with separating code that requires the Microsoft Visual Studio (VS) API from code that works with the structures ReSharper uses […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring legend Ramnivas Laddad]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/05/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-legend-ramnivas-laddad</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/05/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-legend-ramnivas-laddad"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring and cloud legend, Spring Cloud Connectors founder, and Cloud Foundry founder, Ramnivas Laddad (@ramnivas)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On this date]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44533</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723562054/0/sethsblog~On-this-date/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T10:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Something extraordinary happened. A record became a hit, a new technology was proven to work, someone raised their hand and asked an important question… On this date, someone took a chance, connected, opened a door or showed up with generosity. We can celebrate each of these momentous events today. The best way is by doing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the third-largest US county uses Elastic to accelerate investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-the-third-largest-us-county-uses-elastic-to-accelerate-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-the-third-largest-us-county-uses-elastic-to-accelerate-investigations"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Across the US, law enforcement teams are using solutions like Elastic to save time and improve accuracy as they use data for investigations. Harris County, TX, is one such government seeing success with accelerated, consolidated investigative search.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Suber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the third-largest US county uses Elastic to accelerate investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-the-third-largest-us-county-uses-elastic-to-accelerate-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-the-third-largest-us-county-uses-elastic-to-accelerate-investigations"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As law enforcement organizations benefit from readily available online information and databases, they also face the challenge of combing through vast amounts of information, often housed in siloed systems and databases. Across the US, law enforcement teams in state and local government are turning to solutions such as Elastic to save time and improve accuracy as they use data for investigations.
Harris County, Texas, is one such government seeing success with accelerated, consolidated investigative search. Harris County is the third-largest county in the US by population, and it includes most of Houston. With over 70 law enforcement agencies and over 50 fire agencies, the county conducts a large number of investigations, where time is of the essence. 
Shing H. Lin, CTO Harris County’s C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Suber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Retroactive Default StorageClass]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/05/retroactive-default-storage-class/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/05/retroactive-default-storage-class/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Roman Bednář (Red Hat)
The v1.25 release of Kubernetes introduced an alpha feature to change how a default StorageClass was assigned to a PersistentVolumeClaim (PVC).
With the feature enabled, you no longer need to create a default StorageClass first and PVC second to assign the class. Additionally, any PVCs without a StorageClass assigned can be updated later.
This feature was graduated to beta in Kubernetes 1.26.
You can read retroactive default StorageClass assignment in the Kubernetes documentation for more details about how to use that,
or you can read on to learn about why the Kubernetes project is making this change.
Why did StorageClass assignment need improvements
Users might already be familiar with a similar feature that assigns default StorageClasses to new PVCs at the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: December 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-01-04-github-availability-report-december-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-01-04-github-availability-report-december-2022/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T17:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December, we did not experience any incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. This report sheds light into an incident that impacted customers using GitHub Packages and GitHub Pages in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Developer Advocate: Part 1, Public Speaking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-1-public-speaking</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-1-public-speaking"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first installment in a series of blog posts on how to build the skills needed to become a developer advocate (or similar technical roles). This post focuses on public speaking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | January 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=310520</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/01/04/net-annotated-monthly-january-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T11:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? Though these terms are often used interchangeably, there is a difference between a parameter and an argument. A parameter is only the definition of something that’s passed into a function and is found in the function’s signature. Parameters usually define the name and type of allowed for the argument to use. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pareto optimality]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43518</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723494468/0/sethsblog~Pareto-optimality/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easier to understand than it is to say. The baker and the blacksmith should trade. The baker can make a loaf of bread more easily and efficiently than the blacksmith, and the blacksmith would ruin her productivity if she stopped making rakes and horseshoes in order to put a loaf in the oven. If […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 resolutions for state & local government leaders to reduce tool sprawl in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/4-resolutions-for-state-local-government-leaders-to-reduce-tool-sprawl-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/4-resolutions-for-state-local-government-leaders-to-reduce-tool-sprawl-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get organized. Spend less money. Learn a new skill. Work on relationships. These familiar New Year's resolutions can also be strategic goals for state and local governments to get smarter about tool consolidation, data sprawl, and cost savings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Torassa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How governments can generate mainframe savings and delight users by "freeing their data"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-governments-generate-mainframe-savings-delight-users-freeing-their-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-governments-generate-mainframe-savings-delight-users-freeing-their-data"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments around the globe are looking for ways to balance books while also answering the call to improve citizen engagement and trust through enhanced digital service delivery. But how can they achieve both?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johan Swanepoel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 resolutions for state & local government leaders to reduce tool sprawl in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/4-resolutions-for-state-local-government-leaders-to-reduce-tool-sprawl-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/4-resolutions-for-state-local-government-leaders-to-reduce-tool-sprawl-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Get organized. Spend less money. Learn a new skill. Work on your relationships. These are fairly common resolutions you hear this time of year, almost everywhere you turn. While they might be old news in your personal life, these goals can have far-reaching benefits when implemented by state and local government agencies. Taking a hard look at your technology tools and what’s required to maintain and operate them can lead to better efficiencies, savings, and citizen experiences. 

Below, we’ll show how implementing these four resolutions can help your government agency reduce tool sprawl and do more with your data.
Get organized
As US state and local government agencies move more tools and services online, data has become an increasingly strategic asset.
But while it’s beneficial to have…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Torassa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How governments can generate mainframe savings and delight users by "freeing their data"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-governments-generate-mainframe-savings-delight-users-freeing-their-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-governments-generate-mainframe-savings-delight-users-freeing-their-data"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Governments around the globe are looking for ways to balance books while also answering the call to improve citizen engagement and trust through enhanced digital service delivery. But how can they achieve both? 

A proven way to quickly reduce cost and increase customer experience is to add an application speed layer between user-facing systems and mainframe applications. Using this approach could potentially save millions of dollars.

We see financial institutions leveraging this approach to drive down costs and enhance the user experience. Royal Bank of Canada, for example, estimates a cost savings of C$2.4 million per year just in mainframe transaction (MIPS) fees. In addition, once in place, this capability allows services to deliver greater value through enhanced user experience. As…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johan Swanepoel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biology vs Robotics]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2720/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2720/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/biology_vs_robotics.png" title="Sorry, I've just always had these random things I don't like--like olives, or robots drilling holes in me without warning." alt="Sorry, I've just always had these random things I don't like--like olives, or robots drilling holes in me without warning." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.17.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/03/spring-tools-4-17-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/03/spring-tools-4-17-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.17.1 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: Eclipse STS 4.17 takes 96 % processor time on Intel i9 (#934)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: BootLanguageServerBootApp class is taking all available cpu continuously (#932)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: OpenRewrite unchecked, but always Language Server Background Job(Loading Rewrite Recipes) (#925)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: [validation] spring.factories EnableAutoConfiguration key for boot 3.0 ignores ‘on’ setting (#917)

  
(VSCode) fixed: [vscode] Boot LS is broken if Java LS launch mode is ‘Hybrid’ (#919)


known issues


  
(Spring Boot): The newly introduced additional reconciling for Java source files which is used to show up additional validations and quick fixes can cause increased memory and CPU consumption. In case you stumble upon issues in this area, feel free to disable the reconciling via Preferences -> Extensions -> Spring Boot Tools -> Open Rewrite (in VSCode) or Preferences -> Language Servers -> Spring Language Servers -> Spring Boot Language Server -> Open Rewrite (in Eclipse).


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2023-01-03-4171-release-incl-language-servers-version-1430

Spring Tools 4.17.2 is scheduled to be released in early February 2023.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hustles end badly]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44518</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723439518/0/sethsblog~Hustles-end-badly/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“They can always say no” is the mantra of someone who is hustling for attention, promo or a sale. But when you hustle a colleague or a friend, they can tell. They can tell that you’re being selfish, angling for a short-term win and trading something precious for something now. When we ask someone to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy’s New Projects and Topics: January Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=310460</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/01/03/jetbrains-academy-s-new-projects-and-topics-january-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T08:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The start of the new year is the perfect opportunity to follow through with resolutions to learn something new or sharpen your skills. Luckily, there are plenty of knowledge areas to explore in computer science and lots of ways to go about it. JetBrains Academy can help! This month we’ve prepared 7 new projects and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasiia Pogorelova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - Jan 3rd, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/03/this-week-in-spring-jan-3rd-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/03/this-week-in-spring-jan-3rd-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Happy new year! It’s 2023 already! Who saw that comin’? I sure didn’t. This year promises to be more amazing than ever, and I can’t wait to be a part of it.

As usual, the first week of January is when we mark the date of the first installment of this humble roundup, This Week in Spring, waaaay back in the first week of January 2011! 12 years of This Week in Spring! Now that’s consistency! 

And it’s only possible because of you, dear community. Thank you. You, who have been consistently excellent every week of the year for years and years, are truly the reason for the season, and we appreciate you. This week is no exception! There’s a ton of great content, so let’s kick the year off right!


  
First, I’ll be speaking at the Atlanta JUG on the 16th of this month, by the by, so please join me, and we’ll dive headfirst into Spring in 2023!

  
Last week, I had the pleasure of interviewing my friend, and teammate, the legendary DaShaun Carter on a Bootiful Podcast

  
I love this post by Rafael Winterhalter (create of ByteBuddy and Bootiful Podcast guest on the amazing publish/subscribe capabilities of PostgreSQL. I love PostgreSQL. But then he goes even further, turning the mechanism into support in Spring Integration. He explains everything in this epic post, Using Postgres as a Message Queue

  
Create a new Git branch with no history - not strictly speaking Spring-related, but I thought it was interesting. Unless you’re not using Git… I suppose.

  
NonUniqueResultException in Spring Data JPA

  
Observability with Spring Boot 3

  
Oddity with shutdown methods in Spring Boot 3 AOT and GraalVM

  
Spring Boot (3) Spring Native (GraalVM) with Kubernetes & Istio🔥

  
Using Watermarks with iText in Java

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Job Tracking, to Support Massively Parallel Batch Workloads, Is Generally Available

  
Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: Advancements in Kubernetes Traffic Engineering

  
Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: Alpha support for cross-namespace storage data sources]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to put your untapped data to work in real time to transform your business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-put-your-untapped-data-to-work-to-transform-your-business</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-put-your-untapped-data-to-work-to-transform-your-business"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to put your organization’s untapped data to work in three steps to reduce cyber risk, increase operational resilience, and improve user experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Klinger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking back at 2022 — Elastic year in review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-at-2022-elastic-year-in-review</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-at-2022-elastic-year-in-review"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022 was an amazing year for Elastic with the introduction of new innovations across our solutions, new customers, and deepening partnerships. As we take a moment to reflect on the year in review, we’ve rounded up our top blog posts of 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Marketing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to put your untapped data to work in real time to transform your business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-put-your-untapped-data-to-work-to-transform-your-business</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-put-your-untapped-data-to-work-to-transform-your-business"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Ensure business continuity, protect your organization from cyber risk, and improve your customers’ and employees’ experiences all by putting your data to work in real-time. You already have the data — why not make it chip in for rent? A recent study found that 80% of companies surveyed saw an increase in revenue due to real-time data analytics. 
The reason you can solve these all-encompassing, complex business problems with data? It’s because so many of your business problems are really just data problems in disguise. Let’s dive into a few of those problems and how you can solve them.
Business problems are actually data problems
Data problem #1: Your enterprise applications and infrastructure must be optimized for availability and performance. Imagine you’re the IT leader of a streaming …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Klinger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking back at 2022 — Elastic year in review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-at-2022-elastic-year-in-review</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-at-2022-elastic-year-in-review"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
2022 was an amazing year for Elastic with the introduction of dozens of new innovations across our Observability, Security, and Enterprise Search solutions, new customers, and deepening partnerships.
As we take a moment to reflect on the year in review, we’ve rounded up our top blog posts of 2022. We hope you enjoy them!
Elastic 8.0 
As we began the year, we also launched a new chapter with Elastic 8.0: A new era of speed, scale, relevance, and simplicity. Elastic 8.0 was the culmination of years of investment in the 7.x series to reduce memory usage and query overhead, and introduce new features to enhance relevance.
For example, we increased the speed of date histograms and search aggregations, enhanced the performance of page caching, and created a new “pre-filter” search phase. In ad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Marketing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtually no one]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43488</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723385438/0/sethsblog~Virtually-no-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compared to the overall population, virtually no one built Wikipedia, virtually no one voted for that senator and virtually no one starts a business. Virtually no one cares enough to help a stranger in need, and virtually no one leads the way. And that’s okay. Because virtually no one is enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hydrogen Isotopes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2719/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2719/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/hydrogen_isotopes.png" title="Oops, All Neutrons is also known as Neutral Quadrium, Nydnonen, and Goth Tritium." alt="Oops, All Neutrons is also known as Neutral Quadrium, Nydnonen, and Goth Tritium." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: Alpha support for cross-namespace storage data sources]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/02/cross-namespace-data-sources-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/02/cross-namespace-data-sources-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Takafumi Takahashi (Hitachi Vantara)
Kubernetes v1.26, released last month, introduced an alpha feature that
lets you specify a data source for a PersistentVolumeClaim, even where the source
data belong to a different namespace.
With the new feature enabled, you specify a namespace in the dataSourceRef field of
a new PersistentVolumeClaim. Once Kubernetes checks that access is OK, the new
PersistentVolume can populate its data from the storage source specified in that other
namespace.
Before Kubernetes v1.26, provided your cluster had the AnyVolumeDataSource feature enabled,
you could already provision new volumes from a data source in the same
namespace.
However, that only worked for the data source in the same namespace,
therefore users couldn't provision a PersistentVolume with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arguing for inaction]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43422</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723339578/0/sethsblog~Arguing-for-inaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[…is surprisingly easy. “We’ve done all this work and things haven’t gotten better,” so, apparently, we should stop trying and go back to what we were doing. “We’ve done all this work and things are getting better,” so that means that there’s no need to keep trying and we can go back to what we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[年賀イラスト] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190247049337281</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190247049337281"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The world as it is]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43643</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/723296176/0/sethsblog~The-world-as-it-is/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one sees reality. It’s worth repeating: No one accurately sees the world as it is. A person with hearing loss doesn’t experience the world the same way a synesthete does. A rock climber doesn’t see a steep slope the same way an elderly person does. And an optimist and a pessimist rarely experience opportunities […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub and the Ekoparty 2022 Capture the Flag]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-30-github-and-the-ekoparty-2022-capture-the-flag/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-30-github-and-the-ekoparty-2022-capture-the-flag/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T17:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the design behind, and solutions to, several of GitHub’s CTF challenge for Ekoparty’s 2022 event!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: Advancements in Kubernetes Traffic Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/30/advancements-in-kubernetes-traffic-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/30/advancements-in-kubernetes-traffic-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Andrew Sy Kim (Google)
Kubernetes v1.26 includes significant advancements in network traffic engineering with the graduation of
two features (Service internal traffic policy support, and EndpointSlice terminating conditions) to GA,
and a third feature (Proxy terminating endpoints) to beta. The combination of these enhancements aims
to address short-comings in traffic engineering that people face today, and unlock new capabilities for the future.
Traffic Loss from Load Balancers During Rolling Updates
Prior to Kubernetes v1.26, clusters could experience loss of traffic
from Service load balancers during rolling updates when setting the externalTrafficPolicy field to Local.
There are a lot of moving parts at play here so a quick overview of how Kubernetes manages load balancers migh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub’s top 10 blog posts of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-29-githubs-top-10-blog-posts-of-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-29-githubs-top-10-blog-posts-of-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-29T17:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the year winds down, we're highlighting some of the incredible work from GitHub’s engineers, product teams, and security researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: DaShaun Carter: amazing human being, father, friend, engineer, and fellow Spring Developer Advocate]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/29/a-bootiful-podcast-dashaun-carter-amazing-human-being-father-friend-engineer-and-fellow-spring-developer-advocate</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/29/a-bootiful-podcast-dashaun-carter-amazing-human-being-father-friend-engineer-and-fellow-spring-developer-advocate"/>
        <updated>2022-12-29T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! this episode, we turn it to 11 and ring in the new year with a fantastic human being, father, friend, engineer, and fellow Spring Developer Advocate: DaShaun Carter (@dashaun). 

Happy new year!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Job Tracking, to Support Massively Parallel Batch Workloads, Is Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/29/scalable-job-tracking-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/29/scalable-job-tracking-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Aldo Culquicondor (Google)
The Kubernetes 1.26 release includes a stable implementation of the Job
controller that can reliably track a large amount of Jobs with high levels of
parallelism. SIG Apps
and WG Batch
have worked on this foundational improvement since Kubernetes 1.22. After
multiple iterations and scale verifications, this is now the default
implementation of the Job controller.
Paired with the Indexed completion mode,
the Job controller can handle massively parallel batch Jobs, supporting up to
100k concurrent Pods.
The new implementation also made possible the development of Pod failure policy,
which is in beta in the 1.26 release.
How do I use this feature?
To use Job tracking with finalizers, upgrade to Kubernetes 1.25 or newer and
create new Jobs. You can also use …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2022.3.1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=310298</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/12/2022-3-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T22:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can get the latest version from our website, via the Toolbox App, from inside the IDE, or by using snaps if you’re a Ubuntu user. Here are the most notable improvements in the new version: The option to display editor tabs on multiple rows is available in the new UI. [IDEA-295095] Actions on Save […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.3.1 is released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=310266</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/12/phpstorm-2022-3-1-is-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T17:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first bug-fix update for PhpStorm 2022.3 is now available. You can update to it using the Toolbox App or right from inside the IDE. You can also download PhpStorm 2022.3.1 from the website. Notable changes in this update: The option to display editor tabs on multiple rows is available in the new UI [IDEA-295095]. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda community values]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=70025&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=70025</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/camunda-community-values/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the values that represent the culture and beliefs of our Camunda community. Thank you for being a part of it!
The post Camunda community values appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Alcantara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring  - Happy New Year 2023 edition - December 27th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/27/this-week-in-spring-happy-new-year-2023-edition-december-27th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/27/this-week-in-spring-happy-new-year-2023-edition-december-27th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! It’s 27 December as I write this and - being honest - I couldn’t be happier. It’s raining outside. I’m in a warm cozy office. Good music is playing. People are asleep in my home. I can hear the raindrops and wind outside the window. I’m at peace as I code. And code I have. I’ve been updating my blog, and a half dozen little side projects, to the new Spring Boot 3. This has given me a chance to do a little, shall we say, Spring cleaning, and also update my Github Actions to the latest and greatest. I’m pleasantly surprised by how many builds I’ve switched over to 3.0 and then used the AOT engine to build a GraalVM native image and it just worked! 

How were or are your holidays going? My family and I had a lovely Chris…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.3.1 is released!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=309923</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2022/12/rubymine-2022-3-1-is-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.3 is out! You can get the new build from our website or via the free Toolbox App. The new version includes some important updates, and here are the highlights you need to know about. Find usages of let variables in RSpec shared contexts Find Usages can now help you search for all usages […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iryna Pisklyarova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perf8: Performance metrics for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/perf8-performance-metrics-for-python</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/perf8-performance-metrics-for-python"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perf8 is a tool Enterprise Search has started to develop to standardize the creation of performance reports for its Python applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarek Ziadé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perf8: Performance metrics for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/perf8-performance-metrics-for-python</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/perf8-performance-metrics-for-python"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We're building this neat service in Python to ingest data in Elasticsearch from various sources (MySQL, Network Drive, AWS, etc.) for Enterprise Search.
Sucking data from a third-party service to Elasticsearch is usually an I/O-bound activity. Your code sits on opened sockets and passes data from one end to the other. That's a great use case for an asynchronous application in Python, but it needs to be carefully crafted.
When data flows through that pipeline, we want to ensure we don't blow the available resources (RAM/CPU/FDs). We also want to maximize the output without killing Elasticsearch or the backend service.
So it's all about implementing the right throttling and backpressure safeguards and surfacing the right settings, so you can properly size how aggressive the service will be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarek Ziadé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: CPUManager goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/27/cpumanager-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/27/cpumanager-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author:
Francesco Romani (Red Hat)
The CPU Manager is a part of the kubelet, the Kubernetes node agent, which enables the user to allocate exclusive CPUs to containers.
Since Kubernetes v1.10, where it graduated to Beta, the CPU Manager proved itself reliable and
fulfilled its role of allocating exclusive CPUs to containers, so adoption has steadily grown making it a staple component of performance-critical
and low-latency setups. Over time, most changes were about bugfixes or internal refactoring, with the following noteworthy user-visible changes:
support explicit reservation of CPUs: it was already possible to request to reserve a given
number of CPUs for system resources, including the kubelet itself, which will not be used for exclusive CPU allocation. Now it is possible to also
expli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Pod Scheduling Readiness]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/26/pod-scheduling-readiness-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/26/pod-scheduling-readiness-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Wei Huang (Apple), Abdullah Gharaibeh (Google)
Kubernetes 1.26 introduced a new Pod feature: scheduling gates. In Kubernetes, scheduling gates
are keys that tell the scheduler when a Pod is ready to be considered for scheduling.
What problem does it solve?
When a Pod is created, the scheduler will continuously attempt to find a node that fits it. This
infinite loop continues until the scheduler either finds a node for the Pod, or the Pod gets deleted.
Pods that remain unschedulable for long periods of time (e.g., ones that are blocked on some external event)
waste scheduling cycles. A scheduling cycle may take ≅20ms or more depending on the complexity of
the Pod's scheduling constraints. Therefore, at scale, those wasted cycles significantly impact the
scheduler's performance. See …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make 2023 the Year of Process Improvement [Recap]]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=70032&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=70032</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/how-to-make-2023-the-year-of-process-improvement-recap/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T21:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what you need to know to make 2023 the year of process improvement. We look back at 2022 and ahead at the key trends coming next year.
The post How to Make 2023 the Year of Process Improvement [Recap] appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What&#8217;s with all the ducks?]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-23-whats-with-all-the-ducks/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-23-whats-with-all-the-ducks/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T17:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What in the world do rubber ducks have to do with programming? And why were they everywhere at GitHub Universe? A lot of you asked, so I’m here to help explain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 0.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/23/spring-modulith-0-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/23/spring-modulith-0-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce the availability of Spring Modulith 0.2. The release adds the following features:


  
We introduced @ApplicationModuleListener to ease the declaration of asynchronous, transactional event listeners that run in a transaction themselves. A model that we recommend as default to integration application modules. (#80, reference documentation)

  
The application module dependency structure is now also exposed as Spring Boot actuator. This allows operating infrastructure to visualize insights it provides to operations teams to be aligned with the application module structure (HTTP traces by module etc.) (#87, reference documentation

  
The Postgres event publication registry schema now follows Postgres best practices. (#81)


The release also contains the obligatory upgrade to Spring Boot 3.0.1. Find more information on the release page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/spring-boot-3-0-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/spring-boot-3-0-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.1 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 54 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Support for Passing Pod fsGroup to CSI Drivers At Mount Time]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/23/kubernetes-12-06-fsgroup-on-mount/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/23/kubernetes-12-06-fsgroup-on-mount/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Fabio Bertinatto (Red Hat), Hemant Kumar (Red Hat)
Delegation of fsGroup to CSI drivers was first introduced as alpha in Kubernetes 1.22,
and graduated to beta in Kubernetes 1.25.
For Kubernetes 1.26, we are happy to announce that this feature has graduated to
General Availability (GA).
In this release, if you specify a fsGroup in the
security context,
for a (Linux) Pod, all processes in the pod's containers are part of the additional group
that you specified.
In previous Kubernetes releases, the kubelet would always apply the
fsGroup ownership and permission changes to files in the volume according to the policy
you specified in the Pod's .spec.securityContext.fsGroupChangePolicy field.
Starting with Kubernetes 1.26, CSI drivers have the option to apply the fsGroup settings durin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Field CTO and Chief Evangelist at Gradle Justin Reock]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/a-bootiful-podcast-field-cto-and-chief-evangelist-at-gradle-justin-reock</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/a-bootiful-podcast-field-cto-and-chief-evangelist-at-gradle-justin-reock"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans and happy holidays!! In this installment, Josh Long talks to Field CTO and Chief Evangelist at Gradle Justin Reock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.7 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/spring-boot-2-7-7-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/22/spring-boot-2-7-7-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T18:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.7 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 24 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Ambassador Call for Submissions 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-ambassador-call-for-submissions-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-ambassador-call-for-submissions-2023"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The submission window for HashiCorp Ambassador — our program to recognize individuals for knowledge sharing, mentorship, and kindness in the community — is now open.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.3.2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=309876</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/12/22/datagrip-2022-3-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T14:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! We’ve released the second bug-fix update for DataGrip 2022.3. Here’s what’s been improved: DBE-16825: The default name for created objects is selected so that it’s easy to replace it. DBE-16899: Virtual views are correctly refreshed. DBE-16824: Virtual views can be found via the Search dialog. DBE-15968: [PostgreSQL] Database names with slashes are supported. DBE-16862: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maksim Sobolevskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletproofing Zeebe against concurrency bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69968&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69968</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/bulletproofing-zeebe-concurrency-bugs/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how we test and identify hard-to-find critical bugs in Zeebe, the workflow engine powering Camunda Platform 8, using property-based testing.
The post Bulletproofing Zeebe against concurrency bugs appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepthi Akkoorath</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.3.1 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=309556</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/12/webstorm-2022-3-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T10:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.3.1, the first bug-fix update for WebStorm 2022.3, is now available! It’s packed with improvements, including the fix for the disturbing regression bug with Actions on Save (IDEA-307368). We’ve also fixed several issues with Vue, Vitest, and Angular and added Prisma ORM support. You can update to v2022.3.1 by using the Toolbox App, installing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Ryabukha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: GA Support for Kubelet Credential Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/22/kubelet-credential-providers/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/22/kubelet-credential-providers/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Andrew Sy Kim (Google), Dixita Narang (Google)
Kubernetes v1.26 introduced generally available (GA) support for kubelet credential
provider plugins,
offering an extensible plugin framework to dynamically fetch credentials
for any container image registry.
Background
Kubernetes supports the ability to dynamically fetch credentials for a container registry service.
Prior to Kubernetes v1.20, this capability was compiled into the kubelet and only available for
Amazon Elastic Container Registry, Azure Container Registry, and Google Cloud Container Registry.
 
Figure 1: Kubelet built-in credential provider support for Amazon Elastic Container Registry, Azure Container Registry, and Google Cloud Container Registry.
Kubernetes v1.20 introduced alpha support for kubelet credential provide…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EHR-Safe: Generating High-Fidelity and Privacy-Preserving Synthetic Electronic Health Records]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/ehr-safe-generating-high-fidelity-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/ehr-safe-generating-high-fidelity-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T18:57:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jinsung Yoon and Sercan O. Arik, Research Scientists, Google Research, Cloud AI Team  
Analysis of Electronic Health Records (EHR) has a tremendous potential for enhancing patient care, quantitatively measuring performance of clinical practices, and facilitating clinical research. Statistical estimation and machine learning (ML) models trained on EHR data can be used to predict the probability of various diseases (such as diabetes), track patient wellness, and predict how patients respond to specific drugs. For such models, researchers and practitioners need access to EHR data. However, it can be challenging to leverage EHR data while ensuring data privacy and conforming to patient confidentiality regulations (such as HIPAA).  

Conventional methods to anonymize data (e.g., de-id…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Gives 2022: Creating positive, lasting contributions in our communities]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-21-github-gives-2022-creating-positive-lasting-contributions-in-our-communities/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-21-github-gives-2022-creating-positive-lasting-contributions-in-our-communities/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T16:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, we took GitHub Gives, our company-wide giving campaign, to new heights and wanted to share our learnings to provide best practices in programming a successful hybrid giving campaign for employees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Santa drives his sleigh using Kibana Dashboards!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/santa-drives-his-sleigh-using-kibana-dashboards</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/santa-drives-his-sleigh-using-kibana-dashboards"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how Santa keeps track of his journey to deliver presents across the world? He uses Kibana! In this festive post, learn how Lens, TSVB, and Vega controls can be used to make Santa’s sleigh dashboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Each Elastic office has its own locally-designed mural. See them all.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-each-elastic-office-has-its-own-locally-designed-mural</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-each-elastic-office-has-its-own-locally-designed-mural"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building community is one of our top priorities. We want our employees to feel at home in their local office, so we hired local designers to create murals on the walls of each office to bring to life the essence of each Elastic city.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Santa drives his sleigh using Kibana Dashboards!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/santa-drives-his-sleigh-using-kibana-dashboards</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/santa-drives-his-sleigh-using-kibana-dashboards"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
It’s the festive season. Regardless of whether you believe in Santa or celebrate Christmas or another holiday in December, we can all appreciate the speed at which good ol’ St. Nick flies around the world with his trusty reindeer delivering presents to all the good children.

He’s been doing this job for a long time. But in 2022, his sleigh got an upgrade thanks to Kibana dashboards! He is now able to track the cities he’s visited along the way, the state of his journey, and his cool Christmas playlist.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt710d158fc999aff7/63a1fc518f1f170dcb413236/blog-elastic-dashboard.png,blog-elastic-dashboard.png,
This blog post shares details of building some of the key controls Santa uses to drive his sleigh and track his journey across th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Each Elastic office has its own locally-designed mural. See them all.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-each-elastic-office-has-its-own-locally-designed-mural</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-each-elastic-office-has-its-own-locally-designed-mural"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re a distributed, global company (and proud of it), but we do want to give Elasticisians a place to connect face-to-face should they choose. In fact, building community is one of our top priorities here at Elastic. That’s why we have offices in 15 cities around the world. While some Elasticians use them to work and connect, we also use them to host in-person events, like this summer’s Elasticamp. 

Currently, we have offices in: Amsterdam, Arlington, Austin, Bangalore, Berlin, Chicago, Copenhagen, London, Munich, New York, Paris, San Francisco, Singapore, Sydney, and Tokyo. 

What makes our offices special is that each one is designed with its location in mind. We want our employees to feel at home in their local office, so we hired local designers to create murals on the walls of eac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Awarded the Palo Alto Networks 2022 Global Technology Partner of the Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-awarded-palo-alto-networks-2022-global-technology-partner-of-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-awarded-palo-alto-networks-2022-global-technology-partner-of-year"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp wins the 2022 Palo Alto Networks Global Technology Partner of the Year Award.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differential Privacy Accounting by Connecting the Dots]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/differential-privacy-accounting-by.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/differential-privacy-accounting-by.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T18:29:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Pritish Kamath and Pasin Manurangsi, Research Scientists, Google Research  
Differential privacy (DP) is an approach that enables data analytics and machine learning (ML) with a mathematical guarantee on the privacy of user data.  DP quantifies the “privacy cost” of an algorithm, i.e., the level of guarantee that the algorithm’s output distribution for a given dataset will not change significantly if a single user’s data is added to or removed from it. The algorithm is characterized by two parameters, ε and δ, where smaller values of both indicate “more private”. There is a natural tension between the privacy budget (ε, δ) and the utility of the algorithm: a smaller privacy budget requires the output to be more “noisy”, often leading to less utility. Thus, a fundamental goal of D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase developer productivity, save time on developer onboarding, and drive ROI in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-20-increase-developer-productivity-save-time-on-developer-onboarding-and-drive-roi-in-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-20-increase-developer-productivity-save-time-on-developer-onboarding-and-drive-roi-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forrester's Total Economic Impact™ study dives into how GitHub Enterprise Cloud and GitHub Advanced Security help businesses drive ROI, increase developer productivity, and save time on developer onboarding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not just flightless birds: How EMUs secure and scale identity and access management for your GitHub Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-20-emus-more-than-just-flightless-birds/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-20-emus-more-than-just-flightless-birds/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T18:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise has evolved to support the needs of enterprise administrators, corporate security teams, and individual developers who contribute to open source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contributing to Camunda’s Connector ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69911&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69911</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/contributing-to-camunda-connector-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T17:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can contribute a Connector to Camunda’s Community Hub, either as another partner of ours or as a community member. 
The post Contributing to Camunda’s Connector ecosystem appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we use GitHub to be more productive, collaborative, and secure]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-20-how-we-use-github-to-be-more-productive-collaborative-and-secure/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-20-how-we-use-github-to-be-more-productive-collaborative-and-secure/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our engineering and security teams have done some incredible work in 2022. Let’s take a look at how we use GitHub to be more productive, build collaboratively, and shift security left.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp 2022 Year in Review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2022-year-in-review</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2022-year-in-review"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before we ring in the new year, here’s a look back at some of the most important moments in 2022 for HashiCorp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top 10 Ansible Blogs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/top-10-ansible-blogs-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/top-10-ansible-blogs-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
 
If you're looking to brush up on the most popular Ansible information from 2022 (or just grasping at any excuse to break away from your relatives for a few minutes during the holidays), you've come to the right place. What follows are the top 10 blogs that have captured the most attention from Ansible.com readers in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>trmcconn@redhat.com (Tricia McConnell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 20th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/20/this-week-in-spring-december-20th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/20/this-week-in-spring-december-20th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! It’s the 20th of December, 2022 as I write this, which means that by the time we meet again, here on this humble blog, Tuesday next week, Christmas will already have come and gone. Chanukah is already here! Time is sure flying! So, to those of you who celebrate: Happy Chanukah, Merry Christmas, and happy holidays! 

There’s arguably nothing better than the gift of knowledge, so let’s dive right into this week’s roundup:


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft’s Brian Benz on the state of Java, Microsoft, Azure, and so much more

  
Spring Framework 6.0.3 available now

  
Spring Security 6.0.1, 5.8.1, 5.7.6 and 5.6.10 available now

  
Spring for Apache Pulsar 0.1.0 available now

  
Spring for GraphQL 1.1.1 released

  
Fixing the No Main Manifest Attribute in Spring Boot

  
Oracle has a nice post: Go Native with Spring Boot 3 and GraalVM

  
Baeldung has an interesting tutorial on Pinpoint, which looks to be a large APM suite with some interesting capabilities.

  
[Stream Large Byte[] to File With WebClient](https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/722459996/0/baeldung~Stream-Large-Byte-to-File-With-WebClient)

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Alpha API For Dynamic Resource Allocation

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Device Manager graduates to GA

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Introducing Validating Admission Policies

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Non-Graceful Node Shutdown Moves to Beta

  
Running Multiple Thread Groups in JMeter

  
Extract Values using AssertJ in Java

  
Interesting, and well worth bookmarking: how to build a statically linked or mostly-statically linked native executable with GraalVM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.1.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/20/spring-for-graphql-1-1-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/20/spring-for-graphql-1-1-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T10:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pleased to announce that Spring for GraphQL 1.1.1 is now available on Maven Central.

This first maintenance release in the 1.1.x generation includes 19 fixes and documentation improvements. This version will be shipped with Spring Boot 3.0.1, to be released later this week.
How can you help?

If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-graphql tag.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing search to advance equity in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/harnessing-search-to-advance-equity-in-healthcare</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/harnessing-search-to-advance-equity-in-healthcare"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores how Elastic’s search capabilities can help address potential barriers to health equity, specifically by utilizing NLP and search analytics to support Medicare beneficiaries with limited English proficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isra Sunhachawi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Log monitoring and unstructured log data, moving beyond tail -f]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-monitoring-management-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-monitoring-management-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Log data and system logs can be a treasure trove of information and insights for SREs and DevOps team with the right tools. Take a dive into the Elastic Platform, a leader in log management and monitoring capabilities, based on the proven ELK stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Wintergerst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing search to advance equity in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/harnessing-search-to-advance-equity-in-healthcare</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/harnessing-search-to-advance-equity-in-healthcare"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As more productive and healthy populations live longer, healthcare will be one of the most important aspects of society. The COVID-19 pandemic has accelerated adoption of modern technologies and shined a light on the importance of patient experiences. As more consumers are taking control of their data, healthcare systems are getting stretched. According to a study published by Deloitte and the Scottsdale Institute, 92% of healthcare technology leaders see digital capabilities as a path to achieve better patient experience.

In this blog post, we’ll explore how Elastic’s search capabilities can help address potential barriers to health equity, as outlined in the Center for Medicare & Medicaid Services (CMS) strategic pillars — specifically, how to deliver relevant results for healthcare i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isra Sunhachawi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Log monitoring and unstructured log data, moving beyond tail -f]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-monitoring-management-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-monitoring-management-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Log files and system logs have been a treasure trove of information for administrators and developers for decades. But with more moving parts and ever more options on where to run modern cloud applications, keeping an eye on logs and troubleshooting problems have become increasingly difficult. 

While it’s often possible to ssh into a server and run commands like tail -f, this approach doesn’t scale for most developers and administrators. Even if you’re good on the command line, you might be able to find what you’re looking for in a log file using awk and grep and could even calculate some simple statistics around how often certain errors occur. But what if the applications are running across hundreds of servers or Kubernetes pods? Or even worse, what if the applications are split across…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Wintergerst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Introducing Validating Admission Policies]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/20/validating-admission-policies-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/20/validating-admission-policies-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Joe Betz (Google), Cici Huang (Google)
In Kubernetes 1.26, the 1st alpha release of validating admission policies is
available!
Validating admission policies use the Common Expression
Language (CEL) to offer a declarative,
in-process alternative to validating admission
webhooks.
CEL was first introduced to Kubernetes for the Validation rules for
CustomResourceDefinitions.
This enhancement expands the use of CEL in Kubernetes to support a far wider
range of admission use cases.
Admission webhooks can be burdensome to develop and operate. Webhook developers
must implement and maintain a webhook binary to handle admission requests. Also,
admission webhooks are complex to operate. Each webhook must be deployed,
monitored and have a well defined upgrade and rollback plan. To make matte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do you create and grow a Center of Excellence?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69868&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69868</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/how-to-create-grow-center-of-excellence/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T21:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering how to get your CoE started and how to run one effectively? Check out this extended Q&A and our live CamundaCon panel for the answers.
The post How do you create and grow a Center of Excellence? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Strauch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – December 19, 2022]]></title>
        <id>352365395483907fe0b79316529e5f6a73acb358</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-december-19-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T19:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are half way between the re:Invent conference and the end-of-year holidays, and I did expect the cadence of releases and news to slow down a bit, but nothing is further away from reality. Our teams continue to listen to your feedback and release new capabilities and incremental improvements. This week, many items caught my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.0.1, 5.8.1, 5.7.6 and 5.6.10 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/19/spring-security-6-0-1-5-8-1-5-7-6-and-5-6-10-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/19/spring-security-6-0-1-5-8-1-5-7-6-and-5-6-10-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 6.0.1, 5.8.1, 5.7.6 and 5.6.10 are available now. In all cases, the releases are mostly composed of bug fixes and documentation improvements.



To learn more, please visit the 6.0.1, 5.8.1, 5.7.6 and
 5.6.10 release summaries.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Celebrates 10 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-celebrates-10-years</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-celebrates-10-years"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-Founders Armon Dadgar and Mitchell Hashimoto share their thoughts on HashiCorp’s 10th Anniversary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Device Manager graduates to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/19/devicemanager-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/19/devicemanager-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Swati Sehgal (Red Hat)
The Device Plugin framework was introduced in the Kubernetes v1.8 release as a vendor
independent framework to enable discovery, advertisement and allocation of external
devices without modifying core Kubernetes. The feature graduated to Beta in v1.10.
With the recent release of Kubernetes v1.26, Device Manager is now generally
available (GA).
Within the kubelet, the Device Manager facilitates communication with device plugins
using gRPC through Unix sockets. Device Manager and Device plugins both act as gRPC
servers and clients by serving and connecting to the exposed gRPC services respectively.
Device plugins serve a gRPC service that kubelet connects to for device discovery,
advertisement (as extended resources) and allocation. Device Manager connects to
t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.0  (codename Kilburn) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/16/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-codename-kilburn-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/16/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-codename-kilburn-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-17T01:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the General Availability (RELEASE) of the Spring Cloud 2022.0 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2022.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2022.0.0 Release Train

Spring Cloud 2022.0.0 is a major release that builds upon Spring Framework 6.x and Spring Boot 3.x. This includes compatibility with Jakarta EE and requires a Java 17 baseline. See here for the issues included in this release. Below are highlights from all of the 2022.0.0 milestone, release candidate and GA releases.
Spring Cloud OpenFeign feature complete announcement

Since Spring now provides its own interface HTTP clients solution, starting with 2022.0.0, we’re going to treat Spri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating Text Generation with Confident Adaptive Language Modeling (CALM)]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/accelerating-text-generation-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/accelerating-text-generation-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tal Schuster, Research Scientist, Google Research    
Language models (LMs) are the driving force behind many recent breakthroughs in natural language processing. Models like T5, LaMDA, GPT-3, and PaLM have demonstrated impressive performance on various language tasks. While multiple factors can contribute to improving the performance of LMs, some recent studies suggest that scaling up the model’s size is crucial for revealing emergent capabilities. In other words, some instances can be solved by small models, while others seem to benefit from increased scale. 

Despite recent efforts that enabled the efficient training of LMs over large amounts of data, trained models can still be slow and costly for practical use. When generating text at inference time, most autoregressive LMs …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Non-Graceful Node Shutdown Moves to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/16/kubernetes-1-26-non-graceful-node-shutdown-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/16/kubernetes-1-26-non-graceful-node-shutdown-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Xing Yang (VMware), Ashutosh Kumar (VMware)
Kubernetes v1.24 introduced an alpha quality implementation of improvements
for handling a non-graceful node shutdown.
In Kubernetes v1.26, this feature moves to beta. This feature allows stateful workloads to failover to a different node after the original node is shut down or in a non-recoverable state, such as the hardware failure or broken OS.
What is a node shutdown in Kubernetes?
In a Kubernetes cluster, it is possible for a node to shut down. This could happen either in a planned way or it could happen unexpectedly. You may plan for a security patch, or a kernel upgrade and need to reboot the node, or it may shut down due to preemption of VM instances. A node may also shut down due to a hardware failure or a software problem.
To tr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Run Tasks From Check Point, Rapid7, ZScaler and Others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-run-tasks-from-checkpoint-rapid7-zscaler-and-others</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-run-tasks-from-checkpoint-rapid7-zscaler-and-others"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Cloud Run Tasks partners provide more options to ensure security and compliance for cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many shards should I have in my Elasticsearch cluster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T15:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch is a very versatile platform that supports a variety of use cases and provides great flexibility around data organisation and replication strategies. This flexibility can, however, sometimes make it hard to determine up-front how to best organize your data into indices and shards, especially if you are new to the Elastic Stack. While suboptimal choices will not necessarily cause problems when first starting out, they have the potential to cause performance problems as data volumes grow over time. The more data the cluster holds, the more difficult it also becomes to correct the problem, as reindexing of large amounts of data can sometimes be required.
When we come across users that are experiencing performance problems, it is not uncommon that this can be traced back to issue…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Dahlqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many shards should I have in my Elasticsearch cluster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T15:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Dahlqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Pulsar 0.1.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/spring-for-apache-pulsar-0-1-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/spring-for-apache-pulsar-0-1-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring for Apache Pulsar 0.1.0 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This is the initial GA minor release of the framework. The full 1.0.0 GA release is expected mid Q12023 and will contain many more features. Although it still lives in the experimental Spring projects it is expected to move into the main Spring projects as part of the full release.
Notable Changes

We have been busy adding features since our last blog. Notable new features include:


  
Reactive support

  
GraalVM Native Image Support


Please see the release notes for more detail.

A great place to get started is the Quick Tour in the reference docs.
Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on GitHub.

GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Predicts: What to Expect in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-predicts-what-to-expect-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-predicts-what-to-expect-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leaders from around HashiCorp share their predictions for the coming year on everything from Kubernetes to AI to zero trust security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Custom Rules for Ansible Lint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-custom-rules-for-ansible-lint</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-custom-rules-for-ansible-lint"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Ansible Lint? 
 
Ansible Lint is a command-line tool (part of the ansible-lint upstream community project) for linting of Ansible Playbooks, Roles, and Collections. Ok, so what exactly is “linting?” Its fundamental objective is to promote proven behaviors, patterns, and practices while avoiding typical traps that can quickly result in errors or make code more difficult to maintain. That is - leverage community recommendations and opinions in writing Ansible content by means of a tool to help ensure what you’re writing is generally valid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vineeth Reddy Katuru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft's Brian Benz on the state of Java, Microsoft, Azure, and so much more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-brian-benz-on-the-state-of-java-microsoft-azure-and-so-much-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-brian-benz-on-the-state-of-java-microsoft-azure-and-so-much-more"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Microsoft’s Brian Benz (@bbenz)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/spring-framework-6-0-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/15/spring-framework-6-0-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T09:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.3 is available now.

Spring Framework 6.0.3 includes 48 fixes and documentation improvements. This version will be shipped with Spring Boot 3.0.1, to be released next week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notice of Permissions Changes to repo.spring.io, January 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/14/notice-of-permissions-changes-to-repo-spring-io-january-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/14/notice-of-permissions-changes-to-repo-spring-io-january-2023"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T06:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical piece of infrastructure, the Spring Artifactory instance lies at the heart of the Spring portfolio development work. Since 2013, JFrog, Inc., has generously sponsored the instance for the Spring developer community.

In October 2020, we announced some permissions changes to our Artifactory instance to restrict anonymous access to the platform for third-party dependencies.

At that time, we asked the Community to source Spring releases from Maven Central. Today, we are announcing some changes to our infrastructure in alignment with that request so that we can better position repo.spring.io for the long term.
How to use repo.spring.io

repo.spring.io is intended for the download of snapshots and milestone artifacts that are not available from Maven Central. All other artifacts …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Alpha API For Dynamic Resource Allocation]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/15/dynamic-resource-allocation/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/15/dynamic-resource-allocation/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Patrick Ohly (Intel), Kevin Klues (NVIDIA)
Dynamic resource allocation is a new API for requesting resources. It is a
generalization of the persistent volumes API for generic resources, making it possible to:
access the same resource instance in different pods and containers,
attach arbitrary constraints to a resource request to get the exact resource
you are looking for,
initialize a resource according to parameters provided by the user.
Third-party resource drivers are responsible for interpreting these parameters
as well as tracking and allocating resources as requests come in.
Dynamic resource allocation is an alpha feature and only enabled when the
DynamicResourceAllocation feature
gate and the
resource.k8s.io/v1alpha1 API group are enabled. For details, see the
--feature-gat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Said What? Recorder's On-device Solution for Labeling Speakers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/who-said-what-recorders-on-device.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/who-said-what-recorders-on-device.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T17:03:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Quan Wang, Senior Staff Software Engineer, and Fan Zhang, Staff Software Engineer, Google  
In 2019 we launched Recorder, an audio recording app for Pixel phones that helps users create, manage, and edit audio recordings. It leverages recent developments in on-device machine learning to transcribe speech, recognize audio events, suggest tags for titles, and help users navigate transcripts. 
 
Nonetheless, some Recorder users found it difficult to navigate long recordings that have multiple speakers because it's not clear who said what. During the Made By Google event this year, we announced the "speaker labels" feature for the Recorder app. This opt-in feature annotates a recording transcript with unique and anonymous labels for each speaker (e.g., "Speaker 1", "Speaker 2", etc.)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Plugin Framework Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-plugin-framework-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-plugin-framework-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform Plugin Framework 1.0 is now generally available to provide a modern and extensible way for developers to create Terraform providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Bring ML Models Built Anywhere into Amazon SageMaker Canvas and Generate Predictions]]></title>
        <id>3f44cecf80edbc14ee966c9c46596ccede484f1f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-bring-ml-models-built-anywhere-into-amazon-sagemaker-canvas-and-generate-predictions/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T16:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Canvas provides business analysts with a visual interface to solve business problems using machine learning (ML) without writing a single line of code. Since we introduced SageMaker Canvas in 2021, many users have asked us for an enhanced, seamless collaboration experience that enables data scientists to share trained models with their business analysts […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第221話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190247031398461</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190247031398461"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform now available in AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-now-available-in-aws-marketplace</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-now-available-in-aws-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AnsibleFest 2022 in the “windy city” Chicago, Red Hat announced Ansible Automation Platform’s upcoming availability in AWS Marketplace. That day is here!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hicham Mourad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heads-Up: Amazon S3 Security Changes Are Coming in April of 2023]]></title>
        <id>f76cf7ff0047a1af2e03a6a49905cd0af60accb7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/heads-up-amazon-s3-security-changes-are-coming-in-april-of-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T21:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting in April of 2023 we will be making two changes to Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) to put our latest best practices for bucket security into effect automatically. The changes will begin to go into effect in April and will be rolled out to all AWS Regions within weeks. Once the changes are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66150</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/december-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T18:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Failures in the “Account Parallelism Sync Analytics Job”.
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2 Patch 4
The post December patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RT-1: Robotics Transformer for Real-World Control at Scale]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/rt-1-robotics-transformer-for-real.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/rt-1-robotics-transformer-for-real.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T16:48:00.016Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted Keerthana Gopalakrishnan and Kanishka Rao, Google Research, Robotics at Google    
Major recent advances in multiple subfields of machine learning (ML) research, such as computer vision and natural language processing, have been enabled by a shared common approach that leverages large, diverse datasets and expressive models that can absorb all of the data effectively. Although there have been various attempts to apply this approach to robotics, robots have not yet leveraged highly-capable models as well as other subfields. 

Several factors contribute to this challenge. First, there’s the lack of large-scale and diverse robotic data, which limits a model’s ability to absorb a broad set of robotic experiences. Data collection is particularly expensive and challenging for robotics bec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69517&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69517</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/camunda-modeler-5-6-release-blog-post/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the release of Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.6, which ships with broader BPMN support and some key UI improvements.
The post Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.6 released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maciej Barelkowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.10 alpha2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69519&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69519</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/optimize-3-10-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See what's new in Camunda Optimize. Camunda Optimize provides business activity monitoring for workflows, supporting continuous process improvement.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.10 alpha2 released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.19.0-alpha2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69518&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69518</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/camunda-automation-platform-7-19-0-alpha2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7, including new REST docs, support for PostgreSQL 15 and more.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.19.0-alpha2 released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 13th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/13/this-week-in-spring-december-13th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/13/this-week-in-spring-december-13th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I truly, absolutely, can not believe that we’re nearly done with the year already! Have you made your new years’ resolutions? Submitted your expense reports? It’s that time of the year when I’m going to start focusing on staying warm and avoiding undue work for a while :-) I hope you do too. This is why I’m glad I write these roundups: I hope they save people from extra, undue work! So, with that… let’s dive into the roundup!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Vaadin’s Marcus Hellberg on rich UIs, Spring Boot 3, GraalVM native images, and more

  
A Guide to Spring CredHub

  
Do more with Azure Spring Apps – scale to zero and enhance productivity

  
Form Login and Basic Authentication in springdoc-openapi

  
Getting Started with Blaze Persistence

  
Guide to Java PriorityQueue

  
Java Generics PECS – Producer Extends Consumer Super

  
RSocket Security with Spring Boot via Spring Security | VMware Tanzu Developer Center

  
Rate Limiting With Client IP in Spring Cloud Gateway

  
Reinitialize Singleton Bean in Spring Context

  
a very important release - v3.0.0 - of the rickroll-security-spring-boot-starter  · TomCools/rickroll-security-spring-boot-starter!

  
Running Spring Boot Applications with the Embedded Camunda Engine

  
Securing RSocket TCP with TLS | VMware Tanzu Developer Center

  
Spring Cloud Data Flow version 2.10.0 released

  
Spring Dependency Injection | VMware Tanzu Developer Center

  
Spring Tools 4.17.0 released

  
Tracing a Reactive Kotlin App with Spring Cloud Sleuth | VMware Tanzu Developer Center]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Windows HostProcess Containers Are Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/13/windows-host-process-containers-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/13/windows-host-process-containers-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Brandon Smith (Microsoft) and Mark Rossetti (Microsoft)
The long-awaited day has arrived: HostProcess containers, the Windows equivalent to Linux privileged
containers, has finally made it to GA in Kubernetes 1.26!
What are HostProcess containers and why are they useful?
Cluster operators are often faced with the need to configure their nodes upon provisioning such as
installing Windows services, configuring registry keys, managing TLS certificates,
making network configuration changes, or even deploying monitoring tools such as a Prometheus's node-exporter.
Previously, performing these actions on Windows nodes was usually done by running PowerShell scripts
over SSH or WinRM sessions and/or working with your cloud provider's virtual machine management tooling.
HostProcess containe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – December 12, 2022]]></title>
        <id>38646395c7ef57fef2041e8de74e54446ae45793</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-december-12-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T22:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! The world is asynchronous, is what Werner Vogels, Amazon CTO, reminded us during his keynote last week at AWS re:Invent. At the beginning of the keynote, he showed us how […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crank up your automation with Ansible validated content]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/crank-up-your-automation-with-ansible-validated-content</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/crank-up-your-automation-with-ansible-validated-content"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible validated content is expert-built automation content packaged as Collections that contain Ansible roles and playbooks that you can use “out-the-box” through Ansible Automation Platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Data Flow version 2.10.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/12/spring-cloud-data-flow-version-2-10-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/12/spring-cloud-data-flow-version-2-10-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, we are very excited to announce the 2.10.0 release of Spring Cloud Data Flow is now available from Maven Central.
Spring updates

Updates to the following versions:


  
Spring Boot 2.7.6

  
Spring Framework 5.3.24

  
Spring Cloud 2021.0.5


Spring Shell

Spring Shell has been updated to 2.1.4.
Documentation Updates
Container images for ARM.

Spring Cloud Data Flow and Skipper, and Stream Application projects contain scripts to use in creating containers when running on an ARM platform. The Reference Guide has a section describing the use of the scripts.
Scripts for local Kuberenetes Development

We have added a collection of scripts to the Spring Cloud Data Flow that makes it easy to launch a local Kuberenetes cluster and install SCDF with MariaDB and RabbitMQ or Kafka. See the Reference Guide for more info.

The detailed release notes contain more info.
Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on Stackoverflow or GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 214 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66155</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-214-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T15:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[List of New Boards Hub bugs fixed in sprint 214. We enabled the “Try New Boards Hub” message across another ring of accounts. The process continues to go slower than originally expected. Every time we enable the message, we receive more feedback on issues that need to be fixed.
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 214 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest 2022 recap]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69423&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69423</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/hacktoberfest-2022-recap/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T13:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn all about our Hacktoberfest 2022 challenge. We hope you all had a great time participating in it and Hacktoberfest as a whole! 
The post Hacktoberfest 2022 recap appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mia Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: We're now signing our binary release artifacts!]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/12/kubernetes-release-artifact-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/12/kubernetes-release-artifact-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
The Kubernetes Special Interest Group (SIG) Release is proud to announce that we
are digitally signing all release artifacts, and that this aspect of Kubernetes
has now reached beta.
Signing artifacts provides end users a chance to verify the integrity of the
downloaded resource. It allows to mitigate man-in-the-middle attacks directly on
the client side and therefore ensures the trustfulness of the remote serving the
artifacts. The overall goal of out past work was to define the used tooling for
signing all Kubernetes related artifacts as well as providing a standard signing
process for related projects (for example for those in kubernetes-sigs).
We already signed all officially released container images (from Kubernetes v1.24 onwards).
Image signing was alpha for v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>