<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-02-04T01:03:11.103Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-02-04T01:03:11.103Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.12.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demonstrate your AWS Cloud Storage knowledge and skills with new digital badges!]]></title>
        <id>7575cda5d88818dd7121ef796bc78e85c48004ec</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/demonstrate-your-aws-cloud-storage-knowledge-and-skills-with-new-digital-badges/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T16:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a cloud storage professional or an on-premises storage pro who’s curious about cloud storage? Are you interested in demonstrating your AWS Storage knowledge and skills with potential employers and your community of peers? If so, I’d like to bring to your attention the recent launch of digital badges aligned to Learning Plans for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code coverage for eBPF programs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/code-coverage-for-ebpf-programs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/code-coverage-for-ebpf-programs"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Until today, there was no simple way to visualize how the flow of your eBPF program running in the kernel was. Hopefully, there is one starting today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leonardo Di Donato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code coverage for eBPF programs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/code-coverage-for-ebpf-programs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/code-coverage-for-ebpf-programs"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
I bet we all have heard so much about eBPF in recent years. Data shows that eBPF is quickly becoming the first choice for implementing tracing and security applications, and Elastic is also working relentlessly on supercharging our security solutions (and more) with eBPF. 
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt1288e08485151449/61f9784fd970ea1bb42ad274/code-coverage-ebpf-programs-annotated-screenshot-llvm-patches-our-instructions.png,code-coverage-ebpf-programs-annotated-screenshot-llvm-patches-our-instructions.png,If you write an eBPF program incrementing a counter (defined as an eBPF global variable) you will notice that the resulting instructions will be like those here in the screenshot. It means we can keep these the way they are generated by LLVM and let it …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leonardo Di Donato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud is now using Automated Certificate Management with Let's Encrypt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-using-automated-certificate-management-with-lets-encrypt</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-using-automated-certificate-management-with-lets-encrypt"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud TLS certificates have migrated to Let's Encrypt to support sustainable and fully automated certificate management as part of our ongoing commitment to offer customers the most secure way to run workloads in the cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Riccardo Marinelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud is now using Automated Certificate Management with Let's Encrypt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-using-automated-certificate-management-with-lets-encrypt</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-using-automated-certificate-management-with-lets-encrypt"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
At Elastic we are committed to offering our customers the most secure way to run their workloads in the cloud. To help ensure this commitment, we have migrated our Elastic Cloud Transport Layer Security (TLS) certificates to Let’s Encrypt to best support sustainable and fully automated certificate management as our product offerings and available regions continue to expand.
To achieve this change, we have built a fully automated regional ACM (ACME Certificate Manager). We will walk you through our internal process of why we needed to upgrade, what options we explored, the implementation, and how we use our own Elastic Uptime Monitoring and Kibana to monitor the certificates.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltd8bd941b2d1c6932/61f9b6ffc1f2271a3225df9a/acm-certificate-manager-how-it-works-lets-encrypt.png,acm-certificate-manager-how-it-works-lets-encrypt.pngHow do we monitor the certificates,
We use Elastic Uptime Monitoring and Kibana to check, report and alert on certificate validity and expiration based on configurable threshold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Riccardo Marinelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy groundhog’s day]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42266</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/680677708/0/sethsblog~Happy-groundhogs-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, did we just say that? Every day is the same if you let it. Of course, spiders, dogs and walruses prefer if the world doesn’t change. But humans are different. Change is fuel for growth and possibility. It’s easy to lull ourselves into a media-fueled commercial stupor, digging an ever-deeper rut. Same job, same […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.0.0-rc2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-0-0-rc2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-0-0-rc2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are delighted to announce the second release candidate of 8.0.0 following release candidate 1. Again, we want to remind you that this is not for production use. There is no guarantee that 8.0.0-rc2 will be compatible with other preview releases or with 8.0.0 general availability (GA).
We’d love to get your feedback and tips on any bugs you find through our Pioneer Program. To become an Elastic Pioneer, try out the preview of any (preferably, every) part of the Elastic Stack and open issues as you find them in the appropriate repo — Elasticsearch, Kibana, Beats, Logstash, and APM. When you open an issue, mention that you found the bug in 8.0.0-rc2, and we’ll add a “Pioneer Program” label.
If you have questions about preparing for your upgrade to 8.0, visit our forums or community Slack channel, and we’d be happy to help!
8.0.0-rc2 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Workplace Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.0.0-rc2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-0-0-rc2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-0-0-rc2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.0.0-rc2 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Logstash, Beats, APM, Enterprise Search, Elastic Security, ECK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Overcame Long-Running Job Limitations in Jenkins Declarative Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=42944</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/how-we-overcame-long-running-job-limitations-in-jenkins-declarative-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T21:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get the technical details about the challenges we faced while building advanced declarative pipelines for our workflow and decision engine. 
The post How We Overcame Long-Running Job Limitations in Jenkins Declarative Pipelines appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed AbouZaid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Robots Follow Instructions for New Tasks?]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/can-robots-follow-instructions-for-new.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/can-robots-follow-instructions-for-new.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T18:47:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Chelsea Finn, Research Adviser and Eric Jang, Senior Research Scientist, Robotics at Google 
People can flexibly maneuver objects in their physical surroundings to accomplish various goals. One of the grand challenges in robotics is to successfully train robots to do the same, i.e., to develop a general-purpose robot capable of performing a multitude of tasks based on arbitrary user commands. Robots that are faced with the real world will also inevitably encounter new user instructions and situations that were not seen during training. Therefore, it is imperative for robots to be trained to perform multiple tasks in a variety of situations and, more importantly, to be capable of solving new tasks as requested by human users, even if the robot was not explicitly trained on those t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Observability at Scale Using Datadog’s Vector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-observability-at-scale-using-datadog-s-vector</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-observability-at-scale-using-datadog-s-vector"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get technical insight into how HCP Vault uses Datadog’s Vector integration to meet the observability needs of customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The trough of inefficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41325</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/680518906/0/sethsblog~The-trough-of-inefficiency/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful organizations of just one or two freelancers have very high revenue per employee, effective labor utilization and few communications problems. And significant organizations of a hundred or a thousand people also produce enormous amounts of revenue, profit and perhaps value. In between, though, there’s a slog. That’s because a successful tiny organization that adds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.13.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/02/spring-tools-4-13-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/02/spring-tools-4-13-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.13.1 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) improvement: Consider if content assist can be offered for spring.config.import property keys (#536)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: YAML editor generates wrong EOL characters in Windows (#709)

  
(VSCode) fixed: Always pop up a prompt box: indexing spring boot properties (#697)

  
(VSCode) fixed: Spring Boot Tools for VS Code incorrectly misidentifies internal JDK for Language Support for Java as a JRE (#715)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Create or modify new project - maven update problem (#703)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


If you are updating an existing Spring Tools 4.12.1 (or prior) installation, please make sure you to prepare your installation properly: https://twitter.com/springtools4/status/1468587842838355980

Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-02-02-4131-release-incl-language-servers-version-1300

Spring Tools 4.14.0 is scheduled to be released in late March 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Control Group]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2576/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2576/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/control_group.png" title="Placeble 228 x/6
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜" alt="Placeble 228 x/6
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜
⬜⬜⬜⬜⬜" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Activate Red Hat Insights for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/activate-insights-for-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/activate-insights-for-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T19:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: This blog refers to Red Hat Insights using Ansible Automation Platform 2.1. Automation controller is the control plane for Ansible Automation Platform, formerly known as Red Hat Ansible Tower. 
An indispensable but sometimes overlooked tool included with an Ansible Automation Platform subscription is the cloud-based service, Red Hat Insights for Ansible Automation Platform.
 
Insights is a suite of reporting and analytics tools to help you identify, troubleshoot, and resolve operational, business, and security issues across your entire ecosystem. You can also use Insights to track the ROI of your automation investment and plan future automation projects to prioritize your efforts where they will have the biggest impact on your business.
 
Before you can start using Insights to better understand your automation estate and make data-driven decisions, you need to set up the flow of information from your enterprise into the Red Hat Hybrid Cloud Console.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-17-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-17-0"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17 delivers a new and improved Upgrade Assistant, with guided steps and more automated fixes to address deprecation issues, to support users through how to upgrade with confidence to the next major series, 8.x. Also, Stack users benefit from performance and scalability improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeline Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-17-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-17-0"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The Elastic Stack 7.17 introduces the last installment of the 7.x series, and includes the latest Upgrade Assistant which helps users upgrade to 8.0 and beyond. This latest version will bring you the best of search, analysis, visualizations, and actionable workflows, whether you’re using one or all of Elastic’s solutions.
The Elastic Stack continues to grow more performant, scalable, and faster for users of Elastic’s managed cloud service (and those using a self-managed deployment). New features include:

A new and improved Upgrade Assistant to guide users through Elasticsearch and Kibana deprecations, providing automated system remediation where possible and instructions for manual remediation as needed.
Enhancements for performance and scalability.
Updated Docker images for all product…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeline Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Differential Privacy to Large Scale Image Classification]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/applying-differential-privacy-to-large.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/applying-differential-privacy-to-large.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alexey Kurakin, Software Engineer and Roxana Geambasu, Visiting Faculty Researcher, Google Research 
Machine learning (ML) models are becoming increasingly valuable for improved performance across a variety of consumer products, from recommendations to automatic image classification.  However, despite aggregating large amounts of data, in theory it is possible for models to encode characteristics of individual entries from the training set.  For example, experiments in controlled settings have shown that language models trained using email datasets may sometimes encode sensitive information included in the training data and may have the potential to reveal the presence of a particular user’s data in the training set. As such, it is important to prevent the encoding of such charac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling Transparent Data Encryption for Microsoft SQL with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/enabling-transparent-data-encryption-for-microsoft-sql-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/enabling-transparent-data-encryption-for-microsoft-sql-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HashiCorp Vault can help secure data in Microsoft SQL Server using a defense-in-depth encryption strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying Interviewing for Backend Engineers @ Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/aceb26a83495</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/demystifying-interviewing-for-backend-engineers-netflix-aceb26a83495?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T14:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Karen Casella, Director of Engineering, Access & Identity Management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and AWS Serverless Application Repository (SAR): Speed time to actionable insights with frictionless log ingestion from Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-serverless-application-repository-speed-time-to-actionable-insights-with-frictionless-log-ingestion-from-amazon-s3</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-serverless-application-repository-speed-time-to-actionable-insights-with-frictionless-log-ingestion-from-amazon-s3"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ingest logs frictionlessly from Amazon S3 with Elastic’s new serverless forwarder available in the AWS Serverless Application Repository (SAR). Accelerate actionable insights with a unified view across your multi-cloud environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravi Kesarwani,Uday Theepireddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and AWS Serverless Application Repository (SAR): Speed time to actionable insights with frictionless log ingestion from Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-serverless-application-repository-speed-time-to-actionable-insights-with-frictionless-log-ingestion-from-amazon-s3</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-serverless-application-repository-speed-time-to-actionable-insights-with-frictionless-log-ingestion-from-amazon-s3"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As companies leverage the Amazon Web Services (AWS) cloud platform and services to drive operational efficiency and bring products to market, logs are often stored in Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) then shipped to an external monitoring and analysis solution. Now AWS users can quickly ingest logs stored in Amazon S3 with the new Elastic serverless forwarder, an AWS Lambda application, and view them in the Elastic Stack alongside other logs and metrics for centralized analytics. 
Skip lengthy processes like provisioning a VM or installing data shippers — and reduce management overhead by ingesting data directly from AWS to Elastic. 
In this blog, we will teach you how to use the Elastic serverless forwarder —  that is published in the AWS Serverless Application Repository (SAR …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravi Kesarwani,Uday Theepireddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - February 1st, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/01/this-week-in-spring-february-1st-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/01/this-week-in-spring-february-1st-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! It’s a new Lunar year, so that’s exciting, and I just celebrated my birthday, and that of my late father, as well. That was exciting. But there was also some bittersweet news. Let’s get that out of the way first…

My friend, my hero, Stéphane Maldini, former project lead of Project Reactor and cofounder of the Reactive Streams initiative, passed away two months ago. We in the Java community made him a Java Champion posthumously. We miss him dearly. I think of him when I write reactive code. 

Mon ami, mon héros, Stéphane Maldini, ancien lead de l’equipe Reactor et cofondateur des Reactive Streams, est mort il y a deux mois. La commaunité Java l’a nommé un Java Champion. Il nous manque beaucoup. Je pense a lui lorsque j’ecris du code reactive. 

Java Champions on Twitter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In temporary residence]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41307</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/680359846/0/sethsblog~In-temporary-residence/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T09:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They will outlast you. Why are some industries so irrational (when seen from the point of view of the customer)? So many things about college, funerals, real estate, hotels, weddings and the contractor trade are frustrating and opaque to customers. It almost seems as though they’re organized with a long-term, industry-wide focus away from customer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42247</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/680211780/0/sethsblog~On-schedule/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-31T09:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We get a huge benefit from making a simple commitment: Don’t miss deadlines. The benefit is that once we agree to the deadline, we don’t have to worry about it anymore. We don’t have to negotiate, come up with excuses or even stress about it. It won’t ship when it’s perfect. It will ship because […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What If? 2]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2575/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2575/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/what_if_2.png" title="CLARIFICATION: By 9/13, I mean September 13th, not the 9th day of Jancember, the cursed 13th month that exists between December and January in the transdimensional temporal plane." alt="CLARIFICATION: By 9/13, I mean September 13th, not the 9th day of Jancember, the cursed 13th month that exists between December and January in the transdimensional temporal plane." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broken links]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42243</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/680117802/0/sethsblog~Broken-links/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-30T12:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blog post I did a few hours ago was filled with broken links, the result of some weird sort of rift in the time-space continuum. Sorry for the hassle. It’s fixed now. If you get this blog via email or some other form of intermediated transposition, you can always click on the name of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Books for the journey]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42223</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/680102570/0/sethsblog~Books-for-the-journey/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-30T09:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My bookshelves are filled with books I’ve read once. But there are others that I come back to again and again. I hand them out like Halloween candy to colleagues, and often, they end up paying them forward as I did. Authors and ideas for the long haul. Classics in our field, in fact. One […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The asking price]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41311</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/679985294/0/sethsblog~The-asking-price/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-29T10:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The asking price is true, but it’s also an illusion. If you are offered a job and negotiate a raise of 10% over what was originally offered, that’s good, but it has nothing at all to do with what you’re actually worth. If you buy a house for 15% over asking price, it doesn’t mean […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controlling Neural Networks with Rule Representations]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/controlling-neural-networks-with-rule.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/controlling-neural-networks-with-rule.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T18:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sungyong Seo, Software Engineer and Sercan O. Arik, Research Scientist, Google Research, Cloud AI Team  
Deep neural networks (DNNs) provide more accurate results as the size and coverage of their training data increases. While investing in high-quality and large-scale labeled datasets is one path to model improvement, another is leveraging prior knowledge, concisely referred to as “rules” — reasoning heuristics, equations, associative logic, or constraints. Consider a common example from physics where a model is given the task of predicting the next state in a double pendulum system. While the model may learn to estimate the total energy of the system at a given point in time only from empirical data, it will frequently overestimate the energy unless also provided an equation th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.9 Adds Cross-Stack References and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-9-adds-cross-stack-references-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-9-adds-cross-stack-references-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform 0.9 (CDKTF) enables cross-stack references and improves generated resources for providers and modules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway Now in Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-now-in-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-now-in-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Consul API Gateway has now reached its first beta release, adding TCPRoute support, Helm chart support, and a new HashiCorp Learn tutorial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crowded markets]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41309</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/679849786/0/sethsblog~Crowded-markets/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T10:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At first glance, it makes sense to avoid a crowded market. Better to sell your services or your products in a place where you’re the only one. But crowded markets also have lots of customers. A mutual understanding of what’s expected. People ready to pay to solve their problems. Word of mouth. And competitors to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.28]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63348</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-01-28/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T09:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.01.28 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.28 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Modeler 5.0.0-alpha.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=41898&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=41898</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/camunda-modeler-5-0-0-alpha-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're happy to announce the Camunda Modeler 5.0 release. It provides Camunda Cloud 1.1 support, BPMN in color support, and more improvements.
The post Camunda Modeler 5.0.0-alpha.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andreas Geier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate Your Camunda Modeler Plugins to Work with Camunda Modeler 5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=41903&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=41903</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/how-to-migrate-your-camunda-modeler-plugins-to-work-with-camunda-modeler-5-x/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to update Camunda Modeler plugins to benefit from its new features and make them compatible with Camunda Modeler 5 and subsequent versions. 
The post How to Migrate Your Camunda Modeler Plugins to Work with Camunda Modeler 5.0 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maximilian Trumpf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M1 (codename Kilburn) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/27/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m1-codename-kilburn-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/27/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m1-codename-kilburn-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Milestone 1 (M1) of the Spring Cloud 2022.0 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2022.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2022.0.0 Release Train

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.

The 2022.0.0-M1 release is all about compatibility with Spring Framework 6.0.0-M2, Spring Boot 3.0.0-M1, Java 17, Jakarta EE, and all the other milestones of Spring projects such as Spring Security, Spring Data, etc…

Changes include: moving to a Java 17 baseline, migrating from javax.* packages to jakarta.*, changes for removed classes and methods marked for deprecation, updating dependencies to ver…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Framework cofounder and project lead, friend, and all around amazing human being, Juergen Hoeller]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/27/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-framework-cofounder-and-project-lead-friend-and-all-around-amazing-human-being-juergen-hoeller</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/27/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-framework-cofounder-and-project-lead-friend-and-all-around-amazing-human-being-juergen-hoeller"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of A Bootiful Podcast! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring Framework co-founder and project lead, friend, and all-around amazing human being, Juergen Hoeller (@springjuergen) about Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How banking giant ING is future-proofing payment processing with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-banking-giant-ing-is-future-proofing-payment-processing-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-banking-giant-ing-is-future-proofing-payment-processing-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why global financial powerhouse ING is retiring its COBOL-based payment messaging platform, and entrusting Elastic as a successor to this mission-critical system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lieven Merckx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy onboarding and ingestion, and a unified and actionable experience: How Elastic Observability has advanced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/look-back-at-elastic-observability-in-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/look-back-at-elastic-observability-in-2021"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year-end review of all the new features and capabilities brought to Elastic Observability in 2021. Learn about how observability built on search is a better solution for monitoring distributed systems, cloud migrations & digital transformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Wen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How banking giant ING is future-proofing payment processing with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-banking-giant-ing-is-future-proofing-payment-processing-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-banking-giant-ing-is-future-proofing-payment-processing-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltd6b6b3639ad41485/61f407081e207a3729b8fec8/ING-guestblog.png,ING-guestblog.png,
ING Group is a Dutch-based multinational banking and financial services corporation serving more than 38 million customers globally. It’s one of the biggest banks in the world, and consistently ranks among the top 30 largest banks globally.
Our 20-year-old COBOL-based financial messaging system — which provides electronic instructions to enable financial transactions between banks and customers — is slowly becoming obsolete and difficult to integrate. COBOL is declining in popularity among developers, and many programmers with COBOL experience are retiring or will soon.
In addition, we’re seeing competition from fintech startups that are lowering the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lieven Merckx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy onboarding and ingestion, and a unified and actionable experience: How Elastic Observability has advanced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/look-back-at-elastic-observability-in-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/look-back-at-elastic-observability-in-2021"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Observability continues to grow and become top of mind for IT professionals and developers around the world. As you modernize your application stack for the cloud, you should align your DevOps processes and tools to support your on-premises and cloud environment. Elastic Observability has been hard at work improving and introducing exciting innovation in our observability solution to meet your evolving requirements. 
With increased complexity and need to deliver end to end observability, we focused on delivering along the following themes - easy onboarding and data ingestion, a unified observability experience, and finally, actionable observability supported by machine-learning powered anomaly detection and ad hoc analytics. Here’s a look back at the year and some of what we delivered!
h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Wen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autoresponder]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2574/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2574/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/autoresponder.png" title="I ADMIRE HOW YOU SET BOUNDARIES AND I HOPE YOUR COLLEAGUES RESPECT THEM! PLEASE SPARE MY LIFE!" alt="I ADMIRE HOW YOU SET BOUNDARIES AND I HOPE YOUR COLLEAGUES RESPECT THEM! PLEASE SPARE MY LIFE!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Your Medical Image Classifier Know What It Doesn’t Know?]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/does-your-medical-image-classifier-know.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/does-your-medical-image-classifier-know.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T18:01:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Abhijit Guha Roy, Research Software Engineer and Jie Ren, Research Scientist, Google Research    
Deep machine learning (ML) systems have achieved considerable success in medical image analysis in recent years. One major contributing factor is access to abundant labeled datasets, which are used to train highly effective supervised deep learning models. However, in the real-world, these models may encounter samples exhibiting rare conditions that are individually too infrequent for per-condition classification. Nevertheless, such conditions can be collectively common because they follow a long-tail distribution and when taken together can represent a significant portion of cases — e.g., in a recent deep learning dermatological study, hundreds of rare conditions composed around 20%…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandboxing anti-malware products for fun and profit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/sandboxing-anti-malware-products-for-fun-and-profit</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/sandboxing-anti-malware-products-for-fun-and-profit"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Security team has found an unpatched Windows flaw that allows malware to disable security products. Here’s how to fix it using Elastic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriel Landau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandboxing anti-malware products for fun and profit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/sandboxing-anti-malware-products-for-fun-and-profit</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/sandboxing-anti-malware-products-for-fun-and-profit"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic researchers enjoy finding new means for users to protect their organizations against attack. Recently, the Elastic Security team identified an unpatched Windows flaw in the Windows Protected Process Light (PPL) mechanism that lets malware disable security products, and incorporated a fix into Elastic Security to protect our users. 
In our full analysis, the team summarizes what Windows protected anti-malware services include, and how both sandboxing and access tokens can operate in a Windows environment. The author, Gabriel Landau, provides detailed insight into the way tokens can be leveraged by hackers to penetrate and evade Windows-based systems. The article also includes a recorded demonstration showing exactly how sandboxing can quietly incapacitate anti-malware products. 
Landau’s analysis also goes into depth about how anti-malware vendors can defend themselves  against this exposure with an obscure Windows feature called trusted labels. 
To find threats like malware and ransomware in your environment, install the latest version of Elastic Security, and be sure to take advantage of our quick start training to set yourself up for success. 
If you’re new to Elastic Cloud, you can always get started for free with a free 14-day trial of Elastic Cloud or download the self-managed version of the Elastic Stack for free.
Happy hunting!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriel Landau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul on Amazon ECS 0.3 Adds Extended Configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-3-adds-extended-configuration</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-3-adds-extended-configuration"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T17:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest version of HashiCorp Consul on Amazon ECS adds extended configuration to support more deployment scenarios along with several other new features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第202話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496725200155</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496725200155"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline configuration processes with an official Elastic Stack Terraform provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/streamline-configuration-processes-with-official-elastic-stack-terraform-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/streamline-configuration-processes-with-official-elastic-stack-terraform-provider"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Stack Terraform provider allows operations and SRE teams to safely manage their production-related infrastructure and fully control the configuration of Elasticsearch, Kibana, Fleet, and any other component within the Elastic Stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Kushmaro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline configuration processes with an official Elastic Stack Terraform provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/streamline-configuration-processes-with-official-elastic-stack-terraform-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/streamline-configuration-processes-with-official-elastic-stack-terraform-provider"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re excited to announce that operation and SRE teams can now take advantage of an official Elastic Stack Terraform provider to configure the Elastic Stack across all types of infrastructure, whether on Elastic Cloud, or on-premises and self-managed.
This Elastic Stack Terraform provider will allow you to fully control the configuration of Elasticsearch, Kibana, Fleet, and any other component within the Elastic Stack.
The Terraform provider helps you safely manage production-related infrastructure using methodologies like infrastructure as code, which allow you to apply peer-reviewed infrastructure changes in an automated and controlled fashion.
Let’s walk through an example of how to spin up an Elastic Cloud deployment, then immediately configure it with an index lifecycle policy — usi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Kushmaro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Innovation and domain knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41538</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/679725672/0/sethsblog~Innovation-and-domain-knowledge/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T11:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has this ever been done before? Why not? Did it work? Why not? If it’s new and useful, what problem is it solving? Why has the audience rejected similar innovations in the past? One day, this market will change. What will cause that change to happen?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 X2iezn Instances Powered by the Fastest Intel Xeon Scalable CPU for Memory-Intensive Workloads]]></title>
        <id>84680f474bcddfcb3d45b07aa0b7d72597777988</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-x2iezn-instances-powered-by-the-fastest-intel-xeon-scalable-cpu-for-memory-intensive-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T21:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electronic Design Automation (EDA) workloads require high computing performance and a large memory footprint. These workloads are sensitive to faster CPU performance and higher clock speeds since the faster performance allows more jobs to be completed on the lower number of cores. At AWS re:Invent 2020, we launched Amazon EC2 M5zn instances which use second-generation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resolving High-Energy Impacts on Quantum Processors]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/resolving-high-energy-impacts-on.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/resolving-high-energy-impacts-on.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T19:57:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Matt McEwen, Student Researcher, Google Quantum AI and Lara Faoro, Research Fellow, LPTHE- Sorbonne Université and CNRS (Paris) 
Quantum processors are made of superconducting quantum bits (qubits) that — being quantum objects — are highly susceptible to even tiny amounts of environmental noise. This noise can cause errors in quantum computation that need to be addressed to continue advancing quantum computers. Our Sycamore processors are installed in specially designed cryostats, where they are sealed away from stray light and electromagnetic fields and are cooled down to very low temperatures to reduce thermal noise.  
However, the world is full of high-energy radiation. In fact, there’s a tiny background of high-energy gamma rays and muons that pass through everything around u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server patches]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63316</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-and-team-foundation-server-patches/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T19:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With this patch cycle, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server, as well as Team Foundation Server 2018.3.2. Please see the release notes for additional installation instructions.
Upgraded search plugins to use log4j core version 2.17.1.
The post Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server patches appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 66 – Building real-time apps with @Azure SignalR with @chris_noring]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63331</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-66-building-real-time-apps-with-azure-signalr-with-chris_noring/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T17:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 66 – Building real-time apps with @Azure SignalR with @chris_noring appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Vault Integration via Sidecar Agent Injector vs. CSI Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-vault-integration-via-sidecar-agent-injector-vs-csi-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-vault-integration-via-sidecar-agent-injector-vs-csi-provider"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A detailed comparison of two HashiCorp-supported methods for HashiCorp Vault and Kubernetes integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic's Diane Tetrault on what parenting, scuba diving, and product marketing have in common]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-diane-tetrault-what-parenting-scubadiving-productmarketing-have-in-common</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-diane-tetrault-what-parenting-scubadiving-productmarketing-have-in-common"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We sat down with Diane to learn more about how she balances her passions, her career, and her family, including how her role at Elastic makes all of that possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Plumhoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic's Diane Tetrault on what parenting, scuba diving, and product marketing have in common]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-diane-tetrault-what-parenting-scubadiving-productmarketing-have-in-common</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-diane-tetrault-what-parenting-scubadiving-productmarketing-have-in-common"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As an instructor of other scuba diving instructors, Diane Tetrault knows how to convey life-saving lessons in a way that encourages and supports her students. And as it turns out, that skill is highly transferable to two other key roles in her life: manager and mother.
Diane is the Senior Director of Product Marketing at Elastic and is also a mom of two sons. In the water, at work, and with her family, she’s gotten plenty of practice creating the right environment for other people to learn and enjoy.
“Scuba diving is something lots of people have on their bucket list, where they say, ‘Oh, I wish I could do that, but I’m too afraid.’ But I know lots of people would love it if they tried.”
Diane’s not one to shy away from new experiences, even when it seems like they’d be hard to work into…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Plumhoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.2.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/26/spring-authorization-server-0-2-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/26/spring-authorization-server-0-2-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.2.2.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




compile 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.2.2'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the sample to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues |  ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Here we go again”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40254</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/679571510/0/sethsblog~Here-we-go-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T09:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have a script? Most of us do. Here’s a new piece of software. Do you immediately read the manual front to back? Dive in and see how it works? Tense up in fear and distaste? She’s going to give you some feedback. Is your first reaction to be defensive, or to lean into […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Native 0.11.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/26/spring-native-0-11-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/26/spring-native-0-11-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Native 0.11.2 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release.

This release includes 30 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alien Mission]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2573/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2573/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/alien_mission.png" title="Fine, we can go search the Himalayas for the Yeti ONE more time, but keep a safe altitude over the Pacific and PLEASE watch where you're going. We can't afford another Amelia Earhart incident." alt="Fine, we can go search the Himalayas for the Yeti ONE more time, but keep a safe altitude over the Pacific and PLEASE watch where you're going. We can't afford another Amelia Earhart incident." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - January 25th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/25/this-week-in-spring-january-25th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/25/this-week-in-spring-january-25th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-01-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Can you believe it’s already the 25th of the first month of a brand new year!? And we’re fast approaching the Lunar New Year, often also called the Chinese New Year, which will arrive next Tuesday. Reunion dinner will be on the 31st of January, and the two weeks of celebration will begin. All that to say that this is my last real chance, speaking I’m sure for the entire Tanzu team, to wish everyone around the planet (billions of people!) who celebrates a very happy Lunar New Year (Mandarin: 新年快乐 (pronounced: xin nian kauai le ) / Cantonese: 新年快乐 (pronounced: san nin fai lok )) and to say that we hope you enjoy prosperity in the new year (Mandarin: 恭喜发财 (pronounced: gong xi fa cai) / Cantonese: 恭喜发财 (pronounced: gong hei fat choy))! 

That said, let’s get into this week’s …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Replication for Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)]]></title>
        <id>18ded4a0d0007ca9f441a1476a3932c125d70866</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-replication-for-amazon-elastic-file-system-efs/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-25T22:28:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) allows EC2 instances, AWS Lambda functions, and containers to share access to a fully-managed file system. First announced in 2015 and generally available in 2016, Amazon EFS delivers low-latency performance for a wide variety of workloads and can scale to thousands of concurrent clients or connections. Since the 2016 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix: A Culture of Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/394bc7d0f94c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/netflix-a-culture-of-learning-394bc7d0f94c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-01-25T16:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Tingley with Wenjing Zheng, Simon Ejdemyr, Stephanie Lane, Colin McFarland, Mihir Tendulkar, and Travis Brooks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: How Can I Upgrade Spring Boot Maven Dependencies for the Enterprise Edition?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=41727</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/qa-how-can-i-upgrade-spring-boot-maven-dependencies-for-the-enterprise-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New to the enterprise edition of Spring Boot? Let us walk you through each task involved with upgrading from the community edition. 
The post Q&A: How Can I Upgrade Spring Boot Maven Dependencies for the Enterprise Edition? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing Performance Regressions Before they Happen]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/eab2602b86fe</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/fixing-performance-regressions-before-they-happen-eab2602b86fe?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T21:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How the Netflix TVUI team implemented a robust strategy to quickly and easily detect performance anomalies before they a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accurate Alpha Matting for Portrait Mode Selfies on Pixel 6]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/accurate-alpha-matting-for-portrait.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/accurate-alpha-matting-for-portrait.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sergio Orts Escolano and Jana Ehman, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Image matting is the process of extracting a precise alpha matte that separates foreground and background objects in an image. This technique has been traditionally used in the filmmaking and photography industry for image and video editing purposes, e.g., background replacement, synthetic bokeh and other visual effects. Image matting assumes that an image is a composite of foreground and background images, and hence, the intensity of each pixel is a linear combination of the foreground and the background.  
   
In the case of traditional image segmentation, the image is segmented in a binary manner, in which a pixel either belongs to the foreground or background. This type of segmentation, however, is unab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Ansible.utils Collection for Playbook Creators: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-ansible.utils-collection-for-playbook-creators-part-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-ansible.utils-collection-for-playbook-creators-part-2"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T18:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use Case: Operational state assessment using ansible.utils collection
 
In ansible.utils, there are a variety of plugins which we can use for operational state assessment of network devices. I overviewed the ansible.utils collection in part one of this two part blog series. If you have not reviewed part one, I recommend you do so, since I will build on this information in this part two blog. We will see how the ansible.utils collection can be useful in operational state assessment as an example use case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwini Mhatre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Ansible.utils Collection for Playbook Creators: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-ansible.utils-collection-for-playbook-creators-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-ansible.utils-collection-for-playbook-creators-part-1"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T18:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible ansible.utils collection includes a variety of plugins that aid in the management, manipulation and visibility of data for the Ansible playbook developer. The most common use case for this collection is when you want to work with the complex data structures present in an Ansible playbook, inventory, or returned from modules. See each plugin documentation page for detailed examples for how these utilities can be used in tasks. In this two-part blog we will overview this collection in part one and see an example use case of using the utils collection in detail in part two.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwini Mhatre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Separating Birdsong in the Wild for Classification]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/separating-birdsong-in-wild-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/separating-birdsong-in-wild-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T17:53:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tom Denton, Software Engineer and Scott Wisdom, Research Scientist, Google Research 
Birds are all around us, and just by listening, we can learn many things about our environment. Ecologists use birds to understand food systems and forest health — for example, if there are more woodpeckers in a forest, that means there’s a lot of dead wood. Because birds communicate and mark territory with songs and calls, it’s most efficient to identify them by ear. In fact, experts may identify up to 10x as many birds by ear as by sight. 
In recent years, autonomous recording units (ARUs) have made it easy to capture thousands of hours of audio in forests that could be used to better understand ecosystems and identify critical habitat. However, manually reviewing the audio data is very time co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Initializr 0.12.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/24/spring-initializr-0-12-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/24/spring-initializr-0-12-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T14:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Initializr 0.12.0 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 10 fixes, improvements and dependency upgrades.
Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

For full upgrade instructions and new and noteworthy features please see the release notes.

GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LaMDA: Towards Safe, Grounded, and High-Quality Dialog Models for Everything]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/lamda-towards-safe-grounded-and-high.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/lamda-towards-safe-grounded-and-high.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T19:00:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Heng-Tze Cheng, Senior Staff Software Engineer and Romal Thoppilan, Senior Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
Language models are becoming more capable than ever before and are helpful in a variety of tasks — translating one language into another, summarizing a long document into a brief highlight, or answering information-seeking questions. Among these, open-domain dialog, where a model needs to be able to converse about any topic, is probably one of the most difficult, with a wide range of potential applications and open challenges. In addition to producing responses that humans judge as sensible, interesting, and specific to the context, dialog models should adhere to Responsible AI practices, and avoid making factual statements that are not supported by external …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty Enhances Detection of EC2 Instance Credential Exfiltration]]></title>
        <id>515d068b8af84fffa0abe6327c926b5299f1a638</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-guardduty-enhances-detection-of-ec2-instance-credential-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T18:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[This blog post was updated on Jan. 23rd to show how to use imdsv2 instead of imdsv1] Amazon GuardDuty is a threat detection service that continuously monitors for malicious activity and unauthorized behavior to protect your AWS accounts, workloads, and data stored in Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3). Informed by a multitude of public […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.21]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63278</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-01-21/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T09:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.01.21 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.21 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-M1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-3-0-0-m1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-3-0-0-m1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-M1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This milestone starts our exciting journey to the next generation of the Spring Framework and raises our baseline from Java 8 to Java 17. We are planning to release a new milestone of Spring Boot 3.0 every two months. M2 should arrive on March 24 and we are planning on a GA release in late November.

If you are trying an existing application with Spring Boot 3.0 you’ll need to be aware that we’ve migrated all Java EE APIs to their equivalent Jakarta EE variant. For most users, this means you’ll need to replace any javax imports with jakarta. For example, javax.servlet.Filter would be replaced with jakarta.servlet.Filter.

We’re still waiting for a few third-party libraries to release Jakarta EE compatible versions, so not all Spring Boot 2.x features are available with this first milestone. We plan to reintroduce features as and when libraries provide appropriate releases.

Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

If you’re interested in trying this new release, you can easily generate a project from start.spring.io.
Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests. 
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: RedHat's Kate Stanley on the distinction between traditional brokers and Apache Kafka]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/a-bootiful-podcast-redhat-s-kate-stanley-on-the-distinction-between-traditional-brokers-and-apache-kafka</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/a-bootiful-podcast-redhat-s-kate-stanley-on-the-distinction-between-traditional-brokers-and-apache-kafka"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to returning guest RedHat’s Kate Stanley (@KateStanley91) on the distinction between traditional brokers and Apache Kafka.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0-M1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-7-0-m1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-7-0-m1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T19:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0-M1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 111 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Spring GraphQL starter

  
Operating system and Java vendor information in actuator info endpoint

  
Support for RabbitStreamTemplate


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests. 
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul UI Now Supports End-to-End Deployment with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-consul-ui-feature-speeds-setup-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-consul-ui-feature-speeds-setup-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul users can now auto-generate ready-to-apply Terraform configurations to deploy HCP Consul end-to-end with a demo application in less than 20 minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.3 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-6-3-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-6-3-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.3 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 39 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Automation Trends, Questions and Answers]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=41026</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/2022-automation-trends-questions-and-answers/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into our answers for the top-ranked questions from our recent webinar, Looking Back to the Future: 5 Process Automation Trends in 2022.
The post 2022 Automation Trends, Questions and Answers appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevRel Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data JDBC - How Can I Do a Partial Update of an Aggregate Root?]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-data-jdbc-how-can-i-do-a-partial-update-of-an-aggregate-root</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-data-jdbc-how-can-i-do-a-partial-update-of-an-aggregate-root"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T13:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the fourth article of a series about how to tackle various challenges you might encounter when using Spring Data JDBC.
The series consists of:





Spring Data JDBC - How to Use Custom ID Generation.



Spring Data JDBC - How Do I Make Bidirectional Relationships?



Spring Data JDBC - How Do I Implement Caching?



Spring Data JDBC - How Can I Do a Partial Update of an Aggregate Root? (this article)





If you are new to Spring Data JDBC, you should start by reading introduction and this article, which explains the relevance of aggregates in the context of Spring Data JDBC. Trust me. It is important.



Spring Data JDBC is built around the idea of aggregates and repositories.
Repositories are collection-like objects that find, load, save, and delete aggreg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.9 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-5-9-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-5-9-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T11:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.9 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 32 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0 M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/spring-batch-5-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/spring-batch-5-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T23:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who contributed, I am pleased to announce that the first milestone release of Spring Batch 5.0 is available now from https://repo.spring.io/milestone. This first milestone includes a number of major changes such as requiring Java 17+, migrating to Jakarta EE 9 APIs as well as upgrading our dependencies across the portfolio to major versions such as Spring Framework 6.0. For a complete list of changes, please check the change log.

We also took the opportunity of this major version to remove deprecated APIs and fix some issues that require non backward compatible changes. The migration guide contains more details about these changes and provides the upgrade instructions.

As we continue our work on Spring Batch 5, we look forward to your feedback on this first milestone!

Spring Batch Home | Source on GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Adopt a Producer-Consumer Model for HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-adopt-a-producer-consumer-model-for-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-adopt-a-producer-consumer-model-for-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn our best practices and get customer-tested templates that help HashiCorp Vault users adopt efficient producer-consumer models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0.0-M5 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/spring-for-graphql-1-0-0-m5-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/spring-for-graphql-1-0-0-m5-released"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T15:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring for GraphQL 1.0.0-M5 is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

The M5 release is a quick follow-on after the feature-rich M4 release from December. The main goal for M5 was to move the Boot starter out of the Spring GraphQL repository and into Spring Boot proper, ahead of the first Spring Boot 2.7 milestone this Thursday. In addition to that, as always, there was plenty of feedback leading to a number of refinements and fixes.
Spring Boot GraphQL Starter

The GraphQL starter has moved out of the Spring for GraphQL project repository and into the Spring Boot repository, from where it will be made available in the upcoming 2.7.0-M1 release. Here is the GraphQL section in the Spring B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40654</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/camunda-automation-platform-7170-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T15:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the third alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17. This release features the following improvements: Camunda Run improvements 3 Bug Fixes You can download Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17.0 for free or run it with Docker. For a complete list of all improvements, take a look at the release notes. Please also see the list of known issues. If you want to dig in deeper, you can find the source code on GitHub. Camunda Run improvements We are constantly working to get the Camunda Run distro closer to what is offered from our other Camunda distros. The 7.17.0-alpha3 release provides a start to the improvements of the Camunda Run distro. Groovy scripting engine included A large...
The post Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Microsoft Azure - Unified Observability for Spring Boot applications]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/elastic-and-microsoft-azure-unified-observability-for-spring-boot-applications</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/elastic-and-microsoft-azure-unified-observability-for-spring-boot-applications"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Today, we are excited to announce the availability of Elastic integrations for unified observability of Spring Boot applications on Azure. You can seamlessly ship Microsoft Azure Spring Cloud logs and metrics into Elastic, instrument Spring Boot apps, and monitor every step of your cloud journey. And gain a holistic view across Spring Boot applications and other logs and metrics in your cloud and on-premises environments.

Over the past two years, we worked with many enterprise customers to learn about the scenarios they face. Many of these customers have thousands of Spring Boot applications running in on-premises data centers. As they migrate these applications to the cloud, they need to aggregate logs and metrics from these applications and instrument them for applicat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing StylEx: A New Approach for Visual Explanation of Classifiers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/introducing-stylex-new-approach-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/introducing-stylex-new-approach-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Oran Lang and Inbar Mosseri, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Neural networks can perform certain tasks remarkably well, but understanding how they reach their decisions — e.g., identifying which signals in an image cause a model to determine it to be of one class and not another —  is often a mystery. Explaining a neural model’s decision process may have high social impact in certain areas, such as analysis of medical images and autonomous driving, where human oversight is critical. These insights can also be helpful in guiding health care providers, revealing model biases, providing support for downstream decision makers, and even aiding scientific discovery. 
Previous approaches for visual explanations of classifiers, such as attention maps (e.g., Grad-CAM), highlight whic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - January 18th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/18/this-week-in-spring-january-18th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/18/this-week-in-spring-january-18th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another jam-packed, fun-filled, rock’em sock’em installment of This Week in Spring! It’s the 18th of January and I’m feelin’ great because I just got back from a three-day weekend. Here in the US, we celebrated on Monday the life of the good Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., a civil rights activist who advanced the plight of African American civil rights. Dr. King is another one of my favorite doctors, along with Drs. Syer, Strange, Who, Subramaniam, and Pollack.

How’re you? We’ve got a lot to cover so let’s get to it! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud Data Flow legend Sabby Anandan

  
First Spring Data 2022.0.0 and 2021.2.0 milestones released

  
Michael Coté on Twitter

  
the Oracle Java team’s Sharat Chander (@sharat_chandler) recently took time to thank me, along with my heroes and Bootiful Podcast guests Dr. Venkat Subramaniam (@venkat_s) and Matt Raible (@mraible), for our contributions to the Java ecosystem. I want to return the favor, Sharat, here on this very large platform: thank YOU for all you’ve done for the community. You’re an inspiration.

  
Spring Data 2021.1 SR1 and 2021.0 SR8 released

  
Spring Framework 6.0.0-M2 and 5.3.15 available now

  
Spring REST Docs 2.0.6.RELEASE

  
Spring REST Docs 3.0.0-M1

  
Spring Security 6.0.0-M1 and 5.7.0-M1 available now

  
An update about the rollout of the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK on Azure Platform Services]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 65 – @Azure Durable Functions For Automation With @LBugnion]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63268</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-65-azure-durable-functions-for-automation-with-lbugnion/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T16:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 65 – @Azure Durable Functions For Automation With @LBugnion appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: How Can I Complete a Service Task via the REST API?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40667</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/qa-how-can-i-complete-a-service-task-via-the-rest-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let us help you make your external client claim a task, complete it, and return control to your Camunda process.
The post Q&A: How Can I Complete a Service Task via the REST API? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring REST Docs 3.0.0-M1]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/17/spring-rest-docs-3-0-0-m1</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/17/spring-rest-docs-3-0-0-m1"/>
        <updated>2022-01-17T17:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring REST Docs 3.0.0-M1 is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This initial 3.0 milestone contains 13 enhancements, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. It covers the baseline upgrade efforts, in particular requiring JDK 17 and Spring Framework 6 and migrating to the Jakarta EE 9 APIs as announced in this blog post.

Please note that support for REST Assured has been removed temporarily as it is not yet compatible with Jakarta EE 9. We hope to reinstate support in a subsequent milestone prior to 3.0’s release towards the end of this year.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safely Upgrade Your Pipelines from Azure DevOps Server 2019 to Server 2020]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63226</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/safely-upgrade-from-azure-devops-server-2019-to-server-2020/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-17T16:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2019 and 2020 use two different models for retaining builds. In Azure DevOps Server 2019, users configure retention settings for each pipeline. Organization-level defaults are applied if a pipeline is not explicitly configured for retention. Builds that are retained indefinitely or by releases are marked and handled using a common bit in the build record.
The post Safely Upgrade Your Pipelines from Azure DevOps Server 2019 to Server 2020 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silviu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.0.0-M1 and 5.7.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/17/spring-security-6-0-0-m1-and-5-7-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/17/spring-security-6-0-0-m1-and-5-7-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-01-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 6.0.0-M1 and 5.7.0-M1 are available now.



This initial 6.0 milestone covers the baseline upgrade efforts, in particular requiring JDK 17+ and migrating to the Jakarta EE 9 APIs, required by Spring Framework 6, as announced in this blog post.



For the release changes, please refer to the releases page.



Stay tuned for the announcement of Spring Boot 3.0.0-M1 this week!



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Route by Task for Efficient Inference]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/learning-to-route-by-task-for-efficient.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/learning-to-route-by-task-for-efficient.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T19:10:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sneha Kudugunta, Research Software Engineer and Orhan Firat, Research Scientist, Google Research   
Scaling large language models has resulted in significant quality improvements in natural language understanding (T5), generation (GPT-3) and multilingual neural machine translation (M4). One common approach to building a larger model is to increase the depth (number of layers) and width (layer dimensionality), simply enlarging existing dimensions of the network. Such dense models take an input sequence (divided into smaller components, called tokens) and pass every token through the full network, activating every layer and parameter. While these large, dense models have achieved state-of-the-art results on multiple natural language processing (NLP) tasks, their training cost incre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s Security and Compliance Program Takes Another Step Forward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-s-security-and-compliance-program-takes-another-step-forward</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-s-security-and-compliance-program-takes-another-step-forward"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp has renewed its SOC II Type II report for HCP Vault and HCP Consul, and obtained ISO 27017 and ISO 27018 certificates for its cloud products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Zeebe’s gRPC Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40630</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/securing-zeebes-grpc-communication/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curious about security between components? Take a look at Zeebe’s communication channels and how to secure them in a production deployment.
The post Securing Zeebe’s gRPC Communication appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.14]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63237</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-01-14/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T09:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.01.14 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.14 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-Diagnosis and Remediation in Netflix Data Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5bcc52d853d1</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/auto-diagnosis-and-remediation-in-netflix-data-platform-5bcc52d853d1?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T04:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Vikram Srivastava and Marcelo Mayworm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.7 Reimagines UI and Extends Deployment Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-7-reimagines-ui-and-extends-deployment-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-7-reimagines-ui-and-extends-deployment-workflows"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.7 focuses on enhancing user experience with a significant UI redesign, improved support for more complex deployment workflows, and extensible CI integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Vision with Sparse Mixture of Experts]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/scaling-vision-with-sparse-mixture-of.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/scaling-vision-with-sparse-mixture-of.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T18:04:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Carlos Riquelme, Research Scientist and Joan Puigcerver, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
Advances in deep learning over the last few decades have been driven by a few key elements. With a small number of simple but flexible mechanisms (i.e., inductive biases such as convolutions or sequence attention), increasingly large datasets, and more specialized hardware, neural networks can now achieve impressive results on a wide range of tasks, such as image classification, machine translation, and protein folding prediction. 
However, the use of large models and datasets comes at the expense of significant computational requirements. Yet, recent works suggest that large model sizes might be necessary for strong generalization and robustness, so training large models whil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第201話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496701320583</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496701320583"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Azure AD Identity with HashiCorp Vault — Part 2: Vault OIDC Auth Method]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/integrating-azure-ad-identity-with-hashicorp-vault-part-2-vault-oidc-auth-method</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/integrating-azure-ad-identity-with-hashicorp-vault-part-2-vault-oidc-auth-method"/>
        <updated>2022-01-12T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to configure HashiCorp Vault’s OIDC auth method to use Azure as an identity provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New AWS Console Home Experience]]></title>
        <id>0cf5407d49bfeca70f467a351f1a027b407f2638</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/a-new-aws-console-home-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-12T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are reading this blog, there is a high chance you frequently use the AWS Management Console. I taught AWS classes for years. During classes, students’ first hands-on experience with the AWS Cloud happened on the console, and I bet yours did too. Until today, the home page of the console showed your most […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 64 – Building SOC Efficiency with @Azure Sentinel with @rodtrent]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63217</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-64-building-soc-efficiency-with-azure-sentinel-with-rodtrent/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-12T16:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 64 – Building SOC Efficiency with @Azure Sentinel with @rodtrent appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Processes for Camunda Cloud and Zeebe]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40582</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/testing-processes-for-camunda-cloud-and-zeebe/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T21:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Zeebe-Process-Test featured in the 1.3.0 release. Learn how you can unit test BPMN processes for Camunda Cloud and Zeebe.
The post Testing Processes for Camunda Cloud and Zeebe appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research: Themes from 2021 and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/google-research-themes-from-2021-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/google-research-themes-from-2021-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T19:01:00.010Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeff Dean, Senior Fellow and SVP of Google Research, on behalf of the entire Google Research community
Over the last several decades, I've witnessed a lot of change in the fields of machine learning (ML) and computer science. Early approaches, which often fell short, eventually gave rise to modern approaches that have been very successful. Following that long-arc pattern of progress, I think we'll see a number of exciting advances over the next several years, advances that will ultimately benefit the lives of billions of people with greater impact than ever before. In this post, I’ll highlight five areas where ML is poised to have such impact. For each, I’ll discuss related research (mostly from 2021) and the directions and progress we’ll likely see in the next few years. 
      …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experimentation is a major focus of Data Science across Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f67923f8e985</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/experimentation-is-a-major-focus-of-data-science-across-netflix-f67923f8e985?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T16:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Tingley with Wenjing Zheng, Simon Ejdemyr, Stephanie Lane, Colin McFarland, Andy Rhines, Sophia Liu, Mihir Tendulkar, Kevin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cawemo Enterprise (On-Premises) 1.9.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40505</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/cawemo-enterprise-on-premises-1-9-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re happy to announce the 1.9.0 release of Cawemo Enterprise On-Premises. If you’re not yet a Camunda customer, sign up for a free trial.
The post Cawemo Enterprise (On-Premises) 1.9.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cawemo Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 Hpc6a Instance Optimized for High Performance Computing]]></title>
        <id>0a641a338fac9c602c3f4814b6c048cf09fa4740</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-hpc6a-instance-optimized-for-high-performance-computing/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T00:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Performance Computing (HPC) allows scientists and engineers to solve complex, compute-intensive problems such as computational fluid dynamics (CFD), weather forecasting, and genomics. HPC applications typically require instances with high memory bandwidth, a low latency, high bandwidth network interconnect and access to a fast parallel file system. Many customers have turned to AWS to run […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.07]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63171</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-01-07/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T11:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.01.07 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.07 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DiscoverDev - curated engineering articles for Fri, 07 Jan 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://discoverdev.io/archive/2022-01-07.html</id>
        <link href="http://discoverdev.io/archive/2022-01-07.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shops on Facebook and Instagram: Understanding relationships between products to improve buyer and seller experience 
 
          
            
 General and Scalable Parallelization for Neural Networks 
 
          
            
 Video: Understanding Queuing Theory and Software Performance 
 
          
            
 Snaring the Bad Folks 
 
          
            
 Deep Learning vs Machine Learning Challenger Models for Default Risk with Explainability]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service Adds IPv6 Networking]]></title>
        <id>a25768b407b6c7537fa13a1b030520c8673d316b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-elastic-kubernetes-service-adds-ipv6-networking/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T17:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can deploy applications that use IPv6 address space on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS). Many of our customers are standardizing Kubernetes as their compute infrastructure platform for cloud and on-premises applications. Amazon EKS makes it easy to deploy containerized workloads. It provides highly available clusters and automates tasks such as patching, node […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp 2021 Year in Review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2021-year-in-review</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2021-year-in-review"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look back at some of the most important moments of a very eventful 2021 for HashiCorp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>