<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-09-04T02:20:16.162Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-04T02:20:16.162Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cultural distress (and consumerism)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43675</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/709325620/0/sethsblog~Cultural-distress-and-consumerism/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-03T08:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For decades, marketers (and politicians) have been working to amplify cultural distress, a hack on our emotions. Not the tragic emotional distress of being unable to care for your kids, find a place to live or deal with trauma, but the invented cultural distress of modern industrialized societies. This is the easily created shame of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · August 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-02-release-radar-aug-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-02-release-radar-aug-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T23:13:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We&#8217;ve been gearing up to launch GitHub Universe 2022 and our community has been launching cool projects left right and center.  These projects include everything from world-changing technology to developer tooling, and weekend hobbies. Here are some of the open source projects that released major version updates this August. Read more about these projects in [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git&#8217;s database internals V: scalability]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-02-gits-database-internals-v-scalability/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-02-gits-database-internals-v-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T13:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fifth and final part of our blog series exploring Git's internals shows several strategies for scaling your Git repositories that match related database sharding techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2.2 Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=276558</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/09/phpstorm-2022-2-2-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T10:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a preview available of PhpStorm 2022.2.2, the upcoming minor release of PhpStorm. It brings a number of bug fixes and quality-of-life improvements. Here are the most notable changes and bug fixes in this build: Added: support for remote interpreters for Rector (WI-66504) Fixed: ESLint 8.23 fatal error (WEB-57089) Fixed: control + click in VSC […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The last minute]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42639</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/709174952/0/sethsblog~The-last-minute/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you do anything at the last minute that takes more than a minute, you’re not organizing your project properly. The last minute is not a buffer zone, nor is it the moment to double-check your work. The last minute is simply sixty seconds to enjoy and to remind yourself that you successfully planned ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Internet Interaction]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2667/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2667/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/first_internet_interaction.png" title="To that stranger on the KOOL Tree House chat room, I gotta hand it to you: You were, ultimately, not wrong." alt="To that stranger on the KOOL Tree House chat room, I gotta hand it to you: You were, ultimately, not wrong." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing COSI: Object Storage Management using Kubernetes APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/02/cosi-kubernetes-object-storage-management/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/02/cosi-kubernetes-object-storage-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Sidhartha Mani (Minio, Inc)
This article introduces the Container Object Storage Interface (COSI), a standard for provisioning and consuming object storage in Kubernetes. It is an alpha feature in Kubernetes v1.25.
File and block storage are treated as first class citizens in the Kubernetes ecosystem via Container Storage Interface (CSI). Workloads using CSI volumes enjoy the benefits of portability across vendors and across Kubernetes clusters without the need to change application manifests. An equivalent standard does not exist for Object storage.
Object storage has been rising in popularity in recent years as an alternative form of storage to filesystems and block devices. Object storage paradigm promotes disaggregation of compute and storage. This is done by making data avail…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Standardize Cryptography in the Enterprise with HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-standardize-cryptography-in-the-enterprise-with-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-standardize-cryptography-in-the-enterprise-with-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how centralizing encryption tools in a self-service platform for developers lowers the cost of ownership, centralizes best practices, and makes auditing easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: introducing the new, larger GitHub-hosted runners beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-01-github-actions-introducing-the-new-larger-github-hosted-runners-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-01-github-actions-introducing-the-new-larger-github-hosted-runners-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T16:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now your team can spend less time managing infrastructure and more time writing code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git&#8217;s database internals IV: distributed synchronization]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-01-gits-database-internals-iv-distributed-synchronization/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-01-gits-database-internals-iv-distributed-synchronization/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T13:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're examining Git’s internals to help make your engineering system more efficient. This post views Git as a distributed database and looks into its synchronization techniques, specifically ‘git fetch’ and ‘git push’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t blame the mouse]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41723</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/709012278/0/sethsblog~Dont-blame-the-mouse/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you leave your cheese out and the mouse eats it, the mouse is simply being a mouse. While it might be nice if the mouse didn’t wreck your dinner, that’s his job. Often, we show up with our cheese and then become indignant when the mouse does what mice do. “Oh, you’re a mouse.” […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Dr. Kris De Volder on Spring Tools, VS Code, and so much more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/01/a-bootiful-podcast-dr-kris-de-volder-on-spring-tools-vs-code-and-so-much-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/01/a-bootiful-podcast-dr-kris-de-volder-on-spring-tools-vs-code-and-so-much-more"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode Josh Long (@starbuxman)  talks to Dr. Kris De Volder, a longtime member of the Spring Tools team, about all the cool stuff he’s worked on and is going to work on. And then we get knee deep into a discussion around building IDE integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud price change to create alignment across purchasing options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-price-change-to-create-alignment-across-purchasing-options</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-price-change-to-create-alignment-across-purchasing-options"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud pricing is changing to simplify and bring parity across Direct and Marketplace prices. Customers will pay the same price for Elastic Cloud whether they purchase from Elastic or their preferred Cloud Service Provider’s marketplace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanda Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud price change to create alignment across purchasing options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-price-change-to-create-alignment-across-purchasing-options</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-price-change-to-create-alignment-across-purchasing-options"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Effective November 1, 2022 Elastic is making changes to Elastic Cloud pricing to simplify and bring parity across Direct and Marketplace prices. Moving forward, customers will pay the same price for Elastic Cloud whether they purchase directly from Elastic or through their preferred Cloud Service Provider’s marketplace. Thanks to our close partnership with the cloud providers over the last few years, we've significantly reduced the marketplace fees our customers have been paying and are now able to align pricing across all purchasing avenues.

Many customers prefer to use their pre-committed cloud marketplace spend to purchase software as it helps shorten the purchase cycle and accelerate onboarding. With this change, when customers purchase an Elastic subscription using their pre-committed cloud provider marketplace spend, they will pay the same price they would pay Elastic directly.

As a result of this change, some customers will see a small price decrease, while others may see slightly higher prices (up to 4%), but many will see little or no change. Elastic has directly communicated with all impacted customers. The price change for impacted customers will be reflected in the November billing statement made available in December 2022.

In addition, to help customers optimize their Elastic deployment and reduce costs, we’ve added a number of features. These include simple, no-downtime migration capability to help users adopt the most price-performant instance type for their use case, as well as Searchable Snapshots, which enables users to leverage cost-effective cloud-based object storage. Please see our blog post, Top 5 ways to optimize your Elastic Cloud costs. 

We encourage you to reach out to your account team if you have questions. If you are unsure who your account representative is, you can Contact Elastic. For information on Elastic pricing, you can visit our pricing page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanda Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022.2 Updates of All JetBrains IDEs and .NET Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=276166</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/blog/2022/08/31/2022-2-updates-of-all-jetbrains-ides-and-net-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T20:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post offers a general overview of the major changes you will find in the 2022.2 releases of all JetBrains IDEs and .NET tools. Check out the summary below, and follow the links to learn about the updates in more detail. IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 includes multiple quality improvements to the remote development functionality, making […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Toporov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Patent Phrase Similarity Dataset]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/announcing-patent-phrase-similarity.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/announcing-patent-phrase-similarity.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted Grigor Aslanyan, Software Engineer, Google 
Patent documents typically use legal and highly technical language, with context-dependent terms that may have meanings quite different from colloquial usage and even between different documents. The process of using traditional patent search methods (e.g., keyword searching) to search through the corpus of over one hundred million patent documents can be tedious and result in many missed results due to the broad and non-standard language used. For example, a "soccer ball" may be described as a "spherical recreation device", "inflatable sportsball" or "ball for ball game". Additionally, the language used in some patent documents may obfuscate terms to their advantage, so more powerful natural language processing (NLP) and semantic similari…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 209 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65658</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-209-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T16:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We fixed a bunch more issues for New Boards Hub in sprint 209. Here is a list of the items that have been resolved.
Issue
OnBlur instead of onChange
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 209 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What you can expect at GitHub Universe 2022: cloud, security, community, and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-31-what-you-can-expect-at-github-universe-2022-cloud-security-community-and-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-31-what-you-can-expect-at-github-universe-2022-cloud-security-community-and-ai/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T16:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Register now to attend GitHub Universe virtually or in-person at the Yerba Buena Center for the Arts in San Francisco on November 9-10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git&#8217;s database internals III: file history queries]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-31-gits-database-internals-iii-file-history-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-31-gits-database-internals-iii-file-history-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git’s file history queries use specialized algorithms that are tailored to common developer behavior. Level up your history spelunking skills by learning how different history modes behave and which ones to use when you need them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation in banking: 6 considerations for digital transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60932</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/automation-in-banking-6-considerations-for-digital-transformation/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation and banking have been two peas in a technological pod since the 1934 introduction of the IBM ® 801 Bank Proof machine, a check sorting machine. Later innovations like the automated teller machine and the debit card continued the banking automation trend of digitizing analog processes. With the advent of the internet, machine learning, and cloud computing, there are still so many automation opportunities to explore.  For instance, using AI for risk assessment, automating the classification of unstructured data, or reducing manual work can help you increase the agility of the overall organization, improve the customer experience, and get new features and products to market much more rapidly. We’re going to explore six concepts to keep in mind for...
The post Automation in banking: 6 considerations for digital transformation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Algorithms and Data Structures on JetBrains Academy]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=276369</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/08/31/computer-algorithms-and-data-structures-on-jetbrains-academy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T12:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost everything in programming has to do with data: collecting, storing, transforming, validating, analyzing, and so on. A developer needs to know how to perform these operations efficiently. Let’s say you’re building a dictionary app. If the app takes a long time to find a word, and can’t store hundreds or thousands of different words, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The advice gap]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43637</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/708807568/0/sethsblog~The-advice-gap/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T08:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wisdom and good advice are everywhere, now more than ever. And yet, despite the abundance that’s available, people often make errors in job searches, product launches, or even planning a party. There might be three reasons: The advice might not be good, or it doesn’t appear to be valid. It’s hard to tell good advice […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price Reduction - Azure Spring Apps does more, costs less!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/31/price-reduction-azure-spring-apps-does-more-costs-less</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/31/price-reduction-azure-spring-apps-does-more-costs-less"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We believe in providing the most innovative cloud offerings at incredibly competitive prices. As we operate Azure Spring Apps, we continue to build efficiencies and economies of scale. We are passing those efficiencies to you. 

Many customers have asked us to lower the size of the base unit to make it easier to get started and accommodate smaller projects. 
Announcing Price and Base Unit Reduction

Effective September 1st, we are reducing the base unit of Azure Spring Apps Standard and Enterprise to 6 vCPUs and 12 GB of Memory. And reducing the overage prices for vCPU and Memory. 


New Monthly FREE Grants

Furthermore, to help you get started, effective mid-September, we are offering monthly FREE grants – 50 vCPU hours and 100 Memory GB hours. 

Let’s look at a few examples: 

Note…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank BRI mitigates cybercrime and financial risk with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bank-bri-mitigates-cybercrime-and-financial-risk-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bank-bri-mitigates-cybercrime-and-financial-risk-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bank BRI is one of the largest banks in Indonesia and Southeast Asia. As Bank BRI continues to grow its ecosystem, the number of assets it must defend against cybercrime only increases. Learn how the organization set out to find new tools to protect its complex network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank BRI mitigates cybercrime and financial risk with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bank-bri-mitigates-cybercrime-and-financial-risk-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bank-bri-mitigates-cybercrime-and-financial-risk-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Bank BRI is one of the largest banks in Indonesia and Southeast Asia, providing end-to-end financial solutions to more than 130 million customers. As part of its core mission, the bank has a particular focus on empowering microbusinesses and advancing the financial inclusiveness of the countries it serves.

With such a wide range of customers and partners, Bank BRI has created an extensive network across the region. Its long history within the financial sector also means that it has an array of IT assets and tools across the bank, which consist of legacy systems, cutting-edge solutions, and everything in between. In addition, the company’s tremendous size and heterogeneity have created many unique challenges, including difficulty obtaining complete visibility into all of the bank’s syste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Universe Price Tiers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2666/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2666/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/universe_price_tiers.png" title="In Universe Pro®™ the laws of physics remain unchanged under time reversal, to maintain backward compatibility." alt="In Universe Pro®™ the laws of physics remain unchanged under time reversal, to maintain backward compatibility." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: cgroup v2 graduates to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/31/cgroupv2-ga-1-25/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/31/cgroupv2-ga-1-25/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors:: David Porter (Google), Mrunal Patel (Red Hat)
Kubernetes 1.25 brings cgroup v2 to GA (general availability), letting the
kubelet use the latest container resource
management capabilities.
What are cgroups?
Effective resource management is a
critical aspect of Kubernetes. This involves managing the finite resources in
your nodes, such as CPU, memory, and storage.
cgroups are a Linux kernel capability that establish resource management
functionality like limiting CPU usage or setting memory limits for running
processes.
When you use the resource management capabilities in Kubernetes, such as configuring
requests and limits for Pods and containers,
Kubernetes uses cgroups to enforce your resource requests and limits.
The Linux kernel offers two versions of cgroups: cgroup v1 and cgr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Live Webinar: Working With SQL and Databases in WebStorm]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=276104</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/08/live-webinar-working-with-sql-and-databases-in-webstorm/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T20:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us Friday, September 16, 10 am – 11 am (EDT) / 4 pm – 5 pm (CEST), for our free live webinar, Working With SQL and Databases in WebStorm. Our speaker will be Maxim Sobolevskiy, a fellow JetBrainer and the Team Lead of DataGrip, our database IDE. In this webinar, we’ll show the basics […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Aganezova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and VMware Announce VMware Cloud on AWS integration with Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP]]></title>
        <id>fdb3e5851333d5a35feee69841bc3b0de7ed14eb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-and-vmware-announce-vmware-cloud-on-aws-integration-with-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our customers are looking for cost-effective ways to continue to migrate their applications to the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is a fully managed, jointly engineered service that brings VMware’s enterprise-class, software-defined data center architecture to the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS offers our customers the ability to run applications across operationally consistent VMware vSphere-based […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git&#8217;s database internals II: commit history queries]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-30-gits-database-internals-ii-commit-history-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-30-gits-database-internals-ii-commit-history-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores Git commit history as a database where ‘git log’ is the query language. Learn about Git’s custom query index – the commit-graph file – and how to make sure it's enabled in your repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can a Service Mesh Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-can-a-service-mesh-do</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-can-a-service-mesh-do"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A service mesh is a force multiplier that can do everything from service discovery to zero trust security, load balancing, multi-cloud connectivity, automation, and north-south traffic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New on JetBrains Marketplace: Automated Follow-Up Emails for Plugin Trial Users]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=276197</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2022/08/follow-up-emails-for-plugin-trial-users/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T15:29:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve added a new way for plugin vendors to maintain an additional point of contact with their users. Plugin trial users now receive automated follow-up emails through JetBrains Marketplace. This includes a welcome email, a reminder about the trial period’s end date, and a follow-up email asking users to rate the plugin if they decided […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is committed to the success of Java developers]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/microsoft-is-committed-to-the-success-of-java-developers</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/microsoft-is-committed-to-the-success-of-java-developers"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! This is a guest post from our friend Julia Liuson, President, Developer Division, Microsoft

As a company, we are committed to making Java developers as efficient and productive as possible. This commitment means empowering you to use any tool, framework, and application server on any operating system. Wherever you are with Java, Microsoft supports your workload with an abundance of choices and with a wide range of developer tools and services. 
Code, Deploy, and Scale Java Your Way

Today, more and more Java developers are looking at how they can bring their existing Java applications to the cloud—or how to build new cloud-native applications. We have been working to make it easier for you to bring your Java applications to the cloud using the tools and frameworks you l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BPMN and DMN Modeler for Atlassian Confluence]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60833</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/bpmn-and-dmn-modeler-for-atlassian-confluence/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Document business processes with the BPMN and DMN Modeler for Confluence - two plugins available for free on the Atlassian Marketplace.
The post BPMN and DMN Modeler for Atlassian Confluence appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactor code to use new C# language features]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=265563</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/08/30/refactor-code-to-use-new-c-language-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T12:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modernizing, or migrating to modern language features in any language can help make code more readable, efficient and secure. In this blog post, we’ll look at ways to modernize code so it’s better than before.   Take advantage of modern language features Why refactor code just to modernize it? Why fix it if it’s not broken? […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unbeatable vs perfect]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42592</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/708536736/0/sethsblog~Unbeatable-vs-perfect/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T08:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has killed more than 200 projects over the last few decades. They fail all the time. More than once a month they shut down a business that frightened the competition and seduced consumers. That’s part of the recipe for becoming an unbeatable behemoth. Fail a lot. Institutions like Western Union and A & P […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 30th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/this-week-in-spring-august-30th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/this-week-in-spring-august-30th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How are you? How’re you doin’ this fine tuesday morning? I’m doing well, of course, because this week VMware’s tentpole show - VMware Explore - is happening not even a mile from my home, here in San Francisco! And this is just the first one - there’ll be another show, my favorite show, in December: SpringOne 2022! I sure hope you’ve registered and that we’ll see you there! 

Indeed, I’ve got a lunch to get to, so let’s get this this week’s wrapup done a little more quickly: without further ado….


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert

  
Creating a custom Spring Cloud Gateway Filter

  
Feign Client Exception Handling

  
Kai Tödter has just announced version 1.6.0 of JSON:API for Spring HATEOAS

  
Multitenancy With Spring Data JPA

  
PKCE Support for Secret Clients with Spring Security

  
Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is available now!

  
Swagger: Specify Two Responses with the Same Response Code

  
Are you building Spring Apps? Join us to learn how to build, deploy and operate Spring Apps at scale.

  
So, here is VMware’s stack for building a platform on the platform as kubernetes, the Tanzu Application Platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Open–AWS Region in the United Arab Emirates (UAE)]]></title>
        <id>abade96b96022cbe9580a09867b67fafe3511c48</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-aws-region-in-the-united-arab-emirates-uae/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T06:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Region in the United Arab Emirates is now open. The official name is Middle East (UAE), and the API name is me-central-1. You can start using it today to deploy workloads and store your data in the United Arab Emirates. The AWS Middle East (UAE) Region is the second Region in the Middle […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Elastic Maps to make public datasets observable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-use-elastic-maps-to-make-public-datasets-observable</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-use-elastic-maps-to-make-public-datasets-observable"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a growing trend among many countries to publish their data as open datasets that are available to the public. These curated datasets are an excellent resource for developers looking to create a demo set for their applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing <i>Elastic Insights</i> magazine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-insights-magazine</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-insights-magazine"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Volume 1 of Elastic Insights, a new digital magazine from Elastic that covers the most pressing technology matters facing digital leaders today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.4.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.4.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.4.1 over the previous versions in 8.4.x.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
8.4.1 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Version 8.4.1 fixes a Kibana issue where any 8.3.x cluster, which contains a currently snoozed rule, will fail to upgrade with a saved object migration failure. This does not apply to indefinite snooze or mute, only to on-demand snooze (i.e., snooze for 1 hour).
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Cote</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Elastic Maps to make public datasets observable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-use-elastic-maps-to-make-public-datasets-observable</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-use-elastic-maps-to-make-public-datasets-observable"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
There’s a growing trend among many countries to publish their data (for example, the number and location of bicycles that have been stolen in Berlin) as open datasets that are available to the public. These curated datasets are an excellent resource for developers looking to create a demo set for their applications.

In this post, we’ll take the example of Berlin’s bicycle theft database to walk through how you can use Elastic Maps to make visual dashboards and maps of publicly available data as demos in your applications.
The dataset
First grab yourself a copy of the CSV from Fahrraddiebstahl in Berlin | Offene Daten Berlin. This is irregularly updated. In this blog, I won’t cover how to retrieve this document regularly and send it to Elasticsearch. If you want to do something like that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing <i>Elastic Insights</i> magazine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-insights-magazine</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-insights-magazine"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Download Volume 1 today!

Elastic today launched Elastic Insights, a new digital magazine for technology leaders about how to better drive results that matter for your organization.  

The theme of this issue is “The Future of Unstructured Data.” This report examines how leaders create growth, resilience, and order from chaos with a set of solutions and processes. We focus on the impact of search-powered technologies to help businesses achieve the outcomes they expect from cloud-driven digital transformation.

“Almost 90% of all the data that matters to any given enterprise is unstructured, according to IDC,” writes Rick Laner, Elastic’s Chief Customer Officer and the guest editor of this debut issue.

“Thinking about the hundreds of technology leaders that I’ve advised, that means that without the right processes and technology, they’d only have a view into 10% of their company,” he writes. “No one can make smart decisions that way.”

Search-powered technologies enable the search of data across multiple sources such as websites, applications, databases, and hybrid cloud environments, according to a study conducted by Forrester Consulting, commissioned by Elastic. 

Contributor and noted tech writer Rusty Weston highlights the impact of search-powered technology in our feature article. Additional articles featuring advice and interviews from our expert contributor network cover digital transformation, customer experience, cybersecurity, and observability challenges that digital business leaders have faced and overcome. 

Elastic Insights will be published quarterly, encompassing the latest research and insights that Elastic’s partners, customers, and Elasticians have to offer. Be sure to download this issue to be informed of future releases.

Get your copy of Elastic Insights today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.4.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Cote</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 29, 2022]]></title>
        <id>d79ee60a7a83272276a7f3bd52c297b82f87c603</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-29-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T19:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve just returned from data and machine learning (ML) conferences in Los Angeles and San Francisco, California. It’s been great to chat with customers and developers about the latest technology trends and use cases. This past week has also been packed with launches at AWS. Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing InfiniTime, Open-source Firmware for the PineTime Smartwatch]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=276068</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/08/developing-infinitime-open-source-firmware-for-the-pinetime-smartwatch/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T16:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are going to talk to Jean-François (JF) Milants, the main contributor to the InfiniTime project, open-source firmware for the Pine64 PineTime smartwatch. Hi Jean-François, can you please tell us about the InfiniTime project? What is it about in a nutshell? How did it get started? InfiniTime is open-source firmware for the PineTime smartwatch. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refresh Secrets for Kubernetes Applications with Vault Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/refresh-secrets-for-kubernetes-applications-with-vault-agent</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/refresh-secrets-for-kubernetes-applications-with-vault-agent"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the system signal and live reload methods for updating Kubernetes applications when secrets change. See an example via a Spring Boot application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA Conf – Celebrating the developer community]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=275974</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/08/intellij-idea-conf-celebrating-the-developer-community/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our intention with IntelliJ IDEA Conf is to celebrate the developer community and its desire to learn and improve everyday. We invite you to join us for this free online conference and learn from industry leaders and experts on September 29–30, 2022. Learn about a variety of topics, like Core Java, Kotlin, Spring, Kubernetes, JUnit, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mala Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git&#8217;s database internals I: packed object store]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-29-gits-database-internals-i-packed-object-store/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-29-gits-database-internals-i-packed-object-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog series will examine Git’s internals to help make your engineering system more efficient. Part I discusses how Git stores its data in packfiles using custom compression techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Red Hat OpenShift - The Easy Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/monitoring-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-red-hat-openshift-the-easy-way</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/monitoring-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-red-hat-openshift-the-easy-way"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform enables teams and organizations to drive their automation from across the cloud and on-premise, keeping Ansible Automation Platform healthy with the ability to monitor key metrics becomes paramount.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“How can I help?”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40863</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/708414432/0/sethsblog~How-can-I-help/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T09:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a simple question that can open doors. But it also creates tension. The person you’re seeking to connect with might not want to believe that help is possible. There’s a solace that comes from being really and truly stuck, and hope might not be on their agenda. Or there might be resistance to thinking […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability helps monitor your Azure workloads on the new Arm-based VMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/microsoft-azure-arm-virtual-machines-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/microsoft-azure-arm-virtual-machines-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The launch of Azure’s new Arm-based virtual machines (VMs) built on Ampere Altra processors brings more flexibility and choice to Azure customers around the world. You can deploy Elastic Observability (available on Azure Marketplace) to monitor and manage your cloud applications built on these new VMs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugo Sangiorgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability helps monitor your Azure workloads on the new Arm-based VMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/microsoft-azure-arm-virtual-machines-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/microsoft-azure-arm-virtual-machines-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Microsoft Azure’s recently launched new Azure Virtual Machines (VMs) feature the Ampere Altra Arm-based processor. These new VMs are engineered to efficiently run horizontally scalable workloads such as web servers, application servers, and open source databases. They deliver excellent price-performance and represent an important addition to Microsoft Azure's portfolio of instance types.

Elastic Observability can give you a holistic view of your cloud resources as you migrate your workloads to the new Arm architecture. Elastic’s native Azure Integration for Activity Logs, VM and Container Metrics along with Elastic APM allows you to collect logs, metrics, and traces for the Azure platform and applications running on it. Once deployed, you can easily compare the performance between Arm-a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugo Sangiorgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How telecom leaders can use sustainable cybersecurity practices to achieve their ESG goals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-telecom-leaders-can-use-sustainable-cybersecurity-practices-to-achieve-their-esg-goals</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-telecom-leaders-can-use-sustainable-cybersecurity-practices-to-achieve-their-esg-goals"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post-pandemic world is highlighting the telecom industry’s impact on the environment — compelling enough to draw the attention of investors, C-suites, and board members. See where cybersecurity fits into these evolving ESG concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How telecom leaders can use sustainable cybersecurity practices to achieve their ESG goals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-telecom-leaders-can-use-sustainable-cybersecurity-practices-to-achieve-their-esg-goals</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-telecom-leaders-can-use-sustainable-cybersecurity-practices-to-achieve-their-esg-goals"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Cybersecurity and environmental, social, and governance (ESG) investing are growing increasingly connected. As more investors seek to support companies that are committed to ESG initiatives and business practices, the need to secure the data and infrastructure that makes those operations possible — particularly in the telecom industry — will continue to expand.

Below, we’ll explore the many factors influencing the growing relationship between cybersecurity and ESG and how telecom leaders can ensure their organization’s cybersecurity efforts are sustainable as this space evolves.
Cyber risks pose a credible business sustainability threat 
An MSCI study1 published in 2021 revealed that USD1.14 billion of investment in communications is in ESG mutual and exchange-traded funds. The study al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America Songs]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2665/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2665/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/america_songs.png" title="Juraaaassic Park, Juraaaassic Park, God shed his grace on theeeee" alt="Juraaaassic Park, Juraaaassic Park, God shed his grace on theeeee" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: CSI Inline Volumes have graduated to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/29/csi-inline-volumes-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/29/csi-inline-volumes-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jonathan Dobson (Red Hat)
CSI Inline Volumes were introduced as an alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.15 and have been beta since 1.16. We are happy to announce that this feature has graduated to General Availability (GA) status in Kubernetes 1.25.
CSI Inline Volumes are similar to other ephemeral volume types, such as configMap, downwardAPI and secret. The important difference is that the storage is provided by a CSI driver, which allows the use of ephemeral storage provided by third-party vendors. The volume is defined as part of the pod spec and follows the lifecycle of the pod, meaning the volume is created once the pod is scheduled and destroyed when the pod is destroyed.
What's new in 1.25?
There are a couple of new bug fixes related to this feature in 1.25, and the CSIInlineVolum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unprepared, as always]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43632</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/708284394/0/sethsblog~Unprepared-as-always/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technological leaps always take us by surprise. What happens when every visual image ever created can be remixed and expanded? Van Gogh, Superman, or Moses. These link to an open search engine, so your mileage may vary. New software allows anyone to create images simply by typing in a dozen or so words. And software […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisionism]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40856</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/708162724/0/sethsblog~Revisionism/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T08:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two marketing problems when it comes to creating interventions for the public good. The first marketing problem is that when it works we take the intervention for granted. The world doesn’t fall apart, and we don’t notice, because our expectation was that the world (whatever world matters to you) should stay on course. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a custom Spring Cloud Gateway Filter]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/26/creating-a-custom-spring-cloud-gateway-filter</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/26/creating-a-custom-spring-cloud-gateway-filter"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we look into writing a custom extension for Spring Cloud Gateway. Before we get started, let’s go over how Spring Cloud Gateway works:




  
First, a client makes a network request to the Gateway

  
The Gateway is defined with a number of routes, each with Predicates to match the request to the route. For example, you can match on the path segment of the URL or the HTTP method of the request.

  
Once matched, the Gateway executes pre-request logic on each of the filters applied to the route. For example, you might want to add query parameters to your request

  
A proxy filter routes the request to the proxied service

  
The service executes and returns a response

  
The gateway receives the response and executes post-request logic on each filter before return…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What HashiCorp Interns Learned This Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-hashicorp-interns-learned-this-summer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-hashicorp-interns-learned-this-summer"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10 interns in HashiCorp’s Early Career Program share what they learned during their summer with the company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways every company can get started with an open-source software strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-26-3-ways-every-company-can-get-started-with-an-open-source-software-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-26-3-ways-every-company-can-get-started-with-an-open-source-software-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T16:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of software development does not exist without open source. However, to maintain today’s software and create the software of the future, the largest organizations and beneficiaries of open source need to expand their collaboration with the community and help it grow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways to involve your community to improve your programs]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60542</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/3-ways-to-involve-your-community-to-improve-your-programs/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community programs are valuable tools for organizations. But enabling engagement in these programs can be challenging.
The post 3 ways to involve your community to improve your programs appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danielle Andrist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“A good study”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41717</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/708029102/0/sethsblog~A-good-study/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T08:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gatekeepers keep disappearing. When it cost $500,000 to produce a record album, you could assume that it was going to reach some people and not be completely amateurish. Today, many songs in the iTunes store have had exactly one listen. When it cost $5,000,000 to make a video or a film, there was a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webhook for Case Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/webhook-for-case-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/webhook-for-case-management"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 8.4, a new Webhook - Case Management connector was introduced. Learn how to connect the Webhook - Case Management connector with a demo instance of Jira (a third-party case management system) and use it with the Kibana Cases feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steph Milovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webhook for Case Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/webhook-for-case-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/webhook-for-case-management"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In 8.4, a new Webhook - Case Management connector was introduced. The Webhook - Case Management connector uses axios to send POST, PUT, and GET requests to a case management RESTful API web service and integrates with the Kibana Cases feature.


In this blog post, we will demonstrate how to connect the Webhook - Case Management connector with a demo instance of Jira (a third-party case management system) and use it with the Kibana Cases feature. We will refer to the Jira API documentation in order to configure the connector.


Note: If you want to connect with Jira quickly, we recommend using the preconfigured Jira connector.
Step 1. Set up connector
In the Webhook - Case Management connector create flyout, begin by entering a connector Name — for example, Jira Test Connector. Basic auth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steph Milovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Swirls]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2664/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2664/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/cloud_swirls.png" title="'Why did you get into fluid dynamics?' 'Well, SOME planet has to have the coolest clouds, odds are it's not ours, and rockets are slow.'" alt="'Why did you get into fluid dynamics?' 'Well, SOME planet has to have the coolest clouds, odds are it's not ours, and rockets are slow.'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the latest AWS Heroes – August 2022]]></title>
        <id>f94b7ec2837a44f904bb188f134e48c449671094</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-latest-aws-heroes-august-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T18:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global AWS community is filled with passionate builders, eager to learn and explore ways to build better and faster on AWS. Within the AWS community, a select few individuals truly go above and beyond to share their knowledge and inspire others through content creation, event organization, open source contributions, and more. These community leaders […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping your skillset fresh as a developer]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-25-keeping-your-skillset-fresh-as-a-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-25-keeping-your-skillset-fresh-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T17:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’re committing 30 minutes or 3 hours a day to learning, consistency is key. Klint Finley asks 3 tech professionals at different stages in their career for more advice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-Definition Segmentation in Google Meet]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/high-definition-segmentation-in-google.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/high-definition-segmentation-in-google.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tingbo Hou and Juhyun Lee, Software Engineers, Google 
In recent years video conferencing has played an increasingly important role in both work and personal communication for many users. Over the past two years, we have enhanced this experience in Google Meet by introducing privacy-preserving machine learning (ML) powered background features, also known as “virtual green screen”, which allows users to blur their backgrounds or replace them with other images. What is unique about this solution is that it runs directly in the browser without the need to install additional software.  
So far, these ML-powered features have relied on CPU inference made possible by leveraging neural network sparsity, a common solution that works across devices, from entry level computers to high-end …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Fine-Grained Visual Embedding Powered by Amazon QuickSight]]></title>
        <id>a1501b50fea420ead40fcf160e7a0bea82b5b85f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-fine-grained-visual-embedding-powered-by-amazon-quicksight/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T16:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing a new feature, Fine-Grained Visual Embedding Powered by Amazon QuickSight. With this feature, individual visualizations from Amazon QuickSight dashboards can now be embedded in high-traffic webpages and applications. Additionally, this feature enables you to provide rich insights for your end-users where they need them the most, without server or software setup […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools Plugin 2022.8 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=275401</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/08/25/edutools-plugin-2022-8-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T11:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools 2022.8 is here with the ability for course creators to specify the input for output tasks. With a predefined set of inputs and outputs, no extra tests are required to check a learner’s solution. We also improved plugin quality by fixing bugs. You can install the EduTool plugin or update it to the latest […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Git With Jupyter Notebooks in DataSpell]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=274407</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2022/08/how-to-use-git-with-jupyter-notebooks/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T08:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re like me and many other data scientists, you’re more of a casual user of Git and mostly use it to keep track of changes to your notebooks and share them with others. As I tend to work on the same project for months, I am always forgetting Git basics such as how to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jodie Burchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And when we disagree…]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41701</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/707898072/0/sethsblog~And-when-we-disagree/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hallmark of a resilient, productive and sustainable culture is that disagreements aren’t risky. When someone cares enough to make an assertion and show their work, a healthy organization or society takes a look. The alternative is the brittle, closed culture of talking points, loyalty oaths and unquestioned status quo. It might be a neighborhood […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-fellow-java-champion-and-timescaledb-developer-advocate-christoph-engelbert</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-fellow-java-champion-and-timescaledb-developer-advocate-christoph-engelbert"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert (@noctarius2k) about PostgreSQL, Java, time series databases, observability, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Run Tasks Ecosystem Continues to Grow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-run-tasks-ecosystem-continues-to-grow</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-run-tasks-ecosystem-continues-to-grow"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teams can now integrate oak9 and Torq into the Terraform Cloud workflow via run tasks. Plus: A list of integrations now validated to work with Terraform Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Console improvements in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-console-improvements-in-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-console-improvements-in-kibana"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how recent improvements in Kibana Console can boost your productivity in versions 8.1 through 8.4 of the Elastic Stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CJ Cenizal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How personalization pays off for online retailers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-personalization-pays-off-for-online-retailers</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-personalization-pays-off-for-online-retailers"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting data back to customers is key to reaping rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Console improvements in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-console-improvements-in-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/big-console-improvements-in-kibana"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For the past nine months, one of our engineers, Muhammad Ibragimov, has been quietly building new features, fixing bugs, and generally polishing the heck out of Kibana Console. From performance improvements to the ability to leave comments inside request bodies, he and the team have done some incredible work on this app that’s used and loved by so many. Read on to learn how these and other improvements can boost your productivity in versions 8.1 through 8.4 of the Elastic Stack.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt3dc4ca4570bbef66/6304fb60e8e6887097a15861/blog-elastic-kibanaconsole-1.png,blog-elastic-kibanaconsole-1.png,
Major features
There are five sweet new features I’d like to share with you.
1. Send requests to Kibana APIs
In 8.3, we shipped the ability to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CJ Cenizal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How personalization pays off for online retailers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-personalization-pays-off-for-online-retailers</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-personalization-pays-off-for-online-retailers"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The concept of 'know your customer' has been the gold standard in the retail world for decades. The more you understand your customers' needs and desires, and the better you're able to connect with them on a one-to-one basis, the more you can ensure their loyalty.



Thanks to ecommerce, stores can know more about their customers than ever before. Online retailers are awash in data detailing how often shoppers visited their stores, what products they searched for, what they considered, and what they ended up buying.



But making that data connect back to information about customers — through demographics, intent, and browsing history — is still a significant challenge. Stores that master this challenge reap much greater rewards. A June 2022 study by Wakefield Research (sponsored by Elas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.25: Pod Security Admission Controller in Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/25/pod-security-admission-stable/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/25/pod-security-admission-stable/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Tim Allclair (Google), Sam Stoelinga (Google)
The release of Kubernetes v1.25 marks a major milestone for Kubernetes out-of-the-box pod security
controls: Pod Security admission (PSA) graduated to stable, and Pod Security Policy (PSP) has been
removed.
PSP was deprecated in Kubernetes v1.21,
and no longer functions in Kubernetes v1.25 and later.
The Pod Security admission controller replaces PodSecurityPolicy, making it easier to enforce predefined
Pod Security Standards by
simply adding a label to a namespace. The Pod Security Standards are maintained by the K8s
community, which means you automatically get updated security policies whenever new
security-impacting Kubernetes features are introduced.
What’s new since Beta?
Pod Security Admission hasn’t changed much since the Beta i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using ML to Boost Engagement with a Maternal and Child Health Program in India]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/using-ml-to-boost-engagement-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/using-ml-to-boost-engagement-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Aparna Taneja, Software Engineer, and Milind Tambe, Principal Scientist, Google Research, India Research Lab 
The widespread availability of mobile phones has enabled non-profits to deliver critical health information to their beneficiaries in a timely manner. While advanced applications on smartphones allow for richer multimedia content and two-way communication between beneficiaries and health coaches, simpler text and voice messaging services can be effective in disseminating information to large communities, particularly those that are underserved with limited access to information and smartphones. ARMMAN1, one non-profit doing just this, is based in India with the mission of improving maternal and child health outcomes in underserved communities. 
    


Overview of ARMMAN

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning for Budget Constrained Recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6cbc5263a32a</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/reinforcement-learning-for-budget-constrained-recommendations-6cbc5263a32a?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Ehtsham Elahi
with James McInerney, Nathan Kallus, Dario Garcia Garcia and Justin Basilico]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS Support App in Slack to Manage Support Cases]]></title>
        <id>7987abd39e83187889bce5fb0aa7f7f73557375e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-support-app-in-slack-to-manage-support-cases/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatOps speeds up software development and operations by enabling DevOps teams to use chat clients and chatbots to communicate and run tasks. DevOps engineers have increasingly moved their monitoring, system management, continuous integration (CI), and continuous delivery (CD) workflows to chat applications in order to streamline activities in a single place and enable better collaboration […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is available now!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/24/spring-batch-5-0-0-m5-is-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/24/spring-batch-5-0-0-m5-is-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is now available from our milestone repository. The main theme of this milestone is improving testing support in Spring Batch. This post walks through the major changes in this area as well as other changes introduced in this milestone release. For the complete list of changes, see the release notes.
Test utilities configuration updates

Up to version 4.3, the JobLauncherTestUtils used to autowire the job under test with the goal of facilitating the test setup. But what if multiple jobs are defined in the test context? And what if no Job beans are defined at all? So while this autowiring was convenient for most cases, it turned out to cause several issues in the aforementioned situations. In this release, and based on community feedback,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps and CI/CD with automation controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/devops-and-ci/cd-with-automation-controller</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/devops-and-ci/cd-with-automation-controller"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog shares practical examples of using Ansible Automation Platform to accelerate your DevOps journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entity Framework Core and Multiple Database Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=267202</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/08/24/entity-framework-core-and-multiple-database-providers/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T12:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While many software developers would prefer to sell software as a service (SaaS), there’s a market for offering your customers a self-hosted solution tailored to their infrastructure choices. Of course, one essential element of any modern software solution is the database, but in 2022 there are hundreds of battle-tested storage solutions. For example, the Entity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Annotated – August 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=275620</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/08/php-annotated-august-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T10:11:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings everyone! Welcome to the August installment of PHP Annotated, where we’ll catch up on the most interesting things that have happened in the PHP world over the last month, including curated news, articles, tools, and videos. News PHP 8.2 Beta 3 has been released The final beta has been delivered according to schedule. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: PodSecurityPolicy: The Historical Context]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/podsecuritypolicy-the-historical-context/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/podsecuritypolicy-the-historical-context/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mahé Tardy (Quarkslab)
The PodSecurityPolicy (PSP) admission controller has been removed, as of
Kubernetes v1.25. Its deprecation was announced and detailed in the blog post
PodSecurityPolicy Deprecation: Past, Present, and Future,
published for the Kubernetes v1.21 release.
This article aims to provide historical context on the birth and evolution of
PSP, explain why the feature never made it to stable, and show why it was
removed and replaced by Pod Security admission control.
PodSecurityPolicy, like other specialized admission control plugins, provided
fine-grained permissions on specific fields concerning the pod security settings
as a built-in policy API. It acknowledged that cluster administrators and
cluster users are usually not the same people, and that creating workloads …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UVQ: Measuring YouTube's Perceptual Video Quality]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/uvq-measuring-youtubes-perceptual-video.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/uvq-measuring-youtubes-perceptual-video.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T17:02:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yilin Wang, Staff Software Engineer, YouTube and Feng Yang, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research 
Online video sharing platforms, like YouTube, need to understand perceptual video quality (i.e., a user's subjective perception of video quality) in order to better optimize and improve user experience. Video quality assessment (VQA) attempts to build a bridge between video signals and perceptual quality by using objective mathematical models to approximate the subjective opinions of users. Traditional video quality metrics, like peak signal-to-noise ratio (PSNR) and Video Multi-Method Assessment Fusion (VMAF), are reference-based and focus on the relative difference between the target and reference videos. Such metrics, which work best on professionally generated content …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why hyperautomation can help developers grow]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60513</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/why-hyperautomation-can-help-developers-grow/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning skills to harness new technologies increases your employability and gives you a leg up to secure a better job and higher salary.
The post Why hyperautomation can help developers grow appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 23rd, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/23/this-week-in-spring-august-23rd-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/23/this-week-in-spring-august-23rd-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We’ve got a ton to cover, so let’s dive right into it!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Flowable founder Joram Barrez on a Bootiful Podcast on workflow, business process management, and more

  
Building IoT Applications Using Fauna and Spring

  
Cosmos DB for Spring Developers, Part I: Using Cosmos DB as a SQL Database

  
How to Build Web Servers with Paketo Buildpacks - Paketo Buildpacks

  
Introducing Experimental Spring Support for Apache Pulsar

  
Propagating Exceptions With OpenFeign and Spring

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M1 available now

  
Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M1 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.6.11 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.7.3 available now

  
Spring Boot Actuator

  
Spring Boot Native image builds with 22.2.0 are failing · Issue #176 paketo-buildpacks/native-image - this is in regards to an issue related to Buildpacks that just appeared last week. There’s a workaround that’s been recently deployed.

  
Spring Boot and Spring Security with JWT including Access and Refresh Tokens 🔑

  
Spring JDBC Batch Inserts

  
Spring Security 5.8.0-M2 is released

  
Spring Shell 2.1.1 is now available

  
Spring for GraphQL with Querydsl.

  
Testcontainers and Spring Boot for local development and integration testing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.25: Combiner]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/kubernetes-v1-25-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/kubernetes-v1-25-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes 1.25 Release Team
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.25!
This release includes a total of 40 enhancements. Fifteen of those enhancements are entering Alpha, ten are graduating to Beta, and thirteen are graduating to Stable. We also have two features being deprecated or removed.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes 1.25: Combiner
The theme for Kubernetes v1.25 is Combiner.
The Kubernetes project itself is made up of many, many individual components that, when combined, take the form of the project you see today. It is also built and maintained by many individuals, all of them with different skills, experiences, histories, and interests, who join forces not just as the release team but as the many SIGs that support the project and the community year-round.
With this rel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 22, 2022]]></title>
        <id>cd57561ca684dacfdb5a73e1204fff6a6bfa1214</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-22-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T18:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I’m back from my summer holidays and ready to get up to date with the latest AWS news from last week! Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Cloud Skills Shortage Is Affecting Multi-Cloud Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-a-cloud-skills-shortage-is-affecting-multi-cloud-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-a-cloud-skills-shortage-is-affecting-multi-cloud-adoption"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 State of Cloud Strategy survey reveals that IT organizations are turning to platform teams and automated tools to bridge a growing skills shortage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 10th Anniversary, Amazon S3 Glacier – A Decade of Cold Storage in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>2d8c2df87af9a66f78fc7d7776db8517bedf54f4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-10th-anniversary-amazon-s3-glacier-a-decade-of-cold-storage-in-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T15:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten years ago, on August 20, 2012, AWS announced the general availability of Amazon Glacier, secure, reliable, and extremely low-cost storage designed for data archiving and backup. At the time, I was working as an AWS customer and it felt like an April Fools’ joke, offering long-term, secure, and durable cloud storage that allowed me […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing a VMware Template Lifecycle with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/managing-a-vmware-template-lifecycle-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/managing-a-vmware-template-lifecycle-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we manage a large number of virtual machines (VMs), we want to reduce the differences between them and create a standard template. By using a standard template, it becomes easier to manage and propagate the same operation on the different nodes. When using VMware vSphere, it is a common practice to share a standardized VM template and use it to create new VMs. This template is often called a golden image. Its creation involves a series of steps that can be automated with Ansible. In this blog, we will see how one can create and use a new golden image.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gonéri Le Bouder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad Service Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-service-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-service-discovery"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad’s addition of native service discovery offers a new option for simple service registration, plus integration with Consul for more complex service mesh use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/22/sig-storage-spotlight/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/22/sig-storage-spotlight/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS)
Since the very beginning of Kubernetes, the topic of persistent data and how to address the requirement of stateful applications has been an important topic. Support for stateless deployments was natural, present from the start, and garnered attention, becoming very well-known. Work on better support for stateful applications was also present from early on, with each release increasing the scope of what could be run on Kubernetes.
Message queues, databases, clustered filesystems: these are some examples of the solutions that have different storage requirements and that are, today, increasingly deployed in Kubernetes. Dealing with ephemeral and persistent storage, local or remote, file or block, from many different vendors, while considering how to provide the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/19/spring-shell-2-1-1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/19/spring-shell-2-1-1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T13:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release and Maven Central.

Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OptFormer: Towards Universal Hyperparameter Optimization with Transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/optformer-towards-universal.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/optformer-towards-universal.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T19:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yutian Chen, Staff Research Scientist, DeepMind, and Xingyou (Richard) Song, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team 
One of the most important aspects in machine learning is hyperparameter optimization, as finding the right hyperparameters for a machine learning task can make or break a model’s performance. Internally, we regularly use Google Vizier as the default platform for hyperparameter optimization. Throughout its deployment over the last 5 years, Google Vizier has been used more than 10 million times, over a vast class of applications, including machine learning applications from vision, reinforcement learning, and language but also scientific applications such as protein discovery and hardware acceleration. As Google Vizier is able to keep track of use patterns i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.4 Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-4-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-4-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.4 introduces support for the new beta version of the Kubernetes Gateway API and HTTP path rewrites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary 0.10 Expands Credential Management and Admin UI IAM Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-10-expands-credential-management-and-admin-ui-iam-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-10-expands-credential-management-and-admin-ui-iam-workflows"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary 0.10 adds support for credential management of SSH keys and enhanced IAM workflows in the admin UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Flowable founder Joram Barrez on a Bootiful Podcast on workflow, business process management, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/a-bootiful-podcast-flowable-founder-joram-barrez-on-a-bootiful-podcast-on-workflow-business-process-management-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/a-bootiful-podcast-flowable-founder-joram-barrez-on-a-bootiful-podcast-on-workflow-business-process-management-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Flowable founder Joram Barrez (@jbarrez) about workflow, business process management (BPM), decision management, rules, and so much more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/spring-boot-2-7-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/spring-boot-2-7-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T07:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.3 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 48 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.11 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-boot-2-6-11-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-boot-2-6-11-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T06:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.11 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 40 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第215話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270375685435178676</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270375685435178676"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Stargazing, solutions and staycations: the Kubernetes 1.24 release interview]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/18/stargazing-solutions-and-staycations-the-kubernetes-1.24-release-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/18/stargazing-solutions-and-staycations-the-kubernetes-1.24-release-interview/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Craig Box (Google)
The Kubernetes project has participants from all around the globe. Some are friends, some are colleagues, and some are strangers. The one thing that unifies them, no matter their differences, are that they all have an interesting story. It is my pleasure to be the documentarian for the stories of the Kubernetes community in the weekly Kubernetes Podcast from Google. With every new Kubernetes release comes an interview with the release team lead, telling the story of that release, but also their own personal story.
With 1.25 around the corner, the tradition continues with a look back at the story of 1.24. That release was led by James Laverack of Jetstack. James was on the podcast in May, and while you can read his story below, if you can, please do listen to it i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrialized Workflows - Using Microsoft CAF Patterns and Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/industrialized-workflows-using-microsoft-caf-patterns-and-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/industrialized-workflows-using-microsoft-caf-patterns-and-terraform"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how even non-technical operators can use HashiCorp Terraform Cloud to deploy Azure resources based on Microsoft's Cloud Adoption Framework (CAF) templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Trusted Advisor – New Priority Capability]]></title>
        <id>b0c7ecebd1612af876be081dc850f50a0a0ebf98</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-trusted-advisor-new-priority-capability/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T17:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Trusted Advisor is a service that continuously analyzes your AWS accounts and provides recommendations to help you to follow AWS best practices and AWS Well-Architected guidelines. Trusted Advisor implements a series of checks. These checks identify ways to optimize your AWS infrastructure, improve security and performance, reduce costs, and monitor service quotas. Today, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Survey Shows Broad Cloud Waste — HashiCorp Terraform Can Help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-survey-shows-broad-cloud-waste-hashicorp-terraform-can-help</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-survey-shows-broad-cloud-waste-hashicorp-terraform-can-help"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to our 2022 State of Cloud Strategy Survey, 94% of organizations have avoidable cloud spending. See where the money’s going and how Terraform can help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating automation execution environments using ansible-builder and Shipwright]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-automation-execution-environments-using-ansible-builder-and-shipwright</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-automation-execution-environments-using-ansible-builder-and-shipwright"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reproducibility and consistency are two key traits that are the driving forces behind the popularity of containers. Consistency is also a principle found within Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. With only a few lines of YAML-formatted manifests, thousands of instances can be set up and configured uniformly. While the management of target instances is simple, it is the control node, or where the Ansible execution is initiated, that can  be the most challenging aspect. As Ansible is written in Python, does the machine have the correct version of Python installed?  Are the necessary Python modules installed? Are there any operating system dependencies needed? The list goes on and on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ablock@redhat.com (Andrew Block)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-1-0-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-1-0-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M1.



You can download it from repo.spring.io milestone repository by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:1.0.0-M1'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-0-4-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-0-4-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M1.



You can download it from repo.spring.io milestone repository by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.4.0-M1'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Grillo Built a Low-Cost Earthquake Early Warning System on AWS]]></title>
        <id>13b116ed4d0b61d043f96e454e4cc6a616f9f183</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-grillo-built-a-low-cost-earthquake-early-warning-system-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T18:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is estimated that 50 percent of the injuries caused when a high magnitude earthquake affects an area are because of falls or falling hazards. This means that most of these injuries could have been prevented if the population had a few seconds of warning to take cover. Grillo, a social impact enterprise focused on seismology, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.8.0-M2 is released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/spring-security-5-8-0-m2-is-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/spring-security-5-8-0-m2-is-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.8.0-M2 is available now.



This release includes dependency upgrades, bug fixes, and enhancements. Here are a few noteworthy changes:





Hash-based Content-Security-Policy for SAML post pages



Customization of redirect strategy





See the 5.8.0-M2 release notes for more details.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards Helpful Robots: Grounding Language in Robotic Affordances]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/towards-helpful-robots-grounding.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/towards-helpful-robots-grounding.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T14:02:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brian Ichter and Karol Hausman, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Over the last several years, we have seen significant progress in applying machine learning to robotics. However, robotic systems today are capable of executing only very short, hard-coded commands, such as “Pick up an apple,” because they tend to perform best with clear tasks and rewards. They struggle with learning to perform long-horizon tasks and reasoning about abstract goals, such as a user prompt like “I just worked out, can you get me a healthy snack?” 
Meanwhile, recent progress in training language models (LMs) has led to systems that can perform a wide range of language understanding and generation tasks with impressive results. However, these language models are inherently not grounded i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Experimental Spring Support for Apache Pulsar]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/introducing-experimental-spring-support-for-apache-pulsar</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/introducing-experimental-spring-support-for-apache-pulsar"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce that we are incubating a new experimental Spring project for Apache Pulsar. This project aims to provide Spring-friendly APIs, building blocks, and programming models for writing Java applications that interact with Apache Pulsar. 

Apache Pulsar is a popular messaging system with a growing ecosystem of developers in the enterprise messaging and streaming space. Here are some main features and advantages of using Apache Pulsar for messaging-based software applications:


  
Apache Pulsar provides both the traditional queuing semantics of RabbitMQ, ActiveMQ, and others and the log-based structure of Apache Kafka through various subscription models.

  
The broker in Apache Pulsar is stateless, and the storage is not part of the broker. Instead, it uses another A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 16th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/this-week-in-spring-august-16th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/this-week-in-spring-august-16th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another wonder-filled installment of This Week in Spring! It’s been a week! Sometimes I can scarcely believe it myself. And can you believe it’s August 16th already?? My daughter’s starting school this week! We’re in the northern hemisphere, and Summer break is already over and done with for her. There’s still another month and some change of summer, officially, though. So, I hope you all are doing whatever you can to maximize your enjoyment of it before the darker and colder months arrive. 

Twitter helps me pass the time. I’ve been working on some code and wanted to use Twitter’s OAuth 2 and PKCE support in the application but couldn’t quite make it work. So I pinged my pal (everybody’s pal, really!) and Spring Security lead Rob Winch (@rob_winch) for some cl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.3 and 5.6.7 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/15/spring-security-5-7-3-and-5-6-7-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/15/spring-security-5-7-3-and-5-6-7-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.7.3 and 5.6.7 are available now. In both cases the releases are largely composed of dependency upgrades and minor fixes.



To learn more, please visit the 5.7.3 and
 5.6.7 release summaries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Decade of Ever-Increasing Provisioned IOPS for Amazon EBS]]></title>
        <id>62b434c84905bf2a24ca8943b82a7e2149abf628</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/a-decade-of-ever-increasing-provisioned-iops-for-amazon-ebs/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T22:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress is often best appreciated in retrospect. It is often the case that a steady stream of incremental improvements over a long period of time ultimately adds up to a significant level of change. Today, ten years after we first launched the Provisioned IOPS feature for Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS), I strongly believe that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – HTTP/3 Support for Amazon CloudFront]]></title>
        <id>a4970c24e76d5efa333710d9e50da964387520ea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-http-3-support-for-amazon-cloudfront/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T22:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudFront is a content delivery network (CDN) service, a network of interconnected servers that is geographically closer to the users and reaches their computers much faster. Amazon CloudFront reduces latency by delivering data through 410+ globally dispersed Points of Presence (PoPs) with automated network mapping and intelligent routing. With Amazon CloudFront, content, API requests […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 15, 2022]]></title>
        <id>ec58e447970e428041f23a062ac4b1e7cf8bc433</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-15-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love the AWS Twitch channel for watching interesting online live shows such as AWS On Air, Containers from the Couch, and Serverless Office Hours. Last week, AWS Storage Day 2022 was hosted virtually on the AWS Twitch channel and covered recent announcements and insights that address customers’ needs to reduce and optimize storage costs and build data resiliency […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.13 Introduces Cluster Peering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-introduces-cluster-peering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-introduces-cluster-peering"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This release enhances a number of features in Consul while adding such new features as a Consul on Kubernetes CNI plugin and a beta version of cluster peering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.9.5 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/15/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-9-5-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/15/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-9-5-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.9.5 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release contains an update of the Spring Boot version (2.5.14) and numerous bug fixes. See the release notes for more information.
Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on Stackoverflow or GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Meet Our Contributors - APAC (China region)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/15/meet-our-contributors-china-ep-03/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/15/meet-our-contributors-china-ep-03/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors & Interviewers: Avinesh Tripathi, Debabrata Panigrahi, Jayesh Srivastava, Priyanka Saggu, Purneswar Prasad, Vedant Kakde
Hello, everyone 👋
Welcome back to the third edition of the "Meet Our Contributors" blog post series for APAC.
This post features four outstanding contributors from China, who have played diverse leadership and community roles in the upstream Kubernetes project.
So, without further ado, let's get straight to the article.
Andy Zhang
Andy Zhang currently works for Microsoft China at the Shanghai site. His main focus is on Kubernetes storage drivers. Andy started contributing to Kubernetes about 5 years ago.
He states that as he is working in Azure Kubernetes Service team and spends most of his time contributing to the Kubernetes community project. Now he is the mai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.15.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/12/spring-tools-4-15-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/12/spring-tools-4-15-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.15.3 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: Spring Boot Tools slow down code complete (#808)

  
(Language Server) fixed: Copied files should retain copyright ownership (#807)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-08-11-4153-release-incl-language-servers-version-1380

Spring Tools 4.16.0 is scheduled to be released in mid September 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS Private 5G – Build Your Own Private Mobile Network]]></title>
        <id>8f6fde13422a7d6f709abd13a6bff48a21025568</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-private-5g-build-your-own-private-mobile-network/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T22:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the mid-1990’s, I had a young family and 5 or 6 PCs in the basement. One day my son Stephen and I bought a single box that contained a bunch of 3COM network cards, a hub, some drivers, and some cables, and spent a pleasant weekend setting up our first home LAN. Introducing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rax: Composable Learning-to-Rank Using JAX]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/rax-composable-learning-to-rank-using.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/rax-composable-learning-to-rank-using.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T18:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rolf Jagerman and Honglei Zhuang, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Ranking is a core problem across a variety of domains, such as search engines, recommendation systems, or question answering. As such, researchers often utilize learning-to-rank (LTR), a set of supervised machine learning techniques that optimize for the utility of an entire list of items (rather than a single item at a time). A noticeable recent focus is on combining LTR with deep learning. Existing libraries, most notably TF-Ranking, offer researchers and practitioners the necessary tools to use LTR in their work. However, none of the existing LTR libraries work natively with JAX, a new machine learning framework that provides an extensible system of function transformations that compose: automatic different…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Sentinel Policies to the Terraform Registry (Beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-sentinel-policies-to-the-terraform-registry</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-sentinel-policies-to-the-terraform-registry"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Sentinel policies are now available in the Terraform Registry so you can publish policies you want to share and search the Registry for policies you need.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Successful Multi-Cloud Adoption Requires Automated Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/successful-multi-cloud-adoption-requires-automated-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/successful-multi-cloud-adoption-requires-automated-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HashiCorp’s new State of Cloud Strategy survey, 89% of respondents said that security is the key driver of their cloud success — here’s how to best secure your multi-cloud environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Enhancing Kubernetes one KEP at a Time]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/11/enhancing-kubernetes-one-kep-at-a-time/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/11/enhancing-kubernetes-one-kep-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ryler Hockenbury (Mastercard)
Did you know that Kubernetes v1.24 has 46 enhancements? That's a lot of new functionality packed into a 4-month release cycle. The Kubernetes release team coordinates the logistics of the release, from remediating test flakes to publishing updated docs. It's a ton of work, but they always deliver.
The release team comprises around 30 people across six subteams - Bug Triage, CI Signal, Enhancements, Release Notes, Communications, and Docs.  Each of these subteams manages a component of the release. This post will focus on the role of the enhancements subteam and how you can get involved.
What's the enhancements subteam?
Great question. We'll get to that in a second but first, let's talk about how features are managed in Kubernetes.
Each new feature requ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to AWS Storage Day 2022]]></title>
        <id>895c8f94e7763a3e32f7029ecb7f0e5aefa364af</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/welcome-to-aws-storage-day-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are on the fourth year of our annual AWS Storage Day! Do you remember our first Storage Day 2019 and the subsequent Storage Day 2020? I watched Storage Day 2021, which was streamed live from downtown Seattle. We continue to hear from our customers about how powerful the Storage Day announcements and educational sessions […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual Production — A Validation Framework For Unreal Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/aab780b2f8c8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/virtual-production-a-validation-framework-for-unreal-engine-aab780b2f8c8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T14:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The use of virtual production and real time technologies in film & tv has accelerated in recent years. Game engines, such as Unreal Engine, have been a major part driving the democratization of advanced in-camera visual effects (ICVFX). But with infinite configuration and setting combinations, how can a production get it right?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Kubernetes Dynamic Inventories with kubernetes.core Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-kubernetes-dynamic-inventories-with-kubernetes.core-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-kubernetes-dynamic-inventories-with-kubernetes.core-modules"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When managing infrastructure, there are times when a dynamic inventory is essential. Kubernetes is a perfect example of this where you may create multiple applications within a namespace but you will not be able to create a static inventory due to Kubernetes appending a systems-generated string to uniquely identify objects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why R-KOM chose Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60009</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/why-r-kom-chose-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the latest installment of Why Camunda 8, we spoke with R-KOM, a telecommunications company based in Regensburg, Germany.
The post Why R-KOM chose Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Schroth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trust Security for Kubernetes with a Service Mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/zero-trust-security-for-kubernetes-with-a-service-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/zero-trust-security-for-kubernetes-with-a-service-mesh"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A service mesh like HashiCorp Consul can be an essential part of applying zero trust security principles to modern, complex, Kubernetes deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Azure DevOps Server 2022 RC1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65570</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-azure-devops-server-2022-rc1/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T18:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re very excited to announce the first release candidate (RC) of Azure DevOps Server 2022!
Delivery Plans
There are many more features with this release and you can read all about those features in our release notes.
The post Introducing Azure DevOps Server 2022 RC1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Video-Text Learning with Iterative Co-tokenization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/efficient-video-text-learning-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/efficient-video-text-learning-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T17:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by AJ Piergiovanni and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Video is an ubiquitous source of media content that touches on many aspects of people’s day-to-day lives. Increasingly, real-world video applications, such as video captioning, video content analysis, and video question-answering (VideoQA), rely on models that can connect video content with text or natural language. VideoQA is particularly challenging, however, as it requires grasping both semantic information, such as objects in a scene, as well as temporal information, e.g., how things move and interact, both of which must be taken in the context of a natural-language question that holds specific intent. In addition, because videos have many frames, processing all of them to learn spatio-temp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[August patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65582</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/august-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T16:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Fix identity value error while assigning a work item to an identity which appears in different domains.
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2 Patch 2
The post August patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha4 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=59448</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/camunda-automation-platform-7180-alpha4-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.18. This release features the following improvements: Support for H2 2.1 Traditional Chinese translations are available Improved status monitoring of batch jobs Improved safety of executing a batch operation on the Batch Operation page 8 Bug Fixes You can download Camunda for free or run it with Docker. For a complete list of all improvements, take a look at the release notes. Please also see the list of known issues. If you want to dig in deeper, you can find the source code on GitHub. Support for H2 2.1 This release adds support for the H2 database in version 2.1, which provides fixes for vulnerabilities. Enterprise customers...
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha4 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0 alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=59822</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce a new release of Camunda Optimize. Camunda Optimize provides business activity monitoring for workflows, supporting continuous process improvement by providing transparency into your automated workflows and decisions. Business-friendly reports, dashboards, and alerts make it possible to identify process bottlenecks, improve end-to-end processes, and evaluate the success of your process automation initiative. In the rest of this post, we’ll highlight some of the new capabilities introduced in Optimize 3.9.0 alpha3. What’s new? Ease of adding new reports to dashboard Reports are added to dashboards to design an individual overview of the performance of your processes. Adding reports to dashboards was already possible with previous versions of Optimize, but now we’ve reduced the number of steps to do...
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0 alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 8, 2022]]></title>
        <id>5368b5f3eeaf1b269292cf7fe2e8e38eb5b9e360</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-8-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T20:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an ex-.NET developer, and now Developer Advocate for .NET at AWS, I’m excited to bring you this week’s Week in Review post, for reasons that will quickly become apparent! There are several updates, customer stories, and events I want to bring to your attention, so let’s dive straight in! Last Week’s launches .NET developers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Platform Teams Are Everywhere — Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cloud-platform-teams-are-everywhere-heres-why</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cloud-platform-teams-are-everywhere-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HashiCorp’s new State of Cloud Strategy survey, 86% of respondents said they rely on cloud platform teams — for a wide variety of very good reasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>