<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-18T00:19:56.879Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-18T00:19:56.879Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In search of incompetence]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44058</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873791531/0/sethsblog~In-search-of-incompetence/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-17T08:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning is about becoming incompetent on our way to getting better. If you’re not open to the tension that is caused by knowing you could do better, it’s unlikely you’re willing to do the work to get better. As you’re doing that work, there’s the satisfaction it brings, but also the knowledge that just a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“For what purposes will it be useful?”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48773</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873736463/0/sethsblog~For-what-purposes-will-it-be-useful/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1840, at the dawn of the information age, the king of Sardinia asked Charles Babbage what nearly instant messaging like the telegraph could possibly be good for. Twenty years later, it was obvious. When I first saw Prodigy in 1986, I saw that the consumer internet would have many possibilities, but I didn’t have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HEAL: A framework for health equity assessment of machine learning performance]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/heal-framework-for-health-equity.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/heal-framework-for-health-equity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T18:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mike Schaekermann, Research Scientist, Google Research, and Ivor Horn, Chief Health Equity Officer & Director, Google Core




Health equity is a major societal concern worldwide with disparities having many causes. These sources include limitations in access to healthcare, differences in clinical treatment, and even fundamental differences in the diagnostic technology. In dermatology for example, skin cancer outcomes are worse for populations such as minorities, those with lower socioeconomic status, or individuals with limited healthcare access. While there is great promise in recent advances in machine learning (ML) and artificial intelligence (AI) to help improve healthcare, this transition from research to bedside must be accompanied by a careful understanding of whether and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Update on Xamarin Support in Rider]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=457256</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/03/15/an-update-on-xamarin-support-in-rider/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T15:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft will be ending support for Xamarin on May 1, 2024, with all recent development switching to MAUI cross-platform applications. As Microsoft’s document states: Xamarin.Android, Xamarin.iOS, and Xamarin.Mac are now integrated directly into .NET (starting with .NET 6) as Android, iOS, and Mac for .NET. If you’re building with these project types today, they should […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.3.5 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=456610</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2024/03/webstorm-2023-3-5/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T13:43:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fifth bug-fix update for v2023.3 has arrived!  You can update to this version from inside the IDE, using the Toolbox App, or via snaps, if you’re using Ubuntu. You can also download it directly from our website. Notable fixes Here are some of the notable fixes in v2023.3.5:  That’s all for today! For the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlining Camunda APIs: Providing an Intuitive and Consistent Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102649</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/streamlining-camunda-apis/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're working to streamline our product APIs and provide you with an intuitive and consistent API experience.
The post Streamlining Camunda APIs: Providing an Intuitive and Consistent Experience appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pytest vs. Unittest: Which Is Better?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=456753</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2024/03/pytest-vs-unittest/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T10:47:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python, being a versatile and widely used programming language, offers several testing frameworks to facilitate the testing process. Two prominent choices are pytest and unittest, both of which come with their own sets of features and advantages. In this article, we’ll be covering the following sections: This will help you determine which testing framework is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maha Taqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Later or now?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46930</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873672566/0/sethsblog~Later-or-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we feel like doing something selfish, indulgent, hurtful or short-term, we can simply decide to do it later. And when it occurs to us that we might be able to make a useful contribution or do something important, perhaps we could do it now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run and manage open source InfluxDB databases with Amazon Timestream]]></title>
        <id>3a184bf9dfd95467e0bd27737c7d220b8539ab2b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/run-and-manage-open-source-influxdb-databases-with-amazon-timestream/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T01:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can use InfluxDB as a database engine in Amazon Timestream. This support makes it easy for you to run near real-time time-series applications using InfluxDB and open source APIs, including open source Telegraf agents that collect time-series observations. Now you have two database engines to choose in Timestream: Timestream for LiveAnalytics and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hypermedia and Browser Enhancement]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/15/hypermedia-and-browser-enhancement</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/15/hypermedia-and-browser-enhancement"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Syer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2023.1.4 and 2023.0.10 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/15/spring-data-2023-1-4-and-2023-0-10-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/15/spring-data-2023-1-4-and-2023-0-10-released"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2024.0.0-M2 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/15/spring-data-2024-0-0-m2-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/15/spring-data-2024-0-0-m2-available"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot Testjars founder Rob Winch]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/15/spring-boot-testjars-founder-rob-winch</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/15/spring-boot-testjars-founder-rob-winch"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create ‘Win-Win Scenarios’ for Your Team — Leadership Advice From a Director]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-to-create-win-win-scenarios</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-to-create-win-win-scenarios"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you become a successful leader? Just “go for it,” advises Tehila Shneider, Director of Security Engineering at Elastic....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fairygodboss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create ‘Win-Win Scenarios’ for Your Team — Leadership Advice From a Director]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-to-create-win-win-scenarios</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-to-create-win-win-scenarios"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you become a successful leader? Just “go for it,” advises Tehila Shneider, Director of Security Engineering at Elastic. “Don't let self-doubt or external challenges deter you from pursuing leadership roles,” she continues. “While there will always be concerns and challenges, remember that growth often happens outside of your comfort zone; everything is solvable.”

Being a great leader also involves recognizing the challenges and goals of your team. When asked about what leadership strategies she’s developed to achieve this, Tehila emphasizes the importance of helping team members align their individual professional goals with organizational objectives to create a ‘win-win scenario’ for everyone. “This scenario can be achieved by getting to know your team through open conversations …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fairygodboss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schwa]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2907/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2907/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/schwa.png" title="Doug's cousin, the one from London, runs a Bumble love cult." alt="Doug's cousin, the one from London, runs a Bumble love cult." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cappy: Outperforming and boosting large multi-task language models with a small scorer]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/cappy-outperforming-and-boosting-large.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/cappy-outperforming-and-boosting-large.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T19:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yun Zhu and Lijuan Liu, Software Engineers, Google Research





Large language model (LLM) advancements have led to a new paradigm that unifies various natural language processing (NLP) tasks within an instruction-following framework. This paradigm is exemplified by recent multi-task LLMs, such as T0, FLAN, and OPT-IML. First, multi-task data is gathered with each task following a task-specific template, where each labeled example is converted into an instruction (e.g., "Put the concepts together to form a sentence: ski, mountain, skier”) paired with a corresponding response (e.g., "Skier skis down the mountain"). These instruction-response pairs are used to train the LLM, resulting in a conditional generation model that takes an instruction as input and generates a response. Mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud unveils new run task workflow enhancements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-unveils-new-run-task-workflow-enhancements</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-unveils-new-run-task-workflow-enhancements"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newest enhancements to HashiCorp Terraform Cloud’s run task feature empower users to seamlessly expand their use of essential third-party integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Pi Day 2024: Use your data to power generative AI]]></title>
        <id>e27aadba159a82a8421a846f45b7aa39ba3dae67</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-pi-day-2024-use-your-data-to-power-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T15:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is AWS Pi Day! Join us live on Twitch, starting at 1 PM Pacific time. On this day 18 years ago, a West Coast retail company launched an object storage service, introducing the world to Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3). We had no idea it would change the way businesses across the globe […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking Outside The Microservice Box: Diversity of Endpoints (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102675</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/thinking-outside-the-microservice-box-diverse-endpoints/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T15:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-based microservice architectures are popular but do have limitations. In this post, we'll talk about the effect of diverse endpoints and why it matters.
The post Thinking Outside The Microservice Box: Diversity of Endpoints (Part 2) appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Meets GDC 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=456660</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/03/14/jetbrains-meets-gdc-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark your calendars for March 20–22, 2024, as the Moscone Center in San Francisco, California prepares to host the Game Developers Conference, the largest annual gathering of professional video game developers. JetBrains is thrilled to be part of this event, and we invite you to join us! As a visitor to JetBrains’ booth, you’ll be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Ruban</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin Roundup: Unveiling the New Compose Multiplatform Release, Amper Update, and More!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=456686</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2024/03/kotlin-roundup-feb-march-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T10:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this roundup, we invite you to explore the highlights of what has happened in the Kotlin ecosystem lately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daria Voronina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating a Compromised TeamCity On-Premises Server and Its Build Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=456943</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2024/03/investigating-a-compromised-teamcity-on-premises-server/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T09:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction If you suspect your TeamCity On-Premises server has been compromised through a security vulnerability (such as CVE-2024-27198), and you were unable to patch or upgrade your server prior to the suspected incident, this blog post recommends some of the steps you should take to investigate the incident, along with potential actions for remediation. You […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Gallo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Naming is part of marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48535</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873593804/0/sethsblog~Naming-is-part-of-marketing/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A name is a hook for us to hang a story on. We need to begin with empathy and a useful story… useful to the people who want to believe it, spread it, and use it to accomplish their goals. But then, the story needs firm footing and a way to stick with us. Patagonia […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring HATEOAS 2.1.4, 2.2.1 and 2.3 M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/14/spring-hateoas-2-1-4-2-2-1-and-2-3-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/14/spring-hateoas-2-1-4-2-2-1-and-2-3-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.1.5, 6.0.18 and 5.3.33 Available Now Including Fixes for CVE-2024-22259]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/14/spring-framework-6-1-5-6-0-18-and-5-3-33-available-now-including-fixes-for</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/14/spring-framework-6-1-5-6-0-18-and-5-3-33-available-now-including-fixes-for"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching from the Java High Level Rest Client to the new Java API Client]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/switching-from-the-java-high-level-rest-client-to-the-new-java-api-client</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/switching-from-the-java-high-level-rest-client-to-the-new-java-api-client"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say you have a Java project using Elastic 7.17 and the deprecated High Level Rest Client (HLRC). You have been asked to switch to Elastic 8.11 but the HLRC does not exist for this version. This ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Pilato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching from the Java High Level Rest Client to the new Java API Client]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/switching-from-the-java-high-level-rest-client-to-the-new-java-api-client</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/switching-from-the-java-high-level-rest-client-to-the-new-java-api-client"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm often seeing questions on discuss related to the Java API Client usage. For this, in 2019, I started a GitHub repository to provide some code examples that actually work and answer the questions asked by the community.
Since then, the High Level Rest Client (HLRC) has been deprecated and the new Java API Client has been released.
In order to keep answering questions, I needed recently to upgrade the repository to this new client. Although it uses the same Low Level Rest Client behind the scenes and an upgrade documentation has been provided, it's not really trivial to upgrade it.
I found interesting to share all the steps I had to perform to do this. If you are "just looking" for the pull requests that made the upgrade, have a look at:

Switch to the new Java API Client

Upgrade to Ela…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Pilato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s Claude 3 Haiku model is now available on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>f82acaea0917cce965212856bcf2ac6a924f9e78</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/anthropics-claude-3-haiku-model-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T22:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, Anthropic announced their Claude 3 foundation model family. The family includes three models: Claude 3 Haiku, the fastest and most compact model for near-instant responsiveness; Claude 3 Sonnet, the ideal balanced model between skills and speed; and Claude 3 Opus, the most intelligent offering for top-level performance on highly complex tasks. AWS also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: February 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-13-github-availability-report-february-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-13-github-availability-report-february-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T18:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In February, we experienced two incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-13-github-availability-report-february-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: February 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing OpenTelemetry apps with Elastic AI Assistant and APM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/analyzing-opentelemetry-apps-elastic-ai-assistant-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/analyzing-opentelemetry-apps-elastic-ai-assistant-apm"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T16:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability provides native OpenTelemetry support, but analyzing applications logs, metrics, and traces can be daunting. Elastic Observability not only provides AIOps features but also an AI...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing OpenTelemetry apps with Elastic AI Assistant and APM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/analyzing-opentelemetry-apps-elastic-ai-assistant-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/analyzing-opentelemetry-apps-elastic-ai-assistant-apm"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T16:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTelemetry is rapidly becoming the most expansive project within the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), boasting as many commits as Kubernetes and garnering widespread support from customers. Numerous companies are adopting OpenTelemetry and integrating it into their applications. Elastic® offers detailed guides on implementing OpenTelemetry for applications. However, like many applications, pinpointing and resolving issues can be time-consuming.

The Elastic AI Assistant significantly enhances the process, not only in identifying but also in resolving issues. This is further enhanced by Elastic’s new Service Level Objective (SLO) capability, allowing you to streamline your entire site reliability engineering (SRE) process from detecting potential issues to enhancing the overall …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Migrating to Camunda 8 is Good for Business]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102614</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/why-migrating-camunda-8-good-for-business/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T15:42:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating to Camunda 8 can deliver strong business value to your organization. Read on to learn why you should migrate to Camunda 8 and the business advantages you can achieve.
The post Why Migrating to Camunda 8 is Good for Business appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第240話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755396392866</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755396392866"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate Unit Tests Using AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=448201</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/03/13/generate-unit-tests-using-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T14:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can you make your life easier as a developer by using AI to generate unit tests? AI can provide a bit of automation to this daily development activity and make our development workflow a bit smoother if we use it thoughtfully. So in this blog post, we’ll take a look at using the JetBrains AI […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curation (vs the road to junk)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48757</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873547463/0/sethsblog~Curation-vs-the-road-to-junk/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T08:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The independent bookstore down the street is carefully curated. Each book takes up the spot that a different book could inhabit, so the owner makes sure that there’s a great reason a title is included. Amazon, on the other hand, has no shelf space problem, and the Kindle multiplies it. As a result, the average […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Spring Batch Remote Partitioning, your easy button for data scale!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/13/spring-tips-spring-batch-remote-partitioning-your-easy-button-for-data-scale</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/13/spring-tips-spring-batch-remote-partitioning-your-easy-button-for-data-scale"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.22.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/13/spring-tools-4-22-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/13/spring-tools-4-22-0-released"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lippert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - March 12th, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/13/this-week-in-spring-march-12th-2024</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/13/this-week-in-spring-march-12th-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2906/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2906/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/earth.png" title="Just think of all the countless petty squabbles and misunderstandings, of all the fervent hatreds, over so insignificant a thing as the direction and duration of a rocket engine firing." alt="Just think of all the countless petty squabbles and misunderstandings, of all the fervent hatreds, over so insignificant a thing as the direction and duration of a rocket engine firing." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talk like a graph: Encoding graphs for large language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/talk-like-graph-encoding-graphs-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/talk-like-graph-encoding-graphs-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bahare Fatemi and Bryan Perozzi, Research Scientists, Google Research




Imagine all the things around you — your friends, tools in your kitchen, or even the parts of your bike. They are all connected in different ways. In computer science, the term graph is used to describe connections between objects. Graphs consist of nodes (the objects themselves) and edges (connections between two nodes, indicating a  relationship between them). Graphs are everywhere now. The internet itself is a giant graph of websites linked together. Even the knowledge search engines use is organized in a graph-like way.





Furthermore, consider the remarkable advancements in artificial intelligence — such as chatbots that can write stories in seconds, and even software that can interpret medical repor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68912</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/march-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T20:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 Patch 3
The post March patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3.5 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=453920</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/03/intellij-idea-2023-3-5/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T18:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released one more bug-fix update for v2023.3. You can download the latest build from our website, via the Toolbox App, or by using snaps for Ubuntu. IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3.5. includes the following valuable fixes: For more details, please refer to the release notes. If you spot any bugs, submit a report to our issue tracker. Happy developing!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predictable plugin loading in Packer 1.11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/predictable-plugin-loading-in-packer-1-11</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/predictable-plugin-loading-in-packer-1-11"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To boost stability, Packer 1.11 introduces a predictable plugin loading approach, loading only binaries from its plugin directory with accompanying SHA256SUM files.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Alpha Release March 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102457</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/camunda-alpha-release-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T15:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to announce the March 2024 alpha release of Camunda. Check out what's new.
The post Camunda Alpha Release March 2024 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTelemetry and Elastic: Working together to establish continuous profiling for the community]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-donation-proposal-to-contribute-profiling-agent-to-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-donation-proposal-to-contribute-profiling-agent-to-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T14:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTelemetry is embracing profiling. Elastic is donating its whole-system continuous profiling agent to OpenTelemetry to further this advancement, empowering OTel users to improve computational effic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Ogbole,Alexander Wert,Tim Rühsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTelemetry and Elastic: Working together to establish continuous profiling for the community]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-donation-proposal-to-contribute-profiling-agent-to-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-donation-proposal-to-contribute-profiling-agent-to-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T14:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Profiling is emerging as a core pillar of observability, aptly dubbed the fourth pillar, with the OpenTelemetry (OTel) project leading this essential development. This blog post dives into the recent advancements in profiling within OTel and how Elastic® is actively contributing toward it. 
At Elastic, we’re big believers in and contributors to the OpenTelemetry project. The project’s benefits of flexibility, performance, and vendor agnosticism have been making their rounds; we’ve seen a groundswell of customer interest.
To this end, after donating our Elastic Common Schema and our invokedynamic based java agent approach, we recently announced our intent to donate our continuous profiling agent — a whole-system, always-on, continuous profiling solution that eliminates the need for run-time…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Ogbole,Alexander Wert,Tim Rühsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy Hacks: How to Throw Java Exceptions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=446227</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/03/easy-hacks-how-to-throw-java-exceptions/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T11:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exceptions in Java are used to indicate that an event occurred during the execution of a program and disrupted the normal flow of instructions. When an exception occurs, the Java runtime automatically stops the execution of the current method. It passes an exception object with information about the error to the nearest catch block that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maarten Balliauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ktor Roadmap for 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=453952</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2024/03/the-ktor-roadmap-for-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T10:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As in 2023 and 2022, we have been working on a roadmap for our development of Ktor for the year ahead. In the interests of transparency and accountability, we would like to share our plans with you here. Our ongoing plan Our ongoing plans and goals for Ktor remain consistent with previous years. We aim […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Garth Gilmour</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Iterators Beyond the Basics, Part III – Tips & Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rust&amp;p=455379</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rust/2024/03/12/rust-iterators-beyond-the-basics-part-iii-tips-and-tricks/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T09:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this third and final part of the Rust Iterators series, we’ll learn by example. We’ll explore some useful yet lesser-known iterator features, along with their applications in various popular open-source projects developed in Rust. This multipart series focuses on Rust iterators, covering both their implementation details and practical usage. Getting iterators from data sources […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vitaly Bragilevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Iterators Beyond the Basics, Part II – Key Aspects]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rust&amp;p=455321</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rust/2024/03/12/rust-iterators-beyond-the-basics-part-ii-key-aspects/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T09:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers transitioning to Rust from other programming languages, such as Python, JavaScript, or even C++ or Java, often face challenges with iterators. Rust’s ownership rules, the intricacies of its type system, and its commitment to generating efficient code give Rust iterators a distinctive character. Let’s dig into the details to gain a deeper understanding. This […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vitaly Bragilevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holding on for dear life]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46923</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873502277/0/sethsblog~Holding-on-for-dear-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T07:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s a cliche from the movies. Dangling from a railroad bridge, only determination and firm grip can save the hero. In our modern world, we often end up holding on to ideas, to grievances or to our view of the world. Ironically, the harder we hold on to the things we’re hiding from, the less […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring AI 0.8.1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/12/spring-ai-0-8-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/12/spring-ai-0-8-1-released"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Pollack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Peek at Kubernetes v1.30]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/12/kubernetes-1-30-upcoming-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/12/kubernetes-1-30-upcoming-changes/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Amit Dsouza, Frederick Kautz, Kristin Martin, Abigail McCarthy, Natali Vlatko
A quick look: exciting changes in Kubernetes v1.30
It's a new year and a new Kubernetes release. We're halfway through the release cycle and
have quite a few interesting and exciting enhancements coming in v1.30. From brand new features
in alpha, to established features graduating to stable, to long-awaited improvements, this release
has something for everyone to pay attention to!
To tide you over until the official release, here's a sneak peek of the enhancements we're most
excited about in this cycle!
Major changes for Kubernetes v1.30
Structured parameters for dynamic resource allocation (KEP-4381)
Dynamic resource allocation was
added to Kubernetes as an alpha feature in v1.26. It defines an alternat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chain-of-table: Evolving tables in the reasoning chain for table understanding]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/chain-of-table-evolving-tables-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/chain-of-table-evolving-tables-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zilong Wang, Student Researcher, and Chen-Yu Lee, Research Scientist, Cloud AI Team




People use tables every day to organize and interpret complex information in a structured, easily accessible format. Due to the ubiquity of such tables, reasoning over tabular data has long been a central topic in natural language processing (NLP). Researchers in this field have aimed to leverage language models to help users answer questions, verify statements, and analyze data based on tables. However, language models are trained over large amounts of plain text, so the inherently structured nature of tabular data can be difficult for language models to fully comprehend and utilize.



Recently, large language models (LLMs) have achieved outstanding performance across diverse natural languag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure data is superior data: A security-first approach to the DoD Data Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-data-dod-data-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-data-dod-data-strategy"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security is the foundational tenet on which any tech solution should be built and the common thread through the subsequent goals of VAULTIS. As the DoD works to modernize its data strategy, start the ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meg Novak,Eric Cobb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure data is superior data: A security-first approach to the DoD Data Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-data-dod-data-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-data-dod-data-strategy"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Department of Defense (DoD) has vast reserves of data, and the key to warfighter advantage is leveraging relevant data as a strategic asset to gain battlespace operational advantage, accelerating operational multi-domain decision-making at echelon scale. For the DoD to achieve its vision of “unleashing data to advance the national defense strategy,” relevant data must be securely collected, delivered, and accessed at enterprise scale with speed and protected from unauthorized use and manipulation at rest and in motion.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meg Novak,Eric Cobb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Claude 3 Sonnet support in Bedrock, new instances, and more — March 11, 2024]]></title>
        <id>1ac173b1e82d4b67e6ec4044be26f6b60a2f29dc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-claude-3-sonnet-support-in-bedrock-new-instances-and-more-march-11-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Friday was International Women’s Day (IWD), and I want to take a moment to appreciate the amazing ladies in the cloud computing space that are breaking the glass ceiling by reaching technical leadership positions and inspiring others to go and build, as our CTO Werner Vogels says. Last week’s launches Here are some launches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seamlessly migrate from Consul service discovery to service mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/seamlessly-migrate-from-consul-service-discovery-to-service-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/seamlessly-migrate-from-consul-service-discovery-to-service-mesh"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try this example method for transitioning from Consul service discovery to service mesh without affecting uptimes or development teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hiding the ‘aha’]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48753</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873451520/0/sethsblog~Hiding-the-aha/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most effective persuasion happens when we persuade ourselves. The purpose of the memo or the table or the graph or the presentation is to create the conditions for someone to make up their own minds. Because it’s almost impossible to make up their mind for them. The aha is actually a chemical reaction, a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supergroup]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2905/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2905/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/supergroup.png" title="I love their cover of 1,200 Balloons, Dalmatians, and Miles." alt="I love their cover of 1,200 Balloons, Dalmatians, and Miles." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preference and utility]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46903</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873407816/0/sethsblog~Preference-and-utility/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taste varies. That’s why we don’t call it utility. Taste is individual preference, not absolute truth. In team settings, then, it’s much more helpful to say, “I prefer this over that,” instead of, “this is wrong.” Some things are wrong. There are standards that we can all accept when it comes to utility, efficiency and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Default to surrender]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48740</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873368081/0/sethsblog~Default-to-surrender/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI chatbots highight a challenge that is worth understanding. It applies to customer service, bureaucracies and teachers as well… If you ask an AI a question and it’s not confident in the answer, it should say, “I’m not sure.” That could be followed up with, “do you want me to guess” or “if you could […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Workflow Engine? Key Benefits, Features and Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102261</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/what-is-a-workflow-engine/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T01:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is a workflow engine? How do they work, and why should you use one? Learn why modern workflow engines are critical for process automation and orchestration.
The post What Is a Workflow Engine? Key Benefits, Features and Considerations appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Health-specific embedding tools for dermatology and pathology]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/health-specific-embedding-tools-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/health-specific-embedding-tools-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T19:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dave Steiner, Clinical Research Scientist, Google Health, and Rory Pilgrim, Product Manager, Google Research




There’s a worldwide shortage of access to medical imaging expert interpretation across specialties including radiology, dermatology and pathology. Machine learning (ML) technology can help ease this burden by powering tools that enable doctors to interpret these images more accurately and efficiently. However, the development and implementation of such ML tools are often limited by the availability of high-quality data, ML expertise, and computational resources. 



One way to catalyze the use of ML for medical imaging is via domain-specific models that utilize deep learning (DL) to capture the information in medical images as compressed numerical vectors (called embed…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernizing financial services: A deep dive into Elastic Cloud on AWS for Observability, Security, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-elastic-cloud-aws-observability-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-elastic-cloud-aws-observability-security"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T18:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the landscape continues to evolve across increasingly complex ecosystems, Elastic Cloud in AWS Marketplace serves as a key enabler for observability within the banking, insurance, capital markets, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gareth Muc-Johnson,Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernizing financial services: A deep dive into Elastic Cloud on AWS for Observability, Security, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-elastic-cloud-aws-observability-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-elastic-cloud-aws-observability-security"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T18:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic landscape of financial services, data is not just currency; it's the key to innovation and operational excellence. Data is constantly streamlining from devices, logins, transfers, transactions, and much more, and it’s bound to increase with an ongoing reliance on digital channels. This creates a massive opportunity and responsibility for financial institutions, as their customers (and regulators) demand more from banking providers.

As the landscape continues to evolve across an increasingly complex ecosystem, Elastic Cloud in AWS Marketplace serves as a key enabler for observability within the banking, insurance, capital markets, and payments sectors. Elastic®’s integration with AWS native services provides financial institutions with unparalleled visibility, security, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gareth Muc-Johnson,Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where are you?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46895</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873298445/0/sethsblog~Where-are-you/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T09:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re reading a good historical novel, you might be there and then. When you’re checking your email, you are in a conversation between and among, over there, not here. When you’re imagining what went wrong in that conversation yesterday, you are living in yesterday. And when you’re scripting the next conversation you’re going to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating women in tech this International Women’s Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-international-womens-day-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-international-womens-day-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We regularly share stories from our female technologists, focusing on their roles, interests, and advice. Read them all here. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating women in tech this International Women’s Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-international-womens-day-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-international-womens-day-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[International Women’s Day is recognized globally on March 8th to celebrate the social, economic, cultural, and political achievements of women. This year, the theme is ‘Inspire Inclusion’ which encourages women’s economic empowerment, developing female talent, and supporting women and girls into leadership, decision-making, business and STEM. This theme deeply resonates with us. 
At Elastic®, we strive to empower women and pride ourselves on fostering an inclusive global culture. In 2023, we began to spotlight female-identifying technologists around the world in various roles and at differing levels of seniority to give Elasticians the chance to share their personal stories and experiences. 
Over the last year, we’ve told real Elasticians’ stories and had discussions about technical roles,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physics vs. Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2904/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2904/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/physics_vs_magic.png" title="'At the stroke of midnight, your brother will be hurtling sideways at an altitude of 150 meters' is a regular physics prediction about your nonmagical trebuchet, whereas 'you are cursed to build a brother-launching trebuchet' falls out of the Lagrangian." alt="'At the stroke of midnight, your brother will be hurtling sideways at an altitude of 150 meters' is a regular physics prediction about your nonmagical trebuchet, whereas 'you are cursed to build a brother-launching trebuchet' falls out of the Lagrangian." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting Diverse ML Systems at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2d2e6b6d205d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/supporting-diverse-ml-systems-at-netflix-2d2e6b6d205d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T18:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David J. Berg, Romain Cledat, Kayla Seeley, Shashank Srikanth, Chaoying Wang, Darin Yu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social learning: Collaborative learning with large language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/social-learning-collaborative-learning.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/social-learning-collaborative-learning.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Amirkeivan Mohtashami, Research Intern, and Florian Hartmann, Software Engineer, Google Research




Large language models (LLMs) have significantly improved the state of the art for solving tasks specified using natural language, often reaching performance close to that of people. As these models increasingly enable assistive agents, it could be beneficial for them to learn effectively from each other, much like people do in social settings, which would allow LLM-based agents to improve each other’s performance. 

 


To discuss the learning processes of humans, Bandura and Walters described the concept of social learning in 1977, outlining different models of observational learning used by people. One common method of learning from others is through a verbal instruction (e.g., …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring an increase in circumvention claims in our transparency data]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-07-exploring-an-increase-in-circumvention-claims-in-our-transparency-data/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-exploring-an-increase-in-circumvention-claims-in-our-transparency-data/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our full year of 2023 transparency reporting data is now available and we’re taking a deep dive into how a form change caused an abrupt increase in circumvention claims. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-exploring-an-increase-in-circumvention-claims-in-our-transparency-data/">Exploring an increase in circumvention claims in our transparency data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hard and soft skills for developers coding in the age of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T17:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While AI revolutionizes software development, it still relies on developers to pilot its use. In this blog, we’ll cover the skills that developers need to have for navigating this new AI-powered coding frontier. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/">Hard and soft skills for developers coding in the age of AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking Outside the Microservice Box: Decision Making (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102198</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/thinking-outside-the-microservice-box-decision-making/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-based microservice architectures are popular but do have limitations. In this series, we'll think outside the box and learn new ideas for microservice orchestration.
The post Thinking Outside the Microservice Box: Decision Making (Part 1) appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning vs. AI: Understanding the differences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ml-vs-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ml-vs-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uncover the world of machine learning and artificial intelligence. Learn how they’re different and where they intersect to drive innovation....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Platform team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning vs. AI: Understanding the differences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ml-vs-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ml-vs-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a long time, AI was almost exclusively the plaything of science fiction writers, where humans push technology too far, to the point it comes alive and — as Hollywood would have us believe — starts to wreak havoc. Cheery stuff! However, in recent years, we’ve seen an explosion of AI and machine learning technology that, so far, has shown us a fun side with people using AI for creating, planning, and ideating in a big way.
These emerging technologies are being used to revolutionize everything from healthcare to entertainment. But as with any new technology, people are still trying to wrap their heads around it. And one of the biggest sources of this confusion comes from the similarities and overlap between two of the key terms in this field: AI and machine learning. So in this article, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Platform team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRI-O: Applying seccomp profiles from OCI registries]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/07/cri-o-seccomp-oci-artifacts/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/07/cri-o-seccomp-oci-artifacts/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
Seccomp stands for secure computing mode and has been a feature of the Linux
kernel since version 2.6.12. It can be used to sandbox the privileges of a
process, restricting the calls it is able to make from userspace into the
kernel. Kubernetes lets you automatically apply seccomp profiles loaded onto a
node to your Pods and containers.
But distributing those seccomp profiles is a major challenge in Kubernetes,
because the JSON files have to be available on all nodes where a workload can
possibly run. Projects like the Security Profiles
Operator solve that problem by
running as a daemon within the cluster, which makes me wonder which part of that
distribution could be done by the container
runtime.
Runtimes usually apply the profiles from a local path, for example:
a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Indicates Success for Your Camunda POC?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102164</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/what-indicates-success-camunda-poc/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T20:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you measure and demonstrate success? Learn how to determine success for your Camunda proof of concept.
The post What Indicates Success for Your Camunda POC? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon RDS now supports io2 Block Express volumes for mission-critical database workloads]]></title>
        <id>e1f154044ec7ddbc580e087aadbcf76d2131d2a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-rds-now-supports-io2-block-express-volumes-for-mission-critical-database-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 7, 2024: Post updated to change GB to GiB. March 8, 2024: Post updated to reflect correct region availability. Today, I am pleased to announce the availability of Provisioned IOPS (PIOPS) io2 Block Express storage volumes for all database engines in Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS). Amazon RDS provides you the flexibility to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the newest Heroes of the year – March 2024]]></title>
        <id>1c28a1aa7d172c4f3ef6f586d0d873794d1f054c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-newest-heroes-of-the-year-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Heroes are inspirational thought leaders who go above and beyond to knowledge share in a variety of ways. You can find them speaking at local meetups, AWS Community Days, or even at re:Invent. And these technical experts are never done learning—they’re passionate about solving problems and creating content to enable the community to build […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Croissant: a metadata format for ML-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/croissant-metadata-format-for-ml-ready.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/croissant-metadata-format-for-ml-ready.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Omar Benjelloun, Software Engineer, Google Research, and Peter Mattson, Software Engineer, Google Core ML and President, MLCommons Association






Machine learning (ML) practitioners looking to reuse existing datasets to train an ML model often spend a lot of time understanding the data, making sense of its organization, or figuring out what subset to use as features. So much time, in fact, that progress in the field of ML is hampered by a fundamental obstacle: the wide variety of data representations. 





ML datasets cover a broad range of content types, from text and structured data to images, audio, and video. Even within datasets that cover the same types of content, every dataset has a unique ad hoc arrangement of files and data formats. This challenge reduces productivi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.18 GA improves enterprise reliability with Long-Term Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-18-ga-improves-enterprise-reliability-with-long-term-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-18-ga-improves-enterprise-reliability-with-long-term-support"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.18 improves enterprise reliability with Long-Term Support, fault-injection capabilities, and expanded Amazon ECS support for multi-runtime deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Enterprise Long-Term Support (LTS) improves operational efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-enterprise-long-term-support-lts-improves-operational-efficiency</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-enterprise-long-term-support-lts-improves-operational-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul Enterprise adds Long-Term Support (LTS) releases, reducing operational overhead and risk with extended maintenance and upgrade compatibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging trends in observability: GAI, AIOps, tools consolidation, and OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T17:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of the observability industry through the eyes of over 500 IT decision makers. Find out what’s top of mind for observability in 2024, from AIOps to GAI, tool consolidation and more from yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging trends in observability: GAI, AIOps, tools consolidation, and OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T17:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As technology evolution continues at its rapid pace, so does observability. Observability is becoming critical to driving positive business outcomes, and we wanted to understand how users are evaluating trends and their impact over the coming years. And while every organization approaches observability around its own unique needs, there are usually specific trends and shifts that the broader industry undergoes. 

Elastic® recently surveyed over 500 observability decision-makers around key topics in modern observability. Respondents were asked about the progress and benefits they are seeing in their observability initiatives, and the impact of generative AI and OpenTelemetry on observability. The survey, completed with Dimensional Research in January 2024, delivered some surprising results …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here's how merge queue transformed the way GitHub deploys changes to production at scale, so you can do the same for your organization.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/">How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-06-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>With this version, customers can choose how to best scale their security strategy, gain more control over deployments, and so much more.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-now-generally-available/">GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 is now generally available</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrich your Elasticsearch documents with Logstash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using a jdbc static filter connected to Elasticsearch might speed up your Logstash enrichment pipeline....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Pilato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrich your Elasticsearch documents with Logstash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[input {
  # Read all documents from Elasticsearch
  elasticsearch {
    hosts => ["${ELASTICSEARCH_URL}"]
    user => "elastic"
    password => "${ELASTIC_PASSWORD}"
    index => "kibana_sample_data_logs"
    docinfo => true
    ecs_compatibility => "disabled"
  }
}
filter {
  # Enrich every document with Elasticsearch
  elasticsearch {
    hosts => ["${ELASTICSEARCH_URL}"]
    user => "elastic"
    password => "${ELASTIC_PASSWORD}"
    index => "vip"
    query => "ip:%{[clientip]}"
    sort => "ip:desc"
    fields => {
      "[name]" => "[name]"
      "[vip]" => "[vip]"
    }
  }
  mutate { 
    remove_field => ["@version", "@timestamp"] 
  }
}
output {
  if [name] {
    # Write all modified documents to Elasticsearch
    elasticsearch {
      manage_template => false
      hosts => ["${E…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Pilato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[告知イラスト] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:2550689798289615231</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/2550689798289615231"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bending pause times to your will with Generational ZGC]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/256629c9386b</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/bending-pause-times-to-your-will-with-generational-zgc-256629c9386b?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T01:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The surprising and not so surprising benefits of generations in the Z Garbage Collector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free data transfer out to internet when moving out of AWS]]></title>
        <id>75d716af79fb6ef0c02f33b4b7ca18cfd5dd4743</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/free-data-transfer-out-to-internet-when-moving-out-of-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You told us one of the primary reasons to adopt Amazon Web Services (AWS) is the broad choice of services we offer, enabling you to innovate, build, deploy, and monitor your workloads. AWS has continuously expanded its services to support virtually any cloud workload. It now offers over 200 fully featured services for compute, storage, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping repository maintainer information accurate]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T21:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover how keeping repository maintainer information accurate through CODEOWNERS files and automating maintenance with tools like cleanowners fosters efficient collaboration and sustainable software projects.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/">Keeping repository maintainer information accurate</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolving from Rule-based Classifier: Machine Learning Powered Auto Remediation in Netflix Data…]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/039d5efd115b</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/evolving-from-rule-based-classifier-machine-learning-powered-auto-remediation-in-netflix-data-039d5efd115b?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Binbing Hou, Stephanie Vezich Tamayo, Xiao Chen, Liang Tian, Troy Ristow, Haoyuan Wang, Snehal Chennuru, Pawan Dixit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Learning Pathway: Accelerate your business with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-04-github-copilot-learning-pathway-accelerate-your-business-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-github-copilot-learning-pathway-accelerate-your-business-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn what GitHub Copilot can help your business achieve in this expert-guided GitHub Learning Pathway, featuring insights from tech leaders at top organizations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-github-copilot-learning-pathway-accelerate-your-business-with-ai/">GitHub Copilot Learning Pathway: Accelerate your business with AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — New models for Amazon Bedrock, CloudFront embedded POPs, and more — March 4, 2024]]></title>
        <id>f440c1bc8007c2c450a5b97f3269e968ed59221b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-models-for-amazon-bedrock-cloudfront-embedded-pops-and-more-march-4-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T16:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This has been a busy week – we introduced a new kind of Amazon CloudFront infrastructure, more efficient ways to analyze data stored on Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3), and new generative AI capabilities. Last week’s launches Here’s what got my attention: Amazon Bedrock – Mistral AI’s Mixtral 8x7B and Mistral 7B foundation models […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s Claude 3 Sonnet foundation model is now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>afa44e98fb3dea486d0fe36887411e429dd8794c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/anthropics-claude-3-sonnet-foundation-model-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T16:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September 2023, we announced a strategic collaboration with Anthropic that brought together their respective technology and expertise in safer generative artificial intelligence (AI), to accelerate the development of Anthropic’s Claude foundation models (FMs) and make them widely accessible to AWS customers. You can get early access to unique features of Anthropic’s Claude model in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at APS 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/google-at-aps-2024.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/google-at-aps-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kate Weber and Shannon Leon, Google Research, Quantum AI Team




Today the 2024 March Meeting of the American Physical Society (APS) kicks off in Minneapolis, MN. A premier conference on topics ranging across physics and related fields, APS 2024 brings together researchers, students, and industry professionals to share their discoveries and build partnerships with the goal of realizing fundamental advances in physics-related sciences and technology. 



This year, Google has a strong presence at APS with a booth hosted by the Google Quantum AI team, 50+ talks throughout the conference, and participation in conference organizing activities, special sessions and events. Attending APS 2024 in person? Come visit Google’s Quantum AI booth to learn more about the exciting work we’re d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI models now available on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>89d81f50ad915d63aec01b16bf9f82dd3a8cf534</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/mistral-ai-models-now-available-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T21:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update 3/13/2024: Added additional Region availability Last week, we announced that Mistral AI models are coming to Amazon Bedrock. In that post, we elaborated on a few reasons why Mistral AI models may be a good fit for you. Mistral AI offers a balance of cost and performance, fast inference speed, transparency and trust, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on SIG Cloud Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/01/sig-cloud-provider-spotlight-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/01/sig-cloud-provider-spotlight-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Arujjwal Negi
One of the most popular ways developers use Kubernetes-related services is via cloud providers, but
have you ever wondered how cloud providers can do that? How does this whole process of integration
of Kubernetes to various cloud providers happen? To answer that, let's put the spotlight on SIG
Cloud Provider.
SIG Cloud Provider works to create seamless integrations between Kubernetes and various cloud
providers. Their mission? Keeping the Kubernetes ecosystem fair and open for all. By setting clear
standards and requirements, they ensure every cloud provider plays nicely with Kubernetes. It is
their responsibility to configure cluster components to enable cloud provider integrations.
In this blog of the SIG Spotlight series, Arujjwal Negi interviews
Michael McCune (Re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · February 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-29-game-bytes-february-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-game-bytes-february-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T19:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on! 🕹️</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-game-bytes-february-2024/">Game Bytes · February 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Kayla: A college student and open source ambassador]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-29-meet-kayla-a-college-student-and-open-source-ambassador/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-meet-kayla-a-college-student-and-open-source-ambassador/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From learner to mentor, Kayla, an All In for Students ambassador, has become an open source leader on her campus.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-meet-kayla-a-college-student-and-open-source-ambassador/">Meet Kayla: A college student and open source ambassador</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping secrets out of public repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-29-keeping-secrets-out-of-public-repositories/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-keeping-secrets-out-of-public-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>With push protection now enabled by default, GitHub helps open source developers safeguard their secrets, and their reputations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-keeping-secrets-out-of-public-repositories/">Keeping secrets out of public repositories</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppFabric support expands how HashiCorp Terraform Cloud integrates with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/appfabric-support-expands-how-hashicorp-terraform-cloud-integrates-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/appfabric-support-expands-how-hashicorp-terraform-cloud-integrates-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud now offers even more ways to connect, secure and provision infrastructure with AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Business Process and Why Should You Care]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101992</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/what-is-a-business-process-why-important/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are business processes, and why are they important? Learn how they work, types of business processes, & why well-orchestrated processes are critical.
The post What is a Business Process and Why Should You Care appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X.509 certificate management with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/certificate-management-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/certificate-management-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll look at practical public key certificate management in HashiCorp Vault using dynamic secrets rotation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Delivered 408% ROI According to New Study]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101985</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/camunda-delivered-408-roi-new-study/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T16:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Study demonstrates significant benefits to adopting Camunda and provides a powerful customizable tool to help you understand the impact it can have on your organization.
The post Camunda Delivered 408% ROI According to New Study appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — .Net Runtime for AWS Lambda, PartyRock Hackathon, and more — February 26, 2024]]></title>
        <id>557c364821cd44b128215dafdb19f284275de1ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-net-runtime-for-aws-lambda-partyrock-hackathon-and-more-february-26-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Community AWS re:invent 2023 re:caps continue! Recently, I was invited to participate in one of these events hosted by the AWS User Group Kenya, and was able to learn and spend time with this amazing community. AWS User Group Kenya Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention during the previous […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp and Google Cloud announce GKE Autopilot support for Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-and-google-cloud-announce-gke-autopilot-support-for-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-and-google-cloud-announce-gke-autopilot-support-for-consul"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul is now supported in Google Cloud’s GKE Autopilot partner program, enabling deployment of Consul to GKE Autopilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing bpftop: Streamlining eBPF performance optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6a727c1ae2e5</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/announcing-bpftop-streamlining-ebpf-performance-optimization-6a727c1ae2e5?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T16:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jose Fernandez]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Region in Mexico is in the works]]></title>
        <id>1c1efeb64d8a5864b3db0f67a64b46b33d53cb69</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-region-in-mexico-is-in-the-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T14:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am happy to announce that we are working on an AWS Region in Mexico. This AWS Mexico (Central) Region will be the second Region in Latin America joining the AWS South America (São Paulo) Region and will give AWS customers the ability to run workloads and store data that must remain in-country. Mexico […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Insights to Action: Harnessing Camunda Optimize for Effective Development]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101840</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/insights-to-action-camunda-optimize-effective-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Samantha, as a developer and a new Camunda user, explored Camunda Optimize to enhance their development process.
The post From Insights to Action: Harnessing Camunda Optimize for Effective Development appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samantha Holstine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI models coming soon to Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>308fb7192ffb87eae22e5e1a861fa7efc2aa36a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/mistral-ai-models-coming-soon-to-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI, an AI company based in France, is on a mission to elevate publicly available models to state-of-the-art performance. They specialize in creating fast and secure large language models (LLMs) that can be used for various tasks, from chatbots to code generation. We’re pleased to announce that two high-performing Mistral AI models, Mistral 7B […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VideoPrism: A foundational visual encoder for video understanding]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/videoprism-foundational-visual-encoder.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/videoprism-foundational-visual-encoder.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Long Zhao, Senior Research Scientist, and Ting Liu, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research




An astounding number of videos are available on the Web, covering a variety of content from everyday moments people share to historical moments to scientific observations, each of which contains a unique record of the world. The right tools could help researchers analyze these videos, transforming how we understand the world around us.

 

Videos offer dynamic visual content far more rich than static images, capturing movement, changes, and dynamic relationships between entities. Analyzing this complexity, along with the immense diversity of publicly available video data, demands models that go beyond traditional image understanding. Consequently, many of the approaches that be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A look into the Kubernetes Book Club]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/02/22/k8s-book-club/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/02/22/k8s-book-club/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
Learning Kubernetes and the entire ecosystem of technologies around it is not without its
challenges. In this interview, we will talk with Carlos Santana
(AWS) to learn a bit more about how he created the
Kubernetes Book Club, how it works, and
how anyone can join in to take advantage of a community-based learning experience.

Frederico Muñoz (FSM): Hello Carlos, thank you so much for your availability. To start with,
could you tell us a bit about yourself?
Carlos Santana (CS): Of course. My experience in deploying Kubernetes in production six
years ago opened the door for me to join Knative and then contribute to
Kubernetes through the Release Team. Working on upstream Kubernetes has been one of the best
experiences I've had in open-source. Over the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advances in private training for production on-device language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/advances-in-private-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/advances-in-private-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zheng Xu, Research Scientist, and Yanxiang Zhang, Software Engineer, Google




Language models (LMs) trained to predict the next word given input text are the key technology for many applications [1, 2]. In Gboard, LMs are used to improve users’ typing experience by supporting features like next word prediction (NWP), Smart Compose, smart completion and suggestion, slide to type, and proofread. Deploying models on users’ devices rather than enterprise servers has advantages like lower latency and better privacy for model usage. While training on-device models directly from user data effectively improves the utility performance for applications such as NWP and smart text selection, protecting the privacy of user data for model training is important. 









Gboard features powe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I use Boundary to build automation for live streams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-i-use-boundary-to-build-automation-for-live-streams</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-i-use-boundary-to-build-automation-for-live-streams"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how HashiCorp Developer Advocate Rosemary Wang uses HashiCorp Boundary on live streams to automate access to servers and record commands to build into future automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — AWS Control Tower new API, TLS 1.3 with API Gateway, Private Marketplace Catalogs, and more — February 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>b59bdf9a07666673edfdba0242f35b6312ab73cb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-control-tower-new-api-tls-1-3-with-api-gateway-private-marketplace-catalogs-and-more-february-19-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T18:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past week, our service teams have continued to innovate on your behalf, and a lot has happened in the Amazon Web Services (AWS) universe that I want to tell you about. I’ll also share about all the AWS Community events and initiatives that are happening around the world. Let’s dive in! Last week’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>