<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-06-23T01:55:08.059Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-23T01:55:08.059Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Codespaces for Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-22-whats-new-in-codespaces-for-organizations/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-22-whats-new-in-codespaces-for-organizations/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T21:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re releasing exciting functionalities that will enable organizations to confidently manage and scale with Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Advantage in Learning from Experiments]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/quantum-advantage-in-learning-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/quantum-advantage-in-learning-from.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T18:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jarrod McClean, Staff Research Scientist, Google Quantum AI, and Hsin-Yuan Huang, Graduate Student, Caltech 
In efforts to learn about the quantum world, scientists face a big obstacle: their classical experience of the world. Whenever a quantum system is measured, the act of this measurement destroys the “quantumness” of the state. For example, if the quantum state is in a superposition of two locations, where it can seem to be in two places at the same time, once it is measured, it will randomly appear either ”here” or “there”, but not both. We only ever see the classical shadows cast by this strange quantum world. 
A growing number of experiments are implementing machine learning (ML) algorithms to aid in analyzing data, but these have the same limitations as the people they a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Urban Trees Across North America with the Auto Arborist Dataset]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/mapping-urban-trees-across-north.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/mapping-urban-trees-across-north.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Beery, Student Researcher, and Jonathan Huang, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception Team 
Over four billion people live in cities around the globe, and while most people interact daily with others — at the grocery store, on public transit, at work — they may take for granted their frequent interactions with the diverse plants and animals that comprise fragile urban ecosystems. Trees in cities, called urban forests, provide critical benefits for public health and wellbeing and will prove integral to urban climate adaptation. They filter air and water, capture stormwater runoff, sequester atmospheric carbon dioxide, and limit erosion and drought. Shade from urban trees reduces energy-expensive cooling costs and mitigates urban heat islands. In the US alone, urban fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modeling a Bill’s Journey through the U.S. House of Representatives]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57197</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/modeling-a-bills-journey-through-the-u-s-house-of-representatives/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bill's journey through the U.S. House of Representatives is modeled in Camunda Platform 8 and BPMN. Along the way, see how forms incorporate human tasks throughout the process and how DMN helps minimize errors.
The post Modeling a Bill’s Journey through the U.S. House of Representatives appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Contributors: Announcing new features and ways to earn points]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-contributors-announcing-new-features-and-ways-to-earn-points</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-contributors-announcing-new-features-and-ways-to-earn-points"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Contributors asked, and we listened! Learn more about the new ways to earn points and features in the Elastic Contributor Program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia Petrie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Contributors: Announcing new features and ways to earn points]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-contributors-announcing-new-features-and-ways-to-earn-points</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-contributors-announcing-new-features-and-ways-to-earn-points"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We created the Elastic Contributor Program in 2019 to reward and recognize the hard work of our awesome contributors, encourage knowledge sharing within the Elastic community, and build friendly competition around contributions. Over four cycles and through Contributors’ invaluable feedback, we’ve learned so much and are committed to expanding the program with new features and ways to earn points.
[Related article: 5 reasons to join the Elastic Contributor Program
,What’s new?
1. Additional opportunities to earn bonus points
Contributors can now earn bonus points for submitting content in different solutions and contribution types. We encourage our contributors to venture outside of one solution area, so we provide bonus points to those who submit at least three contributions under Elast…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia Petrie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digitally signing Ansible Content Collections using private automation hub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/digitally-signing-ansible-content-collections-using-private-automation-hub</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/digitally-signing-ansible-content-collections-using-private-automation-hub"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform can manage and execute automation made from many different origins, coming from Red Hat product teams, ISV partners, community and private contributors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet Below Deck, Part IV – Distributed Transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=fleet&amp;p=256817</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/fleet/2022/06/fleet-below-deck-part-iv-distributed-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T11:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a multipart series on building Fleet, a next-generation IDE by JetBrains. Part I – Architecture Overview Part II – Breaking Down the Editor Part III – State Management Part IV – Distributed Transactions In Part III of this series, we focused on how we represent, store, and change elements of Fleet’s state. In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vitaly Bragilevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blueprint Support Comes to ReSharper C++]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rscpp&amp;p=258246</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rscpp/2022/06/22/blueprint-support/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T10:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blueprint files are written in binary form and are usually edited visually. However, they contain a lot of useful information for the developers of the C++ parts of games, since the Blueprint designers extend the baseline system implemented in C++ with Blueprint-specific markup. With all the Blueprint details, developers can avoid code changes that unexpectedly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elvira Mustafina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fear and footnotes]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41313</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/700093062/0/sethsblog~Fear-and-footnotes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T08:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re trying to make an argument in a scientific journal or a history monograph, you’ll need footnotes. Show your work. Make it clear who came before and what you’re basing your thesis on. But it seems as though when we’re nervous and afraid, we don’t need any footnotes. “No,” is all we have to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.11 Adds Kubernetes Secrets Engine, PKI Updates, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-11</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-11"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.11 focuses on improving Vault’s core workflows and making key features production-ready.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Launch and Free Public Beta of HCP Boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-and-free-public-beta-of-hcp-boundary</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-and-free-public-beta-of-hcp-boundary"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary is now available as a managed service on the HashiCorp Cloud Platform in  free public beta to standardize secure remote access to critical infrastructure regardless of where it resides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.3 Introduces HA Logical Gateways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-3-introduces-ha-logical-gateways</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-3-introduces-ha-logical-gateways"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest release of the HashiCorp Consul API Gateway allows users to generate multiple instances of a logical gateway — avoiding single points of failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.13 Tech Preview: Cluster Peering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-tech-preview-cluster-peering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-tech-preview-cluster-peering"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cluster peering in Consul 1.13 offers a whole new model of how Consul handles cross-cluster federation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Azure to go GA, Plus More Consul News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure-to-go-ga-plus-more-consul-news</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure-to-go-ga-plus-more-consul-news"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul is becoming generally available on Azure, Consul API Gateway version 0.3 is going GA, and Consul 1.13 is due later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What If? 2 Countdown]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2636/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2636/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/what_if_2_countdown.png" title="If you don't end the 99 Bottles of Beer recursion at N=0 it just becomes The Other Song That Never Ends." alt="If you don't end the 99 Bottles of Beer recursion at N=0 it just becomes The Other Song That Never Ends." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1.3 Is Out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=258019</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/06/intellij-idea-2022-1-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T18:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new bug-fix update – IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1.3 – is now available!   You can get the latest version from inside the IDE, via the Toolbox App, or by using snaps for Ubuntu. It is also possible to download it from our website. Here are the most notable fixes included in v2022.1.3: Fixed the issues that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot is generally available to all developers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-21-github-copilot-is-generally-available-to-all-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-21-github-copilot-is-generally-available-to-all-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T16:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re making GitHub Copilot, an AI pair programmer that suggests code in your editor, generally available to all developers for $10 USD/month or $100 USD/year. It will also be free to use for verified students and maintainers of popular open source projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IoT ExpressLink Now Generally Available – Quickly Develop Devices That Connect Securely to AWS Cloud]]></title>
        <id>487d07cf76d37f913a79c647cc30be56978e730d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-iot-expresslink-now-generally-available-quickly-develop-devices-that-connect-securely-to-aws-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T14:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced AWS IoT ExpressLink, software for partner-manufactured connectivity modules that makes it easier and faster for original equipment manufacturers to connect any type of product to the cloud, such as industrial sensors, small and large home appliances, irrigation systems, and medical devices. Today we announce the general availability of AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at CVPR 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/google-at-cvpr-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/google-at-cvpr-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T14:09:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shaina Mehta and Kristen Borg, Program Managers 
This week marks the beginning of the premier annual Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition conference (CVPR 2022), held both in-person in New Orleans, LA and virtually. As a leader in computer vision research and a Platinum Sponsor, Google will have a strong presence across CVPR 2022 with over 80 papers being presented at the main conference and active involvement in a number of conference workshops and tutorials. 
If you are attending CVPR this year, please stop by our booth and chat with our researchers who are actively exploring the latest machine learning techniques for application to various areas of machine perception. Our researchers will also be available to talk about and demo several recent efforts, including on-device M…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Kotlin Build Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=256438</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/06/introducing-kotlin-build-reports/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T12:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting with Kotlin 1.7.0, you can create build reports for Kotlin compiler tasks. Reports contain durations of different compilation phases and reasons why incremental compilation could not be used. This functionality is still Experimental, so the list of metrics may change. TRY BUILD REPORTS Build reports are useful when you want to investigate issues with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrey Uskov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thoughts on the solstice]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43193</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699951816/0/sethsblog~Thoughts-on-the-solstice/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T08:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For half the planet, today is the longest day of the year. For the rest of us, the shortest. There was a solstice before there were people. All of our other holidays don’t fit that definition. They’re invented. Short-lived. Worldwide, it’s a moment to realize that this is the only planet in the known universe […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 21st, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/21/this-week-in-spring-june-21st-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/21/this-week-in-spring-june-21st-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you? It’s been a hot minute since we last chatted. I was in Germany this time last week. Now, I’m back in beautiful San Francisco. Today the weather will climb to a monumental 84 F! That’s very unusual, for any time of the year, here in San Francisco. Most places here in San Francisco don’t have air conditioning. Some have heating. I bought a brand new condo in 2014 and it didn’t have air conditioning. You just open the window. I am privileged enough that I have air conditioning today, of course. I mention all this to say that it’s hot here! I worry for the elderly! When it gets this hot, the YMCA and other organizations typically invite elderly people to come in and get some cool air and water. It’s dangerous. Some days it gets even hotter. Very rare, but it does happen. I hope you’re all doing well. Take care of yourselves and each other, my friends. 

And, speaking of being hot, let’s look at this week’s roundup of the latest-and-greatest that’s hot off the press! 


  
Bootiful Podcast: Spring Framework contributor Sébastien Deleuze on GraalVM, AOT, project Leyden, and WebAssembly

  
CVE report published for Spring Cloud Function

  
Debugging Collections, Streams and Watch Renderers

  
Difference Between Flux.create and Flux.generate

  
Handle Spring Security Exceptions With @ExceptionHandler

  
MongoDB Composite Key With Spring Data

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.3.1 available now

  
Monitoring Spring Boot applications using Spring Boot Admin

  
Spring Data 2021.2.1 and 2021.1.5 released

  
Spring Data JPA – Run an App Without a Database

  
Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression Injection Vulnerability (CVE-2022-22980)

  
Spring Framework 5.3.21 available now

  
Spring Security 5.7.2 and 5.6.6 available now

  
Spring Tools 4.15.0 released

  
Spring Tools 4.15.1 released

  
What are the Spring Boot Default Memory Settings?

  
A Guide to Docker Private Registry

  
Is There a Destructor in Java?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HashiCorp Developer Site is Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hashicorp-developer-site-is-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hashicorp-developer-site-is-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our new documentation platform makes it easy to learn from dozens of interactive lab environments, hundreds of tutorials, and thousands of reference docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Adds Drift Detection for Infrastructure Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-drift-detection-for-infrastructure-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-drift-detection-for-infrastructure-management"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drift Detection for Terraform Cloud continuously checks infrastructure state to detect and notify operators of any changes, minimizing risk, downtime, and costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the HCP Waypoint Private Beta Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcp-waypoint-private-beta-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcp-waypoint-private-beta-program"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HCP Waypoint Private Beta Program allows select early adopters to onboard applications and try out HCP Waypoint to develop a proof of concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet the Rainbow Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-rainbow-stack-erg</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-rainbow-stack-erg"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June kicks off Pride season, which started in the U.S and is now celebrated worldwide. It’s an important time for our Rainbow Stack ERG, which welcomes everyone who identifies as LGBTQIA+ and their allies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How public sector organisations connect people with data in the United Kingdom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-public-sector-organisations-connect-people-with-data-in-the-United-Kingdom</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-public-sector-organisations-connect-people-with-data-in-the-United-Kingdom"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public sector leaders gathered in London to discuss how they use data to protect countries from cyber threats, enable police to make discerning decisions, and analyze data for public health breakthroughs. Presentation highlights are captured here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzzanna Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The multicloud advantage: scalability, reliability, flexibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/multicloud-advantage-scalability-reliability-flexibility</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/multicloud-advantage-scalability-reliability-flexibility"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As multicloud adoption grows, so do the risks of sticking with single providers or legacy systems]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet the Rainbow Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-rainbow-stack-erg</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-rainbow-stack-erg"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Employee resource groups, or as we like to call them, Elastician resource groups, have been an informal part of Elastic’s culture since 2016. They started as Slack channels and were formalized in 2021 to ensure that the members would have structure, budget, and ultimately, a voice based on any dimension of diversity, identity, allyship, and advocacy. This was an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy.

Our ERGs are aligned to shared identities, interests, affinities, or allyships. The goal is to create a community of people with something in common and to encourage sharing, learning, and networking. Each has visions and goals they are working towards besides building a sense of community and belonging.
Our Core ERGs
We have seven formal ERGs: The Accessibl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How public sector organisations connect people with data in the United Kingdom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-public-sector-organisations-connect-people-with-data-in-the-United-Kingdom</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-public-sector-organisations-connect-people-with-data-in-the-United-Kingdom"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We have all had to embrace change as a result of the pandemic, be smarter about our online activities due to increased cyber crime, and stay informed geo-politically in light of recent events in Ukraine. We are not, however, on the front lines like public sector leaders and teams. Many of us do not realise just how quickly the public sector needs to move to respond to factors like these in order to sustain our way of life in a changing world. And the key to public sector agility? Connecting people with data.

This theme was made clear at a recent ElasticON Public Sector event in London, where UK public sector leaders, including Gav Smith, Director General for Technology & SRO for National Security Data, GCHQ, shared how their organisations have “become a product of their data, and a prod…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzzanna Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The multicloud advantage: scalability, reliability, flexibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/multicloud-advantage-scalability-reliability-flexibility</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/multicloud-advantage-scalability-reliability-flexibility"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Just as companies discovered the value of cloud storage in recent years, many are starting to benefit from managing multiple cloud systems. Already, more than three-fourths of enterprise organizations use two cloud systems, and roughly a quarter have implemented three or more.

CIOs are leaning into multicloud frameworks for a variety of reasons, such as managing software designed for specific cloud environments, ensuring better system reliability, or streamlining a collection of technology infrastructures inherited through acquisition. Experts say adoption rates will continue to climb for important reasons: The cloud makes enterprise data available anytime and from anywhere and promises sophisticated analytics and top-notch security — without the costs of running or maintaining data cen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.2 and 5.6.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-security-5-7-2-and-5-6-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-security-5-7-2-and-5-6-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.7.2 and 5.6.6 are available now.



You can find more details about the respective releases here and
 here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – High Volume Outbound Communication with Amazon Connect Outbound Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>a20b9048be0b3be3a34bbd843c36e4433e02d727</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-high-volume-outbound-communication-with-amazon-connect-outbound-campaigns/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T19:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new high volume outbound communication capability in Amazon Connect which was announced at Enterprise Connect last year, is now generally available to all. It is named Amazon Connect outbound campaigns. If you haven’t heard about Amazon Connect, it is an easy-to-use cloud contact center service that helps companies of any size deliver superior customer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo – UX/Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64531</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-ux-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T18:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I took the road less traveled, and that has made all the difference.
The post DevOps Dojo – UX/Accessibility appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – June 20, 2022]]></title>
        <id>a332bdf7b28369cb096731e12bebdd69553bacc1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-20-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T17:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Last Week’s Launches It’s been a quiet week on the AWS News Blog, however a glance at What’s New page shows the various service teams have been busy as usual. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub enables the development of functional safety applications by adding support for coding standards AUTOSAR C++  and CERT C++]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-20-adding-support-for-coding-standards-autosar-c-and-cert-c/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-20-adding-support-for-coding-standards-autosar-c-and-cert-c/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub is excited to announce the release of CodeQL queries that implement the standards CERT C++ and AUTOSAR C++. These queries can aid developers looking to demonstrate ISO 26262 Part 6 process compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Phases of Infrastructure Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-3-phases-of-infrastructure-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-3-phases-of-infrastructure-automation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From adoption to standardization to operating and optimizing at scale, the evolution of infrastructure automation is critical to modern hybrid and multi-cloud environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar Recording and Q&A Session: Space – Everything You Need to Start a New Software Development Project]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=257871</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2022/06/20/webinar-recording-start-a-new-software-development-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T15:44:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have a brilliant idea for a project? The recording of our latest webinar, “Space – everything you need to start a new software development project”, is now available on the JetBrains YouTube channel. In this webinar, we explain how Space can help speed up the development, collaboration, and communication processes in your team. Read […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Berendeeva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.3.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-authorization-server-0-3-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-authorization-server-0-3-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.3.1.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.3.1'




See the release notes for complete details.



This release includes downgrading to JDK 1.8 baseline along with some minor enhancements and bug fixes.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Automation Controller for API Driven Workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/scaling-automation-controller-for-api-driven-workloads</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/scaling-automation-controller-for-api-driven-workloads"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When scaling automation controller in an enterprise organization, administrators are faced with more clients automating their interactions with its REST API. As with any web application, automation controller has a finite capacity to serve web requests, and  web clients can experience degraded service if that capacity is met or superseded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elijah Delee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.2.1 and 2021.1.5 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-2021-2-1-and-2021-1-5-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-2021-2-1-and-2021-1-5-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T12:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce Spring Data service releases 2021.2.1 and 2021.1.5.
Both releases ship with a fix for mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot 2.7.1 respective 2.6.9 are going to pick up these releases in the upcoming days.

In addition, these releases include fixes for one vulnerability:


  
CVE-2022-22980
 “Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression Injection Vulnerability”
 SpEL injection attack in MongoDB applications through repository query methods annotated with @Query or @Aggregation using parametrized SpEL statements with non-sanitized input.
 Severity: High


These new versions are recommended upgrades for all Spring Data production scenarios.

To round things off, here are the links to the individual modules, chan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression Injection Vulnerability (CVE-2022-22980)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-mongodb-spel-expression-injection-vulnerability-cve-2022-22980</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-mongodb-spel-expression-injection-vulnerability-cve-2022-22980"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T12:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates 


  
[06-20] CVE-2022-22980 is published

  
[06-20] Spring Data MongoDB 3.4.1 and 3.3.5 are available


Table of Contents


  
Overview

  
Vulnerability

  
Am I Impacted

  
Status

  
Suggested Workarounds


Overview

We would like to announce that we have released Spring Data MongoDB 3.4.1 and 3.3.5 to address the following CVE report:


  
CVE-2022-22980: Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression injection vulnerability through annotated repository query methods


This vulnerability was responsibly reported by Zewei Zhang from NSFOCUS TIANJI Lab on Monday, June 13 2022. The full report will be published to MITRE and as security advisory under tanzu.vmware.com/security in the upcoming days.
Vulnerability

The vulnerability affects Spring Data MongoDB applications u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2 EAP #4: highlighting failed test assertions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=256875</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/06/phpstorm-2022-2-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T11:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to the 2022.2 EAP series! If you’re unsure about what our Early Access Program is, make sure to read the first post in this series. Let’s take a look at what’s new in this week’s EAP build. Download PhpStorm 2022.2 EAP Highlighting failed test assertions When a test assertion fails, we will now […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.2 EAP 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=257851</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/06/20/datagrip-2022-2-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T10:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, DataGrip 2022.2 EAP build #2 is available. Let’s take a closer look at what’s inside. Playground and Script resolve modes Resolving database objects in SQL scripts takes an understanding of what the objects mean. This is necessary for the IDE to provide you with correct code completion and treat the usages of the objects […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Live Stream – Event Streaming Applications: A Live Coding Session]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=257811</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/06/new-live-stream-event-streaming-applications-a-live-coding-session/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T10:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our next IntelliJ IDEA Live Stream will be about Event Streaming :-) Mala Gupta has invited Ko Turk who, during the session, will create a Spring Boot application with the use of Kafka and Springs Actuator. Additionally, Ko will explain how this application he develops compares with REST. Join us on Wednesday, June 29, at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ida Bzowska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of placebos]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43171</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699831270/0/sethsblog~The-rise-of-placebos/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a fan of appropriate placebos. They often have few side effects, they’re inexpensive and they work when used in the right situations. You can check out my rant on them here, it’s been read millions of times to date. A placebo isn’t just a medical intervention. It’s any tool we use to feel better […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superintelligent AIs]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2635/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2635/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/superintelligent_ais.png" title="Your scientists were so preoccupied with whether or not they should, they didn't stop to think if they could." alt="Your scientists were so preoccupied with whether or not they should, they didn't stop to think if they could." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The arc of history]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42056</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699738000/0/sethsblog~The-arc-of-history/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By every geologic measure, modern human life is a tiny blip, a spark of static on a very long-playing record. For most of the time that life has existed on Earth, there were no humans. And when there were human-like creatures, they spent much of their time doing not much. Nomads eat when they need […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acceptance vs. ennui]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43191</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699657182/0/sethsblog~Acceptance-vs-ennui/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T08:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best way to make things better is to see how they are. And then do something about it. Acknowledging the problem is not the same as giving up. Too often, we’d rather not hear about it, or we choose to catastrophize as a way of protecting ourselves from the reality of what’s actually happening. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.15.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/18/spring-tools-4-15-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/18/spring-tools-4-15-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.15.1 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: VScode incorrectly suggests removing @Autowired annotation from methods (#787)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: VScode quick fix should not suggest removing @Autowired annotation from JUnit tests (#786)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Not able to extract the new version of spring-tool-suite-4-4.15.0.RELEASE-e4.24.0-win32.win32.x86_64.self-extracting.jar on windows 11 (#788)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Cannot open Spring Boot Language Server Java Editor settings menu (#789)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-06-17-4151-release-incl-language-servers-version-1360

Spring Tools 4.15.2 is scheduled to be released in early August 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a more comprehensive dependency graph with build time detection]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-17-creating-comprehensive-dependency-graph-build-time-detection/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-17-creating-comprehensive-dependency-graph-build-time-detection/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T19:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expand the completeness of your dependency graph by using the dependency submission API, which will create more comprehensive alerts on supply chain vulnerabilities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2022.2 EAP 3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=257610</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/06/2022-2-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T16:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new PyCharm 2022.2 EAP 3 build is available from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package (if you are using Ubuntu). If you are on macOS, there is a separate build for Apple Silicon (M1 chip).  Important: EAP builds are not fully tested and might be unstable. Keyboard shortcut to change the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 EAP 5: Support for Spring 6 and Spring Boot 3 Features, Enhanced HTTP Client, Kubernetes Updates and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=256683</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/06/intellij-idea-2022-2-eap-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T15:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 EAP 5 is now available! You can get the new build from our website, through the free Toolbox App, or as a snap for Ubuntu. This build brings numerous framework-specific updates that include support for Spring 6 and Spring Boot 3 features, support for Websocket and GraphQL requests,  improvements to the HTTP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 EAP #5]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=256697</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/06/webstorm-2022-2-eap-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T15:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 EAP build #5 is now available! To catch up on all the new features, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up-to-date. You can also manually download the EAP builds from our website. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.2 EAP #5 Is Out with Automatically Injected SQL Statements , Support for WebSocket and GraphQL Endpoints, and More!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=257420</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/06/17/goland-2022-2-eap-5-is-out-with-automatic-sql-injection-support-for-websockets-and-graphql-endpoints-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T15:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.2 EAP #5 is available. You can get the EAP build via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package for Ubuntu, or from inside GoLand select Check IDE updates for Early Access Program in Preferences / Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System Settings | Updates.  DOWNLOAD GOLAND 2022.2 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stores from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 17.06.2022]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64512</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stores-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-17-06-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T10:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last weekend was the Scottish Summit, while this event is local to the UK, people flew in globally to speak and attend one of the best Azure events around! There were so many great sessions from technical folks in the community and an amazing keynote from Dona Sarkar about accessibility.
The post Top Stores from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 17.06.2022 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carrying benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42200</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699541908/0/sethsblog~Carrying-benefits/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T08:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compared to easily-overlooked carrying costs, carrying benefits are practically invisible. Pay once, but come out ahead over and over again. There are habits, assets and learnings that seem too expensive right now. And so we simply stick with our status quo. When we take the time to itemize the carrying benefits and write them down, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Line Through HTTPS]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2634/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2634/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/red_line_through_https.png" title="Some organization has been paying to keep this up and it hasn't been removed from search results. Seems like two votes of confidence to me." alt="Some organization has been paying to keep this up and it hasn't been removed from search results. Seems like two votes of confidence to me." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · May 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-16-release-radar-may-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-16-release-radar-may-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T22:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each month, we highlight open source projects that have shipped major updates. These projects can include everything from world-changing technology to developer tooling, and weekend hobbies. We cover what the project is and some of their breaking changes. Read about the project, and browse their repositories. Without further ado, here are our top staff picks [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Android kernel mitigations obstacle race]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-16-the-android-kernel-mitigations-obstacle-race/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-16-the-android-kernel-mitigations-obstacle-race/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T16:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post I’ll exploit CVE-2022-22057, a use-after-free in the Qualcomm gpu kernel driver, to gain root and disable SELinux from the untrusted app sandbox on a Samsung Z flip 3. I’ll look at various mitigations that are implemented on modern Android devices and how they affect the exploit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Service Mesh Support for AWS Lambda Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul support for AWS Lambda is now available in public beta enabling services in the mesh to invoke AWS Lambda functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​HashiCorp Recognized as a Best Workplace in the Bay Area]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-recognized-as-a-best-workplace-in-the-bay-area</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-recognized-as-a-best-workplace-in-the-bay-area"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp was ranked 28 on the 2022 Great Place to Work and Fortune magazine Best Workplaces in the Bay Area list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Can’t I Delete a Process Definition in Camunda Platform 8?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57095</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/why-cant-i-delete-a-process-definition-in-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deleting process definitions in Camunda Platform 8 requires complex behavior across multiple components in the system.
The post Why Can’t I Delete a Process Definition in Camunda Platform 8? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carrying costs]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42197</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699402318/0/sethsblog~Carrying-costs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T08:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much does a puppy cost? At the shelter, maybe you need to put up a hundred dollar fee or donation. But that’s tiny compared to food, vet bills, time spent walking, chew toys, yak bones, bully sticks, groomers and those ridiculous dog costumes… perhaps $20,000 if you add it all up. Yet we tend […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bootiful Podcast: Spring Framework contributor Sébastien Deleuze on GraalVM, AOT, project Leyden, and WebAssembly]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/16/bootiful-podcast-spring-framework-contributor-s-bastien-deleuze-on-graalvm-aot-project-leyden-and-webassembly</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/16/bootiful-podcast-spring-framework-contributor-s-bastien-deleuze-on-graalvm-aot-project-leyden-and-webassembly"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring Framework contributor Sébastien Deleuze (@sdeleuze) on GraalVM, AOT, project Leyden, and WebAssembly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M3 (codename Kilburn) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m3-codename-kilburn-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m3-codename-kilburn-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T06:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Milestone 3 (M3) of the Spring Cloud 2022.0.0 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2022.0.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2022.0.0 Release Train

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.

Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M3 is compatible with Spring Boot 3.0.0-M3.
Spring Cloud Stream


  
Enhanced support for Kafka “tombstone” records via recently added support for BiFunction/BiConsumer

  
Added support for function-based error-handling, thus no longer requiring annotations


Spring Cloud Kubernetes


  
Load Config Maps and Secrets using spring.config.import removing the need to use B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Merge 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-15-git-merge-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-15-git-merge-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git Merge, the conference dedicated to bringing the Git community together returns on September 14-15 in Chicago, Illinois.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE report published for Spring Cloud Function]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/cve-report-published-for-spring-cloud-function</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/cve-report-published-for-spring-cloud-function"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Spring Cloud Function 3.2.6 to address the following CVE report.


  
CVE-2202-22979: Spring Cloud Function Dos Vulnerability 


Please review the information in the CVE report and upgrade immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect domain generation algorithm (DGA) activity with new Kibana integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-domain-generation-algorithm-activity-with-new-Kibana-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-domain-generation-algorithm-activity-with-new-Kibana-integration"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have added a DGA detection package to the Integrations app in Kibana. In a single click, you can install and start using the DGA model and associated assets, including ingest pipeline configurations, anomaly detection jobs, and detection rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Alvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect domain generation algorithm (DGA) activity with new Kibana integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-domain-generation-algorithm-activity-with-new-Kibana-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-domain-generation-algorithm-activity-with-new-Kibana-integration"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Searching for a way to help protect your network from potential domain generation algorithm (DGA) attacks? Look no further — a DGA detection package is now available in the Integrations app in Kibana. 

In a single click, users can install and start using the DGA model and associated assets, including ingest pipeline configurations, anomaly detection jobs, and detection rules. Read on for step-by-step instructions on installing and fully enabling the DGA package.

[Related article: Automating the Security Protections rapid response to malware]
What is a DGA?
A DGA is a technique employed by many malware authors to ensure that infection of a client machine evades defensive measures. The goal of this technique is to hide the communication between an infected client machine and the command …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Alvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.15.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-tools-4-15-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-tools-4-15-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.15.0 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
updated to Eclipse 2022-06 release (new and noteworthy)


fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: vscode-sts: an edge case of workspace symbol for @PutMapping (#781)

  
(VSCode) fixed: Failed to refresh live data from process 12704 - com.xxxx.xx.xxx.BillingServiceApp after retries: 10 (#748)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: The Spring Boot Language Server is not immediately shutdown after closing the last open editor to avoid the need to restart the server when you open the next file (related to #568)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: When opening symbols, open the compilation unit from the relevant project (#769)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: The issue with the internal web browser not being able to open HTTP URLs on macOS got fixed. If you prefer to use the internal browser instead of an external one, you can make that switch in the preferences.

  
(Concourse) fixed: Update Concourse registry-image schema (#777)

  
(Concourse) fixed: Add registry_mirror & across as a known properties (#752)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-06-15-4150-release-incl-language-servers-version-1340

Spring Tools 4.15.1 is scheduled to be released in early August 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prebuilding codespaces is generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-15-prebuilding-codespaces-is-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-15-prebuilding-codespaces-is-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teams and GHEC customers can now create blazing fast codespaces, even for your largest and most complex projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​Terraform Cloud Run Tasks with Styra DAS Provides OPA Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-with-styra-das-provides-opa-validation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-with-styra-das-provides-opa-validation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration of HashiCorp Terraform with OPA-founder Styra allows users to validate Terraform infrastructure as code with Open Policy Agent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Netflix Content Engineering makes a federated graph searchable (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/49348511c06c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/how-netflix-content-engineering-makes-a-federated-graph-searchable-part-2-49348511c06c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Alex Hutter, Falguni Jhaveri, and Senthil Sayeebaba]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub now publishes malware advisories in the GitHub Advisory Database]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-15-github-now-publishes-malware-advisories-in-the-github-advisory-database/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-15-github-now-publishes-malware-advisories-in-the-github-advisory-database/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To combat the prevalence of malware in the open source ecosystem, GitHub now publishes malware occurrences in the GitHub Advisory Database. These advisories power Dependabot alerts and remain forever free and usable by the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure - Network Access - blog #2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you to Hicham Mourad and Scott Harwell for co-authoring this blog.
 
Introduction
 
In this blog series, we will continue discussing the deployment of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Harwell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.21 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-framework-5-3-21-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-framework-5-3-21-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T09:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.21 is available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.21 includes 22 fixes and improvements.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some questions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43165</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699261769/0/sethsblog~Some-questions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s it for? What’s it for? What change do you seek to make? What’s the hard part? If you could learn one skill that would help your project, what would it be? How can you tell if it’s working? Would it be easier if you had help? Would it be easier to make an impact […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe Is Back: Join Us in Amsterdam or Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years as a fully digital event, HashiConf Europe will once again return to Amsterdam on 20-22 June 2022. Here’s what you can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harness the power of the cloud to build scalable search solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/harness-the-power-of-the-cloud-to-build-scalable-search-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/harness-the-power-of-the-cloud-to-build-scalable-search-solutions"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud is the best way to build highly scalable and performant search solutions using Elastic’s products across any cloud provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Anthem leverages big healthcare data to improve consumers’ lives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-anthem-leverages-big-healthcare-data-to-improve-consumers-lives</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-anthem-leverages-big-healthcare-data-to-improve-consumers-lives"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here we will share our Ansible-based automated deployment solution for ELK, which powers real-time internal search capabilities at Anthem, Inc. and helps the organization improve consumers’ health and wellbeing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miroslav Mihaylov, Ph.D., Anthem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harness the power of the cloud to build scalable search solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/harness-the-power-of-the-cloud-to-build-scalable-search-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/harness-the-power-of-the-cloud-to-build-scalable-search-solutions"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
There are many ways developers can host search applications built with Elastic, ranging from plugging into existing Kubernetes orchestrations to downloading and running the solutions in their own infrastructure. Ultimately, the choice is yours on how you want to manage these solutions. So, how can you ensure you choose the right hosting method? 

Across the board, the best — and easiest — decision is to go with the cloud. Elastic Cloud’s fully managed experience is the optimal way to build highly scalable and performant search solutions using Elastic’s products across any cloud provider. With Elastic Cloud, you can rapidly deploy in your favorite public cloud, or in multiple clouds, and extend the value of Elastic with cloud-native features.

Still not sure? Read on to learn about a few …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Anthem leverages big healthcare data to improve consumers’ lives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-anthem-leverages-big-healthcare-data-to-improve-consumers-lives</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-anthem-leverages-big-healthcare-data-to-improve-consumers-lives"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Challenges with healthcare data  
Healthcare data makes up a third of the world’s data and is projected to grow, in the next few years, at a faster pace than traditional data-rich industries like financial services and manufacturing.* The staggering data volumes in healthcare, in addition to its heterogeneity and fragmentation, represent substantial challenges to extracting data insights for improving healthcare outcomes of individuals and communities. 

At Anthem, Inc., we have undertaken various initiatives to address these challenges — most notably full-text search of healthcare claims.

In this post, we share with you our automated deployment solution for ELK stack. This deployment pattern is in use internally at Anthem to power real-time search capabilities on top of Anthem’s health…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miroslav Mihaylov, Ph.D., Anthem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer Hotline]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2633/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2633/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/astronomer_hotline.png" title="Employment statistics have to correct for the fact that the Weird Bug Hotline hires on a bunch of extra temporary staff every 17 years." alt="Employment statistics have to correct for the fact that the Weird Bug Hotline hires on a bunch of extra temporary staff every 17 years." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating GitHub theme creation with color tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-14-accelerating-github-theme-creation-with-color-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-14-accelerating-github-theme-creation-with-color-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why the GitHub Design Infrastructure team built a dedicated color tool and how they use it to create new color palettes for GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scanned Objects by Google Research: A Dataset of 3D-Scanned Common Household Items]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/scanned-objects-by-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/scanned-objects-by-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:06:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Laura Downs and Anthony Francis, Software Engineers, Robotics at Google  
Many recent advances in computer vision and robotics rely on deep learning, but training deep learning models requires a wide variety of data to generalize to new scenarios. Historically, deep learning for computer vision has relied on datasets with millions of items that were gathered by web scraping, examples of which include ImageNet, Open Images, YouTube-8M, and COCO. However, the process of creating these datasets can be labor-intensive, and can still exhibit labeling errors that can distort the perception of progress. Furthermore, this strategy does not readily generalize to arbitrary three-dimensional shapes or real-world robotic data.  
 

Real-world robotic data collection is very useful, but diffi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problems now (problems later)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41268</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699167198/0/sethsblog~Problems-now-problems-later/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People always address now problems before they work on later problems. Every time. On one night in 2004, you might have had two choices. You could go out for a fancy dinner with friends, or you could buy one share of Google at their IPO. A couple of decades later, your dinner is forgotten but […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57164</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1. Check out the latest improvements including the Management Dashboard, new reports, and Spring Boot migration. 
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (parts 5 and 6 of an ongoing series)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-5-and-6-of-an-ongoing-series</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-5-and-6-of-an-ongoing-series"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In thi^^^ these installments, we continue our series introducing the Spring for GraphQL project. This series features Spring for GraphQL lead Rossen Stoyanchev (@rstoya05) - whose work you may know from basically everything in the wide and wonderful world of Springdom having to do with the web (HTTP, RSocket, WebSockets, GraphQL, JSF, MVC, etc) - and GraphQL Java engine founder and lead Andi Marek (@andimarek) and of course yours truly, Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long (@starbuxman). It provides an in-depth look at all things Spring for GraphQL.

This week I’m publishing two new installments. 

The first of this week’s installments, part five of the series, looks at using GraphQL subscriptions to stream data in a way that is agnostic of the supported transport protoco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye Spring IDE - Welcome Spring Tools 4]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/goodbye-spring-ide-welcome-spring-tools-4</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/goodbye-spring-ide-welcome-spring-tools-4"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 31 of 2004, only a few months after version 1.0 of the Spring Framework itself got released, Torsten Jürgeleit created a repository and made the initial commits to a project that became the tooling support for Spring in Eclipse, the Spring IDE project (while the roots of that work are probably going back further in time, as the comment of the first commit to the repository reads like there was a CVS repository even before that time.). Shortly after, Christian Dupuis joined, led the project for many years and initiated the Spring Tool Suite on top of Spring IDE.

It’s been a long time since then.

On December 4 of 2017, a new chapter for the Spring tooling began with the introduction of the all-new Spring Tools 4 and its first public beta release, followed by the first GA releas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 14th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/this-week-in-spring-june-14th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/this-week-in-spring-june-14th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’ve just arrived in beautiful Berlin, Germany, for the forthcoming We Are Developers show with more than five thousand attendees. I was in Toronto, Canada, for the epic SpringOne Tour installment there. I’ve also had the privilege of taking these last two trips with my daughter, Kimly. She’s on summer break from school. It’s made the long miserable hours in economy bearable, and something for which I couldn’t be more grateful. I’m also looking forward to being at the upcoming SpringOne Tour installment in New York City, later this month. Don’t miss it! 

In the meantime, we’ve got a ton of good stuff to get to this week so let’s dive right in! 


  
Java architect Brian Goetz foreshadows an interesting new feature …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How technology leaders are overcoming challenges to cloud migration across financial, public, and telecom sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/technology-leaders-challenges-cloud-migration-financial-public-telecom</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/technology-leaders-challenges-cloud-migration-financial-public-telecom"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leaders across industries share how they are adopting cloud to drive speed and impact]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Rabinowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How technology leaders are overcoming challenges to cloud migration across financial, public, and telecom sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/technology-leaders-challenges-cloud-migration-financial-public-telecom</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/technology-leaders-challenges-cloud-migration-financial-public-telecom"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The value of an organization’s data is magnified in the cloud — enabling agility and new sources of revenue — but leaders must first overcome critical challenges. 
We interviewed executives in three economic sectors — financial services, public sector, and telecommunications — for their insights on the unique challenges and opportunities they face, and how they’re leading their organization to deliver stronger results in the cloud. Below are edited excerpts from the conversations.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltec70c92aca2e350c/62a92556c4d59b57e0c25686/roundtable.jpg,roundtable.jpgFinancial services: Cloud is a matter of trust,
Milind Nagnur, chief technology officer, Early Warning Services, parent company of the Zelle payment network

Financial institutio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Rabinowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56809</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/camunda-automation-platform-7180-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the second alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7.18. See what's new and learn how you can contribute. 
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 ways financial services leaders can stay ahead of the cybersecurity risk curve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-stay-ahead-of-the-cybersecurity-risk-curve</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-stay-ahead-of-the-cybersecurity-risk-curve"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting the assets of the financial institution and its clients is becoming harder. According to our recent co-sponsored study with ThoughtLab, there are still many steps that must be taken to ensure security in an emerging risk landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.2.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8.2.3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8.2.3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.2.3 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.2.3 over the previous patch versions in 8.2.x.
The 8.2.3 patch contains fixes and small enhancements for the stack. For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
8.2.3 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Landis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 ways financial services leaders can stay ahead of the cybersecurity risk curve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-stay-ahead-of-the-cybersecurity-risk-curve</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-stay-ahead-of-the-cybersecurity-risk-curve"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As financial institutions migrate to modern infrastructure and cloud services, bad actors have extended their skills and capabilities to achieve their missions. This is compounded by the fact that financial and payment vehicles continue to go virtual. Even the slightest breach can result in fines and reputational harm. 

Many financial institutions are successfully taking a risk-based approach to cybersecurity, according to our recent co-sponsored study with ThoughtLab. Cybersecurity Solutions for a Riskier World reports that 91% of financial services companies are either “mid-implementation” or “advanced” in maturity against the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) framework. 

While this is undoubtedly a positive sign for the industry, many steps still need to be taken…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.2.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8.2.3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8.2.3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Landis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – June 13, 2022]]></title>
        <id>f62346f0e4c3f5f23df31341fcd4572e7dafb8ca</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-13-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T19:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Last Week’s Launches I made a short trip to Austin, Texas last week in order to visit and learn from some customers. As is always the case, the days when […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure - Network Access - blog #1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you to Hicham Mourad and Scott Harwell for co-authoring this blog.
 
Introduction
 
In this blog series we will discuss the deployment of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure, specifically focusing on the deployment access types and what that means for accessing Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Azure after deployment completion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Harwell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handmade, original and significant]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43153</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699095656/0/sethsblog~Handmade-original-and-significant/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are still pockets of our culture where a single individual can create and share a body of work that’s resonant and unique. I’ve become hooked on a podcast called A History of Rock Music in 500 Songs. I’m now a backer on Patreon. The show is at https://500songs.com/ [My suggestion is that you start with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (parts 3 and 4 of an ongoing series)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/10/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-3-and-4-of-an-ongoing-series</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/10/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-3-and-4-of-an-ongoing-series"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In thi^^^ these installments, we continue our series introducing the Spring for GraphQL project. This series features Spring for GraphQL lead Rossen Stoyanchev (@rstoya05) - whose work you may know from basically everything in the wide and wonderful world of Springdom having to do with the web (HTTP, RSocket, WebSockets, GraphQL, JSF, MVC, etc) - and GraphQL Java engine founder and lead Andi Marek (@andimarek) and of course yours truly, Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long (@starbuxman). It provides an in-depth look at all things Spring for GraphQL.

This week I’m publishing two new installments. 

In this week’s first installment, episode three of a series, looks at batching requests with Spring for GraphQL’s @BatchMapping support. This mechanism in turn builds on Facebook’s DataLoader facility. 


Then, in this week’s second installment, episode four of a series, we look at how to make a change with mutations. This is one of my favorite parts about GraphQL - it’s plain, pragmatic, and - most importantly - obvious! 


This continues the series we started last week, with episodes one and two, which I recap here: 

In this first installment, we look at the basics of using the GraphQL Java engine that underpins Spring for GraphQL. 


In this second installment, we look at using the Spring for GraphQL component model by writing queries. 


I know it’s been more than a month since we last published a video, so I’m going to be releasing every episode of this series very quickly, over the next week or two. I’ve already recorded and mostly finished producing eight episodes. I’m working on producing a ninth, and that’ll be that! A complete introduction to all things Spring for GraphQL. These are of course part of the usual Spring Tips playlist on YouTube, but also part of the Learn Spring for GraphQL with Josh Long playlist. Follow that one to be notified of any new episodes!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Process and Task Events with Camunda Platform, AWS Kinesis, and Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56867</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/integrating-process-and-task-events-with-camunda-platform-aws-kinesis-and-elasticsearch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Camunda Community Summit 2022, Fidelity Investments Director of Architecture Harish Malavade shared a behind-the-scenes look at Fidelity’s digital automation platform that uses Camunda as its core workflow engine. Here are the technical details. 
The post Integrating Process and Task Events with Camunda Platform, AWS Kinesis, and Elasticsearch appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harish Malavade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 R6id Instances with NVMe Local Instance Storage of up to 7.6 TB]]></title>
        <id>a84adda0652b06fccf7c94df6d0eeed2bdeb3602</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-r6id-instances/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T21:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2021, we launched the memory-optimized Amazon EC2 R6i instances, our sixth-generation x86-based offering powered by 3rd Generation Intel Xeon Scalable processors (code named Ice Lake). Today I am excited to announce a disk variant of the R6i instance: the Amazon EC2 R6id instances with non-volatile memory express (NVMe) SSD local instance storage. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LIMoE: Learning Multiple Modalities with One Sparse Mixture-of-Experts Model]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/limoe-learning-multiple-modalities-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/limoe-learning-multiple-modalities-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:49:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Basil Mustafa, Research Software Engineer and Carlos Riquelme, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain team 
Sparse models stand out among the most promising approaches for the future of deep learning. Instead of every part of a model processing every input (“dense” modeling), sparse models employing conditional computation learn to route individual inputs to different “experts” in a potentially huge network. This has many benefits. First, model size can increase while keeping computational cost constant — an effective and environmentally friendlier way to scale models, which is often key to high performance. Sparsity also naturally compartmentalizes neural networks. Dense models that learn many different tasks simultaneously (multitask) or sequentially (continual learning) of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Kubernetes legend and friend Cora Iberkleid on Tanzu, Cartographer, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/09/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-legend-and-friend-cora-iberkleid-on-tanzu-cartographer-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/09/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-legend-and-friend-cora-iberkleid-on-tanzu-cartographer-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Kubernetes legend and fellow Tanzu Developer Advocate Cora Iberkleid (@ciberkleid) about Kubernetes and Cartographer supply chains]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copy a work item type using Azure DevOps API’s]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64424</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/copy-a-work-item-type-using-azure-devops-apis-undocumented/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, we all love how we can manage engagements in Azure DevOps (ADO). We can create Epics, Features, User Stories and track our progress on Kanban boards. You can customize work item types to suit the needs of your business and project with ease.
The post Copy a work item type using Azure DevOps API’s appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Art Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pump-Up your ITIL with Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/pump-up-your-itil-with-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/pump-up-your-itil-with-automation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of automation and agility, it seems that Information Technology Infrastructure Library (ITIL) doesn’t have a role to play anymore, being marked as an “old school” framework. Can it be the end of the methodology after it served numerous IT organizations for so long as a guideline and blueprint for their processes?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Lavarde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.0-M5 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/09/spring-shell-2-1-0-m5-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/09/spring-shell-2-1-0-m5-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T10:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.0-M5 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernize Your Mainframe Applications & Deploy Them In The Cloud]]></title>
        <id>6b1b29b8416988254d5bb4b9eb7bf37cc88ab414</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/modernize-your-mainframe-applications-deploy-them-in-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are launching AWS Mainframe Modernization service to help you modernize your mainframe applications and deploy them to AWS fully-managed runtime environments. This new service also provides tools and resources to help you plan and implement migration and modernization. Since the introduction of System/360 on April 7 1964, mainframe computers have enabled many industries […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at Cisco Live: Demos, Presentations, Experts, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-cisco-live-demos-presentations-experts-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-cisco-live-demos-presentations-experts-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re at Cisco Live, June 12-16. Find out more details in our pre-event blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo – OKRs (Objectives and Key Results)]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64394</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-okrs-objectives-and-key-results/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is vision?
The post DevOps Dojo – OKRs (Objectives and Key Results) appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Desktop App with React and Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56716</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/building-a-desktop-app-with-react-and-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow along as Principal Developer Advocate David Simmons uses Camunda Platform 8 and React to build an app that requests, fetches, and saves data.
The post Building a Desktop App with React and Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS MGN Update – Configure DR, Convert CentOS Linux to Rocky Linux, and Convert SUSE Linux Subscription]]></title>
        <id>5d64e7849cb97cd88b049a203409a40516c031fb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-mgn-update-configure-dr-convert-centos-linux-to-rocky-linux-and-convert-suse-linux-subscription/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just about a year ago, Channy showed you How to Use the New AWS Application Migration Server for Lift-and-Shift Migrations. In his post, he introduced AWS Application Migration Service (AWS MGN) and said: With AWS MGN, you can minimize time-intensive, error-prone manual processes by automatically replicating entire servers and converting your source servers from physical, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第210話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270296674398611831</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270296674398611831"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 private automation hub features about automation execution environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/8-private-automation-hub-features-about-automation-execution-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/8-private-automation-hub-features-about-automation-execution-environments"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1 introduced automation execution environments, which is a new way to package automation into a container runtime environment. In addition, private automation hub also joined the party by adding significant support for execution environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End-to-end Generative Pre-training for Multimodal Video Captioning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/end-to-end-generative-pre-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/end-to-end-generative-pre-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Paul Hongsuck Seo and Arsha Nagrani, Research Scientists, Google Research, Perception Team  
Multimodal video captioning systems utilize both the video frames and speech to generate natural language descriptions (captions) of videos. Such systems are stepping stones towards the longstanding goal of building multimodal conversational systems that effortlessly communicate with users while perceiving environments through multimodal input streams.  
 Unlike video understanding tasks (e.g., video classification and retrieval) where the key challenge lies in processing and understanding multimodal input videos, the task of multimodal video captioning includes the additional challenge of generating grounded captions. The most widely adopted approach for this task is to train an encoder-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Azure is Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Microsoft Azure is now available in public beta. Get started today with a secure, resilient service mesh for connecting applications running in Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 7th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/07/this-week-in-spring-june-7th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/07/this-week-in-spring-june-7th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’ve just landed in tantalizing Toronto, Canada, for the SpringOne Tour Toronto show. I’m so excited to be here, at long last, after so long away from one of my favorite countries. I’ll be doing two talks - my usual, Kubernetes Native Java, and a talk on building Kubernetes Controllers (a.k.a. “Operators”) using the official Kubernetes Java client, Spring Boot, and Spring Native with my amazing friend and teammate Tiffany Jernigan, who you may recall was on the podcast not too long ago. 

After Toronto, I’m off to beautiful Berlin, Germany, for the We Are Developers show. 

If you’re at either show, don’t hesitate to say hi! 


  
Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (parts 1 and 2 of an ongoing series) Hi Spring …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.10 Achieves FIPS 140-2 Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-1-10-achieves-fips-140-2-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-1-10-achieves-fips-140-2-compliance"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault Enterprise 1.10 has been evaluated as conformant with the Federal Information Processing Standard (FIPS) 140-2 standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64349</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-lean-product-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T09:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 and Part 2 of the DevOps Dojo – Lean Product series, we covered the why, what, and how of the product-centric model and lean product model as outlined in the White & Orange Belts of the DevOps Dojo.
The post DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 3 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – June 6, 2022]]></title>
        <id>809e92b4a5a28eebe9aaedaedb0238c8547ff419</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-6-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I’ve just come back from a long (extended) holiday weekend here in the US and I’m still catching up on all the AWS launches that happened this past week. I’m […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Appsec at Netflix (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c9e0f1488bc5</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/scaling-appsec-at-netflix-part-2-c9e0f1488bc5?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Astha Singhal, Lakshmi Sudheer, Julia Knecht]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Ansible Automation Platform's Automation Services Catalog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-ansible-automation-platforms-automation-services-catalog</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-ansible-automation-platforms-automation-services-catalog"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.2 introduces a technical preview of automation services catalog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 04.06.2022]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64335</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-04-06-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-04T07:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Don’t Accept the Defaults’ -Abel Wang
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 04.06.2022 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring I/O founder, Spring trainer and community legend Sergi Almar]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-i-o-founder-spring-trainer-and-community-legend-sergi-almar</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-i-o-founder-spring-trainer-and-community-legend-sergi-almar"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! At long last, against all odds, Josh Long (@starbuxman) finally gets to talk to Spring I/O founder and more-than-a-decade-long friend Sergi Almar (@sergialmar) about an edition of Spring I/O after 2019!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the newest AWS Heroes – June 2022]]></title>
        <id>c02650163773177062a3b118f232c97abe7eb4ae</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-newest-aws-heroes-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Heroes are some of the worlds most active and vocal leaders in AWS communities, recognized for their unwavering focus on sharing insights and technical knowledge with others. Heroes have a variety of contributions to community learning: they host events, meetups, and workshops, author blogs, contribute to open source projects, speak at conferences, and more. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022 Deprecation of Reporting Services]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64299</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-deprecation-of-reporting-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the Azure DevOps Server 2022 release, we wanted to reiterate the deprecation of the existing data warehouse reporting services. We previously announced this in the Azure DevOps Server 2020 release notes. The warehouse reporting service has been part of TFS and Azure DevOps for over a decade.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022 Deprecation of Reporting Services appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (parts 1 and 2 of an ongoing series)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-1-and-2-of-an-ongoing-series</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-1-and-2-of-an-ongoing-series"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In thi^^^ these installments, we begin a new series introducing the Spring for GraphQL project. 

In this first installment, GraphQL Java lead Andi Marek (@andimarek) and  I (@starbuxman) look at the basics of using the GraphQL Java engine that underpins Spring for GraphQL. 


In this second installment, Andi and I are joined by Spring for GraphQL lead Rossen Stoyanchev (@rstoya05) as we look at using the Spring for GraphQL component model by writing queries. 


I know it’s been more than a month since we last published a video, so I’m going to be releasing every episode of this series very quickly, over the next week or two. I’ve already recorded and mostly finished producing eight episodes. I’m working on producing a ninth, and that’ll be that! A complete introduction to all things Spring for GraphQL. These are of course part of the usual Spring Tips playlist on YouTube, but also part of the Learn Spring for GraphQL with Josh Long playlist. Follow that one to be notified of any new episodes!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB Field Level Encryption with HashiCorp Vault KMIP Secrets Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mongodb-field-level-encryption-with-hashicorp-vault-kmip-secrets-engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mongodb-field-level-encryption-with-hashicorp-vault-kmip-secrets-engine"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how MongoDB’s field-level encryption capability pairs with Vault’s KMIP secrets engine to help organizations deliver strong privacy and security controls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Conversations: Jean Robert Alves, Agi]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56009</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/community-conversations-jean-robert-alves-agibank/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the latest installment of Community Conversations, we sat down with Jean Robert Alves, a Camunda Champion and software architect expert at Agi.
The post Community Conversations: Jean Robert Alves, Agi appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Work Item Revision Limits]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64125</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/work-item-revision-limits/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time a work item is updated, it creates an entry in the work item history. This is a great feature for users to track all the individual changes made to work items. However, we have seen organizations with automated tools that will generate tens of thousands of work item revisions.
The post Work Item Revision Limits appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EMR Serverless Now Generally Available – Run Big Data Applications without Managing Servers]]></title>
        <id>230544885a857a26188de08fe94fb293329b5ed7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-emr-serverless-now-generally-available-run-big-data-applications-without-managing-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced three new serverless options for our data analytics services – Amazon EMR Serverless, Amazon Redshift Serverless, and Amazon MSK Serverless – that make it easier to analyze data at any scale without having to configure, scale, or manage the underlying infrastructure. Today we announce the general availability of Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Support After Our Artifactory Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55942</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/improved-support-after-our-artifactory-migration/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently migrated our 10-year-old artifact storage to a new cloud-based setup. Here's a behind-the-scenes look at the migration and how you can help us continue to improve access and support. 
The post Improved Support After Our Artifactory Migration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Lange</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Released: Automation content navigator 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/released-automation-content-navigator-2.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/released-automation-content-navigator-2.0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation content navigator releases with Ansible Automation Platform 2.2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating multi-vendor network prefix-lists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-multi-vendor-network-prefix-lists</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-multi-vendor-network-prefix-lists"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To keep the networks healthy, cause connectivity matters
 
I love being a network engineer, even though I struggled to explain to non-networking people about the utmost relevance of network administration. However, during the last two years of the COVID-19 pandemic, the world could see the relevance of having connectivity. Networks are the highways of information. Data, applications, entertainment, and factories need the network connectivity roads to make the world run. It’s interesting that even network models to estimate traffic behavior use algorithms that are similar to the ones to estimate transportation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – May 30, 2022]]></title>
        <id>11f85bc4066ba75d8f5b71875bdaee4c76ef9d1a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-30-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T14:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the US observes Memorial Day. South Korea also has a national Memorial Day, celebrated next week on June 6. In both countries, the day is set aside to remember those who sacrificed in service to their country. This time provides an opportunity to recognize and show our appreciation for the armed services and the important […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Camunda in a Low-code Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55577</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/integrating-camunda-in-a-low-code-platform/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Apex Process Consultants integrated Camunda Platform 7 with their low-code platform to make it easier to build processes. 
The post Integrating Camunda in a Low-code Platform appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M6id and C6id Instances with Up to 7.6 TB Local NVMe Storage]]></title>
        <id>dabb34f9d25282db77234ee28cb2826f74cfe7b3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-m6id-and-c6id-instances-with-up-to-7-6-tb-local-nvme-storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T21:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, we launched the Amazon EC2 M6i instances and C6i instances, our sixth-generation offerings that include 3rd generation Intel Xeon Scalable processors. Today we are expanding Amazon EC2 M6id and C6id instances, backed by NVMe-based SSD block-level instance storage physically connected to the host server. These instances are powered by the Intel Xeon Scalable […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTS 0.6 Adds New Terraform Cloud Agent and HCP Consul Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cts-0-6-new-terraform-cloud-agent-hcp-consul-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cts-0-6-new-terraform-cloud-agent-hcp-consul-support"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of HashiCorp Consul-Terraform-Sync (CTS) 0.6 represents a key step in the maturity of our Network Infrastructure Automation (NIA) solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2.2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible product team at Red Hat is thrilled to announce the general availability of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.2, which includes numerous features and bug fixes that further solidify Ansible Automation Platform as the de facto enterprise IT automation solution for developers to operations teams in data centers, clouds, and at the edge. A few of the most noteworthy features in this release include:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andriusb@redhat.com (Andrius Benokraitis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 Webinar Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55344</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-platform-8-webinar-recap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out these answers to the questions we didn't get to answer during our recent Camunda Platform 8 Release Webinar.
The post Camunda Platform 8 Webinar Recap appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning with Label Differential Privacy]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/deep-learning-with-label-differential.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/deep-learning-with-label-differential.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T20:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by  Pasin Manurangsi and Chiyuan Zhang, Research Scientists, Google Research  
Over the last several years, there has been an increased focus on developing differential privacy (DP) machine learning (ML) algorithms. DP has been the basis of several practical deployments in industry — and has even been employed by the U.S. Census — because it enables the understanding of system and algorithm privacy guarantees. The underlying assumption of DP is that changing a single user’s contribution to an algorithm should not significantly change its output distribution. 
 In the standard supervised learning setting, a model is trained to make a prediction of the label for each input given a training set of example pairs {[input1,label1], …, [inputn, labeln]}. In the case of deep learning, previ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.11 Introduces New Provider Command and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-terraform-0-11-introduces-new-provider-command</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-terraform-0-11-introduces-new-provider-command"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform (CDKTF) 0.11 introduces an easier way to add providers to your application and improvements to the debugging process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for AWS DataSync – Move Data Between AWS and Other Public Locations]]></title>
        <id>905a367112dd04b244491567bac3a7266994c9f7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-aws-datasync-move-data-between-aws-and-google-cloud-storage-or-aws-and-microsoft-azure-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moving data to and from AWS Storage services can be automated and accelerated with AWS DataSync. For example, you can use DataSync to migrate data to AWS, replicate data for business continuity, and move data for analysis and processing in the cloud. You can use DataSync to transfer data to and from AWS Storage services, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image-Text Pre-training with Contrastive Captioners]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/image-text-pre-training-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/image-text-pre-training-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zirui Wang and Jiahui Yu, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Oftentimes, machine learning (ML) model developers begin their design using a generic backbone model that is trained at scale and with capabilities transferable to a wide range of downstream tasks. In natural language processing, a number of popular backbone models, including BERT, T5, GPT-3 (sometimes also referred to as “foundation models”), are pre-trained on web-scale data and have demonstrated generic multi-tasking capabilities through zero-shot, few-shot or transfer learning. Compared with training over-specialized individual models, pre-training backbone models for a large number of downstream tasks can amortize the training costs, allowing one to overcome resource limitations when building large s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>