<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-02T01:09:05.483Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-02T01:09:05.483Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Architecture: Production Readiness]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/02/sig-architecture-production-readiness-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/02/sig-architecture-production-readiness-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
This is the second interview of a SIG Architecture Spotlight series that will cover the different
subprojects. In this blog, we will cover the SIG Architecture: Production Readiness
subproject.
In this SIG Architecture spotlight, we talked with Wojciech Tyczynski
(Google), lead of the Production Readiness subproject.
About SIG Architecture and the Production Readiness subproject
Frederico (FSM): Hello Wojciech, could you tell us a bit about yourself, your role and how you
got involved in Kubernetes?
Wojciech Tyczynski (WT): I started contributing to Kubernetes in January 2015. At that time,
Google (where I was and still am working) decided to start a Kubernetes team in the Warsaw office
(in addition to already existing teams in California and Seattle…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestration with Camunda and Kafka Confluent Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93624</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/11/orchestration-camunda-kafka/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would you use both Camunda and Kafka in your architecture? Learn why and how to do it in this easy to follow tutorial.
The post Orchestration with Camunda and Kafka Confluent Cloud appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Game Off 2023 theme announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-01-github-game-off-2023-theme-announcement/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-01-github-game-off-2023-theme-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It’s the moment you’ve all been waiting for. Are you ready?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-01-github-game-off-2023-theme-announcement/">GitHub Game Off 2023 theme announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.7 beta improves Vault and Consul integrations, adds NUMA support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.7 — now in beta — introduces improved workload identity, improved Vault and Consul integrations, NUMA support, Nomad actions, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetNet-3: A state-of-the-art neural weather model available in Google products]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/metnet-3-state-of-art-neural-weather.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/metnet-3-state-of-art-neural-weather.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T17:30:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Samier Merchant, Google Research, and Nal Kalchbrenner, Google DeepMind






Forecasting weather variables such as precipitation, temperature, and wind is key to numerous aspects of society, from daily planning and transportation to energy production. As we continue to see more extreme weather events such as floods, droughts, and heat waves, accurate forecasts can be essential to preparing for and mitigating their effects. The first 24 hours into the future are especially important as they are both highly predictable and actionable, which can help people make informed decisions in a timely manner and stay safe. 
 

Today we present a new weather model called MetNet-3, developed by Google Research and Google DeepMind. Building on the earlier MetNet and MetNet-2 models, MetNet-3 p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul tips and tricks for cloud transformation at HashiConf 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-tips-and-tricks-for-cloud-transformation-at-hashiconf-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-tips-and-tricks-for-cloud-transformation-at-hashiconf-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch our key Consul networking sessions from HashiConf 2023 and give us your feedback on the talks and the future direction of Consul.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Partial Clone Now Supported in Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67877</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/git-partial-clone-now-supported-in-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T17:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git Partial Clone
The post Git Partial Clone Now Supported in Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Carlson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2023.3 EAP 3 is out! Introducing dbt® support!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=401990</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2023/11/2023-3-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T16:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third EAP build for DataSpell 2023.3 brings dbt® support, JetBrains AI Assistant actions via the context menu in Jupyter, and easy access to column statistics and data distribution histograms in tables. To catch up on all of the new features in DataSpell 2023.3, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanislav Garkusha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diversity, inclusion, and belonging at GitHub in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-01-diversity-inclusion-and-belonging-at-github-in-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-01-diversity-inclusion-and-belonging-at-github-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We expanded diversity of our employee base, launched several new employee engagement programs, made investments to improve accessibility, and more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-01-diversity-inclusion-and-belonging-at-github-in-2023/">Diversity, inclusion, and belonging at GitHub in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet JetBrains Academy at the EDUtech Asia 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=401145</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/11/01/meet-jetbrains-academy-at-the-edutech-asia-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T14:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet JetBrains Academy at the EDUtech Asia 2023 in Singapore on November 8–9. Stop by Booth Q11 to talk with us about learning and teaching computer science with JetBrains Academy, grab some swag, or just say hi! We’re thrilled to be taking part in Asia’s largest conference and exhibition for educators and EdTech providers, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Regina Muradova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Striving For Better C++ Code, Part I: Data Flow Analysis Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=401311</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/11/striving-for-better-cpp-code-part-i-data-flow-analysis-basics/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T12:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion comes with a built-in data flow analyzer, which runs constantly when you are writing your code and helps improve your code’s quality. It can reveal various code problems that might later lead to runtime issues, security breaches, and other vulnerabilities. Examples of these useful checks are checks for constant conditions, dead code, null pointer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin Multiplatform Is Stable and Production-Ready]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=401121</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/11/kotlin-multiplatform-stable/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T11:31:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a highly anticipated move, Kotlin Multiplatform, an open-source technology built by JetBrains that allows developers to share code across platforms while retaining the benefits of native programming, has become Stable and is now 100% ready for use in production. Read on to learn about the evolution of Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP), how it can streamline […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Petrova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin 1.9.20 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=400953</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/11/kotlin-1-9-20-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T11:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kotlin 1.9.20 release is out, the K2 compiler for all the targets is now in Beta, and Kotlin Multiplatform is now Stable. Here are some highlights from this release: For the complete list of changes, refer to What’s new in Kotlin 1.9.20 or the release notes on GitHub. The New Kotlin K2 Compiler Is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrey Polyakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two ways to defend the status quo]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46032</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/805183556/0/sethsblog~Two-ways-to-defend-the-status-quo/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T08:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neither is true, helpful or generous. Both happen all the time. Call it out when you see it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.20.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/01/spring-tools-4-20-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/01/spring-tools-4-20-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lippert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Mil-asticians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-mil-asticians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-mil-asticians"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the Mil-asticians, an ERG for those that have a connection with the military community, no matter what the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Mil-asticians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-mil-asticians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-mil-asticians"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
At Elastic, we formalized our employee resource groups in 2021, but they’ve been part of our culture since 2016. These groups are aligned with shared identities, experiences, interests, affinities, and allyships.
As formal groups they are ensured structure, budget, and a voice based on any dimension of diversity, identity, allyship, and advocacy. While we’re always working towards change, this is an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy.
Each ERG has its own mission and goals, but as a whole these groups want to create community and belonging around shared interests and experiences. 
Our Core ERGs
We have seven formal ERGs: The Accessibles, Blasticians, ElastAsians, Elasticians Unidos, Rainbow Stack, Mil-asticians, and Women of Elastic. We’ll be spotlight…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Under the Stars]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2849/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2849/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/under_the_stars.png" title="If you live in Los Angeles (around 33°52'N, roughly the latitude of Hermosa Beach) the black hole in V404 Cygni passes over you each day. On Christmas Day it will be directly overhead around 2pm." alt="If you live in Los Angeles (around 33°52'N, roughly the latitude of Hermosa Beach) the black hole in V404 Cygni passes over you each day. On Christmas Day it will be directly overhead around 2pm." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon EC2 Capacity Blocks for ML to reserve GPU capacity for your machine learning workloads]]></title>
        <id>4c52f5324f0331091a5829e03f9cf90f4f2d5bfb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-ec2-capacity-blocks-for-ml-to-reserve-gpu-capacity-for-your-machine-learning-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T23:02:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent advancements in machine learning (ML) have unlocked opportunities for customers across organizations of all sizes and industries to reinvent new products and transform their businesses. However, the growth in demand for GPU capacity to train, fine-tune, experiment, and inference these ML models has outpaced industry-wide supply, making GPUs a scarce resource. Access to GPU […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Play when you have connectors in your process]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93522</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/using-play-connectors-in-your-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T21:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Camunda's Play feature functions and how to test processes without disrupting your Zeebe cluster.
The post Using Play when you have connectors in your process appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the GitHub transparency center]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-31-introducing-the-github-transparency-center/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-31-introducing-the-github-transparency-center/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T19:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It’s time for our biannual transparency report, where we share how we approach content moderation and disclosure of user information. This year, we’re introducing the transparency center, a new platform for our transparency reporting data.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-31-introducing-the-github-transparency-center/">Introducing the GitHub transparency center</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC2 now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67838</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-1-rc2-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T18:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC2. This is our last planned prerelease before our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2022.1. A direct upgrade is supported from Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC1, any version of TFS, including Team Foundation Server 2015 and newer.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC2 now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Gateway API v1.0: GA Release]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/31/gateway-api-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/31/gateway-api-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Shane Utt (Kong), Nick Young (Isovalent), Rob Scott (Google)
On behalf of Kubernetes SIG Network, we are pleased to announce the v1.0 release of Gateway
API! This release marks a huge milestone for
this project. Several key APIs are graduating to GA (generally available), while
other significant features have been added to the Experimental channel.
What's new
Graduation to v1
This release includes the graduation of
Gateway,
GatewayClass, and
HTTPRoute to v1, which
means they are now generally available (GA). This API version denotes a high
level of confidence in the API surface and provides guarantees of backwards
compatibility. Note that although, the version of these APIs included in the
Standard channel are now considered stable, that does not mean that they are
complete. These…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Boards + GitHub Integration Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67897</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-boards-github-integration-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T16:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The existing Azure Boards + GitHub integration has been in place for several years now. This integration was a great starting point, but it does not offer the level of traceability that our customers have grown accustomed to. Based on your feedback,
The post Azure Boards + GitHub Integration Improvements appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.3 EAP #5]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=401158</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/10/phpstorm-2023-3-eap-5/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T13:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this build, you can find several quality-of-life improvements across the various subsystems. The EAP allows you to try new features from the upcoming PhpStorm version, 2023.3. EAP builds are free to use and you can install them side by side with a stable version of PhpStorm. If something doesn’t work correctly, you can switch […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tania Goral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confronting consciousness]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47611</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/804250295/0/sethsblog~Confronting-consciousness/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T08:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone knows what it is to be conscious, and we imagine that other people are also aware. That we have a voice in our heads, apparent agency and free will, a little person inside who is commenting, making decisions and in charge. We’re not sure if dogs have this, and we’re pretty sure that sunflowers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guest Post: Four Ways To Quickly Display OpenCV Images During Debugging]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=399903</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/10/guest-post-four-ways-to-quickly-display-opencv-images-during-debugging/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a guest blog post by Adrian Boguszewski, author of OpenCV Image Viewer Plugin. The average programmer makes 70 errors per 1,000 lines of code and spends 75% of their time on debugging (source). In computer vision (CV), this process may involve not only fixing the code but also checking that the visual effect […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jodie Burchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · Hacktoberfest 2023 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-30-release-radar-hack-23/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-release-radar-hack-23/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T06:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As Hacktoberfest comes to a close, you still have a day or so left to complete and submit your pull requests. If you&#8217;re struggling to think of projects to contribute to, our picks below might help you. This edition of the Release Radar covers a few projects that shipped major version updates this August and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-release-radar-hack-23/">Release Radar · Hacktoberfest 2023 Edition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda 8.3 Release Webinar, Recap and Extended Q&A]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93435</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/camunda-8-3-webinar-recap-q-a/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T01:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch all the highlights from our latest release webinar, as well as detailed answers to all the questions we couldn't get to live.
The post Camunda 8.3 Release Webinar, Recap and Extended Q&A appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Montalvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What new is coming in reactor-core 3.6.0?]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/31/what-new-is-coming-in-reactor-core-3-6-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/31/what-new-is-coming-in-reactor-core-3-6-0"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleh Dokuka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - October 31st, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/31/this-week-in-spring-october-31st-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/31/this-week-in-spring-october-31st-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking the new US executive order on artificial intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-executive-order-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-executive-order-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 30 2023, President Biden signed the Executive Order on the Safe, Secure, and Trustworthy Development and Use of Artificial Intelligence, which aims to advance and regulate artificial intelligence (AI) in the US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking the new US executive order on artificial intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-executive-order-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-executive-order-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
On Monday, October 30, President Biden signed the Executive Order on the Safe, Secure, and Trustworthy Development and Use of Artificial Intelligence — the longest in history at 117 pages. The executive order (EO) aims to advance and regulate artificial intelligence (AI) in the US. This landmark order pulls together a number of priorities that influence not just the AI industry, but also society at large. 

The EO is an essential step toward operationalizing AI for the benefit of the US government and society as a whole. AI has the potential to change the way everyday citizens interact with the government and can vastly improve the citizen experience.  However, as the EO recognizes, with such promise comes inherent challenges and risks. This EO strikes a healthy balance in offering guida…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MPS 2023.2 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=mps&amp;p=385532</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/mps/2023/10/mps-2023-2-is-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T18:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this release, we’ve achieved objectives from several different areas. You will find substantial improvements to JUnit support and the BaseLanguage integration with Java’s lambdas. The IDE is now more configurable, with the type system offering new ways to override rules in extending languages, as well as the other useful enhancements brought by the updated […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaclav Pech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Annotated – October 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=400977</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/10/php-annotated-october-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the October edition of PHP Annotated! We’ll recap the most interesting developments in the PHP community over the past month, featuring handpicked news, articles, tools, and videos. Highlights PHP 8.3.0 RC5 has been released Another release candidate has been delivered according to schedule. The sixth RC is expected on November 9, and it’ll […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The architecture of today&#8217;s LLM applications]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-30-the-architecture-of-todays-llm-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-the-architecture-of-todays-llm-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here’s everything you need to know to build your first LLM app and problem spaces you can start exploring today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-the-architecture-of-todays-llm-applications/">The architecture of today&#8217;s LLM applications</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – re:Post Selections, SNS and SQS FIFO improvements, multi-VPC ENI attachments, and more – October 30, 2023]]></title>
        <id>c693bec204bcea0b124466b9876c223fba395649</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-repost-selections-sns-and-sqs-fifo-improvements-multi-vpc-eni-attachments-and-more-october-30-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s less than a month to AWS re:Invent, but interesting news doesn’t slow down in the meantime. This week is my turn to help keep you up to date! Last week’s launches Here are some of the launches that caught my attention last week: AWS re:Post – With re:Post, you have access to a community […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.3 EAP 4 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=400935</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/10/2023-3-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T10:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can download the build from our website, get it from the free Toolbox App, or update to it using snaps if you’re an Ubuntu user. Download PyCharm 2023.3 EAP The fourth build of the Early Access Program for PyCharm 2023.3 introduces: You can download the build from our website, get it from the free Toolbox App, or update […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2 x 4 lessons]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46036</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/803673851/0/sethsblog~The-x-lessons/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T08:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll need two 8-foot boards and six five-gallon buckets. Each board is a standard 2 x 4, about two inches by four inches in size. And the bucket is about two feet deep. The first lesson is simple: Put the board on the floor and have a colleague walk from one end to the other. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Livestream: JPA Buddy – From Zero to Hero]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=400579</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/10/new-livestream-jpa-buddy-from-zero-to-hero/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T08:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for the new IntelliJ IDEA LiveStream episode with Marco Behler to learn about JPA Buddy’s functionality. Date: November 9, 2023 Time: 3:00 pm – 4:00 pm UTC REGISTER FOR THE LIVESTREAM Session abstract In this #noslides live-coding session, you’ll learn about JPA Buddy’s functionality for managing your JPA data model from the ground […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Rovinskaia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackable Halloween games MMXXIII]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-30-hackable-halloween-games-mmxxiii/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-hackable-halloween-games-mmxxiii/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T08:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>13 spooktacular games plus source code for readers to jam on.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-hackable-halloween-games-mmxxiii/">Hackable Halloween games MMXXIII</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.3 EAP5 With the Enhanced Bazel for CLion Plugin and Memory Leak Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=400893</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/10/clion-2023-3-eap5-with-the-enhanced-bazel-for-clion-plugin-and-memory-leak-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T06:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to our Developer Ecosystem survey, 57% of C++ developers used CMake in 2022. However, there are other project models and build systems that are also popular in the C++ ecosystem. Just a couple of weeks ago, we added Meson support in CLion 2023.3. If you use Meson in your projects, consider giving it a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Statemachine 4.0.0-M1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/30/spring-statemachine-4-0-0-m1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/30/spring-statemachine-4-0-0-m1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tracking peak time for trick-or-treaters in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/tracking-peak-time-for-trick-or-treaters-in-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/tracking-peak-time-for-trick-or-treaters-in-kibana"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Halloween! Have you ever wondered when is the busy time on the doorstep for trick or treating? Our developer advocate Carly Richmond has been digging into data from https://www.dataplusscience.com/HalloweenData.html using Kibana to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tracking peak time for trick-or-treaters in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/tracking-peak-time-for-trick-or-treaters-in-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/tracking-peak-time-for-trick-or-treaters-in-kibana"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
It’s the most spooky time of the year! Many of us have fond memories as children of dressing up in scary costumes and heading door to door in search of treats. As adults, we may be on door duty handing out candy.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt0584d8b9e536b807/635c03689a123e5dbdbca267/1.jpg,1.jpg,
Irrespective of which side of the door you’re standing on, have you ever wondered when the peak time for trick or treating is? Below, we’ll explain how to ingest data and build sample visualizations using Kibana to show when to expect trick-or-treaters knocking on the door.
Ingesting our trick-or-treater data
To examine this question, we need data. Thankfully, the wonderful Jeffrey A. Shaffer has been collecting data on the trick-or-treaters coming to his door fr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaker Box]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2848/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2848/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/breaker_box.png" title="Any electrician will warn you to first locate and flip the house's CAUSALITY circuit breaker before touching the CIRCUIT BREAKERS one." alt="Any electrician will warn you to first locate and flip the house's CAUSALITY circuit breaker before touching the CIRCUIT BREAKERS one." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three things about innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46034</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/803519273/0/sethsblog~Three-things-about-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New approaches will never be embraced by everyone at first. If you need unanimous consent, you’re not going to move forward. And it’s not convenient. If it were, someone would have done it already. Finally, it’s not sure to work. If you need any or all three of these things for your project to move […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Stream Applications 2022.0.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/29/spring-cloud-stream-applications-2022-0-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/29/spring-cloud-stream-applications-2022-0-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bono</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big science]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46026</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/803388608/0/sethsblog~Big-science/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To win a Nobel prize a hundred years ago, you might only need a legal pad and a few pencils. Today, it takes millions of dollars, scores of people and many years of effort. That’s because the most straightforward problems have been solved. One side effect of this inevitable shift is that many parts of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audioplethysmography for cardiac monitoring with hearable devices]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/audioplethysmography-for-cardiac.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/audioplethysmography-for-cardiac.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T20:22:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xiaoran "Van" Fan, Experimental Scientist, and Trausti Thormundsson, Director, Google





The market for true wireless stereo (TWS) active noise canceling (ANC) hearables (headphones and earbuds) has been soaring in recent years, and the global shipment volume will nearly double that of smart wristbands and watches in 2023. The on-head time for hearables has extended significantly due to the recent advances in ANC, transparency mode, and artificial intelligence. Users frequently wear hearables not just for music listening, but also for exercising, focusing, or simply mood adjustment. However, hearable health is still mostly uncharted territory for the consumer market. 



In “APG: Audioplethysmography for Cardiac Monitoring in Hearables,” presented at MobiCom 2023, we introduce …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying LLMs: How they can do things they weren&#8217;t trained to do]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-27-demystifying-llms-how-they-can-do-things-they-werent-trained-to-do/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-27-demystifying-llms-how-they-can-do-things-they-werent-trained-to-do/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T16:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore how LLMs generate text, why they sometimes hallucinate information, and the ethical implications surrounding their incredible capabilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-27-demystifying-llms-how-they-can-do-things-they-werent-trained-to-do/">Demystifying LLMs: How they can do things they weren&#8217;t trained to do</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes And Kernel Panics]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ed620b9c6225</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/kubernetes-and-kernel-panics-ed620b9c6225?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T16:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Netflix’s Container Platform Connects Linux Kernel Panics to Pods]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is public key infrastructure (PKI)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-is-public-key-infrastructure-pki</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-is-public-key-infrastructure-pki"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public key infrastructure (PKI) governs the provisioning of digital certificates to protect sensitive data, establish digital identities, and secure communications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are the first group to adopt AI at work. Here’s why that matters.]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-27-developers-are-the-first-group-to-adopt-ai-at-work-heres-why-that-matters/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-27-developers-are-the-first-group-to-adopt-ai-at-work-heres-why-that-matters/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From starting at GitHub over 10 years ago as a developer to becoming the Chief Operating Officer, I’ve learned that developers are often bellwethers for change across the rest of their organizations. That makes investing in—and learning from—them critical. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-27-developers-are-the-first-group-to-adopt-ai-at-work-heres-why-that-matters/">Developers are the first group to adopt AI at work. Here’s why that matters.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Your Camunda Process from an External Form]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93419</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/start-camunda-process-external-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T14:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now you can launch your Camunda processes from an external URL, simplifying collaboration and adoption.
The post Start Your Camunda Process from an External Form appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small groups, well organized]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46013</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/803308964/0/sethsblog~Small-groups-well-organized/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And those are the two challenges of anyone seeking to make an impact. First, we get distracted by the inclination to make the group as big as we can imagine. After all, the change is essential, the idea is a good one. It’s for everyone. Except that’s a trap. Because a group that’s too large […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous profiling: The key to more efficient and cost-effective applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/continuous-profiling-efficient-cost-effective-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/continuous-profiling-efficient-cost-effective-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we discuss why computational efficiency is important and how Elastic Universal Profiling enables your business to use continuous profiling in production environments to make the software that runs your business as efficient as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Knoepfle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous profiling: The key to more efficient and cost-effective applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/continuous-profiling-efficient-cost-effective-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/continuous-profiling-efficient-cost-effective-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Recently, Elastic Universal ProfilingTM became generally available. It is the part of our Observability solution that allows users to do whole system, continuous profiling in production environments. If you're not familiar with continuous profiling, you are probably wondering what Universal Profiling is and why you should care. That's what we will address in this post.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt9f61ecaf8002a6a4/653b443d008d3a0407d4b2bf/elastic-blog-1-universal-profiling.png,elastic-blog-1-universal-profiling.png,
Many businesses today employ polyglot programming — that is, they use multiple languages to build an application — and Universal Profiling is the only profiler available that can build a holistic view across all of these languages. This will …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Knoepfle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dendrochronology]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2847/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2847/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/dendrochronology.png" title="These anomalies are known as Miyake events, named for the pioneering scientist who discovered them and was tragically devoured by a carnivorous tree." alt="These anomalies are known as Miyake events, named for the pioneering scientist who discovered them and was tragically devoured by a carnivorous tree." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new at purple.space?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47681</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/803273837/0/sethsblog~Whats-new-at-purplespace/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are now 1,000 of us in this online community that’s not a social network. Proudly a millionth the size of some other online experiences. It includes the original Creative’s Workshop, with hundreds of people working through it, side by side. And just added, access to the Marketing Seminar. But mostly it’s the peer support, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-secondary performance replication is now available on HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multi-secondary-performance-replication-is-now-available-on-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multi-secondary-performance-replication-is-now-available-on-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Plus clusters can now have more than one additional performance secondary cluster per primary cluster within the same cloud provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting benchmarks for AI safety with MLCommons]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/supporting-benchmarks-for-ai-safety.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/supporting-benchmarks-for-ai-safety.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Anoop Sinha, Technology and Society, and Marian Croak, Google Research, Responsible AI and Human Centered Technology team





Standard benchmarks are agreed upon ways of measuring important product qualities, and they exist in many fields. Some standard benchmarks measure safety: for example, when a car manufacturer touts a “five-star overall safety rating,” they’re citing a benchmark. Standard benchmarks already exist in machine learning (ML) and AI technologies: for instance, the MLCommons Association operates the MLPerf benchmarks that measure the speed of cutting edge AI hardware such as Google’s TPUs. However, though there has been significant work done on AI safety, there are as yet no similar standard benchmarks for AI safety.
 

We are excited to support a new effort by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 tips for making your GitHub profile page accessible]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-26-5-tips-for-making-your-github-profile-page-accessible/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-26-5-tips-for-making-your-github-profile-page-accessible/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T16:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Your profile’s README invites the world to know you and your work, so it’s important that everyone can read and understand it. In this post, we share some tips for making your README more accessible. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-26-5-tips-for-making-your-github-profile-page-accessible/">5 tips for making your GitHub profile page accessible</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spoken question answering and speech continuation using a spectrogram-powered LLM]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/spoken-question-answering-and-speech.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/spoken-question-answering-and-speech.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T15:57:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eliya Nachmani, Research Scientist, and Alon Levkovitch, Student Researcher, Google Research




The goal of natural language processing (NLP) is to develop computational models that can understand and generate natural language. By capturing the statistical patterns and structures of text-based natural language, language models can predict and generate coherent and meaningful sequences of words. Enabled by the increasing use of the highly successful Transformer model architecture and with training on large amounts of text (with proportionate compute and model size), large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable success in NLP tasks. 

 


However, modeling spoken human language remains a challenging frontier. Spoken dialog systems have conventionally been built as a c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a new HashiCorp Women in Tech podcast series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-a-new-hashicorp-women-in-tech-podcast-series</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-a-new-hashicorp-women-in-tech-podcast-series"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our new Women in Tech podcast debuts alongside our Fortune Best Workplaces for Women recognition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trouble in the grey zone]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45998</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/803239685/0/sethsblog~Trouble-in-the-grey-zone/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T09:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many creative industries, there’s a similar pattern. When the stakes are very low, most creators produce things that are fairly banal and ordinary. Part of that is the law of large numbers, but it’s mostly our personal cultural resistance to leaning too far into weird stuff. And so the vast majority of YouTube videos, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrich your Elasticsearch documents within Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-within-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-within-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Elasticsearch, we know that joins should be done "at index time" instead of query time. This blog post starts a series of three posts as there are many approaches we can take within the Elastic ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Pilato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrich your Elasticsearch documents within Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-within-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-within-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[{
  "agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (X11; Linux i686) AppleWebKit/534.24 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/11.0.696.50 Safari/534.24",
  "bytes": 1831,
  "clientip": "30.156.16.164",
  "extension": "",
  "geo": {
    "srcdest": "US:IN",
    "src": "US",
    "dest": "IN",
    "coordinates": {
      "lat": 55.53741389,
      "lon": -132.3975144
    }
  },
  "host": "elastic-elastic-elastic.org",
  "index": "kibana_sample_data_logs",
  "ip": "30.156.16.163",
  "machine": {
    "ram": 9663676416,
    "os": "win xp"
  },
  "memory": 73240,
  "message": "30.156.16.163 - - [2018-09-01T12:43:49.756Z] \"GET /wp-login.php HTTP/1.1\" 404 1831 \"-\" \"Mozilla/5.0 (X11; Linux i686) AppleWebKit/534.24 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/11.0.696.50 Safari/534.24\"",
  "phpmemory": 73240,
  "referer": "http://www.elastic-elastic-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Pilato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.1 RC2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/26/spring-framework-6-1-rc2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/26/spring-framework-6-1-rc2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Mr. Spring in Action, Craig Walls]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/26/a-bootiful-podcast-mr-spring-in-action-craig-walls</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/26/a-bootiful-podcast-mr-spring-in-action-craig-walls"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building trust through digital-first citizen experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-trust-through-digital-first-citizen-experiences</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-trust-through-digital-first-citizen-experiences"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Elastic can help government agencies use data to elevate citizen experiences based on OMB M-23-22, which offers a policy framework for federal agencies as they continue to optimize online services and information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic's contribution: Invokedynamic in the OpenTelemetry Java agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-invokedynamic-opentelemetry-java-agent</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-invokedynamic-opentelemetry-java-agent"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The instrumentation approach in OpenTelemetry's Java Agent comes with some limitations with respect to maintenance and testability. Elastic contributes an invokedynamic-based instrumentation approach that helps overcoming these limitations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Wert,Jack Shirazi,Jonas Kunz,Sylvain Juge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building trust through digital-first citizen experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-trust-through-digital-first-citizen-experiences</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-trust-through-digital-first-citizen-experiences"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Whether referred to as “customer experience” or “citizen experience,” making sure people are satisfied with their digital interactions is a clear priority for the U.S. federal government. In September 2023, the U.S. Office of Management and Budget (OMB), released the “Delivering a Digital First Public Experience” memorandum (OMB M-23-22). This document offers a policy framework for federal agencies as they continue to optimize online services and experiences. It also reflects growing citizen expectations for their digital interactions with the government.
From a citizen’s perspective, digital experience is an area where the government has significant room for improvement. Only 8% of Americans say the U.S. government is responsive to the needs of ordinary Americans, according to Pew Research. And a McKinsey study found that the public sector is ranked lowest of 10 industries for customer satisfaction. Undoubtedly contributing to this dissatisfaction is the fact that private sector companies have set the digital bar so high. From online banking to one-click purchasing, frictionless digital interactions have become the norm for many citizens — and in many cases an expectation versus a “nice-to-have.”
Unlike in many sectors, however, the consequences of a poor customer experience in the public sector can have ramifications beyond lost sales and revenue. The breadth of impact is significant: U.S. federal websites receive about 2 billion visits per month or almost 80 million hours of digital interactions with citizens. A suboptimal digital experience can mean that constituents don’t get access to critical support and services that affect their health and well-being. The U.S. government estimates that $140 billion in potential benefits go unused each year because of “outdated or complicated processes.”
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic's contribution: Invokedynamic in the OpenTelemetry Java agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-invokedynamic-opentelemetry-java-agent</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-invokedynamic-opentelemetry-java-agent"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As the second largest and active Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) project, OpenTelemetry is well on its way to becoming the ubiquitous, unified standard and framework for observability. OpenTelemetry owes this success to its comprehensive and feature-rich toolset that allows users to retrieve valuable observability data from their applications with low effort. The OpenTelemetry Java agent is one of the most mature and feature-rich components in OpenTelemetry’s ecosystem. It provides automatic instrumentation for JVM-based applications and comes with a broad coverage of auto-instrumentation modules for popular Java-frameworks and libraries.

The original instrumentation approach used in the OpenTelemetry Java agent left the maintenance and development of auto-instrumentation modules subject to some restrictions. As part of our reinforced commitment to OpenTelemetry, Elastic® helps evolve and improve OpenTelemetry projects and components. Elastic’s contribution of the Elastic Common Schema to OpenTelemetry was an important step for the open-source community. As another step in our commitment to OpenTelemetry, Elastic started contributing to the OpenTelemetry Java agent. 
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Wert,Jack Shirazi,Jonas Kunz,Sylvain Juge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking back at wildfire research in 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/looking-back-at-wildfire-research-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/looking-back-at-wildfire-research-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T22:10:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yi-Fan Chen, Software Engineer, and Carla Bromberg, Program Lead, Google Research

Wildfires are becoming larger and affecting more and more communities around the world, often resulting in large-scale devastation. Just this year, communities have experienced catastrophic wildfires in Greece, Maui, and Canada to name a few. While the underlying causes leading to such an increase are complex — including changing climate patterns, forest management practices, land use development policies and many more — it is clear that the advancement of technologies can help to address the new challenges.
 
At Google Research, we’ve been investing in a number of climate adaptation efforts, including the application of machine learning (ML) to aid in wildfire prevention and provide information to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claims Processing Automation in Insurance: A Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93359</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/claims-processing-automation-insurance-complete-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Camunda and process orchestration, insurance organizations can scale processes to any level. Learn how and enable claims processing automation today.
The post Claims Processing Automation in Insurance: A Complete Guide appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing ingress2gateway; Simplifying Upgrades to Gateway API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/25/introducing-ingress2gateway/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/25/introducing-ingress2gateway/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Lior Lieberman (Google), Kobi Levi (independent)
Today we are releasing ingress2gateway, a tool
that can help you migrate from Ingress to Gateway
API. Gateway API is just weeks away from graduating to GA, if you
haven't upgraded yet, now's the time to think about it!
Background
In the ever-evolving world of Kubernetes, networking plays a pivotal role. As more applications are
deployed in Kubernetes clusters, effective exposure of these services to clients becomes a critical
concern. If you've been working with Kubernetes, you're likely familiar with the Ingress API,
which has been the go-to solution for managing external access to services.
The Ingress API provides a way to route external traffic to your applications within the cluster,
making it an indispensable tool for many Kub…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grammar checking at Google Search scale]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/grammar-checking-at-google-search-scale.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/grammar-checking-at-google-search-scale.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eric Malmi, Senior Research Scientist, and Jakub Adamek, Senior Software Engineer, Google, Bard Team





Many people with questions about grammar turn to Google Search for guidance. While existing features, such as “Did you mean”, already handle simple typo corrections, more complex grammatical error correction (GEC) is beyond their scope. What makes the development of new Google Search features challenging is that they must have high precision and recall while outputting results quickly.



The conventional approach to GEC is to treat it as a translation problem and use autoregressive Transformer models to decode the response token-by-token, conditioning on the previously generated tokens. However, although Transformer models have proven to be effective at GEC, they aren’t part…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity spotlight on bug bounty researcher @Ammar Askar]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-25-cybersecurity-spotlight-on-bug-bounty-researcher-ammar-askar/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-25-cybersecurity-spotlight-on-bug-bounty-researcher-ammar-askar/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We’re excited to highlight another top contributing researcher to GitHub’s Bug Bounty Program—@Ammar Askar!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-25-cybersecurity-spotlight-on-bug-bounty-researcher-ammar-askar/">Cybersecurity spotlight on bug bounty researcher @Ammar Askar</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving PCI compliance: Leveraging HashiCorp Vault to protect payment data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/achieving-pci-compliance-leveraging-hashicorp-vault-to-protect-payment-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/achieving-pci-compliance-leveraging-hashicorp-vault-to-protect-payment-data"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to address key PCI DSS 4.0 requirements with HashiCorp Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible can help with the Cisco IOS XE Software Web UI Privilege Escalation Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-can-help-with-the-cisco-ios-xe-software-web-ui-privilege-escalation-vulnerability</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-can-help-with-the-cisco-ios-xe-software-web-ui-privilege-escalation-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-20198]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Dubiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The seduction of “why”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47607</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/803163287/0/sethsblog~The-seduction-of-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s classic linkbait. Headlines that explain why something is happening. Questions to AI about why something happens. Even kids, asking their parents. Why is easy to sell. Why is hard to deliver. Consultants make a good living explaining the why. And media companies try to. But most of the time, the why they promise isn’t […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Works – AWS European Sovereign Cloud]]></title>
        <id>eaa67c5d06a038a223f4382ed88baf0665d77ef5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/in-the-works-aws-european-sovereign-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T05:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS European Sovereign Cloud will allow government agencies, regulated industries, and the independent software vendors (ISVs) that support them to store sensitive data and run critical workloads on AWS infrastructure that is operated and supported by AWS employees located in and residents of the European Union (EU). The first Region will be located in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daylight Saving Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2846/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2846/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/daylight_saving_choice.png" title="I average out the spring and fall changes and just set my clocks 39 minutes ahead year-round." alt="I average out the spring and fall changes and just set my clocks 39 minutes ahead year-round." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaffolds and talent]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47619</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/803124713/0/sethsblog~Scaffolds-and-talent/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T20:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kindergarten teachers matter more than you think. Chess isn’t a talent, it’s a learned practice. We’re sorting for head starts, not growth. And that’s just the first chapter. I think Hidden Potential is the most important book in Adam Grant’s career. The indoctrination around test scores and prodigies runs so deep, that most of us […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the Power of Effective Microservices Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93258</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/unlocking-the-power-of-effective-microservices-communication/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T18:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is microservices communication? Learn the difference between synchronous and asynchronous communication and how to choose which is right for your processes.  
The post Unlocking the Power of Effective Microservices Communication appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – CodeWhisperer, CodeCatalyst, RDS, Route53, and more – October 24, 2023]]></title>
        <id>7f6cef8aa03c93e83348e6f22c7a6ae96831967e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-codewhisperer-codecatalyst-rds-route53-and-more-october-23-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T17:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The entire AWS News Blog team is fully focused on writing posts to announce the new services and features during our annual customer conference in Las Vegas, AWS re:Invent! And while we prepare content for you to read, our services teams continue to innovate. Here is my summary of last week’s launches. Last week’s launches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridge the Gap Between Salesforce and Core Business Processes with Camunda]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93237</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/bridge-salesforce-core-business-processes/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bring Salesforce into your core business processes with the new out-of-the-box Salesforce Connector from Camunda.
The post Bridge the Gap Between Salesforce and Core Business Processes with Camunda appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Work Item Chart Filtering in Azure DevOps Dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67602</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-work-item-chart-filtering-in-azure-devops-dashboards/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T08:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce the release of Work Item Chart Filtering in Azure DevOps Dashboards. This enhanced filtering streamlines your workflow just a click away.
With this new feature, not only can you hover over a work item chart,
The post Introducing Work Item Chart Filtering in Azure DevOps Dashboards appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jihye Eom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Use Case for Transactions: Adapting to Transactional Outbox Pattern Semantics in Spring Cloud Stream Kafka Binder]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/24/a-use-case-for-transactions-adapting-to-transactional-outbox-pattern</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/24/a-use-case-for-transactions-adapting-to-transactional-outbox-pattern"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soby Chacko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - October 24th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/24/this-week-in-spring-october-24th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/24/this-week-in-spring-october-24th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CISO’s perspective: Why I’ve read the Elastic Global Threat Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ciso-why-i-have-read-the-elastic-global-threat-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ciso-why-i-have-read-the-elastic-global-threat-report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how Elastic CISO Mandy Andress is using key findings from the 2023 Elastic Global Threat Report to prepare her teams for the upcoming year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mandy Andress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take control of your Elastic Cloud spend with data-driven insights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-spend-data-driven-insights</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-spend-data-driven-insights"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have updated the billing page for our direct monthly, marketplace monthly, and annual customers. The changes include a more user-friendly interface, improved graphical data representations, and repositioned filters for easier navigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunny Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CISO’s perspective: Why I’ve read the Elastic Global Threat Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ciso-why-i-have-read-the-elastic-global-threat-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ciso-why-i-have-read-the-elastic-global-threat-report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
It’s that time of year again. Fall leaves are turning colors, families are gearing up for the holidays, and many vendors are releasing different reports during cybersecurity month. Our researchers at Elastic Security Labs released the 2023 Global Threat Report last week after months of analysis on more than 1 billion data points. As the CISO of Elastic®, my team and I leveraged last year’s report findings and predictions to strategize for the changing threat landscape. This year, I expect our team will dig further on the new threat research discoveries and predictions. In particular, my team and I are taking note of the following insights while preparing for the next year. 
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltd4d7f6d74d502420/6536c2f0796b8e0d6b25d24c/figure-2.p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mandy Andress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take control of your Elastic Cloud spend with data-driven insights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-spend-data-driven-insights</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-spend-data-driven-insights"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re excited to share enhancements made to the Elastic Cloud console billing page, designed to elevate the experience for our direct monthly, marketplace monthly, and annual customers.

The latest features bring simplicity and efficiency, with an intuitive interface, while ensuring you have comprehensive oversight of your usage. You will notice the following changes on the usage page.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltccd32bbedcbc5714/653698bbdae7307c55ace31a/billing-blog.png,billing-blog.pngDaily and monthly usage insights,
Because you have a diverse set of needs, we’ve incorporated an option to view expenditures by day or month. Whether you want to delve into daily usage details or seek a broader monthly usage overview, this feature promises a tailored view aligning with your preferences.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunny Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Plants, process and parties: the Kubernetes 1.28 release interview]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/24/plants-process-and-parties-the-kubernetes-1.28-release-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/24/plants-process-and-parties-the-kubernetes-1.28-release-interview/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Craig Box
Since 2018, one of my favourite contributions to the Kubernetes community has been to share the story of each release. Many of these stories were told on behalf of a past employer; by popular demand, I've brought them back, now under my own name. If you were a fan of the old show, I would be delighted if you would subscribe.
Back in August, we welcomed the release of Kubernetes 1.28. That release was led by Grace Nguyen, a CS student at the University of Waterloo. Grace joined me for the traditional release interview, and while you can read her story below, I encourage you to listen to it if you can.
This transcript has been lightly edited and condensed for clarity.
You're a student at the University of Waterloo, so I want to spend the first two minutes of this interview …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Automation to Transformation: Understanding Digitalization]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93249</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/from-automation-to-transformation-understanding-digitalization/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T22:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uncover the connection between digitalization and the full benefits of automation as well as how they relate to digital transformation.
The post From Automation to Transformation: Understanding Digitalization appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Bloomberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to Automation in Insurance: Top Use Cases and Benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93238</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/camunda-blog-guide-to-automation-in-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T21:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you automate insurance? Read on to learn the specifics and explore how automation is revolutionizing the insurance industry, one process at a time. 
The post A Guide to Automation in Insurance: Top Use Cases and Benefits appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW!!! Getting started landing page for Ansible Automation Platform on Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-getting-started-landing-page-for-ansible-automation-platform-on-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-getting-started-landing-page-for-ansible-automation-platform-on-azure"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is co-authored by Tomas Znamenacek and Hicham (he-sham) Mourad]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas Znamenacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five trends in cloud infrastructure and what they mean]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/five-trends-in-cloud-infrastructure-and-what-they-mean</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/five-trends-in-cloud-infrastructure-and-what-they-mean"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T07:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From AI to the edge, HashiCorp Co-Founder and CTO Armon Dadgar shares his insights on where the cloud is headed, and what that means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Vault 3.1.0-RC1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/23/spring-vault-3-1-0-rc1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/23/spring-vault-3-1-0-rc1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy a Hello World web app with Elastic Observability on Azure Container Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-hello-world-web-app-elastic-observability-azure-container-apps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-hello-world-web-app-elastic-observability-azure-container-apps"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow the step-by-step process of instrumenting Elastic Observability for a Hello World web app running on Azure Container Apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy a Hello World web app with Elastic Observability on Azure Container Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-hello-world-web-app-elastic-observability-azure-container-apps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-hello-world-web-app-elastic-observability-azure-container-apps"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Observability is the optimal tool to provide visibility into your running web apps. Microsoft Azure Container Apps is a fully managed environment that enables you to run containerized applications on a serverless platform so that your applications scale up and down. This allows you to accomplish the dual objective of serving every customer’s need for availability while meeting your needs to do so as efficiently as possible.

Using Elastic Observability and Azure Container Apps is a perfect combination for developers to deploy  web apps that are auto-scaled with fully observable operations.

This blog post will show you how to deploy a simple Hello World web app to Azure Container Apps and then walk you through the steps to instrument the Hello World web app to enable observation …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: PersistentVolume Last Phase Transition Time in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/23/persistent-volume-last-phase-transition-time/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/23/persistent-volume-last-phase-transition-time/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Roman Bednář (Red Hat)
In the recent Kubernetes v1.28 release, we (SIG Storage) introduced a new alpha feature that aims to improve PersistentVolume (PV)
storage management and help cluster administrators gain better insights into the lifecycle of PVs.
With the addition of the lastPhaseTransitionTime field into the status of a PV,
cluster administrators are now able to track the last time a PV transitioned to a different
phase, allowing for more efficient
and informed resource management.
Why do we need new PV field?
PersistentVolumes in Kubernetes play a crucial role in providing storage resources to workloads running in the cluster.
However, managing these PVs effectively can be challenging, especially when it comes
to determining the last time a PV transitioned between different…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public REST API for Web Modeler]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93190</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/public-rest-api-web-modeler/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T03:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the Camunda public REST API for Web Modeler, developers can perform advanced operations, from standard CRUD to creating entirely new projects and more.
The post Public REST API for Web Modeler appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answering billions of reporting queries each day with low latency]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/answering-billions-of-reporting-queries.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/answering-billions-of-reporting-queries.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T17:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jagan Sankaranarayanan, Senior Staff Software Engineer, and Indrajit Roy, Head of Napa Product, Google




Google Ads infrastructure runs on an internal data warehouse called Napa. Billions of reporting queries, which power critical dashboards used by advertising clients to measure campaign performance, run on tables stored in Napa. These tables contain records of ads performance that are keyed using particular customers and the campaign identifiers with which they are associated. Keys are tokens that are used both to associate an ads record with a particular client and campaign (e.g., customer_id, campaign_id) and for efficient retrieval. A record contains dozens of keys, so clients use reporting queries to specify keys needed to filter the data to understand ads performance (e.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rotate Your SSL/TLS Certificates Now – Amazon RDS and Amazon Aurora Expire in 2024]]></title>
        <id>f73464fad068270f248da400702f12effc2a0f1f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/rotate-your-ssl-tls-certificates-now-amazon-rds-and-amazon-aurora-expire-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T15:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t be surprised if you have seen the Certificate Update in the Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) console. If you use or plan to use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) or Transport Layer Security (TLS) with certificate verification to connect to your database instances of Amazon RDS for MySQL, MariaDB, SQL Server, Oracle, PostgreSQL, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: A Quick Recap of 2023 China Kubernetes Contributor Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/20/kcs-shanghai/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/20/kcs-shanghai/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Paco Xu and Michael Yao (DaoCloud)
On September 26, 2023, the first day of
KubeCon + CloudNativeCon + Open Source Summit China 2023,
nearly 50 contributors gathered in Shanghai for the Kubernetes Contributor Summit.
 
All participants in the 2023 Kubernetes Contributor Summit
This marked the first in-person offline gathering held in China after three years of the pandemic.
A joyful meetup
The event began with welcome speeches from Kevin Wang from Huawei Cloud,
one of the co-chairs of KubeCon, and Puja from Giant Swarm.
Following the opening remarks, the contributors introduced themselves briefly. Most attendees were from China,
while some contributors had made the journey from Europe and the United States specifically for the conference.
Technical experts from companies such as Mic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English learners can now practice speaking on Search]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/google-search-can-now-help-with-english-speaking-practice.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/google-search-can-now-help-with-english-speaking-practice.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T16:24:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Christian Plagemann, Director, and Katya Cox, Product Manager, Google Research




Learning a language can open up new opportunities in a person’s life. It can help people connect with those from different cultures, travel the world, and advance their career. English alone is estimated to have 1.5 billion learners worldwide. Yet proficiency in a new language is difficult to achieve, and many learners cite a lack of opportunity to practice speaking actively and receiving actionable feedback as a barrier to learning.




We are excited to announce a new feature of Google Search that helps people practice speaking and improve their language skills. Within the next few days, Android users in Argentina, Colombia, India (Hindi), Indonesia, Mexico, and Venezuela can get even more langua…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Code Coverage Tab Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67794</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/improved-code-coverage-tab-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T09:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re using Azure DevOps for your CI/CD pipeline, you may be interested in our recent improvements to code coverage testing. Code coverage tests can help you identify areas of your code that are not tested, or not tested enough, and improve the quality of your automated tests and overall code quality.
The post Improved Code Coverage Tab Experience appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinayak Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP expands IAM enterprise capabilities by introducing groups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-expands-iam-enterprise-capabilities-by-introducing-groups</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-expands-iam-enterprise-capabilities-by-introducing-groups"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Groups offer a new approach for managing identities and their access to HashiCorp Cloud Platform (HCP) resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measurement-induced entanglement phase transitions in a quantum circuit]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/measurement-induced-entanglement-phase.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/measurement-induced-entanglement-phase.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jesse Hoke, Student Researcher, and Pedram Roushan, Senior Research Scientist, Quantum AI Team




Quantum mechanics allows many phenomena that are classically impossible: a quantum particle can exist in a superposition of two states simultaneously or be entangled with another particle, such that anything you do to one seems to instantaneously also affect the other, regardless of the space between them. But perhaps no aspect of quantum theory is as striking as the act of measurement. In classical mechanics, a measurement need not affect the system being studied. But a measurement on a quantum system can profoundly influence its behavior. For example, when a quantum bit of information, called a qubit, that is in a superposition of both “0” and “1” is measured, its state will sudde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon MSK Replicator – Fully Managed Replication across MSK Clusters in Same or Different AWS Regions]]></title>
        <id>c1324a25314db12bed4d7242f05c870d0bdde108</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-msk-replicator-fully-managed-replication-across-msk-clusters-in-same-or-different-aws-regions/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T17:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka (Amazon MSK) provides a fully managed and highly available Apache Kafka service simplifying the way you process streaming data. When using Apache Kafka, a common architectural pattern is to replicate data from one cluster to another. Cross-cluster replication is often used to implement business continuity and disaster recovery plans […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第239話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755331321453</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755331321453"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform provider code generation now in tech preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-provider-code-generation-now-in-tech-preview</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-provider-code-generation-now-in-tech-preview"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T07:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform provider code generation is an extensible solution that lets developers automate portions of their provider development workflow — now in tech preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Customization Capability in Amazon CodeWhisperer Generates Even Better Suggestions (Preview)]]></title>
        <id>70dd1e1fe2691c02993fd47419de9212cf2249dd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-customization-capability-in-amazon-codewhisperer-generates-even-better-suggestions-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An AI coding companion, such as Amazon CodeWhisperer, aims to improve developers’ productivity by helping them write code quickly and securely. However, in particular cases, developers need to have code recommendations based on their internal libraries and APIs they extensively use every day. As most of the existing AI coding companion tools are trained only […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PKI hosting: Cloud-based PKI vs. self managed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pki-hosting-cloud-based-pki-vs-self-managed</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pki-hosting-cloud-based-pki-vs-self-managed"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T07:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the differences between hosting (public key infrastructure) PKI workloads in the cloud versus on-premises?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDKTF 0.19 adds support for config-driven import and refactoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdktf-0-19-adds-support-for-config-driven-import-and-refactoring</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdktf-0-19-adds-support-for-config-driven-import-and-refactoring"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T07:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.19 adds support for importing existing resources with  auto-generated configuration in CDKTF projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Seventh Generation Memory-optimized Amazon EC2 Instances (R7i)]]></title>
        <id>c59c1841d9d6b3e95d0210c06dd38a524d0993dc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-seventh-generation-memory-optimized-amazon-ec2-instances-r7i/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T18:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier, we introduced a duo of Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances to our lineup: the general-purpose Amazon EC2 M7i instances and the compute-optimized Amazon EC2 C7i instances. Today, I’m happy to share that we’re expanding these seventh-generation x86-based offerings to include memory-optimized Amazon EC2 R7i instances. These instances are powered by custom 4th […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – EBS Status Check, Textract Custom Queries, Amazon Linux 2, and more – October 16, 2023]]></title>
        <id>d9629e933b3b25778325dd23875967d8638a39da</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-ebs-status-check-textract-custom-queries-amazon-linux-2-and-more-october-16-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T18:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With just 41 days until AWS re:Invent 2023 opens, I’m doing my best to stay heads-down and focused on working with the entire AWS News Blog team to create plenty of awesome new posts for your reading pleasure! I’ll take a short break this morning to share some of the most exciting launches and other […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving traffic evacuations: A case study]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/improving-traffic-evacuations-case-study.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/improving-traffic-evacuations-case-study.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T17:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Damien Pierce, Software Engineer, and John Anderson, Senior Research Director, Google Research




Some cities or communities develop an evacuation plan to be used in case of an emergency. There are a number of reasons why city officials might enact their plan, a primary one being a natural disaster, such as a tornado, flood, or wildfire. An evacuation plan can help the community more effectively respond to an emergency, and so could help save lives. However, it can be difficult for a city to evaluate such a plan because it is not practical to have an entire town or city rehearse a full blown evacuation. For example, Mill Valley, a city in northern California, created a wildfire evacuation plan but lacked an estimate for how long the evacuation would take.


Today we describe a c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Linux package archive site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-linux-package-archive-site</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-linux-package-archive-site"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp will cease publishing packages of our products for end-of-life (EoL) distributions to our production packaging sites and migrate EoL versions to our new archive site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Batch calibration: Rethinking calibration for in-context learning and prompt engineering]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/batch-calibration-rethinking.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/batch-calibration-rethinking.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Han Zhou, Student Researcher, and Subhrajit Roy, Senior Research Scientist, Google Research





Prompting large language models (LLMs) has become an efficient learning paradigm for adapting LLMs to a new task by conditioning on human-designed instructions. The remarkable in-context learning (ICL) ability of LLMs also leads to efficient few-shot learners that can generalize from few-shot input-label pairs. However, the predictions of LLMs are highly sensitive and even biased to the choice of templates, label spaces (such as yes/no, true/false, correct/incorrect), and demonstration examples, resulting in unexpected performance degradation and barriers for pursuing robust LLM applications. To address this problem, calibration methods have been developed to mitigate the effects of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2023 HashiCorp Systems Integrator Award winners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2023-hashicorp-systems-integrator-award-winners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2023-hashicorp-systems-integrator-award-winners"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2023 HashiCorp Partner Network Awards for Systems Integrators have been announced. Meet the 13 winners in 5 categories around the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2023 HashiCorp Technology Partner Award winners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2023-hashicorp-technology-partner-award-winners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2023-hashicorp-technology-partner-award-winners"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2023 HashiCorp Technology Partner Awards have been announced. Congratulations to Palo Alto Networks, Datadog, Zscaler, and Tines!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing industrial use cases for physical simulation on future error-corrected quantum computers]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/developing-industrial-use-cases-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/developing-industrial-use-cases-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T20:56:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nicholas Rubin, Senior Research Scientist, and Ryan Babbush, Head of Quantum Algorithms, Quantum AI Team





If you’ve paid attention to the quantum computing space, you’ve heard the claim that in the future, quantum computers will solve certain problems exponentially more efficiently than classical computers can. They have the potential to transform many industries, from pharmaceuticals to energy.



For the most part, these claims have rested on arguments about the asymptotic scaling of algorithms as the problem size approaches infinity, but this tells us very little about the practical performance of quantum computers for finite-sized problems. We want to be more concrete: Exactly which problems are quantum computers more suited to tackle than their classical counterparts, an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Bootstrap an Air Gapped Cluster With Kubeadm]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/12/bootstrap-an-air-gapped-cluster-with-kubeadm/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/12/bootstrap-an-air-gapped-cluster-with-kubeadm/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Rob Mengert (Defense Unicorns)
Ever wonder how software gets deployed onto a system that is deliberately disconnected from the Internet and other networks? These systems are typically disconnected due to their sensitive nature. Sensitive as in utilities (power/water), banking, healthcare, weapons systems, other government use cases, etc. Sometimes it's technically a water gap, if you're running Kubernetes on an underwater vessel. Still, these environments need software to operate. This concept of deployment in a disconnected state is what it means to deploy to the other side of an air gap.
Again, despite this posture, software still needs to run in these environments. Traditionally, software artifacts are physically carried across the air gap on hard drives, USB sticks, CDs, or flo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure and security releases open HashiConf 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/infrastructure-security-lifecycle-releases-open-hashiconf-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/infrastructure-security-lifecycle-releases-open-hashiconf-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf 2023 unveils key announcements covering infrastructure and workflow enhancements as well as new security lifecycle management capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer now supports webhooks and streamlined run task reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-now-supports-webhooks-and-streamlined-run-task-reviews</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-now-supports-webhooks-and-streamlined-run-task-reviews"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Webhooks automatically notify external systems about image-related events. Streamlined run task reviews offer meaningful context on HCP Packer run task evaluations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HCP Vault Secrets, Radar, and other features fight secret sprawl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-vault-secrets-radar-and-other-features-fight-secrets-sprawl</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-vault-secrets-radar-and-other-features-fight-secrets-sprawl"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault adds cross-platform product innovations with an emphasis on resolving secrets sprawl.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Secrets is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-secrets-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-secrets-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Secrets is a managed offering of HashiCorp Vault focusing on secrets management for developers that offers key capabilities including secrets sync.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform testing and UX features reduce toil, errors, and costs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-testing-and-ux-features-reduce-toil-errors-and-costs</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-testing-and-ux-features-reduce-toil-errors-and-costs"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform and Terraform Cloud improve developer usability and velocity with a test framework, generated module tests, and stacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Boundary Desktop embedded terminal, LDAP support, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-boundary-desktop-embedded-terminal-ldap-support-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-boundary-desktop-embedded-terminal-ldap-support-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.14, with an embedded terminal in the desktop client and LDAP GA support, is now available for download as well as for use on HCP Boundary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67748</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/october-patches-for-azure-devops-server-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T17:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 Patch 4
Note: If you have Azure DevOps Server 2022,
The post October patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Insights Collection for Event-Driven Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-insights-collection-for-event-driven-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-insights-collection-for-event-driven-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-Driven Ansible became generally available in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4. As part of the release, Red Hat Insights and Ansible teams collaborated to implement and certify a Red Hat Insights collection integrating Insights events as a source of events for Ansible Automation Platform. This provides a consistent way to receive and handle events triggered from Insights to drive and track automation within the Ansible Automation Platform. The collection is available for installation on Ansible automation hub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerome Marc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: CRI-O is moving towards pkgs.k8s.io]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/10/cri-o-community-package-infrastructure/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/10/cri-o-community-package-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
The Kubernetes community recently announced
that their legacy package repositories are frozen, and now they moved to
introduced community-owned package repositories powered by the
OpenBuildService (OBS).
CRI-O has a long history of utilizing
OBS for their package builds,
but all of the packaging efforts have been done manually so far.
The CRI-O community absolutely loves Kubernetes, which means that they're
delighted to announce that:
All future CRI-O packages will be shipped as part of the officially supported
Kubernetes infrastructure hosted on pkgs.k8s.io!
There will be a deprecation phase for the existing packages, which is currently
being discussed in the CRI-O community.
The new infrastructure will only support releases of CRI-O >= v1.28.2 as well as
release br…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANPO: A Scene understanding, Accessibility, Navigation, Pathfinding, & Obstacle avoidance dataset]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/sanpo-scene-understanding-accessibility.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/sanpo-scene-understanding-accessibility.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T19:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sagar M. Waghmare, Senior Software Engineer, and Kimberly Wilber, Software Engineer, Google Research, Perception Team




As most people navigate their everyday world, they process visual input from the environment using an eye-level perspective. Unlike robots and self-driving cars, people don't have any "out-of-body" sensors to help guide them. Instead, a person’s sensory input is completely "egocentric", or "from the self." This also applies to new technologies that understand the world around us from a human-like perspective, e.g., robots navigating through unknown buildings, AR glasses that highlight objects, or assistive technology to help people run independently.





In computer vision, scene understanding is the subfield that studies how visible objects relate to the sce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Control Tower, Amazon Bedrock, Amazon OpenSearch Service, and More (October 9, 2023)]]></title>
        <id>196aa0e7b4449c650c1db86dcc60997ea5c34699</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-control-tower-amazon-bedrock-amazon-opensearch-service-and-more-october-9-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T19:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Northern Hemisphere enjoys early fall and pumpkins take over the local farmers markets and coffee flavors here in the United States, we’re also just 50 days away from re:Invent 2023! But before we officially enter pre:Invent sea­­son, let’s have a look at some of last week’s exciting news and announcements. Last Week’s Launches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS ExecLeaders Data and Generative AI Day: Fueling Business Growth with Data and Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>88b88bda41c0f93e667725076ecacd7c7f13d55e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-execleaders-data-and-generative-ai-day-fueling-business-growth-with-data-and-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T14:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on Thursday, October 5, 2023, for a free-to-attend online event, Data and Generative AI Day. AWS will stream the event simultaneously across multiple platforms, including LinkedIn Live and YouTube. In the realm of generative AI, the power and potential hidden within your organization’s data are more expansive than ever before. Generative AI has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Architecture: Conformance]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/05/sig-architecture-conformance-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/05/sig-architecture-conformance-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
This is the first interview of a SIG Architecture Spotlight series
that will cover the different subprojects. We start with the SIG
Architecture: Conformance subproject
In this SIG
Architecture
spotlight, we talked with Riaan
Kleinhans (ii-Team), Lead for the
Conformance
sub-project.
About SIG Architecture and the Conformance subproject
Frederico (FSM): Hello Riaan, and welcome! For starters, tell us a
bit about yourself, your role and how you got involved in Kubernetes.
Riaan Kleinhans (RK): Hi! My name is Riaan Kleinhans and I live in
South Africa. I am the Project manager for the ii-Team in New
Zealand. When I joined ii the plan was to move to New Zealand in April
2020 and then Covid happened. Fortunately, being a flexible and
dynamic team we were…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 C7a Instances Powered By 4th Gen AMD EPYC Processors for Compute Optimized Workloads]]></title>
        <id>0cde5cd2f3e484703aa1a6c2b5b1dafcc3b4f5bb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c7a-instances-powered-by-4th-gen-amd-epyc-processors-for-compute-optimized-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T22:29:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched the compute optimized Amazon EC2 C6a instances in February 2022 powered by 3rd Gen AMD EPYC (Milan) processors, running at frequencies up to 3.6 GHz. Today, we’re announcing the general availability of new, compute optimized Amazon EC2 C7a instances, powered by the 4th Gen AMD EPYC (Genoa) processors with a maximum frequency of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon DataZone Now Generally Available – Collaborate on Data Projects across Organizational Boundaries]]></title>
        <id>36ee987902c738b982d7c946ca3bfbd9f6eb6972</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-datazone-now-generally-available-collaborate-on-data-projects-across-organizational-boundaries/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T19:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re announcing the general availability of Amazon DataZone, a new data management service to catalog, discover, analyze, share, and govern data between data producers and consumers in your organization. At AWS re:Invent 2022, we preannounced Amazon DataZone, and in March 2023, we previewed it publicly. During the keynote of the last re:Invent, Swami Sivasubramanian, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scalable spherical CNNs for scientific applications]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/scalable-spherical-cnns-for-scientific.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/scalable-spherical-cnns-for-scientific.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T17:26:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Carlos Esteves and Ameesh Makadia, Research Scientists, Google Research, Athena Team




Typical deep learning models for computer vision, like convolutional neural networks (CNNs) and vision transformers (ViT), process signals assuming planar (flat) spaces. For example, digital images are represented as a grid of pixels on a plane. However, this type of data makes up only a fraction of the data we encounter in scientific applications. Variables sampled from the Earth's atmosphere, like temperature and humidity, are naturally represented on the sphere. Some kinds of cosmological data and panoramic photos are also spherical signals, and are better treated as such. 



Using methods designed for planar images to process spherical signals is problematic for a couple of reasons. Firs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第238話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755278351476</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755278351476"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seeding Ansible Automation Platform Content At Installation Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/seeding-ansible-automation-platform-content-at-installation-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/seeding-ansible-automation-platform-content-at-installation-time"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous blog, I announced the tech preview of containerized Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. With that we introduced a new feature to enable you to pre-seed configuration and content at installation time. This blog will take you through how that works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>