<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-29T02:03:08.633Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-29T02:03:08.633Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craft and imperfection]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41114</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/697903668/0/sethsblog~Craft-and-imperfection/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T09:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As soon as we mechanize, measure and perfect something, it becomes far less interesting. There’s not a lot of discussion about which factory made your can of Coke, because they’re all the same. Implicit in the desire to have something handmade is that while it might be better than what you’re used to, it might […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.2 EAP #2 Is Out With New Inspections For Generics]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=250616</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/05/27/goland-2022-2-eap-2-is-out-with-new-inspections-for-generics/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T18:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second build of our 2022.2 Early Access Program is here. You can get the EAP build via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package (for Ubuntu), or from inside GoLand select Check IDE updates for Early Access Program in Preferences / Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System Settings […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2 Early Access Program Is Open]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=248298</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/05/phpstorm-2022-2-early-access-program-is-open/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T14:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Early Access Program (EAP) for PhpStorm 2022.2 starts today! In this first EAP build, you’ll get a chance to preview many new features related to generics, Rector support, and a bunch of quality-of-life improvements. Download PhpStorm 2022.2 EAP If you’re not familiar with our EAP, here’s a quick recap: We publish new EAP builds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Vault 2.4.0-M1 and 3.0.0-M1 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-vault-2-4-0-m1-and-3-0-0-m1-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-vault-2-4-0-m1-and-3-0-0-m1-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T14:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Vault 2.4.0-M1 and 3.0.0-M1 milestones have been released and are now available from repo.spring.io.



Notable new features include:





Support for PEM-encoded certificates and private keys including Elliptic Curve ("EC")



Support for Vault Repositories using versioned Key/Value secrets engines



Support for Vault-based RevisionRepository using versioned Key/Value secrets engines





Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.



Additionally, Spring Vault 3.0.0-M1 ships with:





Upgrade to Java 17 baseline, Spring Framework 6



Upgrade to AWS SDK v2





Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.



Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.



How can you help?


If you’re interested in helping out, check out the "ideal for contribution" tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-vault tag.



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Release 2.4.0-M1 on GitHub | Documentation for 2.4.0-M1 | Release 3.0.0-M1 on GitHub | Documentation for 3.0.0-M1 | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.2 EAP2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=250500</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2022/05/rubymine-2022-2-eap2/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T13:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second 2022.2 EAP build is now available! Here are the build highlights: Improved support for retrieving types from unknown classes in RBS New option to exit line comment continuation Open Gemfile from a RuboCop suggestion Improved rendering of YARD docs Improved support for retrieving types from unknown classes in RBS Previously, we only provided […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Zykova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.3 is available. Compatible with Spring Boot 2.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-cloud-2021-0-3-is-available-compatible-with-spring-boot-2-7-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-cloud-2021-0-3-is-available-compatible-with-spring-boot-2-7-0"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce the Spring Cloud 2021.0.3 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2021.0.3 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0.3 Release Train

This release is primarily for compatibility with Spring Boot 2.7.0 along with Spring Boot 2.6.x.

To see all the issues and pull requests in this release, please see here.
Spring Cloud Sleuth


  
Bug fixes and minor enhancements


Spring Cloud Contract


  
Bug fixes and JsonAssert upgrade


Spring Cloud Gateway


  
Bug fixes and path variable support for PrefixPath filter.


The following modules were updated as part of 2021.0.3:


  
    

      Module 
      Version 
      Issues
    

  
  
    
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How change happens]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43035</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/697787944/0/sethsblog~How-change-happens/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slowly then all at once For people who aren’t paying attention or actively involved, it can seem like cultural change is sudden. One big shift after another. In fact, cultural change always happens relatively slowly. Person by person, conversation by conversation. Expectations are established, roles are defined, systems are built. From the foundation The people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[npm security update: Attack campaign using stolen OAuth tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-26-npm-security-update-oauth-tokens/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-26-npm-security-update-oauth-tokens/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T04:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[npm's impact analysis of the attack campaign using stolen OAuth tokens and additional findings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Field Topology]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2625/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2625/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/field_topology.png" title="The combination croquet set/10-lane pool can also be used for some varieties of foosball and Skee-Ball." alt="The combination croquet set/10-lane pool can also be used for some varieties of foosball and Skee-Ball." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M6id and C6id Instances with Up to 7.6 TB Local NVMe Storage]]></title>
        <id>dabb34f9d25282db77234ee28cb2826f74cfe7b3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-m6id-and-c6id-instances-with-up-to-7-6-tb-local-nvme-storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T21:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, we launched the Amazon EC2 M6i instances and C6i instances, our sixth-generation offerings that include 3rd generation Intel Xeon Scalable processors. Today we are expanding Amazon EC2 M6id and C6id instances, backed by NVMe-based SSD block-level instance storage physically connected to the host server. These instances are powered by the Intel Xeon Scalable […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTS 0.6 Adds New Terraform Cloud Agent and HCP Consul Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cts-0-6-new-terraform-cloud-agent-hcp-consul-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cts-0-6-new-terraform-cloud-agent-hcp-consul-support"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of HashiCorp Consul-Terraform-Sync (CTS) 0.6 represents a key step in the maturity of our Network Infrastructure Automation (NIA) solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 EAP #2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=250018</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/05/webstorm-2022-2-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T15:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re continuing our build-up to WebStorm 2022.2 with our second EAP build. To catch up on all the new features, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. You can also manually download […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: the good Dr. David Syer on the new and novel in Spring and Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/26/a-bootiful-podcast-the-good-dr-david-syer-on-the-new-and-novel-in-spring-and-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/26/a-bootiful-podcast-the-good-dr-david-syer-on-the-new-and-novel-in-spring-and-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long talks to Spring Boot and Spring Cloud luminary, the good Dr. @David_Syer, about the latest and greatest on Spring and Kubernetes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 GoLand Shortcuts to Boost Your Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=250435</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/05/26/5-goland-shortcuts-to-boost-your-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T14:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand has many shortcuts for any action you can perform in the IDE. The good news is that you don’t have to learn all of them to be productive. How to choose a keymap Let’s start by choosing the right keymap to ensure that you feel right at home more quickly. By default, GoLand has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Zharova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 EAP 2: Improved Support for Bean Validation Annotations, Support for Jakarta Persistence 3.1, And More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=249666</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/05/intellij-idea-2022-2-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T14:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 EAP 2 is now available. The new build brings improvements for working with JSON, YAML, and .properties files, support for new features in Jakarta Persistence 3.1, better support for Bean Validation annotations, and more. You can get the latest build from our website or the free Toolbox App, or via snaps for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2.2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible product team at Red Hat is thrilled to announce the general availability of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.2, which includes numerous features and bug fixes that further solidify Ansible Automation Platform as the de facto enterprise IT automation solution for developers to operations teams in data centers, clouds, and at the edge. A few of the most noteworthy features in this release include:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andriusb@redhat.com (Andrius Benokraitis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 Webinar Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55344</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-platform-8-webinar-recap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out these answers to the questions we didn't get to answer during our recent Camunda Platform 8 Release Webinar.
The post Camunda Platform 8 Webinar Recap appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.2 EAP2: Interval Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=250317</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/05/clion-2022-2-eap2-interval-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T12:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new CLion 2022.2 EAP2, 222.2680.4, is available from our website via the Toolbox App or as a snap package (if you are using Ubuntu). If you are on macOS, there is a separate build for Apple Silicon (M1 chip). Those who are already using EAP1 can apply a patch to update to EAP2. DOWNLOAD […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin API for Apache Spark: Streaming, Jupyter, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=big-data-tools&amp;p=249904</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/big-data-tools/2022/05/26/kotlin-api-for-apache-spark-streaming-jupyter-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T11:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, fellow data engineers! It’s Pasha here, and today I’m going to introduce you to the new release of Kotlin API for Apache Spark. It’s been a long time since the last major release announcements, mainly because we wanted to avoid bothering you with minor improvements. But today’s announcement is huge! First, let me remind […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pasha Finkelshteyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching your search engine]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43003</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/697697018/0/sethsblog~Switching-your-search-engine/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make the choice to upgrade from Google. There are many good reasons to do so, and few downsides. Do it for your efficiency, for the health of the web and for the planet too. First, a quick clarification because this is confusing to many people: The thing you use to browse the internet is not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Annotated – May 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=250208</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/05/php-annotated-may-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T09:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings everyone! Welcome to the May installment of PHP Annotated, where we catch up on the most interesting things that have happened in the PHP world over the last month,including curated news, articles, tools, and videos. Kudos to Sergey Panteleev for helping to compile the May edition of PHP Annotated. News PHP 8.1.6 and PHP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting telecom business results with Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/boosting-telecom-business-results-with-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/boosting-telecom-business-results-with-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telecom providers worldwide are adopting cloud technologies in varying scope as they expand into 5G services. Here, we'll take a look at some key Elastic Cloud capabilities that can make it simpler for telecom providers to scale their services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.2.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-2-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-2-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.2.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
The 8.2.2 patch contains fixes and small enhancements for the stack. For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
8.2.2 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quin Hoxie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting telecom business results with Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/boosting-telecom-business-results-with-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/boosting-telecom-business-results-with-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Telecom providers worldwide are adopting cloud technologies in varying scope as they expand into new 5G services. At this critical point in the industry’s evolution, choosing the right cloud partner is essential. With major networks like T-Mobile already on board, Elastic stands ready to fully support telecom providers in their shift to the cloud. 

Here, we will take a closer look at some of the key Elastic Cloud capabilities that make it possible for telecom companies to effectively scale their services with agility and flexibility.

[Related article: Why Elastic Cloud is the best way to use Elastic]
Scaling to support enterprise customers in new ways
The telecom industry is changing fast, and providers must seek creative ways to stay competitive.

According to a recent Ericsson report…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.2.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-2-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-2-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quin Hoxie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we use Dependabot to secure GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-25-how-we-use-dependabot-to-secure-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-25-how-we-use-dependabot-to-secure-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T22:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A two-part story about how GitHub’s Product Security Engineering team rolled out Dependabot internally to track vulnerable dependencies, and how GitHub tracks and prioritizes technical debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning with Label Differential Privacy]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/deep-learning-with-label-differential.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/deep-learning-with-label-differential.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T20:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by  Pasin Manurangsi and Chiyuan Zhang, Research Scientists, Google Research  
Over the last several years, there has been an increased focus on developing differential privacy (DP) machine learning (ML) algorithms. DP has been the basis of several practical deployments in industry — and has even been employed by the U.S. Census — because it enables the understanding of system and algorithm privacy guarantees. The underlying assumption of DP is that changing a single user’s contribution to an algorithm should not significantly change its output distribution. 
 In the standard supervised learning setting, a model is trained to make a prediction of the label for each input given a training set of example pairs {[input1,label1], …, [inputn, labeln]}. In the case of deep learning, previ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.3.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/25/spring-authorization-server-0-3-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/25/spring-authorization-server-0-3-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.3.0.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.3.0'




See the release notes for complete details.



With this release, you can view the initial version of the reference documentation and the new project page on spring.io.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.11 Introduces New Provider Command and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-terraform-0-11-introduces-new-provider-command</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-terraform-0-11-introduces-new-provider-command"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform (CDKTF) 0.11 introduces an easier way to add providers to your application and improvements to the debugging process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[macOS Environment Setup For MAUI Development]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=248267</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/05/25/macos-environment-setup-for-maui-development/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the latest release of JetBrains Rider 2022.2 EAP, we’ve added preview support for .NET Multi-Platform App UI, more commonly referred to as MAUI. It is the spiritual successor to the popular Xamarin.Forms framework and evolution in ideas and implementation.  MAUI lets you build native apps using a .NET cross-platform UI toolkit with multiple target […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++Now 2022 Trip Report]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=249787</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/05/c-now-2022-trip-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From May 1 to May 6, 2022, I attended the C++Now conference in Aspen, Colorado. This was my third time speaking at C++Now (I also attended in 2016 and 2019), and in my opinion it was the best edition of C++Now so far! This conference is truly different. It is much smaller than other international […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timur Doumler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to do When You Can’t Quickly Migrate to Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55237</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/what-to-do-when-you-cant-quickly-migrate-to-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not ready to migrate to Camunda Platform 8 yet? Learn the alternative approaches you can take now to prepare for migrating later.
The post What to do When You Can’t Quickly Migrate to Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring New Possibilities with the AWS Cloud Control Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/exploring-new-possibilities-with-the-aws-cloud-control-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/exploring-new-possibilities-with-the-aws-cloud-control-collection"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently made available an experimental alpha Collection of generated modules using the AWS Cloud Control API for interacting with AWS Services. This content is not intended for production in its current state. We are making this work available because we thought it was important to share our research and get your feedback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools Plugin 2022.5 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=249672</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/05/25/edutools-plugin-2022-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T11:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With this release, we’re continuing to improve plugin quality by focusing on bug fixes. Here are the highlights: EDU-4869: The issue with the wrong compiler being used when submitting a solution to Codeforces has been fixed. EDU-4512: Fixed the bug with wrongly displayed “Python courses not supported” messages when using IntelliJ IDEA with the EduTools […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Classical music and documentaries]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42067</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/697585754/0/sethsblog~Classical-music-and-documentaries/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T09:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check the ratings, whichever magazine or website you choose: Classical music and documentary films almost always get more stars and higher ratings than pop music and feature films. The reason is simple: The folks who like stuff like that like stuff like that. The smallest viable audience for certain genres is very clear. That allows […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voyager Wires]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2624/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2624/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/voyager_wires.png" title="Also, they're getting increasingly worried that someone will accidentally hit the 'retract' button, and that the end of the cable thrashing around as it winds up could devastate the Earth's surface." alt="Also, they're getting increasingly worried that someone will accidentally hit the 'retract' button, and that the end of the cable thrashing around as it winds up could devastate the Earth's surface." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Open is Camunda Platform 8?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55199</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/how-open-is-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the different components of Camunda Platform 8 and their licenses. Plus, explore the possible paths to production.
The post How Open is Camunda Platform 8? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for AWS DataSync – Move Data Between AWS and Other Public Locations]]></title>
        <id>905a367112dd04b244491567bac3a7266994c9f7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-aws-datasync-move-data-between-aws-and-google-cloud-storage-or-aws-and-microsoft-azure-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moving data to and from AWS Storage services can be automated and accelerated with AWS DataSync. For example, you can use DataSync to migrate data to AWS, replicate data for business continuity, and move data for analysis and processing in the cloud. You can use DataSync to transfer data to and from AWS Storage services, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image-Text Pre-training with Contrastive Captioners]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/image-text-pre-training-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/image-text-pre-training-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zirui Wang and Jiahui Yu, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Oftentimes, machine learning (ML) model developers begin their design using a generic backbone model that is trained at scale and with capabilities transferable to a wide range of downstream tasks. In natural language processing, a number of popular backbone models, including BERT, T5, GPT-3 (sometimes also referred to as “foundation models”), are pre-trained on web-scale data and have demonstrated generic multi-tasking capabilities through zero-shot, few-shot or transfer learning. Compared with training over-specialized individual models, pre-training backbone models for a large number of downstream tasks can amortize the training costs, allowing one to overcome resource limitations when building large s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved REST API documentation]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-24-improved-rest-api-documentation/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-24-improved-rest-api-documentation/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce some big improvements to our REST API documentation. We know developers rely on this documentation to integrate with GitHub, and we are committed to making it trustworthy, easy to find, and easy to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing for Spring Boot 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/preparing-for-spring-boot-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/preparing-for-spring-boot-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.0 was the first release in the 2.x line and was published on Feburary 28th 2018.
We’ve just released Spring Boot 2.7 which means that, so far, we’ve been maintaining the 2.x line for just over 4 years.
In total we’ve published 95 distinct releases over that timeframe!



The entire Spring team, and many in our community of contributors, are now preparing for the next generation of Spring.
We are planning to release Spring Boot 3.0 in November 2022.
This next major revision will be based on Spring Framework 6.0 and will require Java 17 or above.
It will also be the first version of Spring Boot that makes use of Jakarta EE 9 APIs (jakarta.*)  instead of EE 8 (javax.*).



The next six months offer an ideal opportunity to prepare your own projects for this major relea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Spring Apps Enterprise is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/azure-spring-apps-enterprise-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/azure-spring-apps-enterprise-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! This is a guest post by Julia Liuson, President, Developer Division, Microsoft 
Azure Spring Cloud is now Azure Spring Apps

We launched Azure Spring Cloud with VMware in 2019 to solve common challenges developers, IT operators, and DevOps teams face when running Spring Boot applications at scale. Since then we’ve helped many customers adopt the service including Bosch, Digital Realty, FedEx, Kroger, Liantis, Morgan Stanley, National Life, Raley’s, and Swiss Re. They value the fully managed infrastructure of Azure Spring Cloud that lets them focus on their apps, while the service manages dynamic scaling, security patching, out-of-the-box instrumentation for monitoring, and more. Through customer feedback. we have expanded the capabilities of the service, including the Ent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking at taxes]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42928</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/697472588/0/sethsblog~Looking-at-taxes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T08:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since there have been taxes, people have been against paying them. If we define a tax as a “non-productive burden on our activities,” then it makes sense. And a payment doesn’t have to be to the government to be a tax. Is paying your electric bill a tax? Most people don’t mind paying for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 24th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/this-week-in-spring-may-24th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/24/this-week-in-spring-may-24th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! I’m in Spain for business and not just a little pleasure. Yesterday, my partner, her mother, and I went to Formentera, Spain, a little island off of Ibiza, Spain. It was amazing. We’re now in Ibiza, Spain, which is a little island not far from Barcelona, Spain, on the mainland of Spain. It feels a bit like that Inception movie. We traveled by boat to Formentera for a little vacation inside of another little vacation (Ibiza) and inside of another little vacation (Barcelona). Tomorrow I’ll return to Barcelona for the Spring IO event. Yes, technically, this is work. But it’s an oh-so-much pleasure, too. I can’t wait! It’ll be the first time I’ve seen a ton of these people in years! I hope to see y’all there or los vemos!


  
Happily, Spring for GraphQL 1.0 has been release…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Sponsors launches in India]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-23-github-sponsors-launches-in-india/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-23-github-sponsors-launches-in-india/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T03:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Sponsors is now available to all developers in India – no more waitlist, you can sign up right away!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using ECK with helm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-eck-with-helm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-eck-with-helm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using ECK with helm-charts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fram Souza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing ECK with Terraform on GCP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/installing-eck-with-terraform-on-gcp</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/installing-eck-with-terraform-on-gcp"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how-to spin up ECK using terraform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fram Souza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 cybersecurity must-haves for innovative public sector leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/6-cybersecurity-must-haves-for-innovative-public-sector-leaders</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/6-cybersecurity-must-haves-for-innovative-public-sector-leaders"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As digital risks escalate, public sector leaders take the actions necessary to protect people, systems, and data. A new cybersecurity benchmark study reveals where these leaders should focus their time and attention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzzanna Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-4-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-4-released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.17.4 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.4 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
The 7.17.4 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security advisory for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
7.17.4 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution
-Fixes a trusted applications path bug that caused a timeout error when users defined matching Path value without wildcards (https://github.com/elastic/kibana/pull/131085)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norrie Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.2.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-2-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-2-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarek Ziadé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why it’s time to move critical databases to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/move-critical-databases-cloud-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/move-critical-databases-cloud-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five reasons why CIOs should stop putting off the inevitable — from stronger cybersecurity management in the cloud to greater opportunities for innovation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Burrows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using ECK with helm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-eck-with-helm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/using-eck-with-helm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
If you want a solution where you can run only 4 commands and have your Kubernetes observability (logs & metrics, dashboards …) automatically set up, this guide is for you. Here we will use helm to spin up Elastic Stack on ECK (Elastic on Kubernetes), with automatically Kubernetes observability. We are going to run only 4 commands and we will have Elasticsearch, Kibana, Fleet & Elastic Agents (with System & Metrics of Kubernetes enabled). Once you follow this guide, at the end, you can access Kibana and quickly check your Kubernetes healthy, as the image below:
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltb1a6d3e2b38b49cd/628c057db4fa6b61ed70c686/blog-elastic-elk.png,blog-elastic-elk.png,
This page will give a generic way on how to set up ECK resources via helm. Keep in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fram Souza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing ECK with Terraform on GCP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/installing-eck-with-terraform-on-gcp</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/installing-eck-with-terraform-on-gcp"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
On this page, you will find a how-to spin up ECK using Terraform. The main idea is to have a Kubernetes cluster and ECK installed by running only 3 commands.
Demo
To see the demo, please access https://github.com/framsouza/eck-terraform
Features
Every feature will be deployed via Terraform:

Install GKE (Google Kubernetes Engine) cluster
It will contain 1 node pool with 3 nodes (One in each zone) running on region europe-west1
It contains a helm provider that will be responsible to install the ECK operator
Elasticsearch cluster with 3 nodes
One Kibana instance

Requirements
Before starting you should have the following commands installed:

terraform
gcloud

Let's play
As you probably know, Terraform is an infrastructure as code tool, which means we can describe our infrastructure desire …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fram Souza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 cybersecurity must-haves for innovative public sector leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/6-cybersecurity-must-haves-for-innovative-public-sector-leaders</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/6-cybersecurity-must-haves-for-innovative-public-sector-leaders"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
ThoughtLab’s newly released cybersecurity benchmark study revealed that cybersecurity is at a critical inflection point across industries. Although 60% of public sector organizations studied scored at the mid-implementation level according to the NIST maturity framework, mutually reinforcing megatrends such as digital transformation, remote work, platform economy, IoT, multi-clouds, institutionalized cybercrime, cyber warfare, and new regulations make the cybersecurity landscape more complex than ever before. 

It’s no surprise, then, that 34% of these organizations do not consider themselves well prepared for the rapidly changing threat landscape. 

Where should public sector leaders make pivots to bolster their cybersecurity performance in an era of escalating digital risks? We break d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzzanna Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-4-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-4-released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norrie Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.2.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-2-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-2-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
​Version 8.2.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. 

This release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security announcement for more details

This release also contains fixes and small enhancements for the Stack:


APM – Fixes a bug that caused events within batches with metadata.labels set to contain labels from other events in the same batch 8081


For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
8.2.1 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch


Kibana


Beats


Logstash


Elastic Enterprise Search


Enterprise Search


Elastic Observability


APM


Elastic Security


Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarek Ziadé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why it’s time to move critical databases to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/move-critical-databases-cloud-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/move-critical-databases-cloud-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,


Despite the rise of the cloud in the past two decades, many companies have held off on migrating mission-critical databases — until now. 

Database migration is finally picking up speed, as the benefits of moving to the cloud outweigh the risks. According to a recent IDC study, 63% of companies are now migrating databases to the cloud, and 29% are actively considering doing so in the next three years.

“We’re seeing a very strong move to the cloud,” says Mark Linster, chief technology officer at EDB, a database product provider. “Roughly half of companies are opting for cloud-based databases, while the other half are using cloud infrastructure so they can continue running and maintaining the software themselves.”

Here are five reasons why CIOs should stop putting off the inevitable:

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Burrows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 C7g Instances, Powered by AWS Graviton3 Processors]]></title>
        <id>85274dcdcd66e71abf62466cd5e084f9aca8df04</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c7g-instances-powered-by-aws-graviton3-processors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T21:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am excited to announce that Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) C7g instances powered by the latest AWS Graviton3 processors that have been available in preview since re:Invent last year are now available for all. Let’s decompose the name C7g: the “C” instance family is designed for compute-intensive workloads. This is the 7th generation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – May 23, 2022]]></title>
        <id>75cfd7cc41f56e72a28e830102fd6d20f55dbfb1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-27-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T19:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! This is the right place to quickly learn about recent AWS news from last week, in just about five minutes or less. This week, I have collected a couple of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight years of the GitHub Security Bug Bounty program]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-23-eight-years-of-the-github-security-bug-bounty-program/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-23-eight-years-of-the-github-security-bug-bounty-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T17:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was another record year for our Security Bug Bounty program. We're excited to highlight some achievements we’ve made together with the bounty community from 2021!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the HCL Extension for Visual Studio Code 0.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcl-extension-for-visual-studio-code-0-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcl-extension-for-visual-studio-code-0-1"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp adopts the community-created HCL Extension for Visual Studio Code and adds HCL 2.0 support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uplevel your automation skills with Red Hat training for Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/uplevel-your-automation-skills-with-red-hat-training-for-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/uplevel-your-automation-skills-with-red-hat-training-for-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 includes major features that allow customers to onboard more easily with even more flexible automation architectures and use cases. Ansible Automation Platform enables IT professionals to automate at enterprise scale more easily and flexibly. This means that everything you know and love about writing Ansible Playbooks is largely unchanged, but what is evolving is the underlying implementation of how automation is developed, managed, and operated in large complex environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Bonneville</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheers to Our Newest Camunda Champions Cohort]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=54752</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/cheers-to-our-newest-camunda-champions-cohort/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please join us in welcoming our latest batch of Camunda Champions! Check out which community members will participate in our third cohort. 
The post Cheers to Our Newest Camunda Champions Cohort appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Buchholz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharp language]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42086</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/697369546/0/sethsblog~Sharp-language/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T08:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet has provided all of us with an advanced class on using innuendo, piercing invective and anger to make a point with our writing. Now, instead of simply seething or ranting, just about anyone can write an email or a social media post that absolutely destroys someone else. To what end? If the goal […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECK in production environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/eck-in-production-environment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/eck-in-production-environment"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running ECK with Kubernertes monitoring and logs integration, cert-manager, ingress controller, SAML and much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fram Souza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECK in production environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/eck-in-production-environment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/eck-in-production-environment"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
This article will guide you on how to spin up an ECK environment ready for production which contains,

dedicated stack monitoring,
fleet-server & elastic-agent (with kubernetes integration),
elasticsearch autoscaling,
nodeAffinity & nodeSelector,
SAML with auth0,
hot, warm, cold, frozen architecture,
heartbeat monitor SSL certificate expiration,
external-dns (with CloudFlare integration),
cert-manager (with let's encrypt integration),
ingress controller (using Cloudflare to register the endpoints),
Optional: esrally to validate autoscaling and run benchmark against es cluster

Remember you must have basic or enterprise license to run ECK.
Demo
To see the demo and files, please access https://github.com/framsouza/eck-ready-for-production
cert-manager
cert-manager adds certificates and cer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fram Souza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goofs]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2623/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2623/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/goofs.png" title="The film is set in 2018, but when Commander Bremberly chases the hologram through Times Square, there's a billboard for Avengers: Age of Ultron. Depending on the date, that billboard would have been advertising either Infinity War or this movie." alt="The film is set in 2018, but when Commander Bremberly chases the hologram through Times Square, there's a billboard for Avengers: Age of Ultron. Depending on the date, that billboard would have been advertising either Infinity War or this movie." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The smallest viable audience]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42985</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/697259232/0/sethsblog~The-smallest-viable-audience/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-22T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a stepping-stone, not a compromise. The media and our culture push us to build something for everyone, to sand off the edges and to invest in infrastructure toward scale. But it turns out that quality, magic and satisfaction can lie in the other direction. Not because we can’t get bigger, but because we’d rather […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Survey of Causal Inference Applications at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b62d25175e6f</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/a-survey-of-causal-inference-applications-at-netflix-b62d25175e6f?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T15:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Netflix, we want to entertain the world through creating engaging content and helping members discover the titles they will love. Key to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The department of bad behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=29537</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/697139758/0/sethsblog~The-department-of-bad-behavior/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T08:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if organizations had a division that simply did the bad stuff? The people who were responsible for creating system updates that slow down old computers, that cover up bad behavior by employees, the people who dump pollution into the river when no one is watching… If all the folks who invent dark patterns, lobby […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auth0, Fortinet, and Vercel Among New Verified Terraform Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/auth0-fortinet-and-vercel-among-new-verified-terraform-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/auth0-fortinet-and-vercel-among-new-verified-terraform-providers"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the addition of 18 new verified providers to the growing HashiCorp Terraform ecosystem we hit a milestone with 200 verified Terraform providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · April 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-20-release-radar-apr-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-20-release-radar-apr-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T16:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each month, we highlight open source projects that have shipped major updates. These include everything from world-changing technology to developer tooling, and weekend projects. Here are our top staff picks on projects that shipped major version releases in April. Flyte 1.0 I was lucky enough to discover Flyte during Hacktoberfest last year. Now, Flyte has [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Action needed by GitHub Connect customers using GHES 3.1 and older to adopt new authentication token format updates]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-20-action-needed-by-github-connect-customers-using-ghes-3-1-and-older-to-adopt-new-authentication-token-format-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-20-action-needed-by-github-connect-customers-using-ghes-3-1-and-older-to-adopt-new-authentication-token-format-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade to GHES 3.2 or newer by June 3rd to continue using GitHub Connect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Java Applications to Azure using Continuous Delivery]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64092</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploying-java-applications-to-azure-using-continuous-delivery/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T10:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 3 in our series DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions and continuous delivery!
April: [00:00:00] Tune in into this week’s episode of the DevOps lab,
The post Deploying Java Applications to Azure using Continuous Delivery appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switch before perfect]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42044</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696990664/0/sethsblog~Switch-before-perfect/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T08:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1993, when I was raising investment for one of the first internet companies, there weren’t any firms that specialized in this sort of thing. They were VCs from a different era, looking for the next Fedex or pharma company. I pitched dozens of them, and the answer was consistent, “get back to us when […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a Java Application to Azure using Continuous Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64087</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-a-java-application-to-azure-using-continuous-integration/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T07:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 2 in our series for DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions and continuous integration.
April: We’re back this week with the dev ops lab and we’re continuing our series DevOps for Java shops.
The post Deploy a Java Application to Azure using Continuous Integration appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy natural language processing (NLP): Getting started]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-natural-language-processing-nlp-getting-started</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-natural-language-processing-nlp-getting-started"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog describes the process for getting up and running with deep learning models for natural language processing (NLP) in Elasticsearch using HuggingFace and PyTorch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy natural language processing (NLP): Getting started]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-natural-language-processing-nlp-getting-started</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-natural-language-processing-nlp-getting-started"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The release of the Elastic Stack 8.0 introduced the ability to upload PyTorch machine learning models into Elasticsearch to provide modern natural language processing (NLP) in the Elastic Stack. NLP opens up opportunities to extract information, classify text, and provide better search relevance through dense vectors and approximate nearest neighbor search.
In this multi-part blog series, we will walk through end-to-end examples using a variety of PyTorch NLP models.
Part 1: How to deploy text embeddings and vector search
Part 2: Named entity recognition (NER)
Part 3: Sentiment analysis
In each example we will use a prebuilt NLP model from the Hugging Face model hub. Then we will follow the Elastic documented instructions for deploying an NLP model and adding NLP inference to an ingest pipeline.  Because it’s always a good idea to start with a defined use case and an understanding of the text data to process in the model, we’ll start by defining the objective for using NLP and a shared data set for anyone to try out.
To prepare for the NLP example, we will need an Elasticsearch cluster running at least version 8.0, an ML node with at least 2GB RAM, and for the named entity recognition (NER) example we’ll use the required mapper-annotated-text plugin. One of the easiest ways to get started is by following along with these NLP examples with your own free 14-day trial cluster on Elastic Cloud. Cloud trials are able to scale to a max of two 2GB ML nodes, which will allow you to deploy one or two of examples at any one time in this multi-part blog series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Diameter Turnaround]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2622/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2622/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/angular_diameter_turnaround.png" title="Thank you to Katie Mack for teaching me about this effect, and to Janelle Shane for describing redshifts as 'like galaxies sinking into a pool of dilute blood,' which is how I'll see them from now on." alt="Thank you to Katie Mack for teaching me about this effect, and to Janelle Shane for describing redshifts as 'like galaxies sinking into a pool of dilute blood,' which is how I'll see them from now on." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-M3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-3-0-0-m3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-3-0-0-m3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T20:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-M3 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 74 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Auto-configuration for Micrometer Observation, Tracing, and OtlpMeterRegistry

  
Reinstated Support for REST Assured and Pooled JMS


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power of Partners: How Camunda’s Partners are Making an Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=54712</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/the-power-of-partners-how-camundas-partners-are-making-an-impact/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard of our Camunda Connect program? Learn how it's enabling our partners to make process automation more accessible to our clients.
The post The Power of Partners: How Camunda’s Partners are Making an Impact appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation at the Edge - Summit 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-at-the-edge-summit-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-at-the-edge-summit-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As some of you may know, Red Hat Summit was back in person in Boston last week. For those who are not familiar, Red Hat Summit is the premier enterprise open source event for IT professionals to learn, collaborate, and innovate on technologies from the datacenter and public cloud to the edge and beyond. Red Hat made a lot of exciting announcements, with several that included Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. If you could not make the event or would like to revisit some of the content, you can access any session on demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Lathram)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Math support in Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-19-math-support-in-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-19-math-support-in-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T17:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mathematical expressions are key to information sharing amongst engineers, scientists, data scientists, and mathematicians. Today we are pleased to announce that math expressions can be rendered in Markdown on GitHub using $$ as a delimiter for code blocks with math content or the $ delimiter for inline math expressions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we’re continuing to enable all developers to build]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-19-how-were-continuing-to-enable-all-developers-to-build/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-19-how-were-continuing-to-enable-all-developers-to-build/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T16:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about what GitHub is doing to make their products more inclusive, and what’s next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Do Accessible Design and Engineering at HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-do-accessible-design-and-engineering-at-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-do-accessible-design-and-engineering-at-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two HashiCorp engineers discuss accessible design and engineering at HashiCorp, from overall principles to the tools we use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to Azure Pipelines Runtime Variables Settings [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63937</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/updates-to-azure-pipelines-runtime-variables-settings/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have gotten a lot of feedback on this change and after internal deliberation, we are now rolling back this change ASAP.
We have now fully rolled back the change that caused the issue.
The post Updates to Azure Pipelines Runtime Variables Settings [Updated] appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.8 Expands Health and Events Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-8-expands-health-and-events-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-8-expands-health-and-events-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.8 adds key observability features and improvements to identity-based secure remote access for dynamic infrastructure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-2-7-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-2-7-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T13:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the Spring Boot team and everyone that has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0 has been released and is available from Maven Central. 

This release adds a significant number of new features and improvements. For full upgrade instructions and new and noteworthy features please see the release notes.
What’s new in 2.7

The highlights of the 2.7 release include:


  
Auto-configuration and metrics for Spring for GraphQL; see related 1.0 release announcement

  
New @DataCouchbaseTest and @DataElasticsearchTest support

  
Podman can now be used when building images using Cloud Native Buildpacks

  
Support for Cache2k

  
Simplified registration of Jackson Mixins

  
Web server SSL configuration using PEM-encoded certs


Dependency upgrades

Spring Boot 2.7 moves to new versions of several Spring projects:


  
Spring Data 2021.2

  
Spring HATEOAS 1.5

  
Spring LDAP 2.4

  
Spring Security 5.7

  
Spring Session 2021.2


We’ve also upgraded to the latest stable releases of other third-party libraries wherever possible. Please see the release notes for details.
Other changes

There’s a whole host of other changes and improvements that are documented in the release notes. You can also find a list of deprecated classes and methods that we plan to remove in the next version.

Additionally, Spring Boot 2.5 has now reached the end of its OSS support period. More information on Spring Boot’s support dates can be found here.
Thank you

We want to take this opportunity to again thank all our users and contributors.

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask at stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Devoxx UK organizer and VoxxedDays cofounder Mark Hazell on running great conferences]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/a-bootiful-podcast-devoxx-uk-organizer-and-voxxeddays-cofounder-mark-hazell-on-running-great-conferences</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/a-bootiful-podcast-devoxx-uk-organizer-and-voxxeddays-cofounder-mark-hazell-on-running-great-conferences"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Devoxx UK organizer and Voxxed Days cofounder Mark Hazell (@mrhazell).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.8 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-2-6-8-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-2-6-8-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T11:19:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.8 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 35 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-for-graphql-1-0-release</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-for-graphql-1-0-release"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the Spring for GraphQL team and every contributor, it is my pleasure to announce the 1.0 GA release. It’s been 10 months since the project was announced and under 2 years since the first commit, unremarkably called “first commit”. The project began with the modest goal to replace the (now archived) minimal GraphQL Java Spring integration, but has since moved significantly beyond through community feedback and collaboration across Spring Boot, Spring Framework, Spring Data, and Spring Security. 

The following are highlights from the release:


  
Annotation-based programming model for data fetchers

  
Data binding from input arguments with validation

  
Field-level security through annotations on data @Controller methods

  
Server handlers and interception over HTTP, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[False metrics appearing real]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40091</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696816552/0/sethsblog~False-metrics-appearing-real/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T09:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just because they’re easy to measure doesn’t mean they matter. If they appear in round numbers and are easily compared to those from others, we’re tempted to compare. But something that looks like a useful metric might not be. If you’re working with people who say they care about measurement, it might not pay to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.14 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-2-5-14-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/19/spring-boot-2-5-14-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T09:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.14 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 29 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
End of OSS Support

2.5.x has now reached the end of its OSS support period and regular releases will no longer be made. If you are still on this version, please consider upgrading at your earliest convenience. If you cannot upgrade at this time, commercial support is available.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64084</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-a-java-application-to-azure-app-service-using-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T07:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 1 in our series for DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions. Brian also covers off feature flags!
April: Welcome to this week’s episode of the dev ops lab.
The post Deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Session 2021.2 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/18/spring-session-2021-2-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/18/spring-session-2021-2-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T01:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m please to announce the release of Spring Session 2021.2. This release upgrades to Spring Data 2021.2 and provides dependency upgrades, minor enhancements, bug fixes, and strategic changes to prepare Spring Session and it’s users for the next generation of Spring Session built on Spring Framework 6.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.2 Improves Exception Handling and Updates to the CLI-driven Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-2-improves-exception-handling-and-updates-to-the-cli-driven-workflow</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-2-improves-exception-handling-and-updates-to-the-cli-driven-workflow"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now generally available, HashiCorp Terraform 1.2 introduces exception handling with pre- and post-conditions, support for non-interactive Terraform Cloud operations in a CI/CD pipeline, and CLI support for Run Tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Artifacts introduces new Upstreaming capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64079</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-artifacts-introduces-new-upstreaming-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T22:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Artifacts is announcing the long-desired feature of supporting Upstreams for Universal Packages across different ADO organizations.
The post Azure Artifacts introduces new Upstreaming capabilities appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing and delivering high-quality code with innersource metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-18-securing-and-delivering-high-quality-code-with-innersource-metrics/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-18-securing-and-delivering-high-quality-code-with-innersource-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T21:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With innersource, it’s important to measure both the amount of innersource activity and the quality of the code being created. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Backup Now Supports Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP]]></title>
        <id>4a4714ab05fe013a182547e67a8696dc9531dab4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-backup-now-supports-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T20:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a long-time reader of this blog, you know that I categorize some posts as “chocolate and peanut butter” in homage to an ancient (1970 or so) series of TV commercials for Reese’s Peanut Butter Cups. Today, I am happy to bring you the latest such post, combining AWS Backup and Amazon FSx […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.0.0-M5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/18/spring-security-6-0-0-m5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/18/spring-security-6-0-0-m5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 6.0.0-M5 is available now.



This release includes dependency upgrades, bug fixes, and minor enhancements as well as a fix for a bug where the StrictHttpFirewall incorrectly rejects valid CJKV characters. The milestone contains a few noteworthy changes:





Authorization on Every Dispatch Type



Change the default of shouldFilterAllDispatchTypes to true



Default to SecurityContextHolderFilter instead of SecurityContextPersistenceFilter



Remove SAML Deprecations





See the release notes here and here for more details.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 4.3.6 and 5.0.0-M3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/18/spring-batch-4-3-6-and-5-0-0-m3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/18/spring-batch-4-3-6-and-5-0-0-m3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T18:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 4.3.6 has been released to Maven Central and that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M3 is now available from our milestone repository.

Spring Batch 4.3.6 is a patch release that comes with a number of bug fixes, enhancements, and dependency updates. For more details about the changes, see the change log.

This blog post is more about 5.0.0-M3, which comes with three major features:


  
Native support improvements

  
UTF-8 by default

  
New Maven Bill of Materials


Moreover, this milestone release comes with a number of enhancements, bug fixes, and dependency updates. See the change log for more details about the content of this milestone.
Native support improvements

Our effort towards providi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector-Quantized Image Modeling with Improved VQGAN]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/vector-quantized-image-modeling-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/vector-quantized-image-modeling-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jiahui Yu, Senior Research Scientist, and Jing Yu Koh, Research Software Engineer, Google Research 
In recent years, natural language processing models have dramatically improved their ability to learn general-purpose representations, which has resulted in significant performance gains for a wide range of natural language generation and natural language understanding tasks. In large part, this has been accomplished through pre-training language models on extensive unlabeled text corpora.  
This pre-training formulation does not make assumptions about input signal modality, which can be language, vision, or audio, among others. Several recent papers have exploited this formulation to dramatically improve image generation results through pre-quantizing images into discrete integer …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.1, 5.6.5, 5.5.8 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/18/spring-security-5-7-1-5-6-5-5-5-8-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/18/spring-security-5-7-1-5-6-5-5-5-8-released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new round of releases for Spring Security is available now. The new releases fix a bug where the StrictHttpFirewall incorrectly rejects valid CJKV characters.



Please take a look at the release notes for more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps for Java on Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64058</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-for-java-on-azure/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T08:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure loves Java, bring your favorite tools and frameworks to Azure!
The post DevOps for Java on Azure appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 17th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/17/this-week-in-spring-may-17th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/17/this-week-in-spring-may-17th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T23:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I am in beautiful Barcelona, Spain, this week, ahead of the upcoming Spring I/O show. I just spent a wonderful week in amazing England, meeting old friends, speaking at Devoxx UK, etc. 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: EasyMock contributor, Java Champion, and Java luminary Henri Tremblay

  
Also, while we’re on the topic of Spring Boot 2.7, remember that Spring for GraphQL is also 1.0 this week! I’m so excited :)

  
Example of Spring Cloud Function with AWS Lambda

  
I love this - the Activiti 7 developer’s guide - showcases some cool patterns and principles for building service-centric workflow solutions with Spring Boot and Activiti 

  
a handy tip from Maciej Walkowiak on Twitter that Spring Boot 2.7 (due - :checks notes: - this week!) adds native support for Jackson Mixins with @JsonMixin annotation

  
Speed time to developer productivity with v0.12 release of VMware Tanzu Community Edition

  
Spring Boot — Serverless AWS Lambda With API Gateway | by Apurv Sheth | May, 2022 | Medium

  
Spring Data 2021.2 and 2022.0 M4 released.

  
Spring Framework 5.3.20 and 5.2.22 available now

  
Spring Framework 6.0.0-M4 available now

  
Spring Transaction Debugging in Production with Lightrun

  
this article by our own dr. Mark Pollack was written in 1999 and laid the groundwork for what would become EJBDoclet and XDoclet

  
🚀 New in Spring Framework 6: HTTP Interfaces

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.24: Volume Populators Graduate to Beta

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.24: gRPC container probes in beta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64002</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/may-patches-for-azure-devops-server-and-team-foundation-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T22:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact Azure DevOps Server 2019.0.1, as well as the following older Team Foundation Server (TFS) releases: TFS 2015.4.2, TFS 2017.3.1 and TFS 2018.3.2.
Revoke all personal access tokens after a user’s Active Directory account is disabled.
The post May patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contextual Rephrasing in Google Assistant]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/contextual-rephrasing-in-google.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/contextual-rephrasing-in-google.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T19:38:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Aurelien Boffy, Senior Staff Software Engineer, and Roberto Pieraccini, Engineering Director, Google Assistant 
When people converse with one another, context and references play a critical role in driving their conversation more efficiently. For instance, if one asks the question “Who wrote Romeo and Juliet?” and, after receiving an answer, asks “Where was he born?”, it is clear that ‘he’ is referring to William Shakespeare without the need to explicitly mention him. Or if someone mentions “python” in a sentence, one can use the context from the conversation to determine whether they are referring to a type of snake or a computer language. If a virtual assistant cannot robustly handle context and references, users would be required to adapt to the limitation of the technology by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2, 2020.0.2 and 2019.1.2 releases]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64015</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2020-1-2-2020-0-2-and-2019-1-2-releases/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T18:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are releasing multiple versions of our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server. You can find the details of the fixes in the release notes for each version.
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2 ISO
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2 Web Install
Release Notes
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2 ISO
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2 Web Install
Release Notes
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2 ISO
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2 Web Install
Release Notes
The post Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2, 2020.0.2 and 2019.1.2 releases appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Helm and Kubernetes to deploy Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=53853</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/using-helm-and-kubernetes-to-deploy-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know to install, configure, and run Camunda Platform 8 Helm charts. 
The post Using Helm and Kubernetes to deploy Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – May 16, 2022]]></title>
        <id>188f6fbb789cd4b216b2e97a6340bddf3499db79</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-16-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T19:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I had been on the road for the last five weeks and attended many of the AWS Summits in Europe. It was great to talk to so many of you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: The One Where a JSON Request is Sent While Calling an External REST]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=53737</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/qa-the-one-where-a-json-request-is-sent-while-calling-an-external-rest/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Find out which way to post JSON data to an external service is best. From within the BPMN or by an external task implementation?
The post Q&A: The One Where a JSON Request is Sent While Calling an External REST appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask me Anything Recap - April]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ask-me-anything-recap-april</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ask-me-anything-recap-april"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For this webinar, we had an awesome group of individuals with a diverse talent range across multiple skill sets from Product Management, Technical Marketing and Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-22976: BCrypt skips salt rounds for work factor of 31]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/15/cve-2022-22976-bcrypt-skips-salt-rounds-for-work-factor-of-31</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/15/cve-2022-22976-bcrypt-skips-salt-rounds-for-work-factor-of-31"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T05:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.0, 5.6.4, 5.5.7 were released to fix CVE-2022-22976: BCrypt skips salt rounds for work factor of 31. Please update as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-22978: Authorization Bypass in RegexRequestMatcher]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/15/cve-2022-22978-authorization-bypass-in-regexrequestmatcher</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/15/cve-2022-22978-authorization-bypass-in-regexrequestmatcher"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T05:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATES





[05-17] Due to a mixup CVE-2022-22975 should have been CVE-2022-22978. The blog has been updated to reflect this correction.




CVE-2022-22978 : Authorization Bypass in RegexRequestMatcher


Spring Security 5.7.0, 5.6.4, 5.5.7 were released to fix CVE-2022-22978 : Authorization Bypass in RegexRequestMatcher. Please update as soon as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 13.05.2022]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64029</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-06-13-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T12:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back this week for another top stories from the #AzureDevOps #Community!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 13.05.2022 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenges in Multi-objective Optimization for Automatic Wireless Network Planning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/challenges-in-multi-objective.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/challenges-in-multi-objective.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Ahmadian and Matthew Fahrbach, Research Scientists, Google Research, Large-Scale Optimization Team 
Economics, combinatorics, physics, and signal processing conspire to make it difficult to design, build, and operate high-quality, cost-effective wireless networks. The radio transceivers that communicate with our mobile phones, the equipment that supports them (such as power and wired networking), and the physical space they occupy are all expensive, so it’s important to be judicious in choosing sites for new transceivers. Even when the set of available sites is limited, there are exponentially many possible networks that can be built. For example, given only 50 sites, there are 250 (over a million billion) possibilities!  
Further complicating things, for every location wher…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 Adds Native Service Discovery and Edge Workload Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 includes built-in service discovery, improved edge compute support, Container Storage Interface (CSI) general availability, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Language Models Perform Reasoning via Chain of Thought]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/language-models-perform-reasoning-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/language-models-perform-reasoning-via.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jason Wei and Denny Zhou, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain team 
In recent years, scaling up the size of language models has been shown to be a reliable way to improve performance on a range of natural language processing (NLP) tasks. Today’s language models at the scale of 100B or more parameters achieve strong performance on tasks like sentiment analysis and machine translation, even with little or no training examples. Even the largest language models, however, can still struggle with certain multi-step reasoning tasks, such as math word problems and commonsense reasoning. How might we enable language models to perform such reasoning tasks? 
In “Chain of Thought Prompting Elicits Reasoning in Large Language Models,” we explore a prompting method for improving the re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Zero-Resource Machine Translation to Support New Languages in Google Translate]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/24-new-languages-google-translate.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/24-new-languages-google-translate.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:07:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Isaac Caswell and Ankur Bapna, Research Scientists, Google Translate  
Machine translation (MT) technology has made significant advances in recent years, as deep learning has been integrated with natural language processing (NLP). Performance on research benchmarks like WMT have soared, and translation services have improved in quality and expanded to include new languages. Nevertheless, while existing translation services cover languages spoken by the majority of people world wide, they only include around 100 languages in total, just over 1% of those actively spoken globally. Moreover, the languages that are currently represented are overwhelmingly European, largely overlooking regions of high linguistic diversity, like Africa and the Americas. 
 There are two key bottlenecks t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 Now Supports NitroTPM and UEFI Secure Boot]]></title>
        <id>43dd6308bbff890b8b4acc020ae36428fe8fba36</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-now-supports-nitrotpm-and-uefi-secure-boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In computing, Trusted Platform Module (TPM) technology is designed to provide hardware-based, security-related functions. A TPM chip is a secure crypto-processor that is designed to carry out cryptographic operations. There are three key advantages of using TPM technology. First, you can generate, store, and control access to encryption keys outside of the operating system. Second, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第209話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270296674344129439</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270296674344129439"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Cool Features of Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=53306</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/10-cool-features-of-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T12:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how these features support better IT and business collaboration, more efficient process execution, and instant troubleshooting. 
The post 10 Cool Features of Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe Is Back: Join Us in Amsterdam or Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years as a fully digital event, HashiConf Europe will once again return to Amsterdam on 20-22 June 2022. Here’s what you can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a brand new way to automate your Azure cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-a-brand-new-way-to-automate-your-azure-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-a-brand-new-way-to-automate-your-azure-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T13:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December of 2021, Red Hat and Microsoft announced Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hicham Mourad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=53158</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1. Check out the latest improvements and bug fixes with this release.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52734</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-automation-platform-7-18-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're pleased to announce the first alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0. Learn about the improvements made in this release. 
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the HashiCorp Releases API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hashicorp-releases-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hashicorp-releases-api"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Releases API is now available. This API is your one-stop shop for finding and viewing extended metadata about HashiCorp product releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – May 9, 2022]]></title>
        <id>8339454c5a5172e1abc7a324ae07df48c5db2a14</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-9-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Another week starts, and here’s a collection of the most significant AWS news from the previous seven days. This week is also the one-year anniversary of CloudFront Functions. It’s exciting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Applications at the Edge with HashiCorp Nomad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-applications-at-the-edge-with-hashicorp-nomad</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-applications-at-the-edge-with-hashicorp-nomad"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Nomad users in the gaming, farming, and biotech industries are orchestrating applications and devices at the edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous Detection and Mitigation (CDM)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/continuous-detection-and-mitigation-cdm</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/continuous-detection-and-mitigation-cdm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>achenamp@redhat.com (Ajay Chenampara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Observability with OpenTelemetry and Consul Service Mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/improve-observability-with-opentelemetry-and-consul-service-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/improve-observability-with-opentelemetry-and-consul-service-mesh"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Add OpenTelemetry to your Java or .NET applications on Kubernetes and combine them with Consul service mesh metrics and traces for use with Prometheus and Jaeger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.06.05]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63983</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-06-05/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.06.05 are here!
I am April Edwards and every week I try to bring you the latest updates from around the DevOps on Azure community.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.06.05 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Locomotion Skills Safely in the Real World]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/learning-locomotion-skills-safely-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/learning-locomotion-skills-safely-in.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:05:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jimmy (Tsung-Yen) Yang, Student Researcher, Robotics at Google 
The promise of deep reinforcement learning (RL) in solving complex, high-dimensional problems autonomously has attracted much interest in areas such as robotics, game playing, and self-driving cars. However, effectively training an RL policy requires exploring a large set of robot states and actions, including many that are not safe for the robot. This is a considerable risk, for example, when training a legged robot. Because such robots are inherently unstable, there is a high likelihood of the robot falling during learning, which could cause damage. 
The risk of damage can be mitigated to some extent by learning the control policy in computer simulation and then deploying it in the real world. However, this approac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable Self-Service Amazon EKS Deploys with CDK for Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/enable-self-service-aws-eks-deployments-with-cdk-for-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/enable-self-service-aws-eks-deployments-with-cdk-for-terraform"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how platform and developer teams can collaborate effectively using CDK for Terraform, Terraform Cloud, and Sentinel to safely deploy EKS workloads to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphWorld: Advances in Graph Benchmarking]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/graphworld-advances-in-graph.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/graphworld-advances-in-graph.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T21:24:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Palowitch and Anton Tsitsulin, Research Scientists, Google Research, Graph Mining team 
Graphs are very common representations of natural systems that have connected relational components, such as social networks, traffic infrastructure, molecules, and the internet. Graph neural networks (GNNs) are powerful machine learning (ML) models for graphs that leverage their inherent connections to incorporate context into predictions about items within the graph or the graph as a whole. GNNs have been effectively used to discover new drugs, help mathematicians prove theorems, detect misinformation, and improve the accuracy of arrival time predictions in Google Maps. 
A surge of interest in GNNs during the last decade has produced thousands of GNN variants, with hundreds introduced each year. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Run Tasks are Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-are-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-are-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate security, compliance, and cost management into the Terraform Cloud workflow using Run Tasks. Now generally available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpa: Automated Model-Parallel Deep Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/alpa-automated-model-parallel-deep.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/alpa-automated-model-parallel-deep.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T21:30:00.058Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zhuohan Li, Student Researcher, Google Research, and Yu Emma Wang, Senior Software Engineer, Google Core  
  Update — 2022/05/06: This post has been updated to provide additional details about the collaboration with external research partners in the development of Alpa.     
  
Over the last several years, the rapidly growing size of deep learning models has quickly exceeded the memory capacity of single accelerators. Earlier models like BERT (with a parameter size of < 1GB) can efficiently scale across accelerators by leveraging data parallelism in which model weights are duplicated across accelerators while only partitioning and distributing the training data. However, recent large models like GPT-3 (with a parameter size of 175GB) can only scale using model parallel training, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Applications and Servers at the Edge with Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-applications-and-servers-at-the-edge-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-applications-and-servers-at-the-edge-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous blog, Why 2022 will be the year for edge automation, we discussed the objective of edge solutions to bring resources closer to the end user or data source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – May 2, 2022]]></title>
        <id>650b6b46711677bb46ba175a4d35a12387ae3f6a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-2-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Wow, May already! Here in the Pacific Northwest, spring is in full bloom and nature has emerged completely from her winter slumbers. It feels that way here at AWS, too, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extracting Skill-Centric State Abstractions from Value Functions]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/extracting-skill-centric-state.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/extracting-skill-centric-state.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T17:02:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dhruv Shah, Intern, and Brian Ichter, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google 
Advances in reinforcement learning (RL) for robotics have enabled robotic agents to perform increasingly complex tasks in challenging environments. Recent results show that robots can learn to fold clothes, dexterously manipulate a rubik’s cube, sort objects by color, navigate complex environments and walk on difficult, uneven terrain. But "short-horizon" tasks such as these, which require very little long-term planning and provide immediate failure feedback, are relatively easy to train compared to many tasks that may confront a robot in a real-world setting. Unfortunately, scaling such short-horizon skills to the abstract, long horizons of real-world tasks is difficult. For example, how would one trai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>