<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-04T01:08:03.625Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-04T01:08:03.625Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Informed consent (rarely is)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45008</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/792014279/0/sethsblog~Informed-consent-rarely-is/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adults make choices and live with the consequences. No one else should tell us what flavor of ice cream we prefer, or what career to choose. We’re good at knowing what we want. In practice, this works really well for certain kinds of decisions. But when we add the network effect, profit-seeking industrial entities, statistics, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The empathy of useful feedback]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45149</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/791824298/0/sethsblog~The-empathy-of-useful-feedback/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When a friend shows you work in progress, your best contribution is to imagine the point of view and preferences of the person it is being created for. “I don’t like it,” isn’t useful, because it’s not for you. “I could imagine that someone who wants x, y or z would be looking for…” is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join us at CamundaCon 2023 for Everything Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89745</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/join-us-camundacon-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2023 is right around the corner. Check out everything there is to see and learn at the leading process orchestration conference.
The post Join us at CamundaCon 2023 for Everything Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with edge computing]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-01-getting-started-with-edge-computing/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-01-getting-started-with-edge-computing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Edge computing practitioners answer your questions about when and why to build applications at the edge.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-01-getting-started-with-edge-computing/">Getting started with edge computing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-Driven Ansible - ChatOps - From Chat to Action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-chatops-from-chat-to-action</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-chatops-from-chat-to-action"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implement Automated ChatOps: Learn how to use event-driven automation to take action from chat information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Rider Welcomes Visual Studio for Mac Users With a 65% Discount on New Personal Subscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=384445</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/09/01/65-off-rider/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T10:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has just announced their plans to retire Visual Studio for Mac.  We realize this news comes as a shock to some of you. You’re losing the tool you came to rely on. But if you’re reading this post, it’s probably because your fellow .NET developers steered you in the direction of a good alternative.   […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you doing what you said you wanted to do?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45160</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/791609810/0/sethsblog~Are-you-doing-what-you-said-you-wanted-to-do/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T08:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to be a poet, write poetry. Every day. Show us your work. If you want to do improv, start a troupe. Don’t wait to get picked. If you want to help animals, don’t wait for vet school. Volunteer at an animal shelter right now. If you want to write a screenplay, write […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionising Australian government services with generative AI: A new era of engagement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/australian-government-services-generative-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/australian-government-services-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new era of generative AI, Australian government agencies are changing. Apps like ChatGPT and Elasticsearch promise to reshape public services and citizen experiences. But governments must tread carefully, ensuring data privacy isn’t compromised.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionising Australian government services with generative AI: A new era of engagement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/australian-government-services-generative-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/australian-government-services-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In an age where digital connectivity is critical, Australian government bodies are grappling with a growing challenge: providing improved citizen experiences. The pandemic sparked a digital surge, with health.gov.au clocking 6 million daily visits, and servicesaustralia.gov.au witnessing a 650% boost in activity. This points to the urgent need for efficient, seamless service delivery. Embracing transformative tools like OpenAI's GPT-4, Bard, and Elasticsearch® can spark a revolution in service delivery, potentially enhancing citizen satisfaction and inclusivity.

In the context of a “digital first” approach and a swell in online traffic, monitoring public sector IT environments has become crucial. A primary driver of our “digital first” approach is to help direct citizens to find answers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fossil]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2823/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2823/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/fossil.png" title="The two best reasons to get into fossils are booping trilobites and getting to say the word &quot;fossiliferous&quot; a lot." alt="The two best reasons to get into fossils are booping trilobites and getting to say the word &quot;fossiliferous&quot; a lot." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Legacy Package Repositories Will Be Frozen On September 13, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/31/legacy-package-repository-deprecation/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/31/legacy-package-repository-deprecation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Bob Killen (Google), Chris Short (AWS), Jeremy Rickard (Microsoft), Marko Mudrinić (Kubermatic), Tim Bannister (The Scale Factory)
On August 15, 2023, the Kubernetes project announced the general availability of
the community-owned package repositories for Debian and RPM packages available
at pkgs.k8s.io. The new package repositories are replacement for the legacy
Google-hosted package repositories: apt.kubernetes.io and yum.kubernetes.io.
The
announcement blog post for pkgs.k8s.io
highlighted that we will stop publishing packages to the legacy repositories in
the future.
Today, we're formally deprecating the legacy package repositories (apt.kubernetes.io
and yum.kubernetes.io), and we're announcing our plans to freeze the contents of
the repositories as of September 13, 2023.
Ple…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WeatherBench 2: A benchmark for the next generation of data-driven weather models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/weatherbench-2-benchmark-for-next.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/weatherbench-2-benchmark-for-next.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T17:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Stephan Rasp, Research Scientist, and Carla Bromberg, Program Lead, Google Research





In 1950, weather forecasting started its digital revolution when researchers used the first programmable, general-purpose computer ENIAC to solve mathematical equations describing how weather evolves. In the more than 70 years since, continuous advancements in computing power and improvements to the model formulations have led to steady gains in weather forecast skill: a 7-day forecast today is about as accurate as a 5-day forecast in 2000 and a 3-day forecast in 1980. While improving forecast accuracy at the pace of approximately one day per decade may not seem like a big deal, every day improved is important in far reaching use cases, such as for logistics planning, disaster management, agr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub reduces costs with upgraded Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-31-how-github-reduces-costs-with-upgraded-codespaces/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-31-how-github-reduces-costs-with-upgraded-codespaces/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T15:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>See how much more you can get out of GitHub Codespaces by taking advantage of the improved processing power and increased headroom the RAM provides.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-31-how-github-reduces-costs-with-upgraded-codespaces/">How GitHub reduces costs with upgraded Codespaces</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summarize this…]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47073</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/791310296/0/sethsblog~Summarize-this/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T08:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great use of ChatGPT and other AI is to paste relevant text into the chat box and ask for a summary. I did this with 300 suggestions that came via a Google form and it did the work better, faster and with more clarity (and less bias) than a person would. Often, we’re clouded […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Security and Kubernetes legend Daniel Garnier-Moiroux]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/31/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-and-kubernetes-legend-daniel-garnier</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/31/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-and-kubernetes-legend-daniel-garnier"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is the Beginning of the End of the N+1 Problem: Introducing Single Query Loading.]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/31/this-is-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-n-1-problem-introducing-single-query</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/31/this-is-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-n-1-problem-introducing-single-query"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Schauder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modeling and improving text stability in live captions]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/modeling-and-improving-text-stability.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/modeling-and-improving-text-stability.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T19:34:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Vikas Bahirwani, Research Scientist, and Susan Xu, Software Engineer, Google Augmented Reality





Automatic speech recognition (ASR) technology has made conversations more accessible with live captions in remote conferencing software, mobile applications, and head-worn displays. However, to maintain real-time responsiveness, live caption systems often display interim predictions that are updated as new utterances are received. This can cause text instability (a “flicker” where previously displayed text is updated, shown in the captions on the left in the video below), which can impair users' reading experience due to distraction, fatigue, and difficulty following the conversation.






In “Modeling and Improving Text Stability in Live Captions”, presented at ACM CHI 2023, we f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon Managed Service for Apache Flink Renamed from Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics]]></title>
        <id>e40c4472300bd8097a0fe160c607a0e9eeb6e5d5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-managed-service-for-apache-flink-renamed-from-amazon-kinesis-data-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T17:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the rename of Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics to Amazon Managed Service for Apache Flink, a fully managed and serverless service for you to build and run real-time streaming applications using Apache Flink. We continue to deliver the same experience in your Flink applications without any impact on ongoing operations, developments, or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Rust is the most admired language among developers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-30-why-rust-is-the-most-admired-language-among-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-30-why-rust-is-the-most-admired-language-among-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T14:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Rust continues to top the charts as the most admired and desired language by developers, and in this post, we dive a little deeper into how (and why) Rust is stealing the hearts of developers around the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-30-why-rust-is-the-most-admired-language-among-developers/">Why Rust is the most admired language among developers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Azure Infrastructure for High Availability Web Hosting with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-azure-infrastructure-for-high-availability-web-hosting-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-azure-infrastructure-for-high-availability-web-hosting-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it a hassle to set up the infrastructure for a new website every time you need to run a short-term project, such as a marketing campaign or just for testing? Do you spend too much on resources that are only used for a short period? Look no further, because automation is here to save the day!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Leiva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin News: KotlinConf 2024 Tickets, Compose Multiplatform 1.5.0, Grants Program Winners, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=384146</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/08/kotlin-news-jul-aug-23/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T12:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new edition of the Kotlin digest, we’re bringing you the most exciting news and updates from July and August. KotlinConf 2024 tickets are now available! KotlinConf is bringing the Kotlin community together for the fifth time on May 22–24, 2024, at the Bella Center in Copenhagen, Denmark! There will be workshops, talks, networking […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daria Voronina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for JetBrains .NET Day Online ’23]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=383343</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/08/30/dotnet-day-online-23/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T11:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 26, we are holding JetBrains .NET Day Online ’23, a free annual event. We’ve invited 10 amazing community speakers who will cover topics they’re passionate about. Join us for 11 hours of insights into .NET development, lots of demo-rich sessions, and useful tips for all skill levels. Agenda You can choose whether to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Kolesova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The nuanced challenge of “The Regular Kind”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47061</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/790998209/0/sethsblog~The-nuanced-challenge-of-%e2%80%9cThe-Regular-Kind%e2%80%9d/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T10:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a breakthrough study by Alex Berke at MIT, she and her team showed that labeling a menu item as vegan significantly decreased how many people would order it. In similar conditions, it turns out that more people choose exactly the same item if it doesn’t carry that label. One conclusion people might take away […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polars vs. pandas: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=375451</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2023/08/polars-vs-pandas-what-s-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T10:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been keeping up with the advances in Python dataframes in the past year, you couldn’t help hearing about Polars, the powerful dataframe library designed for working with large datasets. Unlike other libraries for working with large datasets, such as Spark, Dask, and Ray, Polars is designed to be used on a single machine, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jodie Burchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wayland Support for IntelliJ-based IDEs]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=384097</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2023/08/wayland-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T08:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Linux users of IntelliJ-based IDEs, an exciting advancement is on the horizon – the upcoming support of the Wayland display server protocol. This update is set to bring a host of benefits, including solving the age-old fractional scaling problem and elevating desktop integration when working with Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSLg), which runs a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Chrzanowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 rules for security leadership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ten-rules-security-leadership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ten-rules-security-leadership"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By understanding their organization's DNA and cultivating a collaborative security culture, CISOs can make an indelible impact on their organization's cybersecurity resilience while maximizing their personal performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mandy Andress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The role of generative AI in higher ed IT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-role-of-generative-ai-in-higher-ed-it</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-role-of-generative-ai-in-higher-ed-it"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI has the potential to transform the IT landscape at universities, increasing productivity and job satisfaction and leading to better student outcomes. Learn how Elasticsearch can serve as the bridge between private data and LLMs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Pane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 rules for security leadership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ten-rules-security-leadership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ten-rules-security-leadership"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
I have worked as a security leader since the early commercial days of the internet, where the CISO role only existed in some areas of financial services. Participating in the growth and maturity of security as a business function has been an amazing journey. I have learned a lot of lessons on my own, through my personal experiences, or via my peers.

One thing I was not able to do was learn from experienced CISOs that have time and distance to reflect on how to best be successful as a CISO. I would have saved myself some painful lessons if I knew these foundational rules in the past. 

The role of chief information security officer (CISO) — and equivalent roles — is a high-stakes position. To thrive, CISOs must master a unique blend of technical expertise, business acumen, and people skills. 

In addition to the “head’s down” day-to-day functions — strategy, risk management, vendor/partner management, security assurance, governance, etc. — there’s a more important side of the job. Internal collaboration and communication with other executives, department heads, and stakeholders helps CISOs align security initiatives with business objectives. This includes participating in board meetings, aligning with business strategy, providing security updates, and collaborating with cross-functional teams.

By understanding their organization's DNA and cultivating a collaborative security culture, CISOs can make an indelible impact on their organization's cybersecurity resilience while maximizing their personal performance.

Drawing from the collective wisdom of industry experts, experienced cybersecurity professionals, and, of course, fellow CISOs, we explore the core principles that separate exceptional CISOs from the rest. From this discussion, we present 10 rules for security leadership:
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt4a4d037f724966c1/64efc0f18b0a2683e12688b1/10_rules_CISO_listicles.png,10_rules_CISO_listicles.png]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mandy Andress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The role of generative AI in higher ed IT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-role-of-generative-ai-in-higher-ed-it</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-role-of-generative-ai-in-higher-ed-it"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
According to an EDUCAUSE survey from April 2023, 83% of respondents say that generative AI will profoundly change higher education in the next three to five years. 

The academic community has been quick to question and imagine the impacts of generative AI on teaching and learning. Scholars and decision makers are exploring what generative AI means for personalized learning, integrity and ethics, and academic research, as well as preparing students for an AI-powered workplace.

In addition to pedagogical impacts, generative AI also has the potential to transform the IT landscape at universities. Specifically, when generative AI applications are used with a university’s internal data, they can produce hyper-relevant, context rich outputs that can increase productivity and job satisfaction…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Pane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[*@gmail.com]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2822/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2822/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/gmail_com.png" title="Hi all, just replying to loop in *@outlook.com and *@yahoo.com." alt="Hi all, just replying to loop in *@outlook.com and *@yahoo.com." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Configuration Service Mesh with On-Demand Cluster Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ac6483b52a51</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/zero-configuration-service-mesh-with-on-demand-cluster-discovery-ac6483b52a51?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T23:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix’s service mesh adoption: history, motivations, and how we worked with the Envoy community on a feature to streamline mesh adoption]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SayTap: Language to quadrupedal locomotion]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/saytap-language-to-quadrupedal.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/saytap-language-to-quadrupedal.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T19:57:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yujin Tang and Wenhao Yu, Research Scientists, Google




Simple and effective interaction between human and quadrupedal robots paves the way towards creating intelligent and capable helper robots, forging a future where technology enhances our lives in ways beyond our imagination. Key to such human-robot interaction systems is enabling quadrupedal robots to respond to natural language instructions. Recent developments in large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated the potential to perform high-level planning. Yet, it remains a challenge for LLMs to comprehend low-level commands, such as joint angle targets or motor torques, especially for inherently unstable legged robots, necessitating high-frequency control signals. Consequently, most existing work presumes the provision of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.10 is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-29-github-enterprise-server-3-10-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-29-github-enterprise-server-3-10-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T18:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Customers using GHES can now ensure secure development is a top priority with enhanced security and compliance controls for their repositories.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-29-github-enterprise-server-3-10-is-now-generally-available/">GitHub Enterprise Server 3.10 is now generally available</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Gateway API v0.8.0: Introducing Service Mesh Support]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/29/gateway-api-v0-8/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/29/gateway-api-v0-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Flynn (Buoyant), John Howard (Google), Keith Mattix (Microsoft), Michael Beaumont (Kong), Mike Morris (independent), Rob Scott (Google)
We are thrilled to announce the v0.8.0 release of Gateway API! With this
release, Gateway API support for service mesh has reached Experimental
status. We look forward to your feedback!
We're especially delighted to announce that Kuma 2.3+, Linkerd 2.14+, and Istio
1.16+ are all fully-conformant implementations of Gateway API service mesh
support.
Service mesh support in Gateway API
While the initial focus of Gateway API was always ingress (north-south)
traffic, it was clear almost from the beginning that the same basic routing
concepts should also be applicable to service mesh (east-west) traffic. In
2022, the Gateway API subproject started the G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The absence of proof]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47056</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/790547294/0/sethsblog~The-absence-of-proof/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Belief makes us human. Belief is our tool to dance with a possible future, confront our fears, and build community. Our personal taste and our preferences belong to us as well, helping us believe in ourselves. For millennia, belief thrived in most parts of our lives. We didn’t need belief to know that fire was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My SpringOne 2023 Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/my-springone-2023-recap</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/my-springone-2023-recap"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 29th, 2023 - the post SpringOne recovery blog]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/this-week-in-spring-august-29th-2023-the-post-springone-recovery-blog</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/this-week-in-spring-august-29th-2023-the-post-springone-recovery-blog"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data JDBC - How To Maintain Your Database Schema]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/spring-data-jdbc-how-to-maintain-your-database-schema</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/29/spring-data-jdbc-how-to-maintain-your-database-schema"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Schauder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic wins Google Cloud's Global Technology Partner of the Year Award]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-wins-google-cloud-global-technology-partner-of-the-year-award</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-wins-google-cloud-global-technology-partner-of-the-year-award"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic has won the 2023 Google Cloud Global Technology Partner of the Year Award. This prestigious award is given to one Google Cloud partner at the forefront of digital innovation working with Google Cloud to solve today's biggest challenges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleta Hubbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic wins Google Cloud's Global Technology Partner of the Year Award]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-wins-google-cloud-global-technology-partner-of-the-year-award</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-wins-google-cloud-global-technology-partner-of-the-year-award"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are happy to announce that Elastic® has won the 2023 Google Cloud Global Technology Partner of the Year Award. This prestigious award is given to one Google Cloud partner at the forefront of digital innovation working with Google Cloud to solve today's biggest global challenges.
A partnership built on growth and innovation,
Elastic and Google Cloud remain at the forefront of innovation. We are steadfast in our commitment to expanding and improving technology, including AI, Elasticsearch Relevance EngineTM (ESRETM), and support for Vertex AI large language models (LLMs). Recent enhancements include support for Google's Cloud Security Command Center, which integrates Google alerts and security events into Elastic Security for SIEM. In addition, Elastic's support for Google's managed Kub…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleta Hubbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – AWS Dedicated Local Zones, Events and More – August 28, 2023]]></title>
        <id>b149aa31ec92d6b50f0246dd76f4b269e108440e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-dedicated-zones-events-and-more-august-28-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T21:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I will meet our customers and partners at the AWS Summit Mexico. If you are around, please come say hi at the community lounge and at the F1 Game Day where I will spend most of my time. I would love to discuss your developer experience on AWS and listen to your stories […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RO-ViT: Region-aware pre-training for open-vocabulary object detection with vision transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/ro-vit-region-aware-pre-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/ro-vit-region-aware-pre-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:59:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dahun Kim and Weicheng Kuo, Research Scientists, Google



The ability to detect objects in the visual world is crucial for computer vision and machine intelligence, enabling applications like adaptive autonomous agents and versatile shopping systems. However, modern object detectors are limited by the manual annotations of their training data, resulting in a vocabulary size significantly smaller than the vast array of objects encountered in reality. To overcome this, the open-vocabulary detection task (OVD) has emerged, utilizing image-text pairs for training and incorporating new category names at test time by associating them with the image content. By treating categories as text embeddings, open-vocabulary detectors can predict a wide range of unseen objects. Various techniqu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 things you didn’t know you could do with GitHub Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-28-10-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-github-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-28-10-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-github-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to optimize your usage of GitHub Projects to plan and track your work from idea to production.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-28-10-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-github-projects/">10 things you didn’t know you could do with GitHub Projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compose Multiplatform 1.5.0 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=382207</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/08/compose-multiplatform-1-5-0-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T14:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of today, Compose Multiplatform 1.5.0 is available for you to use. It takes the Jetpack Compose declarative UI framework for Kotlin and extends it beyond Android to desktop, iOS, and web. The desktop version is stable, iOS is in Alpha, and support for web is experimental. For a full introduction, see the Compose Multiplatform […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Garth Gilmour</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.2.1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=383824</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/08/phpstorm-2023-2-1-is-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T13:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.2.1 is a minor update, and it includes a host of bug fixes and quality-of-life improvements. You can update to it using the Toolbox App or right from inside the IDE. You can also download PhpStorm 2023.2.1 from the website. Here are the most notable changes and bug fixes in this build: The full list of changes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Morozov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Datalore Team Plan: Collaborative Data Science in a Managed Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=383686</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2023/08/28/datalore-team-plan-collaborative-data-science-in-a-managed-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T11:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, Today, we are introducing our new Team plan, which is currently in Beta. The Datalore Team plan allows data-centric teams to create their accounts in seconds and start using Datalore without additional installation steps. The Team plan is all about simplifying and optimizing collaboration among data analysts and scientists within your organization. It’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Anikina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The convenience fee]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44102</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/790258862/0/sethsblog~The-convenience-fee/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s obvious, like the $1 that you get charged for using an ATM or a credit card, and it’s simply not worth the hassle to walk a few blocks. And sometimes it’s not, like the cost we all pay for the conveniently wrapped fruits or vegetables at the market–wrapped in plastic that will not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Hello World Elastic Observability on Google Cloud Run]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-hello-world-elastic-observability-google-cloud-run</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-hello-world-elastic-observability-google-cloud-run"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow the step-by-step process of instrumenting Elastic Observability for a Hello World web app running on Google Cloud Run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Hello World Elastic Observability on Google Cloud Run]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-hello-world-elastic-observability-google-cloud-run</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-hello-world-elastic-observability-google-cloud-run"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Cloud Observability is the premiere tool to provide visibility into your running web apps. Google Cloud Run is the serverless platform of choice to run your web apps that need to scale up massively and scale down to zero. Elastic Observability combined with Google Cloud Run is the perfect solution for developers to deploy web apps that are auto-scaled with fully observable operations, in a way that’s straightforward to implement and manage. 

This blog post will show you how to deploy a simple Hello World web app to Cloud Run and then walk you through the steps to instrument the Hello World web app to enable observation of the application’s operations with Elastic Cloud.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltc1caa5ae5c692d87/64ed05227ea5c52053a072a9/elast…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Path Minimization]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2821/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2821/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/path_minimization.png" title="Of course you get an ice cream cone for the swimmer too! You're not a monster." alt="Of course you get an ice cream cone for the swimmer too! You're not a monster." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: A New (alpha) Mechanism For Safer Cluster Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/28/kubernetes-1-28-feature-mixed-version-proxy-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/28/kubernetes-1-28-feature-mixed-version-proxy-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Richa Banker (Google)
This blog describes the mixed version proxy, a new alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.28. The
mixed version proxy enables an HTTP request for a resource to be served by the correct API server
in cases where there are multiple API servers at varied versions in a cluster. For example,
this is useful during a cluster upgrade, or when you're rolling out the runtime configuration of
the cluster's control plane.
What problem does this solve?
When a cluster undergoes an upgrade, the kube-apiservers existing at different versions in that scenario can serve different sets (groups, versions, resources) of built-in resources. A resource request made in this scenario may be served by any of the available apiservers, potentially resulting in the request ending up at an apiserve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create value]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47019</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/790021583/0/sethsblog~Create-value/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your job feels like a dead end, it might be because you’ve traded agency and responsibility for the feeling of security. But real security lies in creating value. Creating value isn’t easy, but it’s resilient and generous and often profitable. “How do I create more value?” is a much more useful question than, “how […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The maverick and the status quo]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47049</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/789743642/0/sethsblog~The-maverick-and-the-status-quo/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T10:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future isn’t the same as the past. Technology develops, systems change and most of all, someone cares enough to make things better. The maverick isn’t the selfish gunslinger of myth. In fact, she’s focused on resilient, useful interactions that change what we expect, pushing back against the inertia of gobbledygook and bureaucracy. Some principles […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Community Podcast Recap: Inbound and Outbound Connectors: “Woah, it’s so easy!”]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89567</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/camunda-community-podcast-recap-inbound-outbound-connectors-so-easy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T20:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missed the latest episode of the Camunda Community Podcast? Catch up with a quick recap.
The post Camunda Community Podcast Recap: Inbound and Outbound Connectors: “Woah, it’s so easy!” appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · August 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-25-game-bytes-august-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-25-game-bytes-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T18:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-25-game-bytes-august-2023/">Game Bytes · August 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Perception Fairness]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T17:38:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Susanna Ricco and Utsav Prabhu, co-leads, Perception Fairness Team, Google Research





Google’s Responsible AI research is built on a foundation of collaboration — between teams with diverse backgrounds and expertise, between researchers and product developers, and ultimately with the community at large. The Perception Fairness team drives progress by combining deep subject-matter expertise in both computer vision and machine learning (ML) fairness with direct connections to the researchers building the perception systems that power products across Google and beyond. Together, we are working to intentionally design our systems to be inclusive from the ground up, guided by Google’s AI Principles.






Perception Fairness research spans the design, development, and deployment of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started in Data Science: EuroPython 2023 Follow-Up]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=383351</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/08/getting-started-in-data-science-europython-2023-follow-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T13:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my favorite parts of my job as a developer advocate is being able to help people get started in data science. I still remember when I made the transition from academia to data science almost 8 years ago, and how overwhelming it was and how much I felt like I needed to learn […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Win a Trip to KotlinConf’24 in the Kotlin Multiplatform Contest!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=383305</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/08/kotlin-multiplatform-contest-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a student or recent graduate? Have you already tried building projects with Kotlin Multiplatform, a trending technology that lets you build apps for Android, iOS, desktop, web, and server while sharing Kotlin code between all the platforms? If so, don’t miss this opportunity to practice your multiplatform coding skills by taking part in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ksenia Shneyveys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The length trick]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45091</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/789399545/0/sethsblog~The-length-trick/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s possible that the memo or video is simply too long. A 14 minute video explaining how to have a 10 minute brainstorming meeting might benefit from some editing. But it might be that your instruction manual would benefit from some more photos and better in depth explanation. Matching the complexity of the problem to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: cloud native Chris Richardson]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-cloud-native-chris-richardson</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-cloud-native-chris-richardson"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inspiration]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2820/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2820/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/inspiration.png" title="An apple fell on Isaac Newton's head and gave him the idea that the moon might be a tasty apple, though this turned out not to be true--the Apollo program eventually determined that it was just a desolate and bland Red Delicious." alt="An apple fell on Isaac Newton's head and gave him the idea that the moon might be a tasty apple, though this turned out not to be true--the Apollo program eventually determined that it was just a desolate and bland Red Delicious." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.28: Introducing native sidecar containers]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/25/native-sidecar-containers/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/25/native-sidecar-containers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Todd Neal (AWS), Matthias Bertschy (ARMO), Sergey Kanzhelev (Google), Gunju Kim (NAVER), Shannon Kularathna (Google)
This post explains how to use the new sidecar feature, which enables restartable init containers and is available in alpha in Kubernetes 1.28. We want your feedback so that we can graduate this feature as soon as possible.
The concept of a “sidecar” has been part of Kubernetes since nearly the very beginning. In 2015, sidecars were described in a blog post about composite containers as additional containers that “extend and enhance the ‘main’ container”. Sidecar containers have become a common Kubernetes deployment pattern and are often used for network proxies or as part of a logging system. Until now, sidecars were a concept that Kubernetes users applied without n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to compare a noisy quantum processor to a classical computer]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/how-to-compare-noisy-quantum-processor.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/how-to-compare-noisy-quantum-processor.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T22:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sergio Boixo and Vadim Smelyanskiy, Principal Scientists, Google Quantum AI Team




A full-scale error-corrected quantum computer will be able to solve some problems that are impossible for classical computers, but building such a device is a huge endeavor. We are proud of the milestones that we have achieved toward a fully error-corrected quantum computer, but that large-scale computer is still some number of years away. Meanwhile, we are using our current noisy quantum processors as flexible platforms for quantum experiments. 



In contrast to an error-corrected quantum computer, experiments in noisy quantum processors are currently limited to a few thousand quantum operations or gates, before noise degrades the quantum state. In 2019 we implemented a specific computational t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A faster way to manage version updates with Dependabot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-24-a-faster-way-to-manage-version-updates-with-dependabot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-24-a-faster-way-to-manage-version-updates-with-dependabot/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Now, you can group multiple version updates in a single pull request.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-24-a-faster-way-to-manage-version-updates-with-dependabot/">A faster way to manage version updates with Dependabot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching language models to reason algorithmically]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/teaching-language-models-to-reason.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/teaching-language-models-to-reason.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T19:33:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hattie Zhou, Graduate Student at MILA, Hanie Sedghi, Research Scientist, Google




Large language models (LLMs), such as GPT-3 and PaLM, have shown impressive progress in recent years, which have been driven by scaling up models and training data sizes. Nonetheless, a long standing debate has been whether LLMs can reason symbolically (i.e., manipulating symbols based on logical rules). For example, LLMs are able to perform simple arithmetic operations when numbers are small, but struggle to perform with large numbers. This suggests that LLMs have not learned the underlying rules needed to perform these arithmetic operations. 



While neural networks have powerful pattern matching capabilities, they are prone to overfitting to spurious statistical patterns in the data. This does…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: Beta support for using swap on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/24/swap-linux-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/24/swap-linux-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Itamar Holder (Red Hat)
The 1.22 release introduced Alpha support
for configuring swap memory usage for Kubernetes workloads running on Linux on a per-node basis.
Now, in release 1.28, support for swap on Linux nodes has graduated to Beta, along with many
new improvements.
Prior to version 1.22, Kubernetes did not provide support for swap memory on Linux systems.
This was due to the inherent difficulty in guaranteeing and accounting for pod memory utilization
when swap memory was involved. As a result, swap support was deemed out of scope in the initial
design of Kubernetes, and the default behavior of a kubelet was to fail to start if swap memory
was detected on a node.
In version 1.22, the swap feature for Linux was initially introduced in its Alpha stage. This represented
a sign…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2023.05.3 Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=382762</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/08/teamcity-2023-05-3-is-here/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T17:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our newest bug-fix update, 2023.05.3, is now live. In this release cycle, we have addressed 25 issues, including five security problems. As always, you can find the complete list of fixes in our release notes. As with other minor updates, TeamCity 2023.05.3 shares the same data format with all 2023.05.x releases, allowing you to easily […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitrii Korovin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleashing GitHub Codespaces templates to ignite your development]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-24-unleashing-github-codespaces-templates-to-ignite-your-development/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-24-unleashing-github-codespaces-templates-to-ignite-your-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T16:57:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to leverage templating features in GitHub Codespaces to streamline your project setup, improve consistency, and simplify collaboration within your development team.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-24-unleashing-github-codespaces-templates-to-ignite-your-development/">Unleashing GitHub Codespaces templates to ignite your development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.2.1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=382541</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/08/2023-2-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T16:52:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.2.1, the first bug-fix update for PyCharm 2023.2, is now available! You can update to v2023.2.1 by using the Toolbox App, installing it right from the IDE, or downloading it from our website. Download PyCharm 2023.2.1 Here are the most notable fixes available in this version: Updates to profiler support and code coverage Profiler […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Community Day, Berlin 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-community-day-berlin-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-community-day-berlin-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Community Day is a day-long community-focused event to discuss the Ansible project, community, and the broader ecosystem. Announcing the upcoming one in Berlin, with a call for proposals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Ansible Community Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/24/spring-boot-3-2-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/24/spring-boot-3-2-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stéphane Nicoll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/24/spring-boot-3-1-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/24/spring-boot-3-1-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stéphane Nicoll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.10 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/24/spring-boot-3-0-10-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/24/spring-boot-3-0-10-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stéphane Nicoll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.15 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/24/spring-boot-2-7-15-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/08/24/spring-boot-2-7-15-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stéphane Nicoll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Google Cloud collaborate on generative AI and security as a part of an expanded partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-google-cloud-expanded-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-google-cloud-expanded-partnership"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Elastic and Google Cloud are building on our recent joint success with increased investments to accelerate and extend joint go-to-market activities and drive technology integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lon Holden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding passage vector search to Lucene]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-passage-vector-search-to-lucene</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-passage-vector-search-to-lucene"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how we added passage vectors to Apache Lucene, the benefits of doing so, and how existing Lucene structures were used to create an efficient retrieval experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Trent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Google Cloud collaborate on generative AI and security as a part of an expanded partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-google-cloud-expanded-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-google-cloud-expanded-partnership"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic® — Google Cloud’s 2023 Technology Partner of the Year — and Google Cloud are building on our recent joint success with increased investments to accelerate and extend joint go-to-market activities and drive technology integrations. Our collaboration includes the powerful combination of the Elasticsearch Relevance EngineTM (ESRETM) and Google Cloud’s Vertex AI platform, which empowers developers with a scalable toolset to build privacy-first generative AI solutions. Google Distributed Cloud will also now include Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes (ECK) to better serve public sector customers that have the strictest regulatory and compliance requirements. Other advances include a new integration between Elastic and Google Cloud’s Security Command Center (SCC), as well as Elastic support fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lon Holden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding passage vector search to Lucene]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-passage-vector-search-to-lucene</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-passage-vector-search-to-lucene"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Vector search is a powerful tool in the information retrieval tool box. Using vectors alongside lexical search like BM25 is quickly becoming commonplace. But there are still a few pain points within vector search that need to be addressed. A major one is text embedding models and handling larger text input. 

Where lexical search like BM25 is already designed for long documents, text embedding models are not. All embedding models have limitations on the number of tokens they can embed. So, for longer text input it must be chunked into passages shorter than the model’s limit. Now instead of having one document with all its metadata, you have multiple passages and embeddings. And if you want to preserve your metadata, it must be added to every new document.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Trent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connectors: Custom Icons vs. BPMN Symbols]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89461</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/connectors-custom-icons-vs-bpmn-symbols/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T20:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We held discussions with our users on whether custom icons or original BPMN symbols were preferable. The feedback was enlightening.
The post Connectors: Custom Icons vs. BPMN Symbols appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bastian Koerber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-powered impact: GitHub Social Impact’s year ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-23-ai-powered-impact-github-social-impacts-year-ahead/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-23-ai-powered-impact-github-social-impacts-year-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How GitHub Social Impact is working with nonprofit organizations, employees, and more to create positive, lasting change in global communities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-23-ai-powered-impact-github-social-impacts-year-ahead/">AI-powered impact: GitHub Social Impact’s year ahead</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at Google Cloud Next: Seamless infrastructure deployment and management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-google-cloud-next-seamless-infrastructure-deployment-and-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-google-cloud-next-seamless-infrastructure-deployment-and-management"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit us at Google Cloud Next ‘23 in San Francisco, Aug. 29 - 31, for breakout sessions, expert talks, and product demos to accelerate your cloud strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ecommerce marketplace Modalova doubles its revenue by improving search accuracy with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecommerce-marketplace-modalova-search-accuracy-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecommerce-marketplace-modalova-search-accuracy-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gabriel Kaam, the founder of Modalova, implemented Elasticsearch to efficiently handle their vast inventory and deliver more personalized results to customers — resulting in increased conversion rates from 30% to 50% and doubling revenue in a year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Gabriel Kaam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to successfully lead a team in a distributed workplace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lead-distributed-team</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lead-distributed-team"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent Forbes article showed that 98% of workers want to work remotely at least some of the time, but only 16% of companies operate remotely. Elastic has always operated distributedly — we are distributed by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ecommerce marketplace Modalova doubles its revenue by improving search accuracy with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecommerce-marketplace-modalova-search-accuracy-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecommerce-marketplace-modalova-search-accuracy-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Modalova is an up-and-coming French ecommerce marketplace offering a curated selection of top brands like ASOS, Tommy Hilfiger, Michael Kors, and Adidas. Modalova's mission is to bring the best in men's and women's fashion on one site to simplify the online shopping experience — no more opening 35 tabs to find the right article. No more downloading 50 different apps to find the right size — it's all in one location! As Modalova rapidly expands its global audience, it also looks to feature more ethical brands and democratize access by allowing new brands to join the Modalova platform seamlessly.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt0d7288b8d1137e8b/64dec338b1e7d122c0fe8eb7/elastic-blog-1-modalova.png,elastic-blog-1-modalova.png,
This model has empowered Modalova …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Gabriel Kaam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to successfully lead a team in a distributed workplace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lead-distributed-team</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-lead-distributed-team"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
A recent Forbes article showed that 98% of workers want to work remotely at least some of the time, but only 16% of companies operate remotely. 

Elastic® has always operated distributedly — we are distributed by design. But, with Elasticians in more than 40 countries around the world it can prove challenging to create an environment where teams can thrive. 

We asked three team leaders to share their best tips for successfully leading distributed teams. 

Encourage growth
As a manager, you’re at least partially responsible for your team members career progression. But ultimately, each Elasitican needs to drive their own career development with their managers there to support and guide them, Diana Jourdan, Senior Manager Software Engineering, says. 

Stacey King Poling, Director, Softwar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: Node podresources API Graduates to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/23/kubelet-podresources-api-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/23/kubelet-podresources-api-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author:
Francesco Romani (Red Hat)
The podresources API is an API served by the kubelet locally on the node, which exposes the compute resources exclusively
allocated to containers. With the release of Kubernetes 1.28, that API is now Generally Available.
What problem does it solve?
The kubelet can allocate exclusive resources to containers, like
CPUs, granting exclusive access to full cores
or memory, either regions or hugepages.
Workloads which require high performance, or low latency (or both) leverage these features.
The kubelet also can assign devices to containers.
Collectively, these features which enable exclusive assignments are known as "resource managers".
Without an API like podresources, the only possible option to learn about resource assignment was to read the state files th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Azure Artifacts support for Rust Crates]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67425</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-azure-artifacts-support-for-rust-crates/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T20:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust is earning its place as a go-to language for developers everywhere. Why? It’s fast, it’s safe, and the community around it is supportive and hands-on. With clear guides and a collective push to help each other out, Rust feels less like just another tool and more like a reliable coding partner for modern programming challenges.
The post Introducing Azure Artifacts support for Rust Crates appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jorge Fernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Language to rewards for robotic skill synthesis]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/language-to-rewards-for-robotic-skill.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/language-to-rewards-for-robotic-skill.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:47:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Wenhao Yu and Fei Xia, Research Scientists, Google






Empowering end-users to interactively teach robots to perform novel tasks is a crucial capability for their successful integration into real-world applications. For example, a user may want to teach a robot dog to perform a new trick, or teach a manipulator robot how to organize a lunch box based on user preferences. The recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) pre-trained on extensive internet data have shown a promising path towards achieving this goal. Indeed, researchers have explored diverse ways of leveraging LLMs for robotics, from step-by-step planning and goal-oriented dialogue to robot-code-writing agents. 



While these methods impart new modes of compositional generalization, they focus on using lang…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s next: Black Hat 2023 takeaways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/black-hat-2023-takeaways</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/black-hat-2023-takeaways"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black Hat USA 2023 showcased cybersecurity advancements and cutting-edge research. This blog explores major trends and how they may shape the field in the coming months and years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s next: Black Hat 2023 takeaways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/black-hat-2023-takeaways</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/black-hat-2023-takeaways"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,Black Hat USA 2023 showcased advancements in cybersecurity and provided a platform for cutting-edge research. This blog recaps highlights from the event, exploring major trends and examining how they may shape the field in the coming months and years.https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt75e9b8a7dca4d962/64e521eeaa596e76fb819962/blog-elastic-hot-risk.png,blog-elastic-hot-risk.png,
Researchers and engineers from Elastic Security Labs participated at Black Hat and DEFCON and shared new analytics content — including an update to our advanced analytics package for lateral movement. Detecting malicious lateral movement with traditional detection rules can be difficult because attackers use sophisticated methods and tools to move under the security radar. With the addition of prebuilt ML jobs that detect malicious activity from Windows RDP events, these analytics are now generally available. Dig in at our open detection rules repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp updates licensing FAQ based on community questions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-updates-licensing-faq-based-on-community-questions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-updates-licensing-faq-based-on-community-questions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp continues to update our licensing FAQ based on questions from the community about our change to the Business Source License for future releases of HashiCorp products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – AWS AppSync, AWS CodePipeline, Events and More – August 21, 2023]]></title>
        <id>47e2668ee0f78c86ac3d5a66b93a95d71f12cde4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-appsync-aws-codepipeline-events-and-more-august-21-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T18:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a few days, I will board a plane towards the south. My tour around Latin America starts. But I won’t be alone in this adventure, you can find some other News Blog authors, like Jeff or Seb, speaking at AWS Community Days and local events in Peru, Argentina, Chile, and Uruguay. If you see […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from Git 2.42]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-08-21-highlights-from-git-2-42/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-08-21-highlights-from-git-2-42/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T17:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Another new release of Git is here! Take a look at some of our highlights on what's new in Git 2.42.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-08-21-highlights-from-git-2-42/">Highlights from Git 2.42</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform ephemeral workspaces public beta now available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-ephemeral-workspaces-public-beta-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-ephemeral-workspaces-public-beta-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing unused infrastructure resources is important not just for cost control, but for security as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage OSPF for network automation with Ansible validated content]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/manage-ospf-for-network-automation-with-ansible-validated-content</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/manage-ospf-for-network-automation-with-ansible-validated-content"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the quickly evolving networking environment, efficient management of routing protocols is essential for reliable and optimized network performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at Interspeech 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/google-at-interspeech-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/google-at-interspeech-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T07:33:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Catherine Armato, Program Manager, Google




This week, the 24th Annual Conference of the International Speech Communication Association (INTERSPEECH 2023) is being held in Dublin, Ireland, representing one of the world’s most extensive conferences on research and technology of spoken language understanding and processing. Experts in speech-related research fields gather to take part in oral presentations and poster sessions and to build collaborations across the globe.




We are excited to be a Platinum Sponsor of INTERSPEECH 2023, where we will be showcasing more than 20 research publications and supporting a number of workshops and special sessions. We welcome in-person attendees to drop by the Google Research booth to meet our researchers and participate in Q&As and demonst…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: Improved failure handling for Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/21/kubernetes-1-28-jobapi-update/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/21/kubernetes-1-28-jobapi-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kevin Hannon (G-Research), Michał Woźniak (Google)
This blog discusses two new features in Kubernetes 1.28 to improve Jobs for batch
users: Pod replacement policy
and Backoff limit per index.
These features continue the effort started by the
Pod failure policy
to improve the handling of Pod failures in a Job.
Pod replacement policy
By default, when a pod enters a terminating state (e.g. due to preemption or
eviction), Kubernetes immediately creates a replacement Pod. Therefore, both Pods are running
at the same time. In API terms, a pod is considered terminating when it has a
deletionTimestamp and it has a phase Pending or Running.
The scenario when two Pods are running at a given time is problematic for
some popular machine learning frameworks, such as
TensorFlow and JAX, which r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autonomous visual information seeking with large language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/autonomous-visual-information-seeking.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/autonomous-visual-information-seeking.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:28:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ziniu Hu, Student Researcher, and Alireza Fathi, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception Team




There has been great progress towards adapting large language models (LLMs) to accommodate multimodal inputs for tasks including image captioning, visual question answering (VQA), and open vocabulary recognition. Despite such achievements, current state-of-the-art visual language models (VLMs) perform inadequately on visual information seeking datasets, such as Infoseek and OK-VQA, where external knowledge is required to answer the questions. 
 






Examples of visual information seeking queries where external knowledge is required to answer the question. Images are taken from the OK-VQA dataset.

AVIS: Autonomous Visual Information Seeking with Large Language Models”, we i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Hyperautomation Examples and Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89106</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/top-10-use-cases-for-hyperautomation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the top 10 use cases for hyperautomation with examples, and understand its incredible impact across industries.
The post Top 10 Hyperautomation Examples and Use Cases appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.28: Retroactive Default StorageClass move to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/18/retroactive-default-storage-class-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/18/retroactive-default-storage-class-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Roman Bednář (Red Hat)
Announcing graduation to General Availability (GA) - Retroactive Default StorageClass Assignment in Kubernetes v1.28!
Kubernetes SIG Storage team is thrilled to announce that the "Retroactive Default StorageClass Assignment" feature,
introduced as an alpha in Kubernetes v1.25, has now graduated to GA and is officially part of the Kubernetes v1.28 release.
This enhancement brings a significant improvement to how default
StorageClasses are assigned to PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs).
With this feature enabled, you no longer need to create a default StorageClass first and then a PVC to assign the class.
Instead, any PVCs without a StorageClass assigned will now be retroactively updated to include the default StorageClass.
This enhancement ensures that PVCs no longer get stuck in an unbound state, and storage provisioning works seamlessly,
even when a default StorageClass is not defined at the time of PVC creation.
What changed?
The PersistentVolume (PV) controller has been modified to automatically assign a default StorageClass to any unbound
PersistentVolumeClaim with the storageClassName not set. Additionally, the PersistentVolumeClaim
admission validation mechanism within
the API server has been adjusted to allow changing values from an unset state to an actual StorageClass name.
How to use it?
As this feature has graduated to GA, there's no need to enable a feature gate anymore.
Simply make sure you are running Kubernetes v1.28 or later, and the feature will be available for use.
For more details, read about
default StorageClass assignment in the Kubernetes documentation.
You can also read the previous blog post announcing beta graduation in v1.26.
To provide feedback, join our Kubernetes Storage Special-Interest-Group (SIG)
or participate in discussions on our public Slack channel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVA Discovery View: Surfacing Authentic Moments]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b8cd145491cc</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/ava-discovery-view-surfacing-authentic-moments-b8cd145491cc?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T22:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By: Hamid Shahid, Laura Johnson, Tiffany Low]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 Hpc7a Instances Powered by 4th Gen AMD EPYC Processors Optimized for High Performance Computing]]></title>
        <id>b86f604c4015c28675b8f90e5913de842828c831</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-hpc7a-instances-powered-by-4th-gen-amd-epyc-processors-optimized-for-high-performance-computing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January 2022, we launched Amazon EC2 Hpc6a instances for customers to efficiently run their compute-bound high performance computing (HPC) workloads on AWS with up to 65 percent better price performance over comparable x86-based compute-optimized instances. As their jobs grow more complex, customers have asked for more cores with more compute performance and more memory […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neural network pruning with combinatorial optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/neural-network-pruning-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/neural-network-pruning-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T18:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hussein Hazimeh, Research Scientist, Athena Team, and Riade Benbaki, Graduate Student at MIT





Modern neural networks have achieved impressive performance across a variety of applications, such as language, mathematical reasoning, and vision. However, these networks often use large architectures that require lots of computational resources. This can make it impractical to serve such models to users, especially in resource-constrained environments like wearables and smartphones. A widely used approach to mitigate the inference costs of pre-trained networks is to prune them by removing some of their weights, in a way that doesn’t significantly affect utility. In standard neural networks, each weight defines a connection between two neurons. So after weights are pruned, the input…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.18 reduces synthesization time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-18-reduces-synthesization-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-18-reduces-synthesization-time"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newest CDKTF release cuts synthesization times for TypeScript, Python, and Java, drastically improving the user experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYC Automation for Banks: 5 Biggest Benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=88965</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/kyc-automation-banks-5-biggest-benefits/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T21:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With KYC in banking, there are a lot of advantages that every bank should know about. Read on to learn more about KYC automation and how it works.
The post KYC Automation for Banks: 5 Biggest Benefits appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: Non-Graceful Node Shutdown Moves to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/16/kubernetes-1-28-non-graceful-node-shutdown-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/16/kubernetes-1-28-non-graceful-node-shutdown-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Xing Yang (VMware) and Ashutosh Kumar (Elastic)
The Kubernetes Non-Graceful Node Shutdown feature is now GA in Kubernetes v1.28.
It was introduced as
alpha
in Kubernetes v1.24, and promoted to
beta
in Kubernetes v1.26.
This feature allows stateful workloads to restart on a different node if the
original node is shutdown unexpectedly or ends up in a non-recoverable state
such as the hardware failure or unresponsive OS.
What is a Non-Graceful Node Shutdown
In a Kubernetes cluster, a node can be shutdown in a planned graceful way or
unexpectedly because of reasons such as power outage or something else external.
A node shutdown could lead to workload failure if the node is not drained
before the shutdown. A node shutdown can be either graceful or non-graceful.
The Graceful Node Shutd…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curbing Connection Churn in Zuul]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2feb273a3598</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/curbing-connection-churn-in-zuul-2feb273a3598?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix’s Zuul Gateway eliminated tens of millions of connections and reduced almost all connection churn to backends]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join AWS Hybrid Cloud & Edge Day to Learn How to Deploy Your Applications in the Everywhere Cloud]]></title>
        <id>6a2ca8d5448ccbca3f8b3089d50548e5662fbc19</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/join-aws-hybrid-cloud-edge-day-to-learn-how-to-deploy-your-applications-in-the-everywhere-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editor’s note: The live event has ended, but you may still watch the video on demand on Twitch. In his keynote of AWS re:Invent 2021, Dr. Werner Vogels shared the insight of how “the everywhere cloud” is bringing AWS to new locales through AWS hardware and services and spotlighted it as one of his tech […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M7a General Purpose Instances Powered by 4th Gen AMD EPYC Processors]]></title>
        <id>aa69e34d695f6dcbf492a7e3a606a2ef16eeda02</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-m7a-general-purpose-instances-powered-by-4th-gen-amd-epyc-processors/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T22:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2021, we launched Amazon EC2 M6a instances, powered by 3rd Gen AMD EPYC (Milan) processors, running at frequencies up to 3.6 GHz, which offer you up to 35 percent improvement in price performance compared to M5a instances. Many customers who run workloads that are dependent on x86 instructions, such as SAP, are looking […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching Camunda – An Interview with Achim Dannecker]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=88857</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/teaching-camunda-interview-achim-dannecker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about why Achim Dannecker uses Camunda in his classroom, how students work with it and what he hopes everyone can take away from his course.
The post Teaching Camunda – An Interview with Achim Dannecker appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: pkgs.k8s.io: Introducing Kubernetes Community-Owned Package Repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/15/pkgs-k8s-io-introduction/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/15/pkgs-k8s-io-introduction/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Marko Mudrinić (Kubermatic)
On behalf of Kubernetes SIG Release, I am very excited to introduce the
Kubernetes community-owned software
repositories for Debian and RPM packages: pkgs.k8s.io! The new package
repositories are replacement for the Google-hosted package repositories
(apt.kubernetes.io and yum.kubernetes.io) that we've been using since
Kubernetes v1.5.
This blog post contains information about these new package repositories,
what does it mean to you as an end user, and how to migrate to the new
repositories.
Update (August 31, 2023): the legacy Google-hosted repositories are deprecated
and will be frozen starting with September 13, 2023.
Check out the deprecation announcement
for more details about this change.
What you need to know about the new package repositories? (U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STUDY: Socially aware temporally causal decoder recommender systems]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/study-socially-aware-temporally-causal.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/study-socially-aware-temporally-causal.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T19:59:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eltayeb Ahmed, Research Engineer, and Subhrajit Roy, Senior Research Scientist, Google Research




Reading has many benefits for young students, such as better linguistic and life skills, and reading for pleasure has been shown to correlate with academic success. Furthermore students have reported improved emotional wellbeing from reading, as well as better general knowledge and better understanding of other cultures. With the vast amount of reading material both online and off, finding age-appropriate, relevant and engaging content can be a challenging task, but helping students do so is a necessary step to engage them in reading. Effective recommendations that present students with relevant reading material helps keep students reading, and this is where machine learning (ML) c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform integrations with ServiceNow, GitHub, Confluent, VMware, Cisco, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-servicenow-github-confluent-vmware-cisco-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-servicenow-github-confluent-vmware-cisco-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Cloud and community integration partners provide more options to automate and secure cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.28: Planternetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/15/kubernetes-v1-28-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/15/kubernetes-v1-28-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes v1.28 Release Team
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.28 Planternetes, the second release of 2023!
This release consists of 45 enhancements. Of those enhancements, 19 are entering Alpha, 14 have graduated to Beta, and 12 have graduated to Stable.
Release Theme And Logo
Kubernetes v1.28: Planternetes
The theme for Kubernetes v1.28 is Planternetes.
Each Kubernetes release is the culmination of the hard work of thousands of individuals from our community. The people behind this release come from a wide range of backgrounds, some of us industry veterans, parents, others students and newcomers to open-source. We combine our unique experience to create a collective artifact with global impact.
Much like a garden, our release has ever-changing growth, challenges and oppor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – Amazon MWAA, EMR Studio, Generative AI, and More – August 14, 2023]]></title>
        <id>095ee594cacd2042f3e53487e4fe1b5590a0d5e7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-mwaa-emr-studio-generative-ai-and-more-august-14-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T17:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I enjoyed a few days off in California to get a dose of vitamin sea, a lot has happened in the AWS universe. Let’s take a look together! Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my attention: Amazon MWAA now supports Apache Airflow version 2.6 – Amazon Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Secrets extends secret sync to GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-secrets-extends-secret-sync-to-github-actions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-secrets-extends-secret-sync-to-github-actions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Secrets extends secret sync capabilities to GitHub Actions secrets, improves secret versioning, and adds a tutorial on using HCP Vault Secrets with Terraform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interfaces Management with Ansible validated content using the network.interfaces collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/interfaces-management-with-ansible-validated-content-using-the-network.interfaces-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/interfaces-management-with-ansible-validated-content-using-the-network.interfaces-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
 
At AnsibleFest 2022, we announced a new addition to the content ecosystem offered through Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform: Ansible validated content. Ansible validated content is use case-focused and provides an expert-guided path for performing operational tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwini Mhatre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG ContribEx]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/14/sig-contribex-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/14/sig-contribex-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fyka Ansari
Welcome to the world of Kubernetes and its vibrant contributor
community! In this blog post, we'll be shining a spotlight on the
Special Interest Group for Contributor
Experience
(SIG ContribEx), an essential component of the Kubernetes project.
SIG ContribEx in Kubernetes is responsible for developing and
maintaining a healthy and productive community of contributors to the
project. This involves identifying and addressing bottlenecks that may
hinder the project's growth and feature velocity, such as pull request
latency and the number of open pull requests and issues.
SIG ContribEx works to improve the overall contributor experience by
creating and maintaining guidelines, tools, and processes that
facilitate collaboration and communication among contributors. They
als…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous Improvement with Camunda Optimize]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=88661</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/continuous-improvement-with-camunda-optimize/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T20:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize helps you improve your automated processes with insightful dashboards and reports—no coding required. Learn how.
The post Continuous Improvement with Camunda Optimize appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp adopts Business Source License]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-adopts-business-source-license</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-adopts-business-source-license"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp adopts the Business Source License to ensure continued investment in its community and to continue providing open, freely available products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and HashiCorp announce Service Catalog support for Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-and-hashicorp-announce-service-catalog-support-for-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-and-hashicorp-announce-service-catalog-support-for-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and HashiCorp jointly announce the launch of a new integration between AWS Service Catalog and HashiCorp Terraform Cloud to enable large enterprises on AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monolith vs Microservice Architecture: A Comparison]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=88421</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/monolith-vs-microservice-architecture-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T20:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the difference between microservice and monolith architectures, and which is better for your next project.
The post Monolith vs Microservice Architecture: A Comparison appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advances in document understanding]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/advances-in-document-understanding.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/advances-in-document-understanding.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T18:32:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sandeep Tata, Software Engineer, Google Research, Athena Team




The last few years have seen rapid progress in systems that can automatically process complex business documents and turn them into structured objects. A system that can automatically extract data from documents, e.g., receipts, insurance quotes, and financial statements, has the potential to dramatically improve the efficiency of business workflows by avoiding error-prone, manual work. Recent models, based on the Transformer architecture, have shown impressive gains in accuracy. Larger models, such as PaLM 2, are also being leveraged to further streamline these business workflows. However, the datasets used in academic literature fail to capture the challenges seen in real-world use cases. Consequently, academic b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — File Release for Amazon FSx for Lustre]]></title>
        <id>ab7fee828c2716aef7dc8919868ed8b8478993a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-file-release-for-amazon-fsx-for-lustre/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for Lustre provides fully managed shared storage with the scalability and high performance of the open-source Lustre file systems to support your Linux-based workloads. FSx for Lustre is for workloads where storage speed and throughput matter. This is because FSx for Lustre helps you avoid storage bottlenecks, increase utilization of compute resources, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to AWS Storage Day 2023]]></title>
        <id>f8e8802dd8cc05f8d2c1c67f018438d0f1c6f32c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/welcome-to-aws-storage-day-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T15:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fifth annual AWS Storage Day took place on Aug. 9, 2023 and you can see the replay here. The first AWS Storage Day was hosted in 2019, and this event has grown into an innovation day that we look forward to delivering to you every year. In last year’s Storage Day post, I wrote […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第235話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755080540915</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755080540915"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mountpoint for Amazon S3 – Generally Available and Ready for Production Workloads]]></title>
        <id>1f5e24433cd44a849bf1194960ef837075cc5287</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/mountpoint-for-amazon-s3-generally-available-and-ready-for-production-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T14:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mountpoint for Amazon S3 is an open source file client that makes it easy for your file-aware Linux applications to connect directly to Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) buckets. Announced earlier this year as an alpha release, it is now generally available and ready for production use on your large-scale read-heavy applications: data lakes, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Improve Amazon S3 Glacier Flexible Restore Time By Up To 85% Using Standard Retrieval Tier and S3 Batch Operations]]></title>
        <id>6ba5c372510c4fc04b6b69bd89bf73c129951d9b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-improve-amazon-s3-glacier-flexible-restore-time-by-up-to-85-using-standard-retrieval-tier-and-s3-batch-operations/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T14:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, Amazon S3 Glacier celebrated its tenth anniversary. Amazon S3 Glacier is the leader in cloud cold storage, and I wrote about its innovations over the last decade. The Amazon S3 Glacier storage classes provide you with long-term, secure, and durable storage options to optimally archive your data at the lowest cost. The Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulk API in Automation Controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/bulk-api-in-automation-controller</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/bulk-api-in-automation-controller"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation Controller API:
 
Automation controller has a rich ReSTful API. REST stands for Representational State Transfer and is sometimes spelled as “ReST”. It relies on a stateless, client-server, and cacheable communications protocol, usually the HTTP protocol. REST APIs provide access to resources (data entities) via URI paths. You can visit the automation controller REST API in a web browser at: http://<server name>/api/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AdaTape: Foundation model with adaptive computation and dynamic read-and-write]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/adatape-foundation-model-with-adaptive.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/adatape-foundation-model-with-adaptive.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T21:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Fuzhao Xue, Research Intern, and Mostafa Dehghani, Research Scientist, Google







Adaptive computation refers to the ability of a machine learning system to adjust its behavior in response to changes in the environment. While conventional neural networks have a fixed function and computation capacity, i.e., they spend the same number of FLOPs for processing different inputs, a model with adaptive and dynamic computation modulates the computational budget it dedicates to processing each input, depending on the complexity of the input.


Adaptive computation in neural networks is appealing for two key reasons. First, the mechanism that introduces adaptivity provides an inductive bias that can play a key role in solving some challenging tasks. For instance, enabling different num…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New customization options for Terraform Cloud projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-customization-options-for-terraform-cloud-projects</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-customization-options-for-terraform-cloud-projects"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customizable project permissions and policy assignment for HashiCorp Terraform help organizations scale securely and quickly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[August patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67389</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/august-patches-for-azure-devops-server-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T17:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.0.1
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 Patch 2
Note: If you have Azure DevOps Server 2022,
The post August patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – AWS Storage Day, AWS Israel (Tel Aviv) Region, and More – Aug 8, 2023]]></title>
        <id>989c76d0a0870b0f003442a7730832ffc94086a2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-storage-day-aws-israel-tel-aviv-region-and-more-aug-8-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T17:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Editor’s note: Today, we are changing the title of this regular weekly post from AWS Week in Review to AWS Weekly Roundup to better reflect the mix of recent top news and announcements as well as upcoming events you won’t want to miss.) It’s taken me some time to finally be comfortable with being in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Alpha Release August 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=88241</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/camunda-alpha-release-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T13:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to announce the August 2023 alpha release of Camunda. Check out what's new.
The post Camunda Alpha Release August 2023 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault observability: Monitoring Vault at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-observability-monitoring-vault-at-scale</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-observability-monitoring-vault-at-scale"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to implement a mature Vault monitoring and observability strategy to simplify finding answers to important Vault questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Deliver Interactive Real-Time Live Streams with Amazon IVS]]></title>
        <id>2f8852492df93a4d7ea33c5bfa21fc24f2bfd83e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-deliver-interactive-real-time-live-streams-with-amazon-ivs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T19:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live streaming is becoming an increasingly popular way to connect customers with their favorite influencers and brands through interactive live video experiences. Our customers, DeNA and Rooter, rely on Amazon Interactive Video Service (Amazon IVS), a fully managed live streaming solution, to build engaging live stream and interactive video experiences for their audiences. In March we introduced Amazon IVS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New and Next in Private Automation Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-and-next-in-private-automation-hub</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-and-next-in-private-automation-hub"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Private automation hub is the content system for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, hosting and serving up content to the platform in a scalable way with an enhanced security posture. The hosted content ranges from collections to container images, whether it's your own content, certified content from Red Hat or partner content from the extensive partner ecosystem, along with open source content from Ansible Galaxy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>