<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-10T00:21:00.243Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-10T00:21:00.243Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Default to surrender]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48740</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873368081/0/sethsblog~Default-to-surrender/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI chatbots highight a challenge that is worth understanding. It applies to customer service, bureaucracies and teachers as well… If you ask an AI a question and it’s not confident in the answer, it should say, “I’m not sure.” That could be followed up with, “do you want me to guess” or “if you could […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Workflow Engine? Key Benefits, Features and Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102261</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/what-is-a-workflow-engine/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T01:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is a workflow engine? How do they work, and why should you use one? Learn why modern workflow engines are critical for process automation and orchestration.
The post What Is a Workflow Engine? Key Benefits, Features and Considerations appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2024.1 EAP 5: Improved STL Container Rendering in the Debugger and VCS Enhancements]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=455160</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2024/03/clion-2024-1-eap-5-improved-stl-container-rendering-in-the-debugger-and-vcs-enhancements/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T22:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CLion 2024.1 EAP 5 build (241.14494.27) is now out! It’s available from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package if you’re using Ubuntu. DOWNLOAD CLION 2024.1 EAP The highlights: This latest CLion EAP introduces refreshed product icons in line with updates across all JetBrains IDEs, enhancing visual appeal and consistency […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Health-specific embedding tools for dermatology and pathology]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/health-specific-embedding-tools-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/health-specific-embedding-tools-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T19:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dave Steiner, Clinical Research Scientist, Google Health, and Rory Pilgrim, Product Manager Google Research




There’s a worldwide shortage of access to medical imaging expert interpretation across specialties including radiology, dermatology and pathology. Machine learning (ML) technology can help ease this burden by powering tools that enable doctors to interpret these images more accurately and efficiently. However, the development and implementation of such ML tools are often limited by the availability of high-quality data, ML expertise, and computational resources. 



One way to catalyze the use of ML for medical imaging is via domain-specific models that utilize deep learning (DL) to capture the information in medical images as compressed numerical vectors (called embedd…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernizing financial services: A deep dive into Elastic Cloud on AWS for Observability, Security, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-elastic-cloud-aws-observability-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-elastic-cloud-aws-observability-security"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T18:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the landscape continues to evolve across increasingly complex ecosystems, Elastic Cloud in AWS Marketplace serves as a key enabler for observability within the banking, insurance, capital markets, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gareth Muc-Johnson,Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernizing financial services: A deep dive into Elastic Cloud on AWS for Observability, Security, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-elastic-cloud-aws-observability-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-elastic-cloud-aws-observability-security"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T18:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic landscape of financial services, data is not just currency; it's the key to innovation and operational excellence. Data is constantly streamlining from devices, logins, transfers, transactions, and much more, and it’s bound to increase with an ongoing reliance on digital channels. This creates a massive opportunity and responsibility for financial institutions, as their customers (and regulators) demand more from banking providers.

As the landscape continues to evolve across an increasingly complex ecosystem, Elastic Cloud in AWS Marketplace serves as a key enabler for observability within the banking, insurance, capital markets, and payments sectors. Elastic®’s integration with AWS native services provides financial institutions with unparalleled visibility, security, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gareth Muc-Johnson,Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2024.1 EAP 8: Enhanced Support for Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=453627</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2024/03/pycharm-2024-1-eap-8/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2024.1 EAP 8 is now available, providing a sneak peek into some exciting new features planned for the next major release. A notable update of this build is enhanced support for Terraform. You can download the new version from our website, update directly from the IDE or via the free Toolbox App, or use snaps for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goland 2024.1 Beta Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=453953</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2024/03/08/goland-2024-1-beta-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get the Beta build via the Toolbox App, from our website, by using a snap package (for Ubuntu), or right from inside GoLand by selecting Check IDE updates for: Early Access Program in Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System Settings | Updates. Download GoLand 2024.1 Beta The Beta version includes all of the new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ruslan Akhmetzianov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drop the Baggage: Use ‘_’ for Unnamed Local Variables and Patterns in Java 22]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=448606</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/03/drop-the-baggage-use-_-for-unnamed-local-variables-and-patterns-in-java-22/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T11:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How would you feel if you tried to understand a code snippet, only to realize that some of the variables you were trying to make sense of, were never used? This could be due to the programming syntax constraints, or an oversight as a result of changes to a codebase over time. Would you like […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mala Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where are you?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46895</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873298445/0/sethsblog~Where-are-you/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T09:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re reading a good historical novel, you might be there and then. When you’re checking your email, you are in a conversation between and among, over there, not here. When you’re imagining what went wrong in that conversation yesterday, you are living in yesterday. And when you’re scripting the next conversation you’re going to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating women in tech this International Women’s Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-international-womens-day-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-international-womens-day-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We regularly share stories from our female technologists, focusing on their roles, interests, and advice. Read them all here. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating women in tech this International Women’s Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-international-womens-day-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-international-womens-day-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[International Women’s Day is recognized globally on March 8th to celebrate the social, economic, cultural, and political achievements of women. This year, the theme is ‘Inspire Inclusion’ which encourages women’s economic empowerment, developing female talent, and supporting women and girls into leadership, decision-making, business and STEM. This theme deeply resonates with us. 
At Elastic®, we strive to empower women and pride ourselves on fostering an inclusive global culture. In 2023, we began to spotlight female-identifying technologists around the world in various roles and at differing levels of seniority to give Elasticians the chance to share their personal stories and experiences. 
Over the last year, we’ve told real Elasticians’ stories and had discussions about technical roles,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physics vs. Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2904/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2904/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/physics_vs_magic.png" title="'At the stroke of midnight, your brother will be hurtling sideways at an altitude of 150 meters' is a regular physics prediction about your nonmagical trebuchet, whereas 'you are cursed to build a brother-launching trebuchet' falls out of the Lagrangian." alt="'At the stroke of midnight, your brother will be hurtling sideways at an altitude of 150 meters' is a regular physics prediction about your nonmagical trebuchet, whereas 'you are cursed to build a brother-launching trebuchet' falls out of the Lagrangian." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2024.1 Goes Beta!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=454383</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/03/intellij-idea-2024-1-beta/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T20:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024.1 Beta version of IntelliJ IDEA has arrived! You can get the latest build from our website, through the free Toolbox App, or via snaps for Ubuntu. Download IntelliJ IDEA 2024.1 Beta Our latest build integrates all of the significant updates introduced during the IntelliJ IDEA 2024.1 Early Access Program. Here’s a short recap […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting Diverse ML Systems at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2d2e6b6d205d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/supporting-diverse-ml-systems-at-netflix-2d2e6b6d205d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T18:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David J. Berg, Romain Cledat, Kayla Seeley, Shashank Srikanth, Chaoying Wang, Darin Yu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social learning: Collaborative learning with large language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/social-learning-collaborative-learning.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/social-learning-collaborative-learning.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Amirkeivan Mohtashami, Research Intern, and Florian Hartmann, Software Engineer, Google Research




Large language models (LLMs) have significantly improved the state of the art for solving tasks specified using natural language, often reaching performance close to that of people. As these models increasingly enable assistive agents, it could be beneficial for them to learn effectively from each other, much like people do in social settings, which would allow LLM-based agents to improve each other’s performance. 

 


To discuss the learning processes of humans, Bandura and Walters described the concept of social learning in 1977, outlining different models of observational learning used by people. One common method of learning from others is through a verbal instruction (e.g., …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring an increase in circumvention claims in our transparency data]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-07-exploring-an-increase-in-circumvention-claims-in-our-transparency-data/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-exploring-an-increase-in-circumvention-claims-in-our-transparency-data/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our full year of 2023 transparency reporting data is now available and we’re taking a deep dive into how a form change caused an abrupt increase in circumvention claims. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-exploring-an-increase-in-circumvention-claims-in-our-transparency-data/">Exploring an increase in circumvention claims in our transparency data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Livestream Recording – Debug Like a Pro: JavaScript Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=454371</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2024/03/livestream-recording-debug-like-a-pro-javascript-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T17:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recording from the Debug Like a Pro: JavaScript Edition livestream is now available on the JetBrains YouTube channel! As our Developer Advocate Paul Everitt said, “Instead of reaching for the debugger when you have a problem – you should embrace the always-be-debugging mindset. Then, there’s no reaching.” Watch Paul Everitt and Carson Gross from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Aganezova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hard and soft skills for developers coding in the age of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T17:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While AI revolutionizes software development, it still relies on developers to pilot its use. In this blog, we’ll cover the skills that developers need to have for navigating this new AI-powered coding frontier. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/">Hard and soft skills for developers coding in the age of AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dotInsights | March 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=454233</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/03/07/dotinsights-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T16:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to dotInsights by JetBrains! It’s the place for recent .NET and software development related content. 📜 Featured Content This month, we bring you featured content from Chris Woodruff! Chris, along with JetBrains developer advocates Maarten and Khalid host the Breakpoint Show. Catch episodes on .NET development, software, and IT industry careers. Server-Side vs. Client-Side […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Annual Highlights 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=453182</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/blog/2024/03/07/jetbrains-annual-highlights-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:53:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s that time of the year – the JetBrains Annual Highlights are here! For over two decades, JetBrains has been on a mission to make professional software development a more productive and enjoyable experience. From our humble beginnings back in 2000, we have grown into a global company that both creates some of the world’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JetBrains</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MPS 2023.3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=mps&amp;p=436396</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/mps/2024/03/mps-2023-3-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this release, MPS has adopted a new, modern-looking UI style. Under the hood, it gives you the option to document the structure of your languages and introduces improvements in several areas of the user interface, version control management, and build infrastructure. DOWNLOAD MPS 2023.3 Check out the What’s New page to learn all about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaclav Pech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning vs. AI: Understanding the differences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ml-vs-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ml-vs-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uncover the world of machine learning and artificial intelligence. Learn how they’re different and where they intersect to drive innovation....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Tripathi,Jessica Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning vs. AI: Understanding the differences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ml-vs-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ml-vs-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a long time, AI was almost exclusively the plaything of science fiction writers, where humans push technology too far, to the point it comes alive and — as Hollywood would have us believe — starts to wreak havoc. Cheery stuff! However, in recent years, we’ve seen an explosion of AI and machine learning technology that, so far, has shown us a fun side with people using AI for creating, planning, and ideating in a big way.
These emerging technologies are being used to revolutionize everything from healthcare to entertainment. But as with any new technology, people are still trying to wrap their heads around it. And one of the biggest sources of this confusion comes from the similarities and overlap between two of the key terms in this field: AI and machine learning. So in this article, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Tripathi,Jessica Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking Outside the Microservice Box: Decision Making (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102198</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/thinking-outside-the-microservice-box-decision-making/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-based microservice architectures are popular but do have limitations. In this series, we'll think outside the box and learn new ideas for microservice orchestration.
The post Thinking Outside the Microservice Box: Decision Making (Part 1) appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dive Into the World of Coding With the Algorithm and Code Training School 2024!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=454074</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2024/03/07/dive-into-the-world-of-coding-with-the-algorithm-and-code-training-school-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calling all high school students with a knack for coding and a thirst for challenge! Mark April 20–23, 2024, in your calendars and join the Algorithm and Code Training School (ACTS) – an online camp designed by JetBrains Academy and Constructor University to hone your skills for national and international contests. Why ACTS? Every day […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Gupaisova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graceful]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46893</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873239180/0/sethsblog~Graceful/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T09:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long after people forget the details, they’ll remember your kindness. There are many forms of hospitality, but resilience, goodwill and gratitude are often the ones that matter. PS here’s a short ebook I published almost a decade ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Cristian Schuszter on CERN]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/07/a-bootiful-podcast-cristian-schuszter-on-cern</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/07/a-bootiful-podcast-cristian-schuszter-on-cern"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRI-O: Applying seccomp profiles from OCI registries]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/07/cri-o-seccomp-oci-artifacts/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/07/cri-o-seccomp-oci-artifacts/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
Seccomp stands for secure computing mode and has been a feature of the Linux
kernel since version 2.6.12. It can be used to sandbox the privileges of a
process, restricting the calls it is able to make from userspace into the
kernel. Kubernetes lets you automatically apply seccomp profiles loaded onto a
node to your Pods and containers.
But distributing those seccomp profiles is a major challenge in Kubernetes,
because the JSON files have to be available on all nodes where a workload can
possibly run. Projects like the Security Profiles
Operator solve that problem by
running as a daemon within the cluster, which makes me wonder which part of that
distribution could be done by the container
runtime.
Runtimes usually apply the profiles from a local path, for example:
a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Indicates Success for Your Camunda POC?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102164</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/what-indicates-success-camunda-poc/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T20:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you measure and demonstrate success? Learn how to determine success for your Camunda proof of concept.
The post What Indicates Success for Your Camunda POC? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon RDS now supports io2 Block Express volumes for mission-critical database workloads]]></title>
        <id>e1f154044ec7ddbc580e087aadbcf76d2131d2a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-rds-now-supports-io2-block-express-volumes-for-mission-critical-database-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 7, 2024: Post updated to change GB to GiB. March 8, 2024: Post updated to reflect correct region availability. Today, I am pleased to announce the availability of Provisioned IOPS (PIOPS) io2 Block Express storage volumes for all database engines in Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS). Amazon RDS provides you the flexibility to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the newest Heroes of the year – March 2024]]></title>
        <id>1c28a1aa7d172c4f3ef6f586d0d873794d1f054c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-newest-heroes-of-the-year-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Heroes are inspirational thought leaders who go above and beyond to knowledge share in a variety of ways. You can find them speaking at local meetups, AWS Community Days, or even at re:Invent. And these technical experts are never done learning—they’re passionate about solving problems and creating content to enable the community to build […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Croissant: a metadata format for ML-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/croissant-metadata-format-for-ml-ready.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/croissant-metadata-format-for-ml-ready.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Omar Benjelloun, Software Engineer, Google Research, and Peter Mattson, Software Engineer, Google Core ML and President, MLCommons Association






Machine learning (ML) practitioners looking to reuse existing datasets to train an ML model often spend a lot of time understanding the data, making sense of its organization, or figuring out what subset to use as features. So much time, in fact, that progress in the field of ML is hampered by a fundamental obstacle: the wide variety of data representations. 





ML datasets cover a broad range of content types, from text and structured data to images, audio, and video. Even within datasets that cover the same types of content, every dataset has a unique ad hoc arrangement of files and data formats. This challenge reduces productivi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.18 GA improves enterprise reliability with Long-Term Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-18-ga-improves-enterprise-reliability-with-long-term-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-18-ga-improves-enterprise-reliability-with-long-term-support"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.18 improves enterprise reliability with Long-Term Support, fault-injection capabilities, and expanded Amazon ECS support for multi-runtime deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Enterprise Long-Term Support (LTS) improves operational efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-enterprise-long-term-support-lts-improves-operational-efficiency</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-enterprise-long-term-support-lts-improves-operational-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul Enterprise adds Long-Term Support (LTS) releases, reducing operational overhead and risk with extended maintenance and upgrade compatibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging trends in observability: GAI, AIOps, tools consolidation, and OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T17:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of the observability industry through the eyes of over 500 IT decision makers. Find out what’s top of mind for observability in 2024, from AIOps to GAI, tool consolidation and more from yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging trends in observability: GAI, AIOps, tools consolidation, and OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T17:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As technology evolution continues at its rapid pace, so does observability. Observability is becoming critical to driving positive business outcomes, and we wanted to understand how users are evaluating trends and their impact over the coming years. And while every organization approaches observability around its own unique needs, there are usually specific trends and shifts that the broader industry undergoes. 

Elastic® recently surveyed over 500 observability decision-makers around key topics in modern observability. Respondents were asked about the progress and benefits they are seeing in their observability initiatives, and the impact of generative AI and OpenTelemetry on observability. The survey, completed with Dimensional Research in January 2024, delivered some surprising results …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here's how merge queue transformed the way GitHub deploys changes to production at scale, so you can do the same for your organization.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/">How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-06-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>With this version, customers can choose how to best scale their security strategy, gain more control over deployments, and so much more.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-now-generally-available/">GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 is now generally available</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrich your Elasticsearch documents with Logstash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using a jdbc static filter connected to Elasticsearch might speed up your Logstash enrichment pipeline....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Pilato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrich your Elasticsearch documents with Logstash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[input {
  # Read all documents from Elasticsearch
  elasticsearch {
    hosts => ["${ELASTICSEARCH_URL}"]
    user => "elastic"
    password => "${ELASTIC_PASSWORD}"
    index => "kibana_sample_data_logs"
    docinfo => true
    ecs_compatibility => "disabled"
  }
}
filter {
  # Enrich every document with Elasticsearch
  elasticsearch {
    hosts => ["${ELASTICSEARCH_URL}"]
    user => "elastic"
    password => "${ELASTIC_PASSWORD}"
    index => "vip"
    query => "ip:%{[clientip]}"
    sort => "ip:desc"
    fields => {
      "[name]" => "[name]"
      "[vip]" => "[vip]"
    }
  }
  mutate { 
    remove_field => ["@version", "@timestamp"] 
  }
}
output {
  if [name] {
    # Write all modified documents to Elasticsearch
    elasticsearch {
      manage_template => false
      hosts => ["${E…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Pilato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic continues to innovate and grow through AWS Generative AI Competency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-aws-generative-ai-competency</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-aws-generative-ai-competency"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T15:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic has achieved AWS Generative AI Partner Competency by working closely with AWS. This recognition highlights Elastic’s deep technical expertise with generative AI in AWS and proven customer succ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy (Uday),Greg Johnson,Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic continues to innovate and grow through AWS Generative AI Competency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-aws-generative-ai-competency</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-aws-generative-ai-competency"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T15:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic® is excited to share the achievement of the AWS Generative AI Competency status, a testament to our unwavering commitment to equip our valued customers with cutting-edge search technologies. This prestigious accolade underscores our dedication to helping you deliver exceptional search experiences that meet your end users' expectations, all while safeguarding your proprietary data from undue exposure to large language models (LLMs).
The AWS Generative AI Competency is a mark of distinction reserved for AWS partners who have consistently exhibited deep technical expertise and a track record of customer satisfaction in deploying generative AI-driven solutions. Elastic's attainment of this credential required an extensive evaluation of our technical capabilities and a thorough examinat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy (Uday),Greg Johnson,Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[告知イラスト] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:2550689798289615231</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/2550689798289615231"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSAI Program and JetBrains Scholarship at Neapolis University Pafos]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=453660</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2024/03/06/csai-program-and-jetbrains-scholarship-at-neapolis-university-pafos/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T10:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on March 19, 2024, at 4:00 pm CET (3:00 pm UTC) for a livestream where we’ll introduce you to the Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence program team. Don’t miss this chance to ask questions about the admission process and find out how you can apply for a JetBrains scholarship. Meet our guests:  During […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Gupaisova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regressing to the mean all by yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44896</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873133262/0/sethsblog~Regressing-to-the-mean-all-by-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The mean” is the average. Another word for “mediocre.” When an organization gets big enough, by definition, it’s the average. When you have enough customers, they represent the population as a whole. If you find yourself seeking to serve the largest possible number of people, you’ve signed up to be average. Without a doubt, you’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bending pause times to your will with Generational ZGC]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/256629c9386b</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/bending-pause-times-to-your-will-with-generational-zgc-256629c9386b?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T01:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The surprising and not so surprising benefits of generations in the Z Garbage Collector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Function Calling in Java and Spring AI using the latest Mistral AI API]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/06/function-calling-in-java-and-spring-ai-using-the-latest-mistral-ai-api</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/06/function-calling-in-java-and-spring-ai-using-the-latest-mistral-ai-api"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Tzolov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: the Spring Authorization Server: durability of data]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/06/spring-tips-the-spring-authorization-server-durability-of-data</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/06/spring-tips-the-spring-authorization-server-durability-of-data"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earth/Venus Venn Diagram]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2903/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2903/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/earth_venus_venn_diagram.png" title="Actually, the fact that Mars is still orbiting safely over here means that it was technically an *Euler* apocalypse, not a Venn one." alt="Actually, the fact that Mars is still orbiting safely over here means that it was technically an *Euler* apocalypse, not a Venn one." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make a chatbot: Dos and don'ts for developers in an AI-driven world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-make-a-chatbot</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-make-a-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T19:22:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to develop a chatbot effectively with this guide, covering do’s and don'ts for chatbot developers and other useful tips....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make a chatbot: Dos and don'ts for developers in an AI-driven world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-make-a-chatbot</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-make-a-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T19:22:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every day the world is becoming increasingly powered by artificial intelligence. In fact, you’d struggle to find tech companies that have not announced AI integrations into their tech stack in one way or another. Cynics might say this is a passing phase, but the reason AI is so popular is that it’s a versatile set of capabilities that can help solve a lot of problems.
The most direct way AI can be utilized is in the form of a chatbot: a conversational interface that mimics human interaction, generating contextual responses based on what the user inputs. Sometimes these are text-based, such as the customer service bots you often see on websites or apps. And sometimes they’re voice-enabled, like Siri, Google Assistant, and Alexa. These specific examples only just scratch the surface of what …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insights and Timeline: Our Approach to Addressing the Recently Discovered Vulnerabilities in TeamCity On-Premises]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=453253</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2024/03/our-approach-addressing-recently-discovered-vulnerabilities-in-teamcity-on-premises/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T15:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a follow-up to the vulnerability announcement we published on March 4, 2024. It’s important that we properly communicate the timeline for fixing the CVE-2024-27198 and CVE-2024-27199 vulnerabilities from JetBrains’ side. All times below are expressed in CET. February 19 6:54 pm – Rapid7 reached out to us, saying they had discovered significant security […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Gallo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free data transfer out to internet when moving out of AWS]]></title>
        <id>75d716af79fb6ef0c02f33b4b7ca18cfd5dd4743</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/free-data-transfer-out-to-internet-when-moving-out-of-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You told us one of the primary reasons to adopt Amazon Web Services (AWS) is the broad choice of services we offer, enabling you to innovate, build, deploy, and monitor your workloads. AWS has continuously expanded its services to support virtually any cloud workload. It now offers over 200 fully featured services for compute, storage, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The positive auction]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48726</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873056405/0/sethsblog~The-positive-auction/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T12:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Sorry, I hit publish prematurely. I’ll be updating this and correcting the errors as we go.] In 2023, I developed a new idea that transforms an old way of doing commerce. In traditional auctions, there are rounds of bidding and the high bidder pays to get the prize. The last bid is the amount paid, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On building a cathedral]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48713</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873050204/0/sethsblog~On-building-a-cathedral/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T09:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re in need of a gathering place, a dry, functional, centrally located facility for your folks to meet, a cathedral is probably way more than you need. It’s far more expensive to build and maintain and not optimal in delivering what’s required. But what if this building needs to fill other functions as well? […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State of Spring Survey Is Back!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/05/the-state-of-spring-survey-is-back</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/05/the-state-of-spring-survey-is-back"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Minella</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - March 5th, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/05/this-week-in-spring-march-5th-2024</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/05/this-week-in-spring-march-5th-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping repository maintainer information accurate]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T21:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover how keeping repository maintainer information accurate through CODEOWNERS files and automating maintenance with tools like cleanowners fosters efficient collaboration and sustainable software projects.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/">Keeping repository maintainer information accurate</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolving from Rule-based Classifier: Machine Learning Powered Auto Remediation in Netflix Data…]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/039d5efd115b</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/evolving-from-rule-based-classifier-machine-learning-powered-auto-remediation-in-netflix-data-039d5efd115b?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Learning Pathway: Accelerate your business with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-04-github-copilot-learning-pathway-accelerate-your-business-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-github-copilot-learning-pathway-accelerate-your-business-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn what GitHub Copilot can help your business achieve in this expert-guided GitHub Learning Pathway, featuring insights from tech leaders at top organizations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-github-copilot-learning-pathway-accelerate-your-business-with-ai/">GitHub Copilot Learning Pathway: Accelerate your business with AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.13: GA of AI Assistant support for AWS Bedrock and enhancements for AI Assistant and SLO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-13-0"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability announces connectivity to AWS Bedrock for AI Assistant. Other enhancements include contextual awareness of the entry point into the AI Assistant and tech preview of editing and v...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Grabowski,Drew Post</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.13: GA of AI Assistant support for AWS Bedrock and enhancements for AI Assistant and SLO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-13-0"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic® Observability 8.13 announces general availability (GA) for AWS Bedrock support in Elastic AI Assistant, along with enhancements for the AI Assistant and SLOs.
AI Assistant enhancements 

Elastic AI Assistant support for AWS Bedrock

Contextual awareness of the entry point into AI Assistant

Performance improvements

Tech preview of editing and visualizing ES|QL queries from the AI Assistant

SLO enhancements

Ability to group your SLOs by tag, SLI indicator type, or status

Ability to triage burn rate alerts

Elastic Observability 8.13 is available now on Elastic Cloud — the only hosted Elasticsearch® offering to include all of the new features in this latest release. You can also download the Elastic Stack and our cloud orchestration products, Elastic Cloud Enterprise and Elastic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Grabowski,Drew Post</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — New models for Amazon Bedrock, CloudFront embedded POPs, and more — March 4, 2024]]></title>
        <id>f440c1bc8007c2c450a5b97f3269e968ed59221b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-models-for-amazon-bedrock-cloudfront-embedded-pops-and-more-march-4-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T16:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This has been a busy week – we introduced a new kind of Amazon CloudFront infrastructure, more efficient ways to analyze data stored on Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3), and new generative AI capabilities. Last week’s launches Here’s what got my attention: Amazon Bedrock – Mistral AI’s Mixtral 8x7B and Mistral 7B foundation models […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s Claude 3 Sonnet foundation model is now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>afa44e98fb3dea486d0fe36887411e429dd8794c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/anthropics-claude-3-sonnet-foundation-model-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T16:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September 2023, we announced a strategic collaboration with Anthropic that brought together their respective technology and expertise in safer generative artificial intelligence (AI), to accelerate the development of Anthropic’s Claude foundation models (FMs) and make them widely accessible to AWS customers. You can get early access to unique features of Anthropic’s Claude model in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering businesses with Airtel Managed Security Services and Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/airtel-managed-security-services-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/airtel-managed-security-services-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we'll unravel the key features, benefits, and unparalleled security solutions that Airtel brings to its B2B customers and explore the cutting-edge Airtel Managed Security Services, forti...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arvind Bhat,Neeraj Gupta,Puneet Duggal,Ravindra Ramnani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering businesses with Airtel Managed Security Services and Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/airtel-managed-security-services-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/airtel-managed-security-services-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of digital business, security is paramount. As businesses navigate the complexities of today's interconnected world, ensuring the safety of sensitive data and maintaining the integrity of operations becomes a top priority. Partner with Airtel, a trusted leader in telecommunications, and explore the cutting-edge Airtel Managed Security Services, fortified by the robust Elastic Security stack. In this blog, we'll unravel the key features, benefits, and unparalleled security solutions that Airtel brings to its B2B customers.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltda51aa555328c548/65e5fb31aca171625da00bc4/1-airtel-mdr-services.png,1-airtel-mdr-services.pngThe Elastic Security stack: A pillar of strength
Airtel's choice of the Elastic Secur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arvind Bhat,Neeraj Gupta,Puneet Duggal,Ravindra Ramnani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at APS 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/google-at-aps-2024.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/google-at-aps-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kate Weber and Shannon Leon, Google Research, Quantum AI Team




Today the 2024 March Meeting of the American Physical Society (APS) kicks off in Minneapolis, MN. A premier conference on topics ranging across physics and related fields, APS 2024 brings together researchers, students, and industry professionals to share their discoveries and build partnerships with the goal of realizing fundamental advances in physics-related sciences and technology. 



This year, Google has a strong presence at APS with a booth hosted by the Google Quantum AI team, 50+ talks throughout the conference, and participation in conference organizing activities, special sessions and events. Attending APS 2024 in person? Come visit Google’s Quantum AI booth to learn more about the exciting work we’re d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headwinds]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46873</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872990861/0/sethsblog~Headwinds/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T09:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it’s tough going and it feels fraught, it’s easy to imagine that the headwinds will never end. And yet, when all is going well and the wind is at our back, it’s tempting to imagine that this is the way it’s going to stay. Neither is true. The reason we see them as headwinds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Releases for February 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/04/spring-releases-for-february-2024</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/04/spring-releases-for-february-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Konicki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ice Core]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2902/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2902/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/ice_core.png" title="If you find an ash deposition layer from a year in which an eruption destroyed an island that had Camellia sinensis growing on it, you can make a Gone Island Ice_τ." alt="If you find an ash deposition layer from a year in which an eruption destroyed an island that had Camellia sinensis growing on it, you can make a Gone Island Ice_τ." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Becoming intentional about virtual meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45471</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872940299/0/sethsblog~Becoming-intentional-about-virtual-meetings/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A manual I recently read listed the “cons” of having a meeting virtually: To be accurate, every one of these points should have “so far” added. The videogame market is far bigger than the box office of Hollywood films. The people who play video games at home for hours at a time have no problem […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The weird math of halfway]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48706</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872889836/0/sethsblog~The-weird-math-of-halfway/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[6 times 1/2 doesn’t equal 3. It equals zero. We’re tempted to do a little less than we need to. Perhaps we’re busy, with too many options. Perhaps it’s resistance, pushing us to hold a little bit back. Whatever the reason, when we show up just a little, we get zero credit. The smallest viable […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI models now available on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>89d81f50ad915d63aec01b16bf9f82dd3a8cf534</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/mistral-ai-models-now-available-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T21:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, we announced that Mistral AI models are coming to Amazon Bedrock. In that post, we elaborated on a few reasons why Mistral AI models may be a good fit for you. Mistral AI offers a balance of cost and performance, fast inference speed, transparency and trust, and is accessible to a wide range […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The question book]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46857</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872825138/0/sethsblog~The-question-book/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the old days, companies had a suggestion box. It was immortalized in cartoons, but the idea that an employee could anonymously submit a suggestion to make things better is a first step in engagement. Some companies took this much further and paid employees for suggestions that generated profits. Digital communication and more open workplaces […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Support timeline announcement for Spring Framework 6.0.x and 5.3.x]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/01/support-timeline-announcement-for-spring-framework-6-0-x-and-5-3-x</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/01/support-timeline-announcement-for-spring-framework-6-0-x-and-5-3-x"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juergen Hoeller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Functions Catalog 5.0.0‐M1 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/01/spring-functions-catalog-5-0-0-m1-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/01/spring-functions-catalog-5-0-0-m1-available"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Bilan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Women of Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have employee resource groups aligned with a variety of shared identities that allow Elasticians to build a sense of community and belonging at work. Here, we meet Women of Elastic....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Women of Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Employee resource groups, or as we like to call them, Elastician resource groups, have been an informal part of Elastic’s culture since 2016. They started as Slack channels that any Elastician could join.
These ERGs were formalized in 2021 to ensure that the members would have structure, budget, and ultimately, a voice based on any dimension of diversity, allyship, and advocacy. This was an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion journey.
Our ERGs are aligned to shared identities, interests, affinities, or allyships. The goal is to create a community of people with something in common and to encourage sharing, learning, and networking. Each has visions and goals they are working towards besides building a sense of community and belonging.
Our Core ERGs
We have seven f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geographic Qualifiers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2901/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2901/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/geographic_qualifiers.png" title="'Thank you for the loveliest evening I've ever had...' [normal] '...east of the Mississippi.' [instant intrigue!]" alt="'Thank you for the loveliest evening I've ever had...' [normal] '...east of the Mississippi.' [instant intrigue!]" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on SIG Cloud Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/01/sig-cloud-provider-spotlight-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/01/sig-cloud-provider-spotlight-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Arujjwal Negi
One of the most popular ways developers use Kubernetes-related services is via cloud providers, but
have you ever wondered how cloud providers can do that? How does this whole process of integration
of Kubernetes to various cloud providers happen? To answer that, let's put the spotlight on SIG
Cloud Provider.
SIG Cloud Provider works to create seamless integrations between Kubernetes and various cloud
providers. Their mission? Keeping the Kubernetes ecosystem fair and open for all. By setting clear
standards and requirements, they ensure every cloud provider plays nicely with Kubernetes. It is
their responsibility to configure cluster components to enable cloud provider integrations.
In this blog of the SIG Spotlight series, Arujjwal Negi interviews
Michael McCune (Re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · February 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-29-game-bytes-february-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-game-bytes-february-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T19:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on! 🕹️</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-game-bytes-february-2024/">Game Bytes · February 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Kayla: A college student and open source ambassador]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-29-meet-kayla-a-college-student-and-open-source-ambassador/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-meet-kayla-a-college-student-and-open-source-ambassador/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From learner to mentor, Kayla, an All In for Students ambassador, has become an open source leader on her campus.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-meet-kayla-a-college-student-and-open-source-ambassador/">Meet Kayla: A college student and open source ambassador</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping secrets out of public repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-29-keeping-secrets-out-of-public-repositories/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-keeping-secrets-out-of-public-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>With push protection now enabled by default, GitHub helps open source developers safeguard their secrets, and their reputations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-keeping-secrets-out-of-public-repositories/">Keeping secrets out of public repositories</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppFabric support expands how HashiCorp Terraform Cloud integrates with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/appfabric-support-expands-how-hashicorp-terraform-cloud-integrates-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/appfabric-support-expands-how-hashicorp-terraform-cloud-integrates-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud now offers even more ways to connect, secure and provision infrastructure with AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Business Process and Why Should You Care]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101992</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/what-is-a-business-process-why-important/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are business processes, and why are they important? Learn how they work, types of business processes, & why well-orchestrated processes are critical.
The post What is a Business Process and Why Should You Care appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Roni Dover on Digma AI]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/29/a-bootiful-podcast-roni-dover-on-digma-ai</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/29/a-bootiful-podcast-roni-dover-on-digma-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customizing and fine-tuning LLMs: What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-28-customizing-and-fine-tuning-llms-what-you-need-to-know/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-28-customizing-and-fine-tuning-llms-what-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T18:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how your organization can customize its LLM-based solution through retrieval augmented generation and fine-tuning.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-28-customizing-and-fine-tuning-llms-what-you-need-to-know/">Customizing and fine-tuning LLMs: What you need to know</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: the Spring Authorization Server: securing SPAs and messaging flows]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/28/spring-tips-the-spring-authorization-server-securing-spas-and-messaging</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/28/spring-tips-the-spring-authorization-server-securing-spas-and-messaging"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X.509 certificate management with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/certificate-management-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/certificate-management-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll look at practical public key certificate management in HashiCorp Vault using dynamic secrets rotation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Delivered 408% ROI According to New Study]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101985</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/camunda-delivered-408-roi-new-study/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T16:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Study demonstrates significant benefits to adopting Camunda and provides a powerful customizable tool to help you understand the impact it can have on your organization.
The post Camunda Delivered 408% ROI According to New Study appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — .Net Runtime for AWS Lambda, PartyRock Hackathon, and more — February 26, 2024]]></title>
        <id>557c364821cd44b128215dafdb19f284275de1ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-net-runtime-for-aws-lambda-partyrock-hackathon-and-more-february-26-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Community AWS re:invent 2023 re:caps continue! Recently, I was invited to participate in one of these events hosted by the AWS User Group Kenya, and was able to learn and spend time with this amazing community. AWS User Group Kenya Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention during the previous […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp and Google Cloud announce GKE Autopilot support for Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-and-google-cloud-announce-gke-autopilot-support-for-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-and-google-cloud-announce-gke-autopilot-support-for-consul"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul is now supported in Google Cloud’s GKE Autopilot partner program, enabling deployment of Consul to GKE Autopilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing bpftop: Streamlining eBPF performance optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6a727c1ae2e5</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/announcing-bpftop-streamlining-ebpf-performance-optimization-6a727c1ae2e5?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T16:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jose Fernandez]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Region in Mexico is in the works]]></title>
        <id>1c1efeb64d8a5864b3db0f67a64b46b33d53cb69</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-region-in-mexico-is-in-the-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T14:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am happy to announce that we are working on an AWS Region in Mexico. This AWS Mexico (Central) Region will be the second Region in Latin America joining the AWS South America (São Paulo) Region and will give AWS customers the ability to run workloads and store data that must remain in-country. Mexico […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Insights to Action: Harnessing Camunda Optimize for Effective Development]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101840</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/insights-to-action-camunda-optimize-effective-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Samantha, as a developer and a new Camunda user, explored Camunda Optimize to enhance their development process.
The post From Insights to Action: Harnessing Camunda Optimize for Effective Development appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samantha Holstine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picking the Perfect Process for Your Camunda POC]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101958</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/picking-perfect-process-camunda-proof-of-concept/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picking the right process to use for your proof-of-concept is critical. In the next post in our series on creating a Camunda POC, learn how to choose the right one.
The post Picking the Perfect Process for Your Camunda POC appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI models coming soon to Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>308fb7192ffb87eae22e5e1a861fa7efc2aa36a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/mistral-ai-models-coming-soon-to-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI, an AI company based in France, is on a mission to elevate publicly available models to state-of-the-art performance. They specialize in creating fast and secure large language models (LLMs) that can be used for various tasks, from chatbots to code generation. We’re pleased to announce that two high-performing Mistral AI models, Mistral 7B […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VideoPrism: A foundational visual encoder for video understanding]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/videoprism-foundational-visual-encoder.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/videoprism-foundational-visual-encoder.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Long Zhao, Senior Research Scientist, and Ting Liu, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research




An astounding number of videos are available on the Web, covering a variety of content from everyday moments people share to historical moments to scientific observations, each of which contains a unique record of the world. The right tools could help researchers analyze these videos, transforming how we understand the world around us.

 

Videos offer dynamic visual content far more rich than static images, capturing movement, changes, and dynamic relationships between entities. Analyzing this complexity, along with the immense diversity of publicly available video data, demands models that go beyond traditional image understanding. Consequently, many of the approaches that be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Workflow Orchestration? Guide with Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101616</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/what-is-workflow-orchestration-guide-use-cases/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what workflow orchestration is, how it works, its benefits, and how you can get started using it today.
The post What is Workflow Orchestration? Guide with Use Cases appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A look into the Kubernetes Book Club]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/02/22/k8s-book-club/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/02/22/k8s-book-club/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
Learning Kubernetes and the entire ecosystem of technologies around it is not without its
challenges. In this interview, we will talk with Carlos Santana
(AWS) to learn a bit more about how he created the
Kubernetes Book Club, how it works, and
how anyone can join in to take advantage of a community-based learning experience.

Frederico Muñoz (FSM): Hello Carlos, thank you so much for your availability. To start with,
could you tell us a bit about yourself?
Carlos Santana (CS): Of course. My experience in deploying Kubernetes in production six
years ago opened the door for me to join Knative and then contribute to
Kubernetes through the Release Team. Working on upstream Kubernetes has been one of the best
experiences I've had in open-source. Over the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advances in private training for production on-device language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/advances-in-private-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/advances-in-private-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zheng Xu, Research Scientist, and Yanxiang Zhang, Software Engineer, Google




Language models (LMs) trained to predict the next word given input text are the key technology for many applications [1, 2]. In Gboard, LMs are used to improve users’ typing experience by supporting features like next word prediction (NWP), Smart Compose, smart completion and suggestion, slide to type, and proofread. Deploying models on users’ devices rather than enterprise servers has advantages like lower latency and better privacy for model usage. While training on-device models directly from user data effectively improves the utility performance for applications such as NWP and smart text selection, protecting the privacy of user data for model training is important. 









Gboard features powe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I use Boundary to build automation for live streams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-i-use-boundary-to-build-automation-for-live-streams</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-i-use-boundary-to-build-automation-for-live-streams"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how HashiCorp Developer Advocate Rosemary Wang uses HashiCorp Boundary on live streams to automate access to servers and record commands to build into future automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — AWS Control Tower new API, TLS 1.3 with API Gateway, Private Marketplace Catalogs, and more — February 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>b59bdf9a07666673edfdba0242f35b6312ab73cb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-control-tower-new-api-tls-1-3-with-api-gateway-private-marketplace-catalogs-and-more-february-19-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T18:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past week, our service teams have continued to innovate on your behalf, and a lot has happened in the Amazon Web Services (AWS) universe that I want to tell you about. I’ll also share about all the AWS Community events and initiatives that are happening around the world. Let’s dive in! Last week’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Pipelines deprecated tasks retirement schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68388</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-pipelines-deprecated-tasks-retirement-schedule/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T15:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Pipelines includes around 150 build & release tasks as well as many more task extensions. Various included tasks have multiple (major) versions bringing the total to over included 200 tasks.
The post Azure Pipelines deprecated tasks retirement schedule appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How NatWest Built a Center of Excellence to Improve Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101178</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/learn-how-natwest-built-a-center-of-excellence-to-improve-process-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how NatWest accelerated their process automation and orchestration, even as their usage grew, with a CoE using Camunda.
The post Learn How NatWest Built a Center of Excellence to Improve Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Modeling Faster with the New Simplified Modeling Canvas]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101261</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/model-faster-simplified-modeling-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T21:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out our cleaner and more intuitive modeling UI, coming later this month.
The post Start Modeling Faster with the New Simplified Modeling Canvas appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of SSH-RSA support for Azure Repos]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68534</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/ssh-rsa-deprecation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T17:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Repos provides two methods for users to access a git repository in Azure Repos – HTTPS and SSH. To use SSH, you need to create a key pair using one of the supported encryption methods. In the past we’ve been supporting only SSH-RSA and we’ve asked users to enable the SSH-RSA here.
The post End of SSH-RSA support for Azure Repos appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bohdan Janousek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform integrations with Wiz, Cisco, Palo Alto Networks, Couchbase, VMware, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-wiz-cisco-palo-alto-networks-couchbase-vmware</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-wiz-cisco-palo-alto-networks-couchbase-vmware"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[17 new Terraform integrations from 14 partners provide more options to automate and secure cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUnit Attachments Support for Publish Test Results]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67933</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/junit-attachments-support-for-publish-test-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T16:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve recently made some improvements to the Publish Test Results task in Azure Pipelines. This task now supports file attachments when publishing test results from a JUnit report.
The post JUnit Attachments Support for Publish Test Results appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Paquette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning the importance of training data under concept drift]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/learning-importance-of-training-data.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/learning-importance-of-training-data.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T18:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nishant Jain, Pre-doctoral Researcher, and Pradeep Shenoy, Research Scientist, Google Research




The constantly changing nature of the world around us poses a significant challenge for the development of AI models. Often, models are trained on longitudinal data with the hope that the training data used will accurately represent inputs the model may receive in the future. More generally, the default assumption that all training data are equally relevant often breaks in practice. For example, the figure below shows images from the CLEAR nonstationary learning benchmark, and it illustrates how visual features of objects evolve significantly over a 10 year span (a phenomenon we refer to as slow concept drift), posing a challenge for object categorization models. 








Sample ima…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault integrations with New Relic, Cloudbees, Coder, and more continue to strengthen customer security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-new-relic-cloudbees-coder-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-new-relic-cloudbees-coder-and-more"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight new HashiCorp Vault ecosystem integrations extend security use cases for customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DP-Auditorium: A flexible library for auditing differential privacy]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/dp-auditorium-flexible-library-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/dp-auditorium-flexible-library-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T22:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mónica Ribero Díaz, Research Scientist, Google Research





Differential privacy (DP) is a property of randomized mechanisms that limit the influence of any individual user’s information while processing and analyzing data. DP offers a robust solution to address growing concerns about data protection, enabling technologies across industries and government applications (e.g., the US census) without compromising individual user identities.  As its adoption increases, it’s important to identify the potential risks of developing mechanisms with faulty implementations. Researchers have recently found errors in the mathematical proofs of private mechanisms, and their implementations. For example, researchers compared six sparse vector technique (SVT) variations and found that only two…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[February patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68473</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/february-patches-for-azure-devops-server-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T21:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 Patch 2
The post February patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequential A/B Testing Keeps the World Streaming Netflix
Part 1: Continuous Data]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/cba6c7ed49df</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/sequential-a-b-testing-keeps-the-world-streaming-netflix-part-1-continuous-data-cba6c7ed49df?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T19:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lindon, Chris Sanden, Vache Shirikian, Yanjun Liu, Minal Mishra, Martin Tingley]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing SafeTest: A Novel Approach to Front End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/37f9f88c152d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/introducing-safetest-a-novel-approach-to-front-end-testing-37f9f88c152d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T16:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Moshe Kolodny]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workload identity federation for Azure deployments is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68479</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/workload-identity-federation-for-azure-deployments-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T07:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September, we announced the ability to configure Azure service connections that do not need a secret. Azure service connections that use workload identity federation are easier to manage and more secure. Many customers have adopted this feature and we’re excited to announce it is now generally available!
The post Workload identity federation for Azure deployments is now generally available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock now supports Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL and Cohere embedding models]]></title>
        <id>88d3cbd7b505e228dadab86f0501d5938c543301</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/knowledge-bases-for-amazon-bedrock-now-supports-amazon-aurora-postgresql-and-cohere-embedding-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T21:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During AWS re:Invent 2023, we announced the general availability of Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock. With a knowledge base, you can securely connect foundation models (FMs) in Amazon Bedrock to your company data for Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG). In my previous post, I described how Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock manages the end-to-end RAG workflow […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Happy Lunar New Year, IaC generator, NFL’s digital athlete, AWS Cloud Clubs, and more — February 12, 2024]]></title>
        <id>568484dcfa30bc001b0bf56c13972382e5ce2537</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-happy-lunar-new-year-iac-generator-nfls-digital-athlete-aws-cloud-clubs-and-more-february-12-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T20:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Lunar New Year! Wishing you a year filled with joy, success, and endless opportunities! May the Year of the Dragon bring uninterrupted connections and limitless growth 🐉 ☁️ In case you missed it, here’s outstanding news you need to know as you plan your year in early 2024. AWS was named as a Leader […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform gains upgrades for module tests, explorer, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-gains-upgrades-for-module-tests-explorer-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-gains-upgrades-for-module-tests-explorer-and-more"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest Terraform Cloud and Enterprise enhancements help users leverage high-quality modules, monitor their workspace health, minimize management overhead, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing HashiCorp tools in Alpine Linux containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/installing-hashicorp-tools-in-alpine-linux-containers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/installing-hashicorp-tools-in-alpine-linux-containers"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the installation and verification workflow for any Linux distribution that does not include HashiCorp software in its package repository.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>