<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-12-09T00:41:27.029Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-12-09T00:41:27.029Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.1 Improves Refactoring and the Cloud CLI Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-1-improves-refactoring-and-the-cloud-cli-experience</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-1-improves-refactoring-and-the-cloud-cli-experience"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now generally available, HashiCorp Terraform 1.1 offers easier and safer refactoring with ‘moved’ statements and improves the CLI for Terraform Cloud and Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General and Scalable Parallelization for Neural Networks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/general-and-scalable-parallelization.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/general-and-scalable-parallelization.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T19:30:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yuanzhong Xu and Yanping Huang, Software Engineers; Google Research, Brain Team  
Scaling neural networks, whether it be the amount of training data used, the model size or the computation being utilized,  has been critical for improving model quality in many real-world machine learning applications, such as computer vision, language understanding and neural machine translation. This, in turn, has motivated recent studies to scrutinize the factors that play a critical role in the success of scaling a neural model. Although increasing model capacity can be a sound approach to improve model quality, doing so presents a number of systems and software engineering challenges that must be overcome. For instance, in order to train large models that exceed the memory capacity of an accel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.13.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/spring-tools-4-13-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/spring-tools-4-13-0-released"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.13.0 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
updated to Eclipse 2021-12 release (including support for Java 17) (new and noteworthy)

  
builds for Apple Silicon platform (ARM M1) are available now from the regular download page


additional changes


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: STS 4.12.0 (for eclipse) *.yml can’t automatic prompt (#690)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: A StackOverFlow error for serializable Kotlin data class for autocompletion in the Eclipse IDE (#693)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Typescript comparison: An internal error occurred during: “LSP4E Linked Editing Highlight” (#700)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: js syntax highlight disabled by STS4 (#702)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Cannot copy/paste from ANSI console without escape sequences (#667) - fixed in ANSI Color Console project thanks to @mihnita


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


If you are updating an existing Spring Tools 4 installation, please make sure you to prepare your installation propertly this time: https://twitter.com/springtools4/status/1468587842838355980

Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2021-12-08-4130-release-incl-language-servers-version-1290

Spring Tools 4.13.1 is scheduled to be released in early Feb 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure communications end-to-end for Spring Boot apps – in Zero Trust environment]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/secure-communications-end-to-end-for-spring-boot-apps-in-zero-trust-environment</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/secure-communications-end-to-end-for-spring-boot-apps-in-zero-trust-environment"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secure communications end-to-end for Spring Boot apps - in a Zero Trust environment

Hi, Spring fans! Today, we are excited to announce the general availability of all the features to secure communications end-to-end for Spring Boot apps – in a Zero Trust environment. You can secure communications end-to-end or terminate transport level security at any communication point for Spring Boot apps. You can also automate the provisioning and configuration for all the Azure resources needed for securing communications.

Implementing secure communications as part of your solution architecture can be challenging. Many customers manually rotate their certificates or create their own solutions to automate provisioning and configuration. Even then, there is still data exfiltration risk – say unautho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the U.S. Government is scaling their cyber visibility practices with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-usgovernment-scaling-cybervisibility-elastic-cdm-cybersecurity-analyze-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-usgovernment-scaling-cybervisibility-elastic-cdm-cybersecurity-analyze-data"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Continuous Diagnostics and Mitigation (CDM) program has evolved from a cyber-hygiene initiative to a proactive response toolkit powered by the CDM Dashboard. Learn how it enables civilian agencies to analyze cyber risk at speed & scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Harmon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the U.S. Government is scaling their cyber visibility practices with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-usgovernment-scaling-cybervisibility-elastic-cdm-cybersecurity-analyze-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-usgovernment-scaling-cybervisibility-elastic-cdm-cybersecurity-analyze-data"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Amid a  growing network of endpoints to support telework and cloud-based applications, US federal civilian agencies are protecting government resilience and resources with a new Continuous Diagnostics and Mitigation Dashboard (CDM Dashboard) built on the Elastic search platform.
At a recent MeriTalk Cyber Central: Defenders Unite event, participants learned about how Elastic, in partnership with ECS, enables security operations center (SOC) teams with cyber visibility at speed and scale.
Historically, the CDM Dashboard was used by civilian agency cyber executives to get a read on cyber-hygiene compliance. Today, the dashboard enables civilian agency SOC teams to view massive amounts of data from disparate systems, query data where it resides, and share vulnerability and mitigation insigh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Harmon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snaring the Bad Folks]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/66726a1f4c80</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/snaring-the-bad-folks-66726a1f4c80?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T17:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project by Netflix’s Cloud Infrastructure Security team (Alex Bainbridge, Mike Grima, Nick Siow)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving GitHub code search]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-08-improving-github-code-search/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-08-improving-github-code-search/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T17:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are rolling out a technology preview for GitHub code search, the next iteration for search, discovery, and navigation on GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Gateway and gRPC]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/spring-cloud-gateway-and-grpc</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/08/spring-cloud-gateway-and-grpc"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting from version 3.1.0 as part of the Spring Cloud 2021.0.0 (aka Jubilee) release train, Spring Cloud Gateway included support for gRPC and HTTP/2.



We will introduce the basic concepts behind gRPC and how to configure it with two examples:





One that showcases how Spring Cloud Gateway can transparently re-route gRPC traffic without needing to know the proto definition and without having to modify our existing gRPC servers.



Another that showcases how we can create a custom filter in Spring Cloud Gateway to transform a JSON payload to a gRPC message.





Introduction to gRPC and HTTP/2



HTTP/2 makes our applications faster, simpler, and more robust. Reducing latency by enabling request and response
multiplexing, adding efficient compression of HTTP header…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Camunda Holiday Reading List 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=38076</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/12/the-camunda-holiday-reading-list-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T02:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a moment sit back and browse these interesting holiday reading recommendations from Camunda colleagues and our community.
The post The Camunda Holiday Reading List 2021 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.3 is generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-07-github-enterprise-server-3-3-is-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-07-github-enterprise-server-3-3-is-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T01:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server is now generally available for all customers. This release improves performance for CI/CD and for customers with large repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Quick AKS Cluster the Easy Way with Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/build-a-quick-aks-cluster-the-easy-way-with-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/build-a-quick-aks-cluster-the-easy-way-with-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Find providers in HashiCorp Terraform Cloud to help quickly spin up Kubernetes containers in Microsoft’s Azure Kubernetes Service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 7th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/07/this-week-in-spring-december-7th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/07/this-week-in-spring-december-7th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We’ve got a ton of stuff to dive into so let’s get goin’! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: DataStax’s Christopher Bradford on the Apache Cassandra operator for Kubernetes, K8ssandra

  
Accelerate Spring Apps to Cloud at Scale - Discussion with Azure Spring Cloud Customers

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.2.1 available now

  
Spring Cloud 2021.0.0 (codename Jubilee) Has Been Released

  
Spring Cloud Function 3.2 is out!

  
Spring Cloud Sleuth 3.1.0 is out!

  
Spring Tips: @Controllers and RSocket

  
JSON:API for Spring HATEOAS

  
Living with Kubernetes: 12 Commands to Debug Your Workloads

  
Hmm. I wonder what Mark Paluch’s cooking something awesome with the R2DBC SPI. I wonder what…?

  
Nice job, Github Actions! There’s now integrated sigstore support! Safeguard your containers with new container signing capability in GitHub Actions

  
Pull Request #762 adds Knative for incubation at CNCF - hurray!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Vision Transformer Efficiency and Accuracy by Learning to Tokenize]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/improving-vision-transformer-efficiency.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/improving-vision-transformer-efficiency.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T17:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Michael Ryoo, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google and Anurag Arnab, Research Scientist, Google Research 
Transformer models consistently obtain state-of-the-art results in computer vision tasks, including object detection and video classification. In contrast to standard convolutional approaches that process images pixel-by-pixel, the Vision Transformers (ViT) treat an image as a sequence of patch tokens (i.e., a smaller part, or “patch”, of an image made up of multiple pixels). This means that at every layer, a ViT model recombines and processes patch tokens based on relations between each pair of tokens, using multi-head self-attention. In doing so, ViT models have the capability to construct a global representation of the entire image. 
At the input-level, the tokens are fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Sleuth 3.1.0 is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/07/spring-cloud-sleuth-3-1-0-is-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/07/spring-cloud-sleuth-3-1-0-is-out"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of the Spring Cloud 2021.0.0 (aka Jubilee) release train we’re more than happy to announce the general availability of Spring Cloud Sleuth 3.1.0. In this blog post we’ll describe the most notable released features.

Here is the list of most notable features, we’ll elaborate on them in the subsequent parts of this post.


  
JDBC #1930

  
Tomcat Valve #1329

  
Spring Vault #1952

  
Automatic tag table generation for documentation #1950

  
Spring Cloud Deployer #1947

  
R2DBC #1524

  
Kafka #2013 and Reactor Kafka #1708

  
Spring TX #1941

  
Spring Batch #1904

  
RSocket #1677

  
Spring Cloud Task #1903

  
Spring Cloud Config #1915

  
Spring Cloud CircuitBreaker Reactive #1910

  
Cassandra #1974

  
Spring Session #1961

  
Spring Security #201…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrolling all npm publishers in enhanced login verification and next steps for two-factor authentication enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-07-enrolling-npm-publishers-enhanced-login-verification-two-factor-authentication-enforcement/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-07-enrolling-npm-publishers-enhanced-login-verification-two-factor-authentication-enforcement/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're introducing enhanced login verification to the npm registry, and we will begin a staged rollout to maintainers beginning Dec 7.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 7.16: Streamlined data integrations drive results that matter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-16-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-16-0"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the general availability of new Elastic Agent integrations and deeper integration with ServiceNow ITSM, ITOM, and SecOps, Elastic 7.16 extends visibility into complex cloud-native services and streamlines workflows to drive results that matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Courcy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 7.16: Streamlined data integrations drive results that matter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-16-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-16-0"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are pleased to announce the general availability of Elastic 7.16, a release that brings a broad set of new capabilities to the Elastic Search Platform (including Elasticsearch and Kibana) and its three built-in solutions — Elastic Enterprise Search, Elastic Observability, and Elastic Security.
Elastic 7.16 streamlines the process of getting any type of data, from any source, into the Elastic Search Platform. The release extends visibility into complex and distributed cloud-native services with dozens of prebuilt Elastic Agent data integrations, observability tooling for continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) pipelines, two newly certified ServiceNow applications, and native data integration between Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Elastic Cloud.
In addition, the unified u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Courcy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 7.16: Adaptive relevance and Kibana UI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-16-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-16-0"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights for Elastic Enterprise Search 7.16 include adaptive relevance for curated content suggestions, based on collected analytics, i.e., what your users have been searching for, plus, a unified Enterprise Search management interface within Kibana.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Meiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 7.16: Adaptive relevance and Kibana UI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-16-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-16-0"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The 7.16 release of Elastic Enterprise Search features curations powered by adaptive relevance, the general availability (GA) of the unified management interface in Kibana, and a Google Cloud Firestore extension. These new features, plus a host of others, give users more power and flexibility than ever to create, tune, and manage their search experience:

Get automatic recommendations for suggested results based on what real users are searching for
Enjoy a single interface to manage search experiences, right next to all of the other tools inside Kibana
Use the new Google Cloud Firestore extension to build premium search experiences with Elastic App Search
Take advantage of more detailed performance monitoring, additional authentication mechanisms, and new API endpoints
,
Elastic Enterpri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Meiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 7.16: Ad hoc analytics and CI/CD pipeline visibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-16-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-16-0"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 7.16 introduces powerful ad hoc analytics, further extends one-click visibility into complex environments, including build and deployment tools in CI/CD pipelines, and a new native data integration with AWS FireLens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 7.16: Ad hoc analytics and CI/CD pipeline visibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-16-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-16-0"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Observability 7.16 introduces curated data exploration views for ad hoc analysis and further extends visibility into complex and distributed systems with the general availability (GA) of dozens of prebuilt Elastic Agent data integrations, observability tooling for continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) pipelines, and a new native data source integration with Amazon Web Services (AWS) FireLens.
These new features allow customers to:

Conduct ad hoc investigations to analyze “unknown unknowns” for observability
Frictionlessly ingest data from complex, cloud-native environments
Build and deploy faster and automate more reliably with visibility into CI/CD pipelines



Elastic Observability 7.16 is available now on Elastic Cloud — the only hosted Elasticsearch offering…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch, Kibana, and Elastic Cloud 7.16: Integrations and more actionable insights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-7-16-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-7-16-0"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Integrations make it easy to collect, store, search and analyze all of your data securely and at scale. Ingest data easily, explore from an intuitive UI, and make your data actionable and streamline workflows across teams and systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeline Tan,Bianca Laurendine,George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch, Kibana, and Elastic Cloud 7.16: Integrations and more actionable insights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-7-16-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-7-16-0"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
With the release of Elastic 7.16, it’s easier than ever to collect, store, search, and analyze data securely and at scale, no matter the use case. Explore third-party solutions like ServiceNow and cloud-native integrations like Amazon Web Services (AWS) FireLens to make your data actionable and streamline workflows across teams and systems.
In addition, 7.16 improves performance and maximizes resource consumption with enhancements to Elasticsearch, gives users the ability to add more context to Kibana visualizations, and more.
Ready to roll up your sleeves and get started? We have the links you need:

Try out the new features on Elastic Cloud 
Download the latest versions of Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes
Dig deeper in the release notes: Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeline Tan,Bianca Laurendine,George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 7.16: Accelerate SecOps with the most powerful Elastic Security yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-16-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-16-0"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 7.16 adds new data integrations for Elastic Agent, expanded malicious behavior protections, memory threat protection for every OS, and enhanced ECS support for Osquery Manager. Plus, new and enhanced ServiceNow workflow integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 7.16: Accelerate SecOps with the most powerful Elastic Security yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-16-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-16-0"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In Elastic Security 7.16, multiple new out-of-the-box data integrations for Elastic Agent streamline data ingestion and normalization, powering security operations. The release also introduces full production support for several existing data integrations.
Version 7.16 introduces an expanded set of malicious behavior protections, addressing methods related to initial access, privilege escalation, and defense evasion. It also brings memory threat protection to macOS and Linux, and enhances ECS support for Osquery Manager.
Plus, power cross-org collaboration with new and enhanced workflow integrations for ServiceNow.
Let’s jump in.
Amplify visibility to accelerate detection and response
Expansive environmental activity and context powers the work of modern security teams, but onboarding da…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to invite teammates to access and manage Elastic Cloud deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/leverage-multi-user-access-on-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/leverage-multi-user-access-on-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to invite other members of your organization to collaborate with you and manage your Elastic Cloud deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Kushmaro,Bianca Laurendine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to invite teammates to access and manage Elastic Cloud deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/leverage-multi-user-access-on-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/leverage-multi-user-access-on-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Did you know you can invite your co-workers to access and manage your organization’s Elastic Cloud deployments? When you send teammates an invitation, they can create their own credentials to gain access. 
Whether you are a software developer adding search to an application or an IT professional providing Workplace Search to knowledge workers, you can invite your co-workers. This also applies to DevOps and SREs using Elastic Observability, as well as information security professionals protecting their IT investments with Elastic Security. 
Whichever cloud you prefer, AWS, Google Cloud, or Microsoft Azure, we’ve got you covered. Multi-user access enables your colleagues to create, deploy, and operate Elastic Cloud deployments in your account. Plus, you can view an activity log trail that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Kushmaro,Bianca Laurendine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new: an introduction to automation mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.1-automation-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.1-automation-mesh"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the most recent Ansible Automation Platform 2.1 release announced December 2, 2021, we are excited to debut one of the most long-awaited features of the release: automation mesh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic deepens workflow integrations with ServiceNow to improve team productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-integrations-with-servicenow-itsm-sir-itom</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-integrations-with-servicenow-itsm-sir-itom"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic deepens integrations with ServiceNow ITSM, SIR, and ITOM streamlining observability and security workflows and enhancing practitioner productivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Francoeur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic deepens workflow integrations with ServiceNow to improve team productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-integrations-with-servicenow-itsm-sir-itom</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-integrations-with-servicenow-itsm-sir-itom"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In our latest release, we have doubled down on our partnership with ServiceNow®, streamlining observability and security workflows while also improving practitioner productivity.
In addition to deepening existing integrations with the Now Platform® through new extension points for Elastic cases and alerts, we’ve added an integration that streamlines event management for IT operations workflows.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt1f3847e0a987ee9c/619ea9a83865bf22bd95f1f7/screenshot-servicenow-security-case-management-final.png,screenshot-servicenow-security-case-management-final.png,
In 7.16, administrators of Elastic deployments can access two certified applications in the ServiceNow Store that optimize for more efficient and productive IT Service Management (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Francoeur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write more secure code with the OWASP Top 10 Proactive Controls]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-06-write-more-secure-code-owasp-top-10-proactive-controls/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-06-write-more-secure-code-owasp-top-10-proactive-controls/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T22:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This lesser-known OWASP project aims to help developers prevent vulnerabilities from being introduced in the first place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at NeurIPS 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/google-at-neurips-2021.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/google-at-neurips-2021.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T19:38:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jaqui Herman and Cat Armato, Program Managers 
This week marks the beginning of the 35th annual Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS 2021), the biggest machine learning conference of the year. NeurIPS 2021 will be held virtually and includes invited talks, demonstrations and presentations of some of the latest in machine learning research. This year, NeurIPS also announced a new Datasets and Benchmarks track, which will include publications, talks, posters, and discussions related to this research area.   
 Google will have a strong presence with more than 170 accepted papers, additionally contributing to and learning from the broader academic research community via talks, posters, workshops, and tutorials. You can learn more about our work being presented…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safeguard your containers with new container signing capability in GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-06-safeguard-container-signing-capability-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-06-safeguard-container-signing-capability-actions/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T17:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub has partnered with the OpenSSF and Project Sigstore to add container image signing to our default “Publish Docker Container” workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confluent, JFrog, and ServiceNow Integrations Highlight Additions to the Vault Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/confluent-jfrog-servicenow-integrations-highlight-additions-vault-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/confluent-jfrog-servicenow-integrations-highlight-additions-vault-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A pair of new HCP Vault verified integrations and ten new self-managed HashiCorp Vault integrations add to the existing list of more than 100 partner Vault integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debunking]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2551/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2551/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/debunking.png" title="Mark Zuckerberg has only neutral feelings toward Peppa Pig, who he understands is a fictional character, and he blames the coronavirus pandemic on other factors." alt="Mark Zuckerberg has only neutral feelings toward Peppa Pig, who he understands is a fictional character, and he blames the coronavirus pandemic on other factors." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · November 2021 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-03-release-radar-nov-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-03-release-radar-nov-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T22:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The end of the year is getting closer, and our communities are busy working away on their projects. While you&#8217;ve all been busy maintaining open source projects and shipping releases, we&#8217;ve created a new open]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting and blocking unknown KnownDlls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-block-unknown-knowndlls-windows-acl-hardening-attacks-cache-poisoning-escalation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-block-unknown-knowndlls-windows-acl-hardening-attacks-cache-poisoning-escalation"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second in a two-part series discussing a still-unpatched userland Windows privilege escalation. The exploit enables attackers to perform highly privileged actions that typically require a kernel driver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriel Landau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting and blocking unknown KnownDlls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-block-unknown-knowndlls-windows-acl-hardening-attacks-cache-poisoning-escalation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-block-unknown-knowndlls-windows-acl-hardening-attacks-cache-poisoning-escalation"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
This is the second in a two-part series discussing a still-unpatched userland Windows privilege escalation. The exploit enables attackers to perform highly privileged actions that typically require a kernel driver.
Part 1 of this blog series showed how to block these attacks via ACL hardening. If you haven’t already, please read the first part of this series, because it lays an important foundation for this article. Interested readers can also check out the excellent Unknown Known DLLs ... and other Code Integrity Trust Violations for a deeper understanding of code integrity and protected processes.
In part 2 of this series, I’ll show how to detect these attacks in real time, gaining greater visibility into your environment.
Exploit refresher
At a high level, the exploit, previously desc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriel Landau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.12.03]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62907</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-12-03/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T11:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! I am Jay Gordon and every week I try to bring you the latest updates from around the DevOps on Azure community. If you have a post you’d like to have me include, I am always listening. You can reach out on Twitter or LinkedIn and I will be sure to share your latest post with the community.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.12.03 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第199話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496631846058</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496631846058"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: DataStax's Christopher Bradford on the Apache Cassandra operator for Kubernetes, K8ssandra]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/a-bootiful-podcast-datastax-s-christopher-bradford-on-the-apache-cassandra-operator-for-kubernetes-k8ssandra</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/a-bootiful-podcast-datastax-s-christopher-bradford-on-the-apache-cassandra-operator-for-kubernetes-k8ssandra"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to DataStax’s Christopher Bradford on the Apache Cassandra operator for Kubernetes, K8ssandra.


  
KubeCon Talk blogpost part 1

  
KubeCon Talk blogpost part 2

  
We Pushed Helm to the Limit, then Built a Kubernetes Operator 

  
A Case for Databases on Kubernetes from a Former Skeptic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webb]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2550/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2550/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/webb.png" title="Each one contains a chocolate shaped like a famous spacecraft and, for the later numbers, a pamphlet on managing anxiety." alt="Each one contains a chocolate shaped like a famous spacecraft and, for the later numbers, a pamphlet on managing anxiety." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.0 (codename Jubilee) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-codename-jubilee-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-codename-jubilee-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce the General Availability of the Spring Cloud 2021.0 Release Train, codename Jubilee, is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2021.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0 Release Train

2021.0.0 is compatible with Spring Boot 2.6.1

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Support for per LoadBalancer configuration properties (added as well to Gateway, Contract and OpenFeign).


Spring Cloud Config


  
Integration with AWS Secrets Manager, AWS Parameter Store and GCP Secret Manager.


Spring Cloud Function


  
Support for gRPC, FunctionCatalog via actuator endpoint, AWS improvements, Clo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Function 3.2 is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/spring-cloud-function-3-2-is-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/02/spring-cloud-function-3-2-is-out"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.0 is finally out and with it you have Spring Cloud Function 3.2

While the full list of features, enhancements and bug fixes is available here, I’d like to call out few of them in this post and provide some details.
gRPC Support

In addition to an already existing support for invoking function via AWS Lambda, RSocket, Spring Cloud Stream etc., Spring Cloud Function now allows you to invoke function via gRPC.
Two ways to benefit from it. 
Spring Message

Given the wide adaption of Spring Messaging, one way of benefiting from gRPC support is by embracing Spring’s Message.
Spring Cloud Function provides GrpcSpringMessage schema modeled after Spring’s Message. It is internally converted to Spring Message to benefit from all of the existing support for Spring Messaging. 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluating Syntactic Abilities of Language Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/evaluating-syntactic-abilities-of.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/evaluating-syntactic-abilities-of.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jason Wei, AI Resident and Dan Garrette, Research Scientist, Google Research  
In recent years, pre-trained language models, such as BERT and GPT-3, have seen widespread use in natural language processing (NLP). By training on large volumes of text, language models acquire broad knowledge about the world, achieving strong performance on various NLP benchmarks. These models, however, are often opaque in that it may not be clear why they perform so well, which limits further hypothesis-driven improvement of the models. Hence, a new line of scientific inquiry has arisen: what linguistic knowledge is contained in these models? 
 While there are many types of linguistic knowledge that one may want to investigate, a topic that provides a strong basis for analysis is the subject–verb ag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – FreeRTOS Extended Maintenance Plan for Up to 10 Years]]></title>
        <id>7d40e463227e81077de707dea4aea2845e47e6b2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-freertos-extended-maintenance-plan-for-up-to-10-years/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last AWS re:Invent 2020, we announced FreeRTOS Long Term Support (LTS) that offers a more stable foundation than standard releases, as manufacturers deploy and later update devices in the field. FreeRTOS is an open source, real-time operating system for microcontrollers that makes small, low-power edge devices easy to program, deploy, secure, connect, and manage. In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS re:Post – A Reimagined Q&A Experience for the AWS Community]]></title>
        <id>52c5a244baa151c58d56f8df62c2df1d96c3c3b5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-repost-a-reimagined-qa-experience-for-the-aws-community/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet is an excellent resource for well-intentioned guidance and answers. However, it can sometimes be hard to tell if what you’re reading is, in fact, advice you should follow. Also, some users have a preference toward using a single, trusted online community rather than the open internet to provide them with reliable, vetted, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Sustainability Pillar for AWS Well-Architected Framework]]></title>
        <id>f1fac23aefd780d5623728bb3569f0b331f5fa54</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/sustainability-pillar-well-architected-framework/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Well-Architected Framework has been helping AWS customers improve their cloud architectures since 2015. The framework consists of design principles, questions, and best practices across multiple pillars: Operational Excellence, Security, Reliability, Performance Efficiency, and Cost Optimization. Today we are introducing a new Sustainability Pillar to help organizations learn, measure, and improve their workloads using […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Casalboni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of Construct Hub and AWS Cloud Development Kit Version 2]]></title>
        <id>baeea21fcb7d874432a757c3ba44fce9acd8b91b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-general-availability-of-construct-hub-and-aws-cloud-development-kit-version-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T17:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to announce that both the Construct Hub and AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) version 2 are now generally available (GA). The AWS CDK is an open-source framework that simplifies working with cloud resources using familiar programming languages: C#, TypeScript, Java, Python, and Go (in developer preview). Within their applications, developers create […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Azure Static Web Apps in Azure Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62906</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/automating-azure-static-web-apps-in-azure-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T16:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Static Web Apps were launched earlier in 2021 and out of the box they had the capability to integrate your existing repository and deploy your Static Web App from Azure DevOps. You can reference the full getting started guide for the end-to-end deployment setup.
The post Automating Azure Static Web Apps in Azure Pipelines appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use New Amazon EC2 M1 Mac Instances to Build & Test Apps for iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple Watch, and Apple TV]]></title>
        <id>699ccea03204f481929c95c6a5aa2c90f42d3171</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-amazon-ec2-m1-mac-instances-to-build-test-macos-ios-ipados-tvos-and-watchos-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T16:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year at AWS re:Invent, Jeff Barr wrote about the exciting availability of Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) Mac instances. Today, we’re announcing the preview of a new EC2 M1 Mac instance. The introduction of EC2 Mac instances brought the flexibility, scalability, and cost benefits of AWS to all Apple developers. EC2 Mac instances […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Behind the IT Transformation of Covéa Insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=37914</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/12/the-secret-behind-the-it-transformation-of-covea-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get details on how solutions built with Camunda enabled Covea to organize data more effectively and create an even-stronger user experience.
The post The Secret Behind the IT Transformation of Covéa Insurance appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce the general availability of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1. This is the follow-on to the Ansible Automation Platform 2.0 Early Access released this summer, and announced at AnsibleFest 2021. Red Ansible Automation Platform 2.1 introduces major features that allow customers to onboard more easily with even more flexible automation architectures and use cases. Ansible Automation Platform 2.1 is the culmination of many years of reimagining how enterprise automators automate for today and tomorrow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 62 – Supercharge your Java Apps on Azure with @rorypreddy]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62880</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-62-supercharge-your-java-apps-on-azure-with-rorypreddy/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T10:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a short break for some Microsoft streaming events, AzureFunBytes returns to LearnTV for another fun conversation about the products, people, and services that make for a delightful Azure experience.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 62 – Supercharge your Java Apps on Azure with @rorypreddy appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Site-to-Site Connectivity with AWS Direct Connect SiteLink]]></title>
        <id>55ab2625372c8e72c8276741e6a5057f4a9040ab</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-site-to-site-connectivity-with-aws-direct-connect-sitelink/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are launching AWS Direct Connect SiteLink, a new capability of AWS Direct Connect that lets you create connections between your on-premises networks through the AWS global network backbone. Until today, when you needed direct connectivity between your data centers or branch offices, you had to rely on public internet or expensive and hard-to-deploy fixed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Enhanced Dead-letter Queue Management Experience for Amazon SQS Standard Queues]]></title>
        <id>8644204a7230b8ce822a50054999a4a95a9027bb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/enhanced-dlq-management-sqs/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:29:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hundreds of thousands of customers use Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS) to build message-based applications to decouple and scale microservices, distributed systems, and serverless apps. When a message cannot be successfully processed by the queue consumer, you can configure SQS to store it in a dead-letter queue (DLQ). As a software developer or architect, you’d […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Casalboni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Address Management and Auditing at Scale with Amazon VPC IP Address Manager]]></title>
        <id>91077886bb96f2e3b9a037e2c2d884a56171b3cb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/network-address-management-and-auditing-at-scale-with-amazon-vpc-ip-address-manager/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:25:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing, monitoring, and auditing IP address allocation for at-scale networks, as the growth in cloud workloads and connected devices continues at a rapid pace, is a complex, time-consuming, and potentially error-prone task. Traditionally, network administrators have resorted to using combinations of spreadsheets, home-grown tools, and scripts to track address assignments across multiple accounts, virtual private […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon VPC Network Access Analyzer]]></title>
        <id>82f2efc595c375405b34fa67c8fc70587c4a2d27</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-vpc-network-access-analyzer/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a member of your organization’s networking, cloud operations, or security teams, you are going to love this new feature. The new Amazon VPC Network Access Analyzer helps you identify network configurations that lead to unintended network access. As you will see in a moment, it will point out ways that you can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Shield Advanced Update – Automatic Application Layer DDoS Mitigation]]></title>
        <id>25af4ed6c26e6c324812d06b1d417d07416f6636</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-shield-advanced-update-automatic-application-layer-ddos-mitigation/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2016, we launched AWS Shield, a managed Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection service that safeguards applications running on AWS. AWS Shield provides always-on detection and automatic inline mitigations that minimize application downtime and latency without needing to contact AWS Support. There are two tiers of AWS Shield: Standard and Advanced. All AWS customers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: November 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-01-github-availability-report-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-01-github-availability-report-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T20:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November, we experienced one incident resulting in significant impact and degraded state of availability for multiple services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RLDS: An Ecosystem to Generate, Share, and Use Datasets in Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/rlds-ecosystem-to-generate-share-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/12/rlds-ecosystem-to-generate-share-and.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sabela Ramos, Software Engineer and Léonard Hussenot, Student Researcher, Google Research, Brain Team 
Most reinforcement learning (RL) and sequential decision making algorithms require an agent to generate training data through large amounts of interactions with their environment to achieve optimal performance. This is highly inefficient, especially when generating those interactions is difficult, such as collecting data with a real robot or by interacting with a human expert. This issue can be mitigated by reusing external sources of knowledge, for example, the RL Unplugged Atari dataset, which includes data of a synthetic agent playing Atari games.  
 However, there are very few of these datasets and a variety of tasks and ways of generating data in sequential decision making …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Scholarship Program Helps Underrepresented and Underserved Students Prep for Careers in AI and ML]]></title>
        <id>36dd9d3bf20f530368ca29c6cf90d04d91dc31f4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-scholarship-program-helps-underrepresented-and-underserved-students-prep-for-careers-in-ai-and-ml/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a woman working in information technology (IT) for many years, it has always been close to my heart to challenge long-standing gender stereotypes and inspire more young learners to consider a career in tech. With artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) defining the future of technology, this future also depends on diverse representation. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now in Preview – Amazon SageMaker Studio Lab, a Free Service to Learn and Experiment with ML]]></title>
        <id>1927d6ce6648e935cc728859b8d14b9d628b7745</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-in-preview-amazon-sagemaker-studio-lab-a-free-service-to-learn-and-experiment-with-ml/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our mission at AWS is to make machine learning (ML) more accessible. Through many conversations over the past years, I learned about barriers that many ML beginners face. Existing ML environments are often too complex for beginners, or too limited to support modern ML experimentation. Beginners want to quickly start learning and not worry about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon SageMaker Inference Recommender]]></title>
        <id>57696c6a1a2c6cfda41e948287037f5b21ead2e8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-sagemaker-inference-recommender/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re pleased to announce Amazon SageMaker Inference Recommender — a brand-new Amazon SageMaker Studio capability that automates load testing and optimizes model performance across machine learning (ML) instances. Ultimately, it reduces the time it takes to get ML models from development to production and optimizes the costs associated with their operation. Until now, no […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean M. Tracey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Introducing SageMaker Training Compiler]]></title>
        <id>9062a6f94e60c2751154482eb447547bf95806bb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-introducing-sagemaker-training-compiler/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re pleased to announce Amazon SageMaker Training Compiler, a new Amazon SageMaker capability that can accelerate the training of deep learning (DL) models by up to 50%. As DL models grow in complexity, so too does the time it can take to optimize and train them. For example, it can take 25,000 GPU-hours to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean M. Tracey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Create and Manage EMR Clusters and Spark Jobs with Amazon SageMaker Studio]]></title>
        <id>15e2986b6ad7e2ed810c28b51458fd55c9ec0c01</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-create-and-manage-emr-clusters-and-spark-jobs-with-amazon-sagemaker-studio/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re very excited to offer three new enhancements to our Amazon SageMaker Studio service. As of now, users of SageMaker Studio can create, terminate, manage, discover, and connect to Amazon EMR clusters running within a single AWS account and in shared accounts across an organization—all directly from SageMaker Studio. Furthermore, SageMaker Studio Notebook users […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean M. Tracey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using ChatOps to help Actions on-call engineers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-12-01-using-chatops-to-help-actions-on-call-engineers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-12-01-using-chatops-to-help-actions-on-call-engineers/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can multiply the impact of your domain experts by building their common workflows into ChatOps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth Plus]]></title>
        <id>90908fa995f0be9abc2109eedc874cd9fc8553ef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-sagemaker-ground-truth-plus/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re pleased to announce the latest service in the Amazon SageMaker suite that will make labeling datasets easier than ever before. Ground Truth Plus is a turn-key service that uses an expert workforce to deliver high-quality training datasets fast, and reduces costs by up to 40 percent. The Challenges of Machine Learning Model Creation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean M. Tracey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate Spring Apps to Cloud at Scale - Discussion with Azure Spring Cloud Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/01/accelerate-spring-apps-to-cloud-at-scale-discussion-with-azure-spring-cloud-customers</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/01/accelerate-spring-apps-to-cloud-at-scale-discussion-with-azure-spring-cloud-customers"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! I love the Azure Spring Cloud platform - jointly developed with the Spring team and Microsoft - and I’m not alone! So do its users! Check out this panel discussion moderated by Adib Sakali and Asir Selvasingh with Morgan Stanley, Bosch, and Digital Realty Trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New DynamoDB Table Class – Save Up To 60% in Your DynamoDB Costs]]></title>
        <id>0ca1e66606cb25277f37424382ba8f4fc650c532</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-dynamodb-table-class-save-up-to-60-in-your-dynamodb-costs/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing Amazon DynamoDB Standard-Infrequent Access (DynamoDB Standard-IA). A new table class for DynamoDB that reduces storage costs by 60 percent compared to existing DynamoDB Standard tables, and that delivers the same performance, durability, and scaling. Nowadays, many customers are moving their infrequently accessed data between DynamoDB and Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon RDS Custom for SQL Server Is Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>0a304ebf551106001072e05ee8faa86c88be77c3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-rds-custom-for-sql-server-is-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 26, 2021, we launched Amazon RDS Custom for Oracle, a managed database service for applications that require customization of the underlying operating system and database environment. RDS Custom lets you access and customize your database server host and operating system, for example, by applying special patches and changing the database software settings to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon DevOps Guru for RDS to Detect, Diagnose, and Resolve Amazon Aurora-Related Issues using ML]]></title>
        <id>0babac98dfd335531b1699c60e9d6bf5ef545aec</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-devops-guru-for-rds-to-detect-diagnose-and-resolve-amazon-aurora-related-issues-using-ml/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing Amazon DevOps Guru for RDS, a new capability for Amazon DevOps Guru. It allows developers to easily detect, diagnose, and resolve performance and operational issues in Amazon Aurora. Hundreds of thousands of customers nowadays are using Amazon Aurora because it is highly available, scalable, and durable. But as applications grow in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.2.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/01/spring-authorization-server-0-2-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/01/spring-authorization-server-0-2-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.2.1.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




compile 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.2.1'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the sample to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues |  ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: @Controllers and RSocket]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/01/spring-tips-controllers-and-rsocket</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/12/01/spring-tips-controllers-and-rsocket"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment of Spring Tips (@SpringTipsLive), we continue our tour of all things @Controller, this time focusing on the Spring support for RSocket. You might also want to watch the expanded discussion of RSocket in earlier Spring Tips  videos: 


  
The RSocket Revolution - watch this next!

  
Raw RSocket support

  
RSocket Messaging and the @Controller component model

  
RSocket and Spring Security

  
Spring Retrosocket]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Externships: enabling India’s next generation of developers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-30-github-externships-enabling-indias-next-generation-of-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-30-github-externships-enabling-indias-next-generation-of-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T03:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a student in India? Applications are open for the GitHub Externships Winter Cohort!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced Amazon S3 Integration for Amazon FSx for Lustre]]></title>
        <id>761df4d7e43dcf9cf7d21b7218211e17b9e6ca4a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/enhanced-amazon-s3-integration-for-amazon-fsx-for-lustre/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T00:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing two additional capabilities of Amazon FSx for Lustre. First, a full bi-directional synchronization of your file systems with Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3), including deleted files and objects. Second, the ability to synchronize your file systems with multiple S3 buckets or prefixes. Lustre is a large scale, distributed parallel file […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge Cake]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2549/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2549/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/edge_cake.png" title="Every time IERS adds or removes a leap second, they send me a birthday cake out of superstition." alt="Every time IERS adds or removes a leap second, they send me a birthday cake out of superstition." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MURAL: Multimodal, Multi-task Retrieval Across Languages]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/mural-multimodal-multi-task-retrieval.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/mural-multimodal-multi-task-retrieval.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T21:03:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Aashi Jain, AI Resident and Yinfei Yang, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research    
For many concepts, there is no direct one-to-one translation from one language to another, and even when there is, such translations often carry different associations and connotations that are easily lost for a non-native speaker. In such cases, however, the meaning may be more obvious when grounded in visual examples. Take, for instance, the word "wedding". In English, one often associates a bride in a white dress and a groom in a tuxedo, but when translated into Hindi (शादी), a more appropriate association may be a bride wearing vibrant colors and a groom wearing a sherwani. What each person associates with the word may vary considerably, but if they are shown an image of the intended concep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecating weak cryptographic standards (TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1) in Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62891</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deprecating-weak-cryptographic-standards-tls-1-0-and-tls-1-1-in-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T19:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to the potential for future protocol downgrade attacks and other Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocol versions 1.0 and 1.1 vulnerabilities not specific to Microsoft’s implementation, it is required that dependencies on all security protocols older than TLS 1.2 be removed wherever possible.
The post Deprecating weak cryptographic standards (TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1) in Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Ramamurthy (MSFT)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - November 30th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/30/this-week-in-spring-november-30th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/30/this-week-in-spring-november-30th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! This last week’s been nutty! Here in the US, we just celebrated the Thanksgiving holiday, and I am fat with turkey and pie, and lazy. But happy. I hope you’re well fed and happy, too. Time’s flying. (Also: can you believe we’re a month away from the new year? I think there’s like four or five weeks (and thus _This Week in Spring_s!) left in the year!) 

We’ve got a ton of stuff to get into this week, so let’s go:


  
Security Report for Spring AMQP (Spring for RabbitMQ)

  
Spring Boot 2.6.1 is now available

  
Spring Data MongoDB - Relation Modelling

  
Thymeleaf 3.0.13 now available! This new version includes security improvements, make sure to check the release notes

  
In last week’s installmetn of A Bootiful Podcast, I talked about reactive-systems with functional programming legend Debasish Ghosh

  
The Apache Cassandra project is working hard to officially support JDK 17 in the next Apache Cassandra major release.

  
I love to see how far the JVM has come. One great indicator of its progress: its garbage collector. Check out this post on garbage collection progress from JDK 8 to JDK 17

  
This is so cool! There’s now an Oracle Database Kubernetes Operator

  
JEP 420: Pattern Matching for switch (Second Preview)

  
Java on Visual Studio Code Update – October 2021

  
For a lot of folks, the days of using Docker Desktop for free are numbered. You might be interested in this blog on Rancher Desktop - A Docker Desktop Replacement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 DevOps tips to speed up your developer workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-30-5-devops-tips-to-speed-up-your-developer-workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-30-5-devops-tips-to-speed-up-your-developer-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T17:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From learning YAML to scripting with Bash, here are a few simple tips for developers who want to speed up their workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Teams with AWS on New Control Tower Account Factory for Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-teams-with-aws-on-new-control-tower-account-factory-for-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-teams-with-aws-on-new-control-tower-account-factory-for-terraform"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T23:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Control Tower Account Factory for HashiCorp Terraform (AFT), the evolution of Terraform Landing Zones, offers an easy way to set up and govern a secure, multi-account AWS environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Report for Spring AMQP (Spring for RabbitMQ)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/29/security-report-for-spring-amqp-spring-for-rabbitmq</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/29/security-report-for-spring-amqp-spring-for-rabbitmq"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T17:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recently released versions of Spring AMQP (2.4.0, 2.3.12, 2.2.20) contain a fix for CVE-2021-22095, which can cause a potential OutOfMemoryError for very large messages.



Spring Boot version 2.6.0 and 2.5.7 will bring in the 2.4.0 and 2.3.12 versions of spring-amqp respectively. Users of Boot 2.4.x should override the spring-amqp and spring-rabbit versions to 2.3.12; users of Spring Boot 2.3.x should override the versions to 2.2.20.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AWS Provider Continues to Expand Coverage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-aws-provider-continues-to-expand-coverage</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-aws-provider-continues-to-expand-coverage"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During 2021, HashiCorp and Amazon Web Services have partnered to bring hundreds of new services and features to the Terraform providers for AWS and AWS Cloud Control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Boards Ux Modernization – Public Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62857</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-boards-ux-modernization-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T16:41:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team is excited to release the public preview of the Ux modernization for Azure Boards! The web platform has been updated to provide a faster Ux, consistency with other parts of the product, and accessibility compliance.
The post Azure Boards Ux Modernization – Public Preview appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/29/spring-boot-2-6-1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/29/spring-boot-2-6-1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T13:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.1 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 11 bug fixes and documentation improvements. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data MongoDB - Relation Modelling]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/29/spring-data-mongodb-relation-modelling</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/29/spring-data-mongodb-relation-modelling"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB’s flexible schema allows for multiple patterns when it comes to modeling relationships between entities. Also, for many use cases, a denormalized data model (storing related data right within a single document) might be the best choice, because all information is kept in one place, so that the application requires fewer queries to fetch all data. However, this approach also has its downsides, such as potential data duplication, larger documents, and the maximum document size.



In general, MongoDB recommends using normalized data models when the advantages of embedding are neglected by the implications of duplication. In this blog post, we take a look at the different possibilities of linking documents with manual references and DBRefs when the need occurs to work with relation…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awful People]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2548/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2548/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/awful_people.png" title="Hm, this burger place has a couple of good reviews, but LakeSlayer7 says he got food poisoning there and everyone should try this other place down by the lake instead." alt="Hm, this burger place has a couple of good reviews, but LakeSlayer7 says he got food poisoning there and everyone should try this other place down by the lake instead." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第198話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496620290741</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496620290741"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Developing Java Apps is Easier with a Process Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=37672</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/how-developing-java-apps-is-easier-with-a-process-engine/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how using Camunda’s process engine in your Java application will make development easier and save you time. 
The post How Developing Java Apps is Easier with a Process Engine appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.11.26]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62849</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-11-26/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T11:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.11.26 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.11.26 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Reactive-System and Functional Programming legend Debasish Ghosh]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/25/a-bootiful-podcast-reactive-system-and-functional-programming-legend-debasish-ghosh</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/25/a-bootiful-podcast-reactive-system-and-functional-programming-legend-debasish-ghosh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to functional programming- and reactive systems-legend Debasish Ghosh (@debasishg). And Happy Thanksgiving, if you celebrate!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Elastic Enterprise Search performance using Elastic APM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-elastic-enterprise-search-performance-using-elastic-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-elastic-enterprise-search-performance-using-elastic-apm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Elastic APM integration for Elastic Enterprise Search enables our developers to quickly pinpoint performance bottlenecks in Enterprise Search.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pius Fung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Elastic Enterprise Search performance using Elastic APM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-elastic-enterprise-search-performance-using-elastic-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-elastic-enterprise-search-performance-using-elastic-apm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic APM is a free, open and powerful observability tool that provides intelligence into application performance for a myriad of production applications (e.g., throughput, error rates, latency, resource usage, transaction traces).  You can now enable Elastic APM integration to gain deep insight into the performance behaviors of your Elastic Enterprise Search deployment! 
This article provides step-by-step instructions for enabling the integration between Elastic's APM and Enterprise Search products and showcases how our Enterprise Search team leverages Elastic APM to capture additional intelligence to improve Enterprise Search performance during the development lifecycle.  
The data collected by the APM Ruby agent in Enterprise Search is shipped to an Elastic APM Server and indexed in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pius Fung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DiscoverDev - curated engineering articles for Wed, 24 Nov 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://discoverdev.io/archive/2021-11-24.html</id>
        <link href="http://discoverdev.io/archive/2021-11-24.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CarbonJ: A high performance, high-scale, drop-in replacement for carbon-cache and carbon-relay 
 
          
            
 Mobile Performance @ Lyft 
 
          
            
 Presentation: eBPF - Superpowers for Cloud Native Operations 
 
          
            
 How do CRDTs solve distributed data consistency challenges? 
 
          
            
 Grammar Correction as You Type, on Pixel 6]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at AWS re:Invent: Breakouts, Experts, Demos, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-breakouts-experts-demos-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-breakouts-experts-demos-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit us at AWS re:Invent 2021 in Las Vegas, Nov. 29 - Dec. 3 for breakout sessions, expert talks, and product demos to accelerate your cloud strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Superpowers for Next Level Microservices Orchestration Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=37690</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/3-superpowers-for-next-level-microservices-orchestration-recap/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the questions we didn't have time to answer at the recent 3 Superpowers for Next Level Microservices Orchestration webinar 
The post 3 Superpowers for Next Level Microservices Orchestration Recap appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring (Happy Thanksgiving!) - November 23rd, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/23/this-week-in-spring-happy-thanksgiving-november-23rd-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/23/this-week-in-spring-happy-thanksgiving-november-23rd-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! 

Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring. This Thursday is Thanksgiving here in the US, where I live. it’s a time during which we Americans try to be thankful for what we have. And me, personally? I’ve got a lot of things for which I am grateful, this week and always. 

I am thankful for my family and friends. A person is the company they keep, and I am lucky to have excellent company in my life. 

I am thankful for my health. Right now, pandemic be danged, I’m healthy and happy, something for which I am endlessly grateful because I know what it’s like not to be healthy. 

I am thankful for the fantastic Spring ecosystem. It’s an endlessly replenishing fount of awesomeness. Have you …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring HATEOAS 1.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/22/spring-hateoas-1-4-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/22/spring-hateoas-1-4-released"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am excited to announce that Spring HATEOAS 1.4 GA has been part of the cascade of releases that lead to the Spring Boot 2.6 last week.
The release ships a couple of new features and all bug fixes we have incorporated in the 1.3.x line.
The most notable new features are:





Full support for level 4 URI templates



Support for non-composite request parameter rendering



Improved HAL-FORMS support (additional property constraints, custom media types)



Additional HTML input types (checkbox, radio, file)



General dependency upgrades, including Spring Framework 5.3.13 and Jackson 2.13.9.





Find more detailed information about all changes made in the 1.4 line in the release’s change log.
The release was included in the Spring Boot 2.6 release announced last week.
In other words, if you have upgraded to that, you’ve already successfully upgraded to Spring HATEOAS 1.4.



We have also released maintenance versions for the 1.3 and 1.2 lines.
Please note, that 1.2.11 is the last release of that branch and 1.2 is going out of OSS maintenance.
Find more about the support timelines for each branch in the newly introduced tab of our project homepage.



Also note, that due to a typo during the release procedure for 1.2.11, a 1.12.11 release has made it onto Maven Central.
The binaries are logically equivalent to 1.2.11, but their presence is likely to cause trouble with tools automating library upgrades.
We’re currently working with Sonatype to investigate options to potentially remove the invalid artifacts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 2022 will be the year for edge automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/2022-the-year-for-edge-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/2022-the-year-for-edge-automation"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T19:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seamlessly, every single day, we wake up and check our health statistics in smart watches, scan QR codes to validate information, pay using credit cards in different locations, use surveillance cameras to record our neighborhoods, and connect our smartphones to distributed WiFi access points in our restaurants or coffee shops. According to the Statista, in the Forecast number of mobile users worldwide 2020-2025[1] report, the number of mobile users worldwide reached 7.1 billion in 2021, and this number is projected to grow. This initiates a new set of use cases for edge devices due to the explosive growth of network-connected entry points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predicting Text Selections with Federated Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/predicting-text-selections-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/predicting-text-selections-with.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:21:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Florian Hartmann, Software Engineer, Google Research 
Smart Text Selection, launched in 2017 as part of Android O, is one of Android’s most frequently used features, helping users select, copy, and use text easily and quickly by predicting the desired word or set of words around a user’s tap, and automatically expanding the selection appropriately. Through this feature, selections are automatically expanded, and for selections with defined classification types, e.g., addresses and phone numbers, users are offered an app with which to open the selection, saving users even more time. 

  Today we describe how we have improved the performance of Smart Text Selection by using federated learning to train the neural network model on user interactions responsibly while preserving user p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.7 Brings New Automated Host Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-7</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary 0.7 adds support for partner plugins, dynamic host catalogs, UI support for managed groups and resource filtering, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decisiveness in Imitation Learning for Robots]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/decisiveness-in-imitation-learning-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/decisiveness-in-imitation-learning-for.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T21:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Pete Florence, Research Scientist and Corey Lynch, Research Engineer, Robotics at Google   
Despite considerable progress in robot learning over the past several years, some policies for robotic agents can still struggle to decisively choose actions when trying to imitate precise or complex behaviors. Consider a task in which a robot tries to slide a block across a table to precisely position it into a slot. There are many possible ways to solve this task, each requiring precise movements and corrections. The robot must commit to just one of these options, but must also be capable of changing plans each time the block ends up sliding farther than expected. Although one might expect such a task to be easy, that is often not the case for modern learning-based robots, which often le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.11.19]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62832</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-11-19/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T11:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! I am Jay Gordon and every week I try to bring you the latest updates from around the DevOps on Azure community. If you have a post you’d like to have me include, I am always listening. You can reach out on Twitter or LinkedIn and I will be sure to share your latest post with the community.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.11.19 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/19/spring-boot-2-6-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/19/spring-boot-2-6-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T08:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the Spring Boot team and everyone that has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.0 has been released and is available from Maven Central. 

This release adds a significant number of new features and improvements. For full upgrade instructions and new and noteworthy features please see the release notes.
What’s new in 2.6


  
Support for SameSite attributes on session cookies for servlet applications

  
Support for configuring health groups on the main or management port

  
Enhanced /info endpoint with Java Runtime information

  
Support for testing Spring MVC using WebTestClient

  
Auto-configuration for spring-rabbit-stream

  
Support for pluggable rules for sanitizing properties in /env and configprops


Dependency upgrades

Spring Boot 2.6 moves to new versions of several Spring projects:


  
Spring Data 2021.1

  
Spring HATEOAS 1.4

  
Spring AMQP 2.4

  
Spring Kafka 2.8

  
Spring Security 5.6

  
Spring Session 2021.1


We’ve also upgraded to the latest stable releases of other third-party libraries wherever possible. Please see the release notes for details.
Other changes

There’s a whole host of other changes and improvements that are documented in the release notes. You can also find a list of deprecated classes and methods that we plan to remove in the next version.

Additionally, Spring Boot 2.4.0 has now reached end of OSS support. More information on Spring Boot’s support dates can be found here.
Thank you

We want to take this opportunity to again thank all our users and contributors.

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask at stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to Know a Kubernetes Operator!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/19/get-to-know-a-kubernetes-operator</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/19/get-to-know-a-kubernetes-operator"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.logo {
 --gutter: 10px;  
 --logo-width : 200px;
 grid-area: logo ;
 border: 1px solid white ;
 width: var(--logo-width) ;
 background-color: white ; 
 padding: var(--gutter);
 border-radius: var(--gutter);  

} 

Hi, Spring fans! It’s Friday, and you know what that means? Some poor schlub somewhere is trying fruitlessly to get something deployed to production, or at least rolled back consistently, in time for dinner. And it’s not working. I’ve been there. Deployments are hard. There’s nuance in deployment. I love Kubernetes as much as the next Operator, but let’s not pretend it’s the pinnacle of productivity. Quite the contrary. There’s a whole cottage industry around simplifying application deployments with Kubernetes. See for example KNative,  Cloud Foundry on Ku…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Permutation-Invariant Neural Networks for Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/permutation-invariant-neural-networks.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/permutation-invariant-neural-networks.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:07:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by David Ha, Staff Research Scientist and Yujin Tang, Research Software Engineer, Google Research, Tokyo      “The brain is able to use information coming from the skin as if it were coming from the eyes. We don’t see with the eyes or hear with the ears, these are just the receptors, seeing and hearing in fact goes on in the brain.”
— Paul Bach-y-Rita1
-->  

  
“The brain is able to use information coming from the skin as if it were coming from the eyes. We don’t see with the eyes or hear with the ears, these are just the receptors, seeing and hearing in fact goes on in the brain.”
  
— Paul Bach-y-Rita1-->, quoted in Livewired
  
 People have the amazing ability to use one sensory modality (e.g., touch) to supply environmental information normally gathered by another sense (e.g., …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PagerDuty, Palo Alto Networks, and Splunk Among New Verified Terraform Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pagerduty-palo-alto-networks-and-splunk-among-new-verified-terraform-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pagerduty-palo-alto-networks-and-splunk-among-new-verified-terraform-providers"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We welcome 17 new verified providers to the growing HashiCorp Terraform ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: The One with the SSO Implementation in Camunda]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=37324</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/qa-the-one-with-the-sso-implementation-in-camunda/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering how to make a SSO implementation work in Camunda? Have no fear. The answer you've been waiting for is here! 
The post Q&A: The One with the SSO Implementation in Camunda appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation for the cloud: Cloud Field Day 12 recap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-for-the-cloud-cloud-field-day-12-recap</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-for-the-cloud-cloud-field-day-12-recap"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently had the opportunity to present our Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform cloud strategy at Cloud Field Day 12. 
Cloud Field Day 12 was a three day event that focused on the impact of cloud on enterprise IT. As a presenter, you can use any combination of slides and live demos to foster a discussion with a group of thought leaders. This roundtable included people from many different companies, skill sets, backgrounds and favorite tools. Check out the Cloud Field Day website to see the delegate panel, their backgrounds and Twitter handles. I quite enjoyed, and preferred, the conversational tone of Cloud Field Day, and the delegates who asked questions during the demo made it a lot more interactive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predicting Text Readability from Scrolling Interactions]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/predicting-text-readability-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/predicting-text-readability-from.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T22:31:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sian Gooding, Intern, Google Research  
Illiteracy affects at least 773 million people globally, both young and old. For these individuals, reading information from unfamiliar sources or on unfamiliar topics can be extremely difficult. Unfortunately, these inequalities have been further magnified by the global pandemic as a result of unequal access to education in reading and writing. In fact, UNESCO reports that over 100 million children are falling behind the minimum proficiency level in reading due to COVID-related school closures.  
 With increasing world-wide access to technology, reading on a device, such as a tablet or phone, has largely taken the place of traditional formats. This provides a unique opportunity to observe reading interactions, e.g., how a reader scrolls th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RLiable: Towards Reliable Evaluation & Reporting in Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/rliable-towards-reliable-evaluation.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/rliable-towards-reliable-evaluation.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T18:32:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rishabh Agarwal, Research Scientist and Pablo Samuel Castro, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team   
 Reinforcement learning (RL) is an area of machine learning that focuses on learning from experiences to solve decision making tasks. While the field of RL has made great progress, resulting in impressive empirical results on complex tasks, such as playing video games, flying stratospheric balloons and designing hardware chips, it is becoming increasingly apparent that the current standards for empirical evaluation might give a false sense of fast scientific progress while slowing it down. 
  To that end, in “Deep RL at the Edge of the Statistical Precipice”, accepted as an oral presentation at NeurIPS 2021, we discuss how statistical uncertainty of results needs t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Vault 1.9]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-9</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-9"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.9 can act as an OIDC provider, includes general availability of a key management secrets engine for Google Cloud, and updates to Transform, Namespaces, and the UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Service Mesh on Amazon ECS Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-on-amazon-ecs-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-on-amazon-ecs-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul service mesh on Amazon ECS is now generally available and ready for production environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of HashiCorp Nomad 1.2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-nomad-1-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-nomad-1-2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.2 introduces Nomad Pack, which simplifies application deployment and lifecycle management on Nomad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Intuit Managed 19M Processes During Peak Tax, Accounting Seasons]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=36771</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/how-intuit-managed-19m-processes-during-peak-tax-accounting-seasons/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dig into how Intuit used workflow automation to manage 396 transactions per second during its most demanding months.
The post How Intuit Managed 19M Processes During Peak Tax, Accounting Seasons appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetNet-2: Deep Learning for 12-Hour Precipitation Forecasting]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/metnet-2-deep-learning-for-12-hour.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/metnet-2-deep-learning-for-12-hour.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T21:56:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nal Kalchbrenner and Lasse Espeholt, Google Research  
Deep learning has successfully been applied to a wide range of important challenges, such as cancer prevention and increasing accessibility. The application of deep learning models to weather forecasts can be relevant to people on a day-to-day basis, from helping people plan their day to managing food production, transportation systems, or the energy grid. Weather forecasts typically rely on traditional physics-based techniques powered by the world’s largest supercomputers. Such methods are constrained by high computational requirements and are sensitive to approximations of the physical laws on which they are based.  
 Deep learning offers a new approach to computing forecasts. Rather than incorporating explicit physical law…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building confidence in a decision]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8705834e6fd8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/building-confidence-in-a-decision-8705834e6fd8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T16:20:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Tingley with Wenjing Zheng, Simon Ejdemyr, Stephanie Lane, Michael Lindon, and Colin McFarland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation controller workflow deployment as code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-controller-workflow-deployment-as-code</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-controller-workflow-deployment-as-code"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background: The Automation Controller Collection
 
The Automation Controller Collection allows Ansible Playbooks to automate the interaction with automation controller. For example, manually interacting via the Web-based UI or the API can now be automated just as the targets it manages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Open Source Vibrotactile Haptics Platform for On-Body Applications]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/an-open-source-vibrotactile-haptics.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/an-open-source-vibrotactile-haptics.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T19:07:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Artem Dementyev, Hardware Engineer, Google Research 
Most wearable smart devices and mobile phones have the means to communicate with the user through tactile feedback, enabling applications from simple notifications to sensory substitution for accessibility. Typically, they accomplish this using vibrotactile actuators, which are small electric vibration motors. However, designing a haptic system that is well-targeted and effective for a given task requires experimentation with the number of actuators and their locations in the device, yet most practical applications require standalone on-body devices and integration into small form factors. This combination of factors can be difficult to address outside of a laboratory as integrating these systems can be quite time-consuming and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第197話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496597544962</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496597544962"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.11.12]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62801</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-11-12/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T10:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! I am Jay Gordon and every week I try to bring you the latest updates from around the DevOps on Azure community. If you have a post you’d like to have me include, I am always listening. You can reach out on Twitter or LinkedIn and I will be sure to share your latest post with the community.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.11.12 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Better Future Predictions by Watching Unlabeled Videos]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/making-better-future-predictions-by.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/making-better-future-predictions-by.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T20:26:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dave Epstein, Student Researcher and Chen Sun, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research   
Machine learning (ML) agents are increasingly deployed in the real world to make decisions and assist people in their daily lives. Making reasonable predictions about the future at varying timescales is one of the most important capabilities for such agents because it enables them to predict changes in the world around them, including other agents’ behaviors, and plan how to act next. Importantly, successful future prediction requires both capturing meaningful transitions in the environment (e.g., dough transforming into bread) and adapting to how transitions unfold over time in order to make decisions.  
  
Previous work in future prediction from visual observations has largely been const…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Variable Sets Beta Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-variable-sets-beta-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-variable-sets-beta-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud variable sets let you simplify the management of reusable variables across an entire organization. This feature is now available in public beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating execution environment image builds with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-execution-environment-image-builds-with-github-actions</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-execution-environment-image-builds-with-github-actions"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Automation Platform 2 leverages containers dubbed automation execution environments which bundle in collection, python and platform dependencies to provide predictable, self-contained automation spaces that can be easily distributed across an organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Amazing Camunda Champions Loading…]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=36489</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/more-amazing-camunda-champions-loading/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our next cohort of Camunda Champions are about to begin. Take a look at our new recruits and learn how to join the program.
The post More Amazing Camunda Champions Loading… appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Buchholz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model Ensembles Are Faster Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/model-ensembles-are-faster-than-you.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/model-ensembles-are-faster-than-you.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:03:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xiaofang Wang, Intern and Yair Alon (prev. Movshovitz-Attias), Software Engineer, Google Research    
When building a deep model for a new machine learning application, researchers often begin with existing network architectures, such as ResNets or EfficientNets. If the initial model’s accuracy isn’t high enough, a larger model may be a tempting alternative, but may not actually be the best solution for the task at hand. Instead, better performance potentially could be achieved by designing a new model that is optimized for the task. However, such efforts can be challenging and usually require considerable resources.  
In “Wisdom of Committees: An Overlooked Approach to Faster and More Accurate Models”,  we discuss model ensembles and a subset called model cascades, both of which…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud Wins 2021 CRN Tech Innovator Award]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-cloud-wins-2021-crn-tech-innovator-award</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-cloud-wins-2021-crn-tech-innovator-award"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud takes home the prize in the DevOps Platforms category of the 2021 CRN Tech Innovator Awards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing AV1 Streaming to Netflix Members’ TVs]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b7fc88e42320</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/bringing-av1-streaming-to-netflix-members-tvs-b7fc88e42320?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T19:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Liwei Guo, Ashwin Kumar Gopi Valliammal, Raymond Tam, Chris Pham, Agata Opalach, Weibo Ni]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Known issue with publishing extensions: “Your ability to create global personal access tokens (PATs) is restricted by your organization.”]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62780</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/issue-with-extension-publishing/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T19:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve run into trouble while trying to publish an Azure DevOps or Visual Studio extension to the Visual Studio Marketplace, please ask your administrator if they have enabled the new policy to restrict the creation of global personal access tokens (PATs).
The post Known issue with publishing extensions: “Your ability to create global personal access tokens (PATs) is restricted by your organization.” appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pazand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.3.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=36369</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/camunda-cloud-1-3-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T15:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with Camunda Cloud 1.3.0-alpha1 now! The alpha includes bug fixes and the preparations for the next 1.3.0 release. 
The post Camunda Cloud 1.3.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced Sleep Sensing in Nest Hub]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/enhanced-sleep-sensing-in-nest-hub.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/enhanced-sleep-sensing-in-nest-hub.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T14:40:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Michael Dixon, Software Engineer and Reena Singhal Lee, Product Manager, Google Health 
Earlier this year, we launched Contactless Sleep Sensing in Nest Hub, an opt-in feature that can help users better understand their sleep patterns and nighttime wellness. While some of the most critical sleep insights can be derived from a person’s overall schedule and duration of sleep, that alone does not tell the complete story. The human brain has special neurocircuitry to coordinate sleep cycles — transitions between deep, light, and rapid eye movement (REM) stages of sleep — vital not only for physical and emotional wellbeing, but also for optimal physical and cognitive performance. Combining such sleep staging information with disturbance events can help you better understand what’s hap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 61 – Deploying to @Azure is one “git push” away with @juliendubois]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62700</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-61-deploying-to-azure-is-one-git-push-away-with-juliendubois/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T13:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 61 – Deploying to @Azure is one “git push” away with @juliendubois appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>