<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-02-11T01:23:43.167Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-02-11T01:23:43.167Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research, 2022 & beyond: Algorithmic advances]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/google-research-2022-beyond-algorithmic.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/google-research-2022-beyond-algorithmic.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T20:08:00.017Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Vahab Mirrokni, VP and Google Fellow, Google Research    
    

(This is Part 5 in our series of posts covering different topical areas of research at Google. You can find other posts in the series here.)
   

Robust algorithm design is the backbone of systems across Google, particularly for our ML and AI models. Hence, developing algorithms with improved efficiency, performance and speed remains a high priority as it empowers services ranging from Search and Ads to Maps and YouTube. Google Research has been at the forefront of this effort, developing many innovations from privacy-safe recommendation systems to scalable solutions for large-scale ML. In 2022, we continued this journey, and advanced the state-of-the-art in several related areas. Here we highlight our progress in a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheating at golf]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42780</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726948590/0/sethsblog~Cheating-at-golf/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T10:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone who cheats at a friendly game of golf when nothing much is at stake–how can you possibly trust them with something important? And yet, organizations and individuals “cheat at golf” all the time. They put clever clauses in the fine print. Spam a media list. Conceal the long-term impact of short-term decisions. Steal your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for government to move beyond monitoring and into observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/its-time-for-government-to-move-beyond-monitoring-and-into-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/its-time-for-government-to-move-beyond-monitoring-and-into-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For public sector, traditional monitoring tools are helpful, but they're just the starting point. An observability solution provides true end-to-end visibility, plus the ability to make sense of that data and take action on it via AI and ML.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Stacey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for government to move beyond monitoring and into observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/its-time-for-government-to-move-beyond-monitoring-and-into-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/its-time-for-government-to-move-beyond-monitoring-and-into-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
When thinking about holistic end-to-end observability, it can help to start with what you already have. Many government agencies are already strategically ingesting and storing logs — a key component of observability. 
More than a year and a half after the release of M-21-31, US government agencies continue to work through the logging maturity models outlined in the memorandum. One of the key messages in M-21-31 is the need to keep log data actionable for longer time periods to help detect and mitigate hidden attacks and avoid situations like the SolarWinds breach of 2021.
As agencies examine the capabilities of their logging solutions in light of M-21-31, that actionable data is crucial. Compared with other solutions, Elastic Observability offers faster access to historical data. With E…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Stacey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Advantages and Disadvantages of Microservices: Biggest Benefits of Microservices and Key Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=72372&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=72372</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/02/benefits-of-microservices-advantages-disadvantages/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T22:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the benefits of a microservices architecture, the overall pros and cons of microservices, and when you should use them.
The post Top Advantages and Disadvantages of Microservices: Biggest Benefits of Microservices and Key Use Cases appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The magic of a page a day]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44907</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726900887/0/sethsblog~The-magic-of-a-page-a-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T21:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1979, the page-a-day calendar was born. It’s basically a book on its side, but the user rips off a page each day. My friend Michael Cader took this concept and ran with it, creating calendars that sold millions of copies. Of course, everyone knows what day it is, and if you really need to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amplification at the Quantum limit]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/amplification-at-quantum-limit.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/amplification-at-quantum-limit.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T19:03:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ted White and Ofer Naaman, Staff Research Scientists, Google Quantum AI   
The Google Quantum AI team is building quantum computers with superconducting microwave circuits, but much like a classical computer the superconducting processor at the heart of these computers is only part of the story. An entire technology stack of peripheral hardware is required to make the quantum computer work properly. In many cases these parts must be custom designed, requiring extensive research and development to reach the highest levels of performance.   

In this post, we highlight one aspect of this supplemental hardware: our superconducting microwave amplifiers. In “Readout of a Quantum Processor with High Dynamic Range Josephson Parametric Amplifiers”, published in Applied Physics Letters, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.1 EAP4: Terminal Emulation and Clangd-Based Indexer]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=323053</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/02/clion-2023-1-eap4-terminal-emulation-and-clangd-based-indexer/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T17:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CLion 2023.1 EAP build (231.6890.13) is available from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package (if you are using Ubuntu). Update via patch if you are using the previous EAP build. DOWNLOAD CLION EAP Terminal emulation in CLion If you develop curses or ncurses applications in CLion, you previously […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Global Threat Report Breakdown: Defense Evasion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-global-threat-report-breakdown-defense-evasion</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-global-threat-report-breakdown-defense-evasion"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we published the Elastic Global Threat Report in 2022, it included threat trends and correlations from our analysis of telemetry data shared by our users. In addition to telling us about how well features work for them, it also represents our visibility of the threat landscape.
About 34% of the techniques we saw were related to defense evasion, which we believe is a direct result of endpoint security innovations. Because we believe in free and open principles, we wanted to get a little deeper into what we observed and why it’s important for 2023 and beyond.
What’s the defense evasion category?
The Defense Evasion tactic includes 42 techniques at the time of this publication, dozens of sub-techniques, and a nearly infinite number of procedural variations. In simplest terms, each of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devon Kerr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Global Threat Report Breakdown: Defense Evasion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-global-threat-report-breakdown-defense-evasion</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-global-threat-report-breakdown-defense-evasion"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Devon Kerr breaks down the Defense Evasion statistics from this year's Elastic Global Threat Report, offering additional details from behind the keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devon Kerr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Tabs in the New UI on macOS, No Spell Checks for Hashes and Special Values in GoLand 2023.1 EAP #4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=322873</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2023/02/09/project-tabs-in-the-new-ui-on-macos-no-spell-checks-for-hashes-and-special-values-in-goland-2023-1-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T16:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth GoLand 2023.1 EAP build is out! You can get it via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package (for Ubuntu), or from inside GoLand, select Check IDE updates for: Early Access Program in Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System Settings | Updates.  Download GoLand 2023.1 EAP Project […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MPS Community Meetup 2023 is happening!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=mps&amp;p=322857</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/mps/2023/02/mps-community-meetup-2023-is-happening/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T16:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MPS Community Meetup is back! Join us for the MPS Community Meetup 2023 in Munich on May 11 and 12. Like previous years, the event will be a series of talks from the community and the MPS team sharing the product’s status. Register today! The call for speakers is open! We are accepting talks […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oscar Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.1 EAP #4: Improvements for Vue, PostCSS, React, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=322307</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/02/webstorm-2023-1-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T15:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our work on WebStorm 2023.1 continues, and the fourth EAP build is now available! To catch up on all of the new features you can expect in WebStorm 2023.1, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 EAP 4: Project Tabs in the New UI on macOS, Astro Support, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=321719</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/02/intellij-idea-2023-1-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T15:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth week of the IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 Early Access Program brings highly anticipated features such as project tabs for the new UI on macOS and support for the Astro framework. The new build also introduces improvements for the profiler’s Flame graph, an updated Coverage view, and the long-awaited change to disable spell checks for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Building the tooling I wish I’d had”. An Interview With Charlie Marsh]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=322151</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/02/ruff-python-linter-interview-with-charlie-marsh/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T15:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python has a rich ecosystem of quality, mature tooling: linting, formatting, type checking, and the like. Each has decent performance, but what if the tooling was fast? Really fast – as in, instantaneous? This is the argument posed by Charlie Marsh when he introduced Ruff: a linter with the engine written in Rust. The performance […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Everitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Vision for JetBrains Academy]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=322649</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/02/09/the-new-vision-for-jetbrains-academy/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T15:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our educational journey began in 2014, when JetBrains debuted PyCharm Edu, our first product for students and teachers. By 2016 we were ready to go beyond Python and expanded into Java and Kotlin. Soon enough, we realized we didn’t want to limit ourselves to just interactive IDE courses. We partnered with Hyperskill in 2019 to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatiana Vasilyeva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing faster updates to Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/beginning-with-ansible-automation-platform-2.3-red-hat-brings-you-faster-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/beginning-with-ansible-automation-platform-2.3-red-hat-brings-you-faster-updates"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beginning with Ansible Automation Platform 2.3, this new release mechanism will be the norm. This blog will explain what it means for you and your processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yanis Guenane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Playrix Uses TeamCity to Run Thousands of Builds per Day]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=322157</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/02/how-playrix-uses-teamcity/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T11:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Playrix is among the top 3 mobile gaming companies in the world. Headquartered in Dublin, Ireland, Playrix serves over 30 million users worldwide daily. Some of their best-known games include Homescapes, Fishdom, and Gardenscapes. The company runs over 10,000 builds every day, using 220 TeamCity build agents and running CI/CD processes for over 2,500 projects. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most people (and the people you choose)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41897</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726840116/0/sethsblog~Most-people-and-the-people-you-choose/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T10:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most people want you to make something cheap, write something short, share something funny, and fit in. But the people you serve… they might want something else. The few people you need to thrive in your work might want you to write something they’ll remember for a long time, or to take them on a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance tips for IntelliJ Scala Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=scala&amp;p=315471</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/scala/2023/02/09/performance-tips-for-intellij-scala-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T08:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A full-blown IDE is one of the most complicated applications you can find on an average laptop. This is why we – the Scala plugin team at JetBrains – from time to time receive reports that our product lags in certain situations or works slowly in general. In some of these cases we can help, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maciej Gorywoda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: opensource, Spring Cloud, and Kubernetes maestro Abel Salgado Romero]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/09/a-bootiful-podcast-opensource-spring-cloud-and-kubernetes-maestro-abel</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/09/a-bootiful-podcast-opensource-spring-cloud-and-kubernetes-maestro-abel"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar, Festive Edition · December 2022 &#8211; January 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-08-release-radar-dec-2022-jan-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-08-release-radar-dec-2022-jan-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T23:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to our special edition of the Release Radar 🎄. Between Christmas festivities, end of the year parties, Chinese New Year, or simply enjoying some time off, almost everyone has been celebrating &#8211; us too! Now we&#8217;re taking a moment to celebrate these awesome open source projects that shipped major version releases during December and [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsupervised and semi-supervised anomaly detection with data-centric ML]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/unsupervised-and-semi-supervised.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/unsupervised-and-semi-supervised.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T18:41:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jinsung Yoon and Sercan O. Arik, Research Scientists, Google Research, Cloud AI Team  
Anomaly detection (AD), the task of distinguishing anomalies from normal data, plays a vital role in many real-world applications, such as detecting faulty products from vision sensors in manufacturing, fraudulent behaviors in financial transactions, or network security threats. Depending on the availability of the type of data — negative (normal) vs. positive (anomalous) and the availability of their labels — the task of AD involves different challenges. 
  


(a) Fully supervised anomaly detection, (b) normal-only anomaly detection, (c, d, e) semi-supervised anomaly detection, (f) unsupervised anomaly detection.

  
While most previous works were shown to be effective for cases with fully-lab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.5 beta adds single sign-on and dynamic node metadata]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-5-adds-single-sign-on-and-dynamic-node-metadata</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-5-adds-single-sign-on-and-dynamic-node-metadata"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.5 improves management of security and access with single sign-on and OIDC support, and adds dynamic node metadata, policy management in the UI, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault and HCP Consul add new Canada, Japan, and US AWS regions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-and-hcp-consul-add-new-canada-japan-and-us-aws-regions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-and-hcp-consul-add-new-canada-japan-and-us-aws-regions"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Cloud Platform adds new AWS region support for HCP Vault and HCP Consul  in the U.S. as well as  regions in Canada and Japan for the first time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The K2 Compiler is going stable in Kotlin 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=321784</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/02/k2-kotlin-2-0/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T15:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve been working on a new frontend for the Kotlin compiler (code-named “K2”) for quite a while. The frontend is the part of the compiler that parses your code and performs the semantic analysis, data flow analysis, call resolution, and type inference. This is the part of the compiler that you, the developer, interact with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Petrova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | February 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=322010</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/02/08/net-annotated-monthly-february-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T15:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? The official birthday of the internet is January 1, 1983. While there already was a prototype of several connected computers since the 1960’s, they had no standard way to communicate. That is, until January 1, 1983, when ARPANET and the Defense Data Network moved over to the TCP/IP standard bringing the very […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第224話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4855956445072905450</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4855956445072905450"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update Regarding Kotlin/Native Targets]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=321988</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/02/update-regarding-kotlin-native-targets/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T14:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin/Native supports many targets thanks to its LLVM backend – 27 as of 1.8.0, to be exact! While most of the heavy lifting is already being done by LLVM, we still have a lot of work to do. For example, we still need to: Develop platform-dependent features like a memory manager. Maintain and update platform […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Petrova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The audacity of the crowd anthem]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44898</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726725879/0/sethsblog~The-audacity-of-the-crowd-anthem/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s little doubt that We Are the Champions is one of the great crowd anthems of our time. Just about any group can be stirred into a frenzy just by playing a few bars: The same goes Rapper’s Delight. And yet… Can you imagine how frightening it must have been to play it live for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Bianca Laurendine shares her top 4 tips for how diverse candidates can break into tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-diverse-candidates-break-into-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-diverse-candidates-break-into-tech"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bianca Laurendine transitioned into the tech industry. Now she’s sharing her advice on how to break into tech, especially as a diverse candidate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[36% of CISOs see the shortage of skilled workers as their key cybersecurity challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/cisos-see-shortage-of-skilled-workers-as-key-cybersecurity-challenge</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/cisos-see-shortage-of-skilled-workers-as-key-cybersecurity-challenge"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Cybersecurity Ventures, it's estimated that 3.5 million security analyst positions are unfilled. It’s no surprise, then, that more than a third of CISOs see the skills shortage as their primary challenge, according to a ThoughtLab study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikki Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Bianca Laurendine shares her top 4 tips for how diverse candidates can break into tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-diverse-candidates-break-into-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-diverse-candidates-break-into-tech"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Bianca Laurendine, senior product marketing manager for Elastic Cloud, is no stranger to bucking trends. 

“Every kid wants to be a ballerina,” she says. “I was exploring mechanical engineering and making websites.”

She always knew she wanted to get into the tech industry. 

According to research, only 26.5% of tech jobs in the United States are held by women. And only 7% of tech jobs are held by Black Americans. 

Bianca worked in mechanical engineering and for a geospatial company before "officially" transitioning into tech when she joined Elastic in 2020.

“If you’re always worried about what people will think, you’ll never have any fun,” she says. 
As a product marketing manager, she describes her job as sitting at the intersection of marketing, product, sales, and customer success.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[36% of CISOs see the shortage of skilled workers as their key cybersecurity challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/cisos-see-shortage-of-skilled-workers-as-key-cybersecurity-challenge</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/cisos-see-shortage-of-skilled-workers-as-key-cybersecurity-challenge"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
According to Cybersecurity Ventures, it is estimated that 3.5 million security analyst positions remain unfilled. It’s no surprise, then, that more than a third of CISOs find the skills shortage to be their primary challenge, according to the ThoughtLab study Cybersecurity Solutions for a Riskier World.


With an estimated 3.5 million cybersecurity jobs unfilled, security operations centers are understaffed and overwhelmed 
With this in mind, Elastic Training has developed the Elastic Network Security Analyst learning path focused on developing network security analyst skills. This learning path supports common use cases, such as continuous monitoring, threat prevention and detection, and investigation and incident response.


 

The Elastic Network Security Analyst learning path is desi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikki Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coordinate Plane Closure]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2735/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2735/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/coordinate_plane_closure.png" title="3D graphs that don't contact the plane in the closure area may proceed as scheduled, but be alert for possible collisions with 2D graph lines that reach the hole and unexpectedly enter 3D space." alt="3D graphs that don't contact the plane in the closure area may proceed as scheduled, but be alert for possible collisions with 2D graph lines that reach the hole and unexpectedly enter 3D space." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research, 2022 & beyond: Algorithms for efficient deep learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/google-research-2022-beyond-algorithms.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/google-research-2022-beyond-algorithms.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T19:42:00.012Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sanjiv Kumar, VP and Google Fellow, Google Research    
    

(This is Part 4 in our series of posts covering different topical areas of research at Google. You can find other posts in the series here.)
   
The explosion in deep learning a decade ago was catapulted in part by the convergence of new algorithms and architectures, a marked increase in data, and access to greater compute. In the last 10 years, AI and ML models have become bigger and more sophisticated — they’re deeper, more complex, with more parameters, and trained on much more data, resulting in some of the most transformative outcomes in the history of machine learning.  
 As these models increasingly find themselves deployed in production and business applications, the efficiency and costs of these models has gon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating custom Event-Driven Ansible source plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-custom-event-driven-ansible-source-plugins</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-custom-event-driven-ansible-source-plugins"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event source plugins within Event-Driven Ansible act as a bridge between Ansible and event generating applications and services. Learn how in this blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self restaint vs systemic restraint]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42643</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726616052/0/sethsblog~Self-restaint-vs-systemic-restraint/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T09:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not hypocritical to help yourself at a buffet at the same time you counsel the owner of the restaurant to limit the number of trips that people take so that the restaurant can become sustainable. It’s possible to argue for systemic changes to cultural systems while also doing what classical economics posits that people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - February 7th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/07/this-week-in-spring-february-7th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/07/this-week-in-spring-february-7th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Root cause log analysis with Elastic Observability and machine learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/reduce-mttd-ml-machine-learning-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/reduce-mttd-ml-machine-learning-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability provides more than just log aggregation, metrics analysis, APM, and distributed tracing. Elastic’s machine learning capabilities will help you analyze the root cause of issues allowing you to focus your time on the most important tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Root cause log analysis with Elastic Observability and machine learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/reduce-mttd-ml-machine-learning-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/reduce-mttd-ml-machine-learning-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
With more and more applications moving to the cloud, an increasing amount of telemetry data (logs, metrics, traces) is being collected, which can help improve application performance, operational efficiencies, and business KPIs. However, analyzing this data is extremely tedious and time consuming given the tremendous amounts of data being generated. Traditional methods of alerting and simple pattern matching (visual or simple searching etc) are not sufficient for IT Operations teams and SREs. It’s like trying to find a needle in a haystack. 

In this blog post, we’ll cover some of Elastic’s artificial intelligence for IT operations (AIOps) and machine learning (ML) capabilities for root cause analysis.

Elastic’s machine learning will help you investigate performance issues by providing …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Visualize Your VPC Resources from Amazon VPC Creation Experience]]></title>
        <id>618b90c386fb5f115567e86d8bc9be600673d3a9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-visualize-your-vpc-resources-from-amazon-vpc-creation-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T20:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) resource map, a new feature that simplifies the VPC creation experience in the AWS Management Console. This feature displays your existing VPC resources and their routing visually on a single page, allowing you to quickly understand the architectural layout of the VPC. A year ago, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – February 6, 2023]]></title>
        <id>07d9d666b6ee63ff65006fd22e0156f6d150b6e5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-february-6-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T17:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! If you are looking for a new year challenge, the Serverless Developer Advocate team launched the 30 days of Serverless. You can follow the hashtag #30DaysServerless on LinkedIn, Twitter, or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The technology behind GitHub’s new code search]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-06-the-technology-behind-githubs-new-code-search/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-06-the-technology-behind-githubs-new-code-search/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at what went into building the world's largest public code search index.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to become a developer advocate: Part 3, finding your audience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-3-finding-your-audience</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-3-finding-your-audience"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third part in our series on how to build the skills needed to become a developer advocate. This post focuses on selecting conferences and events to submit to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to mitigate OWASP vulnerabilities while staying in the flow]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-06-how-to-mitigate-owasp-vulnerabilities-while-staying-in-the-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-06-how-to-mitigate-owasp-vulnerabilities-while-staying-in-the-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T15:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how GitHub Advanced Security can help address several of the OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And then that happened]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43773</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726518117/0/sethsblog~And-then-that-happened/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T09:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world changes and we have a choice: • Fight hard to keep it the way it was. • Notice what happened and then decide to do something with that insight. Thirty years ago, AOL was my company’s biggest client. They charged users $3 an hour to use their precursor to the internet, and paid […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Strava data collection with Elastic APM and a custom script solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/optimizing-strava-data-collection-elastic-apm-custom-script</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/optimizing-strava-data-collection-elastic-apm-custom-script"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the fourth blog post in a series of ones to follow. I will take you through a journey of data onboarding, manipulation, and visualization using Strava as a backdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two sides of the same coin: Uniting testing and monitoring with Synthetic Monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/uniting-testing-and-monitoring-with-synthetic-monitoring</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/uniting-testing-and-monitoring-with-synthetic-monitoring"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps aims to establish complementary practices across development and operations. See how Playwright, @elastic/synthetics, GitHub Actions, and Elastic Synthetics can unite development and SRE teams in validating and monitoring the user experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Strava data collection with Elastic APM and a custom script solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/optimizing-strava-data-collection-elastic-apm-custom-script</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/optimizing-strava-data-collection-elastic-apm-custom-script"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
This is the fourth blog post in our Strava series (don’t forget to catch up on the first, second, and third)! I will take you through a journey of data onboarding, manipulation, and visualization.

What is Strava, and why is it the focus? Strava is a platform where recreational and professional athletes can share their activities. All my fitness data from my Apple Watch, Garmin, and Zwift is automatically synced and saved. Getting the data out of Strava is the first step to getting an overview of my fitness.

In the last blog posts, we developed a script that imports all the data from Strava. Now it’s time for some observability and identifying issues with our script.
What is my script doing?
Remember, in the second blog, we wrote quite an extensive script. I will post it here again:
fro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two sides of the same coin: Uniting testing and monitoring with Synthetic Monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/uniting-testing-and-monitoring-with-synthetic-monitoring</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/uniting-testing-and-monitoring-with-synthetic-monitoring"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Historically, software development and SRE have worked in silos with different cultural perspectives and priorities. The goal of DevOps is to establish common and complementary practices across software development and operations. Sadly, in some organizations true collaboration is rare and we still have a way to go to build effective DevOps partnerships.
Outside of cultural challenges, one of the most common reasons for this disconnect is using different tools to achieve similar goals — case in point, end-to-end testing versus synthetic monitoring. As highlighted in our prior blog, synthetic monitoring can replace e2e tests altogether. Uniting around a single tool to validate the user workflow early provides a common language to recreate user issues to validate fixes against.
This blog s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electron Color]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2734/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2734/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/electron_color.png" title="There's quark color, but that's not really color--it's just an admission by 20th century physicists that numbers are boring." alt="There's quark color, but that's not really color--it's just an admission by 20th century physicists that numbers are boring." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: k8s.gcr.io Image Registry Will Be Frozen From the 3rd of April 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/02/06/k8s-gcr-io-freeze-announcement/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/02/06/k8s-gcr-io-freeze-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Mahamed Ali (Rackspace Technology)
The Kubernetes project runs a community-owned image registry called registry.k8s.io to host its container images. On the 3rd of April 2023, the old registry k8s.gcr.io will be frozen and no further images for Kubernetes and related subprojects will be pushed to the old registry.
This registry registry.k8s.io replaced the old one and has been generally available for several months. We have published a blog post about its benefits to the community and the Kubernetes project. This post also announced that future versions of Kubernetes will not be available in the old registry. Now that time has come.
What does this change mean for contributors:
If you are a maintainer of a subproject, you will need to update your manifests and Helm charts to use the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“What’s next?”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44877</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726447437/0/sethsblog~Whats-next/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-05T10:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way we think about our priorities makes a huge difference. Leaders of every stripe make one thing more than any other: decisions. In any environment with constraints (which is, actually, any environment), the decisions about time and resources–about what to do next–change everything. How do we decide what’s next? Is it based on urgency, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“No photos”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41851</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726366908/0/sethsblog~No-photos/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-04T09:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s what it said at the florist shop. I’m guessing because ‘taking’ a photo sometimes feels like a taking. The creativity, skill and effort that goes into making a distinctive arrangement might feel uncompensated when someone simply takes the work and posts it. This misses the real point, though. Once you’ve made something worth photographing, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ludum Dare 52 staff picks 🕹]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-03-ludum-dare-52-staff-picks/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-03-ludum-dare-52-staff-picks/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-04T01:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve got ten top games from the latest Ludum Dare game jam plus source code for you to check out. Pun intended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real-time tracking of wildfire boundaries using satellite imagery]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/real-time-tracking-of-wildfire.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/real-time-tracking-of-wildfire.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T18:05:00.012Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zvika Ben-Haim and Omer Nevo, Software Engineers, Google Research   
   As global temperatures rise, wildfires around the world are becoming more frequent and more dangerous. Their effects are felt by many communities as people evacuate their homes or suffer harm even from proximity to the fire and smoke.  

As part of Google’s mission to help people access trusted information in critical moments, we use satellite imagery and machine learning (ML) to track wildfires and inform affected communities. Our wildfire tracker was recently expanded. It provides updated fire boundary information every 10–15 minutes, is more accurate than similar satellite products, and improves on our previous work. These boundaries are shown for large fires in the continental US, Mexico, and most of Cana…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Adds OpenID Connect (OIDC) Single Sign-On Functionality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-adds-openid-connect-oidc-single-sign-on-functionality</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-adds-openid-connect-oidc-single-sign-on-functionality"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how users of the HashiCorp Cloud Platform (HCP) can now leverage the popular OpenID Connect (OIDC) protocol for their single sign-on (SSO) integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customers using Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 6 should upgrade the OS on Self-hosted agents]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66368</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/customers-using-red-hat-enterprise-linux-rhel-6-should-upgrade-the-os-on-self-hosted-agents/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T15:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RHEL 6 & .NET Core 3.1
The post Customers using Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 6 should upgrade the OS on Self-hosted agents appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s chance to be a leader in the age of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-03-europes-chance-to-be-a-leader-in-the-age-of-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-03-europes-chance-to-be-a-leader-in-the-age-of-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T13:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Below are my prepared remarks delivered at the EU Open Source Policy Summit in Brussels on Feb 3rd.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confusion about performance]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42703</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726270131/0/sethsblog~Confusion-about-performance/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T09:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thing that your product or service delivers could be called performance, and it’s made of two components: –The story and expectations and cultural impact of what you do (the story). –The deliverables that are objectively measured (the spec). It helps to have both. Many hard-working freelancers are confused about their story. Either they insist […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An ever green, ever great way to learn Spring]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/03/an-ever-green-ever-great-way-to-learn-spring</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/03/an-ever-green-ever-great-way-to-learn-spring"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 State of Spring Survey Report]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/03/the-state-of-spring-survey-2022-report</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/03/the-state-of-spring-survey-2022-report"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Size Comparisons]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2733/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2733/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/size_comparisons.png" title="If you shrank the Solar System to the size of Texas, the Houston metro area would be smaller than a grasshopper in Dallas." alt="If you shrank the Solar System to the size of Texas, the Houston metro area would be smaller than a grasshopper in Dallas." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Instrumentation]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/02/03/sig-instrumentation-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/02/03/sig-instrumentation-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Imran Noor Mohamed (Delivery Hero)
Observability requires the right data at the right time for the right consumer
(human or piece of software) to make the right decision. In the context of Kubernetes,
having best practices for cluster observability across all Kubernetes components is crucial.
SIG Instrumentation helps to address this issue by providing best practices and tools
that all other SIGs use to instrument Kubernetes components-like the API server,
scheduler, kubelet and kube-controller-manager.
In this SIG Instrumentation spotlight, Imran Noor Mohamed,
SIG ContribEx-Comms tech lead talked with Elana Hashman,
and Han Kang, chairs of SIG Instrumentation,
on how the SIG is organized, what are the current challenges and how anyone can get involved and contribute.
About SIG Ins…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research, 2022 & beyond: ML & computer systems]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/google-research-2022-beyond-ml-computer.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/google-research-2022-beyond-ml-computer.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T21:13:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Phitchaya Mangpo Phothilimthana, Staff Research Scientist, and Adam Paszke, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research    
    

(This is Part 3 in our series of posts covering different topical areas of research at Google. You can find other posts in the series here.)
   
  Great machine learning (ML) research requires great systems. With the increasing sophistication of the algorithms and hardware in use today and with the scale at which they run, the complexity of the software necessary to carry out day-to-day tasks only increases. In this post, we provide an overview of the numerous advances made across Google this past year in systems for ML that enable us to support the serving and training of complex models while easing the complexity of implementation for end users. This b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the GitHub Docs team uses GitHub Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-02-how-the-github-docs-team-uses-github-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-02-how-the-github-docs-team-uses-github-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T19:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how the GitHub Docs team uses GitHub Projects for content coordination, reviews, and publishing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling branch deployments through IssueOps with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-02-enabling-branch-deployments-through-issueops-with-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-02-enabling-branch-deployments-through-issueops-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T18:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if developers want to leverage branch deployments but don't have a full ChatOps stack integrated with their repositories? We wanted to set out to find a way for all developers to be able to take advantage of branch deployments with ease, right from their GitHub repository, and so the branch-deploy Action was born!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Vizier: Towards reliable and flexible hyperparameter and blackbox optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/open-source-vizier-towards-reliable-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/open-source-vizier-towards-reliable-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T17:56:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xingyou (Richard) Song, Research Scientist, and Chansoo Lee, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team  
Google Vizier is the de-facto system for blackbox optimization over objective functions and hyperparameters across Google, having serviced some of Google’s largest research efforts and optimized a wide range of products (e.g., Search, Ads, YouTube). For research, it has not only reduced language model latency for users, designed computer architectures, accelerated hardware, assisted protein discovery, and enhanced robotics, but also provided a reliable backend interface for users to search for neural architectures and evolve reinforcement learning algorithms. To operate at the scale of optimizing thousands of users’ critical systems and tuning millions of machine learning…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Automation Platform Moving Towards Smarter Inventory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-moving-towards-smarter-inventory</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-moving-towards-smarter-inventory"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR What is this?
 
It has been a long term ask and our desire to make Smart Inventory, well, smarter. We’ve listened to feedback, and are now addressing not only direct customer asks but also presenting solutions to make it better overall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagining cities in a few simple questions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44832</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726170180/0/sethsblog~Reimagining-cities-in-a-few-simple-questions/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T09:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What would happen if public transportation were free? What if it were paid for by congestion pricing, digitally implemented? What if public toilets were safe, beautiful, well-appointed and consistently maintained? What if there were a tax on empty storefronts, payable after three months of vacancy? Shortly after the invention of the car, society made many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Moderne founder Jon Schneider on OpenRewrite, modernizing code bases en masse, freedom and responsibility, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/02/a-bootiful-podcast-moderne-founder-jon-schneider-on-openrewrite-modernizing</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/02/a-bootiful-podcast-moderne-founder-jon-schneider-on-openrewrite-modernizing"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Lateral Movement activity: A new Kibana integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-lateral-movement-activity-a-new-kibana-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-lateral-movement-activity-a-new-kibana-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber attacks are becoming more frequent, targeted, and complex. When it comes to sophisticated attacks, one of the most commonly seen tactics is Lateral Movement. During lateral movement, many attackers try impersonating a legitimate user by abusing admin tools (e.g., SMB, SAMBA, FTP, WMI, WinRM, and PowerShell Remoting) to move laterally from system to system in search of sensitive information. In addition, they may avoid using traditional malware to stay beneath the security radar, making detection more difficult.
This publication will discuss the newly available Lateral Movement Detection package under Kibana’s integrations app. Our new package includes anomaly detection jobs and security rules and takes advantage of the endpoint malware classifier to make finding Lateral Movement in y…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirti Sodhi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.9 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-9-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-9-released"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.17.9 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.9 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
The 7.17.9 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security advisory for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maha Alsayasneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Lateral Movement activity: A new Kibana integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-lateral-movement-activity-a-new-kibana-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-lateral-movement-activity-a-new-kibana-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This publication will discuss the newly available Lateral Movement Detection package under Kibana’s integrations app. Our new package includes anomaly detection jobs and security rules and takes advantage of the endpoint malware classifier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirti Sodhi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.9 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-9-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-9-released"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maha Alsayasneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the launch of the All In for Maintainers DEI Resource Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-01-announcing-the-launch-of-the-all-in-for-maintainers-dei-resource-hub/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-01-announcing-the-launch-of-the-all-in-for-maintainers-dei-resource-hub/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T23:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DEI Resource Hub is a vetted collection of resources, tools, and best practices designed to help open source maintainers create and maintain inclusive and diverse open source communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestration vs Choreography]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=71907&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=71907</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/02/orchestration-vs-choreography/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T22:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the benefits and disadvantages of using Orchestration or Choreography for your microservice architecture.
The post Orchestration vs Choreography appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Flan Collection: Advancing open source methods for instruction tuning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/the-flan-collection-advancing-open.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/the-flan-collection-advancing-open.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T18:16:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shayne Longpre, Student Researcher, and Adam Roberts, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team  
Language models are now capable of performing many new natural language processing (NLP) tasks by reading instructions, often that they hadn’t seen before. The ability to reason on new tasks is mostly credited to training models on a wide variety of unique instructions, known as “instruction tuning”, which was introduced by FLAN and extended in T0, Super-Natural Instructions, MetaICL, and InstructGPT. However, much of the data that drives these advances remain unreleased to the broader research community. 
    
In “The Flan Collection: Designing Data and Methods for Effective Instruction Tuning”, we closely examine and release a newer and more extensive publicly ava…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source’s impact on the world’s 100 million developers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-01-open-sources-impact-on-the-worlds-100-million-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-01-open-sources-impact-on-the-worlds-100-million-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T18:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re taking a look at how open source software has evolved on GitHub, and how the role of a maintainer and contributor has changed alongside the massive growth in open source software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: January 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-01-github-availability-report-january-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-01-github-availability-report-january-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T16:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January, we experienced two incidents, one that resulted in degraded performance for Packages and Pages and another that impacted Git users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.17.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/01/spring-tools-4-17-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/01/spring-tools-4-17-2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lippert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Blasticians introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-blasticians-introduction</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-blasticians-introduction"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of our global DEI initiatives are our employee resource groups. These groups are aligned to shared identities and allow Elasticians to build a sense of community and belonging at work. Here, we discuss their origin and meet the Blasticians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Blasticians introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-blasticians-introduction</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-blasticians-introduction"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We formalized our employee resource groups, or as we like to call them Elastician resource groups, in 2021 but they’ve been a part of the culture at Elastic since 2016. They’ve since evolved into more than just their original Slack channels, and are formal groups focused on community, learning, and much more. 

Each ERG is ensured structure, budget, and ultimately, a voice based on any dimension of diversity, identity, allyship, and advocacy. We feel this was important in framing our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy.

The groups are aligned to shared identities, interests, affinities, or allyships with a goal to create a community of people with something in common and to encourage sharing, learning, and networking. They are also all working towards building a sense of co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bursa of Fabricius]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2732/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2732/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/bursa_of_fabricius.png" title="If an anatomical structure is named for a person, it means they were the only person to have it. Pierre Paul Broca had a special area of his brain that created powerful magnetic fields, enabling him to do 19th century fMRI research." alt="If an anatomical structure is named for a person, it means they were the only person to have it. Pierre Paul Broca had a special area of his brain that created powerful magnetic fields, enabling him to do 19th century fMRI research." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native OPA Support in Terraform Cloud Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/native-opa-support-in-terraform-cloud-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/native-opa-support-in-terraform-cloud-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Native Open Policy Agent (OPA) support allows customers who have standardized on OPA to bring their policies into Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS CloudTrail Lake Supports Ingesting Activity Events From Non-AWS Sources]]></title>
        <id>2cadae3dc824e2c665b70b1870d33db1a034c6c2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-cloudtrail-lake-supports-ingesting-activity-events-from-non-aws-sources/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T19:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2013, we announced AWS CloudTrail to track user activity and API usage. AWS CloudTrail enables auditing, security monitoring, and operational troubleshooting. CloudTrail records user activity and API calls across AWS services as events. CloudTrail events help you answer the questions of “who did what, where, and when?”. Recently we have improved the ability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Hermes, An Open Source Document Management System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-hermes-an-open-source-document-management-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-hermes-an-open-source-document-management-system"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about Hermes, an open source document management system created by HashiCorp to help streamline writing and document processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Helios, HashiCorp’s New Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-helios-hashicorp-s-new-design-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-helios-hashicorp-s-new-design-system"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helios, HashiCorp’s new open source design system, offers a peek into how we create our product UIs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 Configuration as Code Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-2.3-configuration-as-code-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-2.3-configuration-as-code-improvements"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 29, we launched Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.3, which included new and exciting features including improvements for Configuration as Code (CaC). Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 also includes improvements to automation controller as well as the introduction of Ansible validated content. This blog post will walk you through what CaC is and the benefits it can bring to your organization, including a UI and API walkthrough of automation controller and how to take a full Configuration as Code approach to your automation infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - January 31st, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/31/this-week-in-spring-january-31st-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/31/this-week-in-spring-january-31st-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Deployment Pipelines Reference Architecture and Reference Implementations]]></title>
        <id>dd2c157f3c72dd66393258908bba82d05d2db201</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new_deployment_pipelines_reference_architecture_and_-reference_implementations/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T20:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are launching a new reference architecture and a set of reference implementations for enterprise-grade deployment pipelines. A deployment pipeline automates the building, testing, and deploying of applications or infrastructures into your AWS environments. When you deploy your workloads to the cloud, having deployment pipelines is key to gaining agility and lowering time to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Adds Dynamic Provider Credentials for Vault and Official Cloud Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-dynamic-provider-credentials-vault-official-cloud-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-dynamic-provider-credentials-vault-official-cloud-providers"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic provider credentials for Terraform Cloud provide a simple and safe authentication workflow for Vault and official cloud providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – January 30, 2023]]></title>
        <id>7265ce28a89983515038362f8ac766030479bead</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-january-30-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T18:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s review post comes to you from the road, having just wrapped up sponsorship of NDC London. While there we got to speak to many .NET developers, both new and experienced with AWS, and all eager to learn more. Thanks to everyone who stopped by our expo booth to chat or ask questions to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discovering Creative Insights in Promotional Artwork]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/295e4d788db5</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/discovering-creative-insights-in-promotional-artwork-295e4d788db5?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T16:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Grace Tang, Aneesh Vartakavi, Julija Bagdonaite, Cristina Segalin, and Vi Iyengar]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Azure DevOps from Zero to Hero]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66329</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/learn-azure-devops-from-zero-to-hero/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T12:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps is FULL of so many features! Myself and Nana from Techworld with Nana teamed up to bring you an Azure DevOps Zero to Hero video! Many of you reading this blog may already be very experienced with Azure DevOps,
The post Learn Azure DevOps from Zero to Hero appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Zen of Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-zen-of-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-zen-of-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[This blog post is based on my presentation at AnsibleFest 2022 in Chicago and virtually.]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tima@redhat.com (Timothy Appnel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scalable Annotation Service — Marken]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f5ba9266d428</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/scalable-annotation-service-marken-f5ba9266d428?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T03:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Marken (Scalable Annotation Service at Netflix), an annotation is a piece of metadata which can be attached to an object from any domain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: GraalVM advocate Alina Yurenko on a Bootiful Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/a-bootiful-podcast-graalvm-advocate-alina-yurenko-on-a-bootiful-podcast</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/a-bootiful-podcast-graalvm-advocate-alina-yurenko-on-a-bootiful-podcast"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Azure 5.0 is now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/spring-cloud-azure-5-0-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/spring-cloud-azure-5-0-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.1 (codename Kilburn) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/spring-cloud-2022-0-1-codename-kilburn-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/spring-cloud-2022-0-1-codename-kilburn-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Baxter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Atlassian uses Camunda within their hyperautomation tech stack]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=71896&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=71896</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/01/atlassian-camunda-hyperautomation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T20:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why Atlassian turned to process orchestration to hyperautomate their tech stack with Camunda and deliver improved customer and employee experiences.
The post How Atlassian uses Camunda within their hyperautomation tech stack appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning with queried hints]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/learning-with-queried-hints.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/learning-with-queried-hints.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T20:46:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sreenivas Gollapudi, Senior Staff Research Scientist, and Kostas Kollias, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research, Algorithms & Optimization Team  
In many computing applications the system needs to make decisions to serve requests that arrive in an online fashion. Consider, for instance, the example of a navigation app that responds to driver requests. In such settings there is inherent uncertainty about important aspects of the problem. For example, the preferences of the driver with respect to features of the route are often unknown and the delays of road segments can be uncertain. The field of online machine learning studies such settings and provides various techniques for decision-making problems under uncertainty. 
   


A navigation engine has to decide how to route thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary KMS (Key Management Service) Root Key Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-kms-key-management-service-root-key-migration</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-kms-key-management-service-root-key-migration"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to migrate HashiCorp Boundary from one KMS provider to another, and learn more about how its encryption works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第223話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190247133138894</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190247133138894"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disable creation of classic pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66312</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/disable-creation-of-classic-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T07:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YAML pipelines offer the best security for your Azure Pipelines. In contrast to classic build and release pipelines, YAML pipelines:
Can be code reviewed. YAML pipelines are no different from any other piece of code. You can prevent malicious actors from introducing malicious steps in your pipelines by enforcing the use of Pull Requests to merge changes.
The post Disable creation of classic pipelines appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silviu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deciphering clinical abbreviations with privacy protecting ML]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/deciphering-clinical-abbreviations-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/deciphering-clinical-abbreviations-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T22:19:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Posted by Alvin Rajkomar, Research Scientist, and Eric Loreaux, Software Engineer, Google Research  
Today many people have digital access to their medical records, including their doctor’s clinical notes. However, clinical notes are hard to understand because of the specialized language that clinicians use, which contains unfamiliar shorthand and abbreviations. In fact, there are thousands of such abbreviations, many of which are specific to certain medical specialities and locales or can mean multiple things in different contexts. For example, a doctor might write in their clinical notes, “pt referred to pt for lbp“, which is meant to convey the statement: “Patient referred to physical therapy for low back pain.”  Coming up with this translation is tough for laypeople and compu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research, 2022 & beyond: Responsible AI]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/google-research-2022-beyond-responsible.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/google-research-2022-beyond-responsible.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T19:51:00.016Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Marian Croak, VP, Google Research, Responsible AI and Human-Centered Technology    
    

(This is Part 2 in our series of posts covering different topical areas of research at Google. You can find other posts in the series here.)
 
The last year showed tremendous breakthroughs in artificial intelligence (AI), particularly in large language models (LLMs) and text-to-image models. These technological advances require that we are thoughtful and intentional in how they are developed and deployed. In this blogpost, we share ways we have approached Responsible AI across our research in the past year and where we’re headed in 2023. We highlight four primary themes covering foundational and socio-technical research, applied research, and product solutions, as part of our commitment to b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022 Patch 1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66315</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-patch-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T18:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact Azure DevOps Server 2022.
Test data was not being deleted, causing the database to grow. With this fix, we updated build retention to prevent creating new orphan test data.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022 Patch 1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundamentals of Network Automation with Ansible Validated Content using the network.base collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/based-validated-network-content</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/based-validated-network-content"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We introduced resource modules in Ansible 2.9, which provided a path for users to ease network management, especially across multiple different product vendors. This announcement was significant because these resource modules added a well structured representation of device configurations and made it easy to manage common network configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Open — AWS Asia Pacific (Melbourne) Region in Australia]]></title>
        <id>afac5b6dd127ccc85ba88786f7834863c85ce956</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-aws-asia-pacific-melbourne-region-in-australia/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T23:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following up on Jeff’s post on the announcement of the Melbourne Region, today I’m pleased to share the general availability of the AWS Asia Pacific (Melbourne) Region with three Availability Zones and API name ap-southeast-4. The AWS Asia Pacific (Melbourne) Region is the second infrastructure Region in Australia, in addition to the Asia Pacific (Sydney) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-Driven Access Controls with HashiCorp Boundary and Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/event-driven-access-controls-with-hashicorp-boundary-and-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/event-driven-access-controls-with-hashicorp-boundary-and-vault"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s Rift proof-of-concept app automatically grants and revokes infrastructure access to on-call engineers when an incident is triggered and resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer Adds Ancestry to Track Image Relationships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-adds-ancestry-to-track-image-relationships</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-adds-ancestry-to-track-image-relationships"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ancestry tracking for HCP Packer provides visibility into image dependencies across your cloud environment for image lifecycle management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – January 23, 2023]]></title>
        <id>3730c1005965728eaa659a0cc8b3db0855b0fc7e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-january-23-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T18:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to my first AWS Week in Review of 2023. As usual, it has been a busy week, so let’s dive right in: Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that caught my eye last week: Amazon Connect – You can now deliver long lasting, persistent chat experiences for your customers, with the ability to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible and ChatGPT: Putting it to the test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-wisdom-and-chatgpt-putting-it-to-the-test</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-wisdom-and-chatgpt-putting-it-to-the-test"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image: DALL-E]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HashiCorp Employees Celebrate Lunar New Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-employees-celebrate-lunar-new-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-employees-celebrate-lunar-new-year"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp employees from around the world share how they’re celebrating Lunar New Year and the cultural traditions they practice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 216 update]]></title>
        <id>https://localhost/devops/?p=66295</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-216-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T20:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because of the holidays, and our deployment schedule, this update includes our progress for both sprint 215 and 216. You will notice a lot of bugs being fixed in these sprints. Some of the issues being significant.
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 216 update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy production grade automation technology at scale with Red Hat and F5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/deploy-production-grade-automation-technology-at-scale-with-red-hat-and-f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/deploy-production-grade-automation-technology-at-scale-with-red-hat-and-f5"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You will learn how F5 and Red Hat assist network teams transitioning to a NetOps workflow, while reducing risk and increasing productivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George James</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Consider All Microservices Vulnerable — And Monitor Their Behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/20/security-behavior-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/20/security-behavior-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author:
David Hadas (IBM Research Labs)
This post warns Devops from a false sense of security. Following security best practices when developing and configuring microservices do not result in non-vulnerable microservices. The post shows that although all deployed microservices are vulnerable, there is much that can be done to ensure microservices are not exploited. It explains how analyzing the behavior of clients and services from a security standpoint, named here "Security-Behavior Analysis", can protect the deployed vulnerable microservices. It points to Guard, an open source project offering security-behavior monitoring and control of Kubernetes microservices presumed vulnerable.
As cyber attacks continue to intensify in sophistication, organizations deploying cloud services continue t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks, PagerDuty, ServiceNow, and VMware Highlight Continued Vault Ecosystem Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/palo-alto-networks-pagerduty-servicenow-vmware-highlight-vault-eco-growth</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/palo-alto-networks-pagerduty-servicenow-vmware-highlight-vault-eco-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Vault ecosystem continues to grow with the addition of 25 new integrations this past quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnsibleFest 2022 Quick Take: expanding to AWS, Event-Driven Automation and Project Wisdom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansiblefest-2022-quick-take-expanding-to-aws-event-driven-automation-and-project-wisdom</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansiblefest-2022-quick-take-expanding-to-aws-event-driven-automation-and-project-wisdom"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AnsibleFest 2022 was our first in-person event in a few years, and it delivered some exciting news that will impact the growth and expansion of automation for our customers in the months to come. We had more than 450 organizations represented in person in Chicago. Our keynotes featured Red Hat, IBM Research, and Rockwell Automation. During the two days, we announced several new features and capabilities to make adopting automation more accessible. In addition, IDC analyst Jevin Jensen recently published his opinions and insights on AnsibleFest 2022 that we break down below .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.15 Improves Integration with Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-15-improves-integration-with-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-15-improves-integration-with-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform (CDKTF) 0.15 improves on its ease of use with Terraform Cloud and Terraform Enterprise through automatic Terraform workspace creation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is hyperautomation?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=71621&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=71621</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/01/what-is-hyperautomation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T03:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about what hyperautomation is, why it's important and how you can think about applying it to your organization today.
The post What is hyperautomation? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research, 2022 & beyond: Language, vision and generative models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/google-research-2022-beyond-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/google-research-2022-beyond-language.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T19:01:00.021Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeff Dean, Senior Fellow and SVP of Google Research, on behalf of the Google Research community 
   
Today we kick off a series of blog posts about exciting new developments from Google Research. Please keep your eye on this space and look for the title “Google Research, 2022 & Beyond” for more articles in the series.
 
I’ve always been interested in computers because of their ability to help people better understand the world around them.  Over the last decade, much of the research done at Google has been in pursuit of a similar vision — to help people better understand the world around them and get things done. We want to build more capable machines that partner with people to accomplish a huge variety of tasks.  All kinds of tasks.  Complex, information-seeking tasks.  Creativ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to become a developer advocate: Part 2, building empathy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-2-building-empathy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-2-building-empathy"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second installment in a blog series on how to build the skills needed to become a developer advocate (or similar technical roles). This post focuses on building empathy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Adds ‘Projects’ to Organize Workspaces at Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-projects-to-organize-workspaces-at-scale</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-projects-to-organize-workspaces-at-scale"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Projects in Terraform Cloud allow users to isolate particular subsets of workspaces and define permissions within a single organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AAP 2.3 Introducing Remote Execution Mesh Nodes for Openshift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/aap-2.3-introducing-remote-execution-mesh-nodes-for-openshift</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/aap-2.3-introducing-remote-execution-mesh-nodes-for-openshift"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year Ansible Automation Platform (AAP) 2 introduced major changes around the mechanics on how automation is run. Learn about remote execution nodes for Openshift with these changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – January 16, 2023]]></title>
        <id>719a3a544137875e791a469a0df199b6819e71ca</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-january-16-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T19:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we celebrate Martin Luther King Jr. Day in the US to honor the late civil rights leader’s life, legacy, and achievements. In this article, Amazon employees share what MLK Day means to them and how diversity makes us stronger. Coming back to our AWS Week in Review—it’s been a busy week! Last Week’s Launches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build, preview, and test dynamic forms for user tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=71125&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=71125</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/01/build-preview-test-dynamic-forms-user-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T18:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the latest ways to build, preview and test forms to enable effective human workflow orchestration with Camunda Platform 8.
The post Build, preview, and test dynamic forms for user tasks appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Scale Test Report to Observe Gossip Stability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-scale-test-report-to-observe-gossip-stability</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-scale-test-report-to-observe-gossip-stability"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our tests show Consul servers remain healthy under all test configurations and that splitting up a large LAN gossip pool cuts the risk of gossip instability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organization profile image]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66263</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/organization-profile-image/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T22:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, it’s hard to believe it’s already 2023! Here at Azure DevOps, we want to wish all of you a Happy New Year and share a small improvement we just added to the product roadmap.
The post Organization profile image appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brenner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HCP-Based Global Management Plane for Consul Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-based-global-management-plane-for-consul-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-based-global-management-plane-for-consul-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new global management plane for Consul is now available as a free public beta. Try it out to gain full visibility for both self-managed and HCP Consul clusters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>