<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-12T00:17:33.503Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-12T00:17:33.503Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toward Vagrant 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/toward-vagrant-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/toward-vagrant-3-0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In order to support its growing ecosystem and community as we move toward the 3.0 release, we are making changes to Vagrant that will maintain its Ruby-based features while being ported to Go.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle Cloud with Salman Paracha]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11073</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/11/oracle-cloud-with-salman-paracha/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oracle-cloud-with-salman-paracha"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T09:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corey Quinn is guest hosting on Software Engineering Daily this week, presenting a Tour of the Cloud. Corey Quinn is the Chief Cloud Economist at The Duckbill Group, where he helps companies fix their AWS bill by making it smaller and less horrifying. If you’re looking to lower your AWS bill or negotiate a new
The post Oracle Cloud with Salman Paracha appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.06.11]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61839</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-06-11/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T08:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.06.11 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.06.11 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Works – AWS Region in Tel Aviv, Israel]]></title>
        <id>f057ea11c459d137b14bd39a8b215fd1b55c46d0</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/ObHL8-p0Y_0/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T04:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched three AWS Regions (Italy, South Africa, and Japan) in the last 12 months, and are working on regions in Australia, Indonesia, Spain, India, Switzerland, and the United Arab Emirates. Tel Aviv, Israel in the Works Today I am happy to announce that the AWS Israel (Tel Aviv) Region is in the works and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Redgate technical lead for the Flyway team Mikiel Agutu on database migrations and continuous delivery]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/10/a-bootiful-podcast-redgate-technical-lead-for-the-flyway-team-mikiel-agutu-on-database-migrations-and-continuous-delivery</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/10/a-bootiful-podcast-redgate-technical-lead-for-the-flyway-team-mikiel-agutu-on-database-migrations-and-continuous-delivery"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Mikiel Agutu, technical lead for the Flyway team at Redgate software about database migrations and continuous delivery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/10/spring-boot-2-5-1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/10/spring-boot-2-5-1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.1 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes about 70 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Presents: Migrating Your Data – Create Your Cosmos DB]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61708</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-presents-migrating-your-data-create-your-cosmos-db/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T18:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series of posts, I will focus on how to prepare ourselves from having to do manual work to handle our database systems. Each post will provide you with a step to take to begin moving data into the cloud.
The post AzureFunBytes Presents: Migrating Your Data – Create Your Cosmos DB appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to configure Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes with SAML and hot-warm-cold architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-configure-elastic-cloud-on-kubernetes-with-saml-and-hot-warm-cold-architecture</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-configure-elastic-cloud-on-kubernetes-with-saml-and-hot-warm-cold-architecture"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes (ECK) is an easy way to get the Elastic Stack up and running on top of Kubernetes. That’s because ECK automates the deployment, provisioning, management, and setup of Elasticsearch, Kibana, Beats, and more. 

As logging and metric data — or time series data — has a predictable lifespan, you can use hot, warm, and cold architecture to easily manage your data over time as it ages and becomes less relevant.

In this guide, we’ll explain how to set up SAML with auth0 as an identity provider (IdP) as well as how to configure your deployment for hot-warm-cold architecture with ECK. We’ll use production features such as:

Dedicated nodes
Zone awareness
Pod and node affinity
PodDisruption
Dedicated storage class
Before you get started, you should be familiar with SAML. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francismara Souza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.4.7 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/10/spring-boot-2-4-7-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/10/spring-boot-2-4-7-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T12:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.4.7 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 36 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.3.12.RELEASE available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/10/spring-boot-2-3-12-release-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/10/spring-boot-2-3-12-release-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T12:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.3.12.RELEASE has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 26 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Ocean with John Allspaw]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11072</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/10/digital-ocean-with-john-allspaw/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=digital-ocean-with-john-allspaw"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T09:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corey Quinn is guest hosting on Software Engineering Daily this week, presenting a Tour of the Cloud. Corey Quinn is the Chief Cloud Economist at The Duckbill Group, where he helps companies fix their AWS bill by making it smaller and less horrifying. If you’re looking to lower your AWS bill or negotiate a new
The post Digital Ocean with John Allspaw appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome, Camunda Champions]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=22069</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/06/welcome-camunda-champions/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T08:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re thrilled to introduce our first cohort of Camunda Champions - individuals who demonstrate product expertise while actively supporting and contributing to developer communities.
The post Welcome, Camunda Champions appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Buchholz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Named as the Outright Leader in Enterprise MLOps Platforms]]></title>
        <id>0d87f068b55fc7843f4a16efa94e7f39317a52d1</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/XANxIh1DrHo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T18:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few years, Machine Learning (ML) has proven its worth in helping organizations increase efficiency and foster innovation. As ML matures, the focus naturally shifts from experimentation to production. ML processes need to be streamlined, standardized, and automated to build, train, deploy, and manage models in a consistent and reliable way. Perennial IT […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How South Dakota Bureau of Information and Telecommunications deploys Elastic to secure endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-south-dakota-bureau-of-information-and-telecommunications-deploys-elastic-to-secure-endpoints</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-south-dakota-bureau-of-information-and-telecommunications-deploys-elastic-to-secure-endpoints"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The South Dakota Bureau of Information and Telecommunications (BIT) provides quality customer services and partnerships to ensure South Dakota’s IT organization is responsive, reliable, and well-aligned to support the state government’s business needs.

The BIT believes that “People should be online, not waiting in line.”

The bureau’s goals for the state's 885,000 residents include: 

Delivering valuable services at economical costs
Building and retaining a highly skilled workforce
Providing reliable, secure, and modern infrastrastructure
When it comes to meeting the goal of a secure government infrastructure, the BIT discovered that its legacy SIEM solution couldn’t adequately monitor and alert on all of the endpoints associated with more than 9,000 systems. The BIT chose Elastic because…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Packer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-packer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-packer"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer is a new cloud service designed to bridge the gap between image creation and deployment with image-management workflows. The service will be available for beta testing in the coming months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Cloud Platform Adds Transit Gateway, Okta Support, New Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-cloud-platform-adds-transit-gateway-okta-new-skus</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-cloud-platform-adds-transit-gateway-okta-new-skus"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Cloud Platform (HCP) now has expanded capabilities for networking, single sign-on, and more. HCP will also support new configurations of HashiCorp Consul and HashiCorp Vault in the coming months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.8 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/09/spring-framework-5-3-8-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/09/spring-framework-5-3-8-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T09:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.8 is available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.8 includes 35 fixes and improvements. 

Stay tuned for follow-up Spring Boot releases later this week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intelligent Process Automation with Camunda and Amazon Comprehend]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=21971</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/06/intelligent-process-automation-with-camunda-and-amazon-comprehend/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T09:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our partner Novatec combined Business Process Management with Artificial Intelligence, and the result was awesome!
The post Intelligent Process Automation with Camunda and Amazon Comprehend appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCP with Liz Fong-Jones]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11059</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/09/gcp-with-liz-fong-jones/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=gcp-with-liz-fong-jones"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T09:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corey Quinn is guest hosting on Software Engineering Daily this week, presenting a Tour of the Cloud. Corey Quinn is the Chief Cloud Economist at The Duckbill Group, where he helps companies fix their AWS bill by making it smaller and less horrifying. If you’re looking to lower your AWS bill or negotiate a new
The post GCP with Liz Fong-Jones appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 8th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/08/this-week-in-spring-june-8th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/08/this-week-in-spring-june-8th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T06:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! What’s shaking? It’s one of those weeks where, even though the thing I wanted to happen - a vacation with the family - didn’t happen, what did happen - accidentally lots of free time with no meetings - has turned out wonderfully. It was all I could do to pry myself from the IDE to pull together this week’s roundup, but I am glad I did! There’s a ton of great stuff there. Let’s dive into it.


  
I love this post by the good Dr. David Syer: “Wiremock” for RSocket

  
In this week’s installment of A Bootiful Podcast, JHipster creator and Microsoft Java Developer Advocacy manager Julien Dubois

  
Kotlin 1.5.0 Release Community Event

  
This is super interesting: OpenJDK on RISC-V - an update from Alibaba

  
To all the readers of my little book so far: Thank you! Schiko on Twitter: “Reactive Spring” by @starbuxman is without a doubt the best programming book i’ve ever read. Thanks Josh! https://t.co/nAzdK4kNyn #springboot #Java" / Twitter

  
Spring Integration AWS 2.5.1 and Spring Cloud Stream Kinesis Binder 2.2.0 Available

  
The presentation that Brian Sam Bodden and I did for RedisConf - “An application framework worthy of Redis” - is now available on YouTube! Check it out!

  
What’s new with content at VMworld 2021?

  
agschnitzer/multitenant: Multi-Tenant Spring Boot Application using Hibernate and H2

  
Got 30 minutes? Learn how to propel Java applications into the future with @AzureCosmosDB, a fast NoSQL database with open APIs for any scale! Start learning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Time Since Early 2020]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2474/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2474/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/first_time_since_early_2020.png" title="Gotten the Ferris wheel operator's attention" alt="Gotten the Ferris wheel operator's attention" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Access Auditing Is Now Available for Amazon FSx for Windows File Server]]></title>
        <id>0a6f033f543473ec26043a249a9479efeac02c59</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/RJ2Ne6UWkrg/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T21:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for Windows File Server provides fully managed file storage that is accessible over the industry-standard Server Message Block (SMB) protocol. It is built on Windows Server and offers a rich set of enterprise storage capabilities with the scalability, reliability, and low cost that you have come to expect from AWS. In addition to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Beeby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total Economic Impact<sup>TM</sup> study: Elastic delivers 10X performance with up to 75% cost savings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/total-economic-impact-study-elastic-delivers-10x-performance-with-up-to-75-percent-cost-savings</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/total-economic-impact-study-elastic-delivers-10x-performance-with-up-to-75-percent-cost-savings"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten times faster at a fraction of the cost.

If you want a headline as to why you should consider adopting Elastic for security and observability, that is it. 

We often work with our customers to help them establish the business value of Elastic within their organizations. We commissioned Forrester to conduct a Total Economic Impact (TEI) study of our security and observability solutions so our customers have an unbiased view that they can share with their internal stakeholders. The TEI examines the ROI organizations realize by deploying the Elastic Observability and Security solutions. 

This study showcases the incredible value that our customers are achieving and provides guidance to help you consider the costs, benefits, and business impact Elastic can bring to your organization. 

Th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Pruden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ProblemChild: Generate alerts to detect living-off-the-land attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/problemchild-generate-alerts-to-detect-living-off-the-land-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/problemchild-generate-alerts-to-detect-living-off-the-land-attacks"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an earlier blog post, we spoke about building your own ProblemChild framework from scratch in the Elastic Stack to detect living off the land (LOtL) activity. As promised, we have now also released a fully trained detection model, anomaly detection configurations, and detection rules that you can use to get ProblemChild up and running in your environment in a matter of minutes. 

This blog provides a high-level breakdown of the steps to enrich your Windows process event data using the released model to generate alerts when LOtL activity is detected in your environment. A more detailed documentation of the steps to be followed can be found in our publicly available detection-rules repository. 
 
ProblemChild: A brief history

ProblemChild is a framework built using the Elastic Stack to d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Apoorva Joshi,Disha Dasgupta,Justin Ibarra,Craig Chamberlain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 42 – Hybrid Cloud on Azure with @ThomasMaurer]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61745</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-42-hybrid-cloud-on-azure-with-thomasmaurer/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T17:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 42 – Hybrid Cloud on Azure with @ThomasMaurer appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.1.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=22042</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/06/camunda-cloud-110-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T15:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Cloud 1.1.0-alpha1, which includes 1.1.0-alpha1  versions of Zeebe, Operate and
The post Camunda Cloud 1.1.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnsibleFest 2021 CFP is Open]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansiblefest-2021-cfp-is-open</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansiblefest-2021-cfp-is-open"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AnsibleFest will be a free, virtual two day event again this year on September 29-30. You can expect all the usual highlights, like customer keynotes, breakout sessions, direct access to Ansible experts and more. We will also be bringing back tracks from last year like Network, Security, Developer and more to give you exactly the type of information you need for wherever you are in your Ansible journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@ansible.com (Ansible)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Terraform 1.0 General Availability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-terraform-1-0-general-availability</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-terraform-1-0-general-availability"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.0 — now generally available — marks a major milestone for interoperability, ease of upgrades, and maintenance for your automation workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Updates Improve Workflow Visibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-improved-visibility-for-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-improved-visibility-for-workflows"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing several improvements to HashiCorp Terraform Cloud, focusing on visibility and extensibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure with Troy Hunt]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11056</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/08/azure-with-troy-hunt/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=azure-with-troy-hunt"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T09:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corey Quinn is guest hosting on Software Engineering Daily this week, presenting a Tour of the Cloud. Corey Quinn is the Chief Cloud Economist at The Duckbill Group, where he helps companies fix their AWS bill by making it smaller and less horrifying. If you’re looking to lower your AWS bill or negotiate a new
The post Azure with Troy Hunt appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.5.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=21941</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/06/camunda-optimize-3-5-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.5.0-alpha2, featuring a new Elasticsearch header plugin, and Report embedding improvements. 
The post Camunda Optimize 3.5.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Mueller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=21820</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/06/camunda-platform-runtime-7160-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16. This release features the following improvements: Cockpit: Set Variables on Process Instance Migration (Enterprise) 7 Bug Fixes You can Download Camunda for free or Run it with Docker. For a complete list of all improvements, take a look at the release notes. Please also see the list of known issues. If you want to dig in deeper, you can find the source code on GitHub. Cockpit: Set Variables on Process Instance Migration This feature is only available in the Enterprise Edition of the Camunda Platform Runtime — try it out with a free trial. Our last alpha release featured the option to Set Variables on Process...
The post Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda BPM Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Open Third Availability Zone in the AWS China (Beijing) Region]]></title>
        <id>26697c1bef85d014c81418b796139fe7d1cc07af</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/GU_WAN0eq7s/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T23:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I made my first trip to China in late 2008. I was able to speak to developers and entrepreneurs and to get a sense of the then-nascent market for cloud computing. With over 900 million Internet users as of 2020 (according to a recent report from China Internet Network Information Center), China now has the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Windows protected processes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/protecting-windows-protected-processes</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/protecting-windows-protected-processes"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This quick blog is the first in a two-part series discussing a userland Windows exploit initially disclosed by James Forshaw and Alex Ionescu. The exploit enables attackers to perform highly privileged actions that typically require a kernel driver.

Protected process light
Windows 8.1 introduced the concept of Protected Process Light (PPL), which enables specially-signed programs to run in such a way that they are immune from tampering and termination, even by administrative users. The goal is to keep malware from running amok — tampering with critical system processes and terminating anti-malware applications. There is a hierarchy of PPL “levels,” with higher-privilege ones immune from tampering by lower-privilege ones, but not vice-versa. 

For more information on PPL processes, please …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriel Landau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS with Pete Cheslock]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11042</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/07/aws-with-pete-cheslock/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=aws-with-pete-cheslock"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corey Quinn is guest hosting on Software Engineering Daily this week, presenting a Tour of the Cloud. Corey Quinn is the Chief Cloud Economist at The Duckbill Group, where he helps companies fix their AWS bill by making it smaller and less horrifying. If you’re looking to lower your AWS bill or negotiate a new
The post AWS with Pete Cheslock appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pride @ Elastic | Feeling seen and safe as a trans woman]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-pride-at-elastic-feeling-seen-and-safe-as-a-trans-woman</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-pride-at-elastic-feeling-seen-and-safe-as-a-trans-woman"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all want to work for a company where we fit in. That’s why Elastic built a Source Code that encourages all to come as they are. In this Pride blog series, we highlight LGBTQIA+ Elasticians who have a unique story — one, perhaps, just as unique as yours.

We asked Kiley Davidson, IT Systems Engineer, to talk about her experience and share how Elastic’s culture allowed her to come out at work and thrive as a trans woman.
 
How did you know that Elastic was a safe place for you when you joined in 2018?

When I joined Elastic in April of 2018, I knew I was trans, but wasn’t out to anyone but my wife and therapist. Even after starting my transition later that year, the idea of coming out at work was utterly terrifying: considering what often happens when transgender people transition at work…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2473/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2473/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/product_launch.png" title="&quot;Okay, that was weird, but the product reveal was normal. I think the danger is pas--&quot; &quot;One more thing.&quot; &quot;Oh no.&quot;" alt="&quot;Okay, that was weird, but the product reveal was normal. I think the danger is pas--&quot; &quot;One more thing.&quot; &quot;Oh no.&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration AWS 2.5.1 and Spring Cloud Stream Kinesis Binder 2.2.0 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/04/spring-integration-aws-2-5-1-and-spring-cloud-stream-kinesis-binder-2-2-0-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/04/spring-integration-aws-2-5-1-and-spring-cloud-stream-kinesis-binder-2-2-0-available"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T17:51:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,



Today it’s my pleasure to announce releases of Spring Integration for Amazon Web Services extension versions 2.5.1 and Spring Cloud Stream Binder for AWS Kinesis 2.2.0.



These releases can be downloaded from Maven Central:




compile 'org.springframework.integration:spring-integration-aws:2.5.1'




If you don’t use Kinesis Binder.
Or via Binder dependency:




compile 'org.springframework.cloud:spring-cloud-stream-binder-kinesis:2.2.0'




Spring Integration for AWS extension of 2.5.1 has some minor bug fixes after the previous 2.5.0 announcement.



The Spring Cloud Stream Binder for AWS Kinesis 2.2.0 is the first release in the project generation which is based on a new independent Spring Cloud for AWS artifact. It also was upgraded to the latest Spring Cloud 2020.0.3 and has some other bug fixes and improvements.



Any feedback is welcome via all the available communication channels!



Spring Integration for AWS resources:



Project Page | Contributing | Help | Chat



Spring Cloud Stream Binder for AWS Kinesis resources:



Project Page | Contributing | Help | Chat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.06.04]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61806</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-06-04/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T12:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.06.04 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.06.04 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning: The Great Stagnation with Mark Saroufim]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11012</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/04/machine-learning-the-great-stagnation-with-mark-saroufim/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=machine-learning-the-great-stagnation-with-mark-saroufim"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Saroufim is the author of an article entitled “Machine Learning: The Great Stagnation”. Mark is a PyTorch Partner Engineer with Facebook AI. He has spent his entire career developing machine learning and artificial intelligence products. Before joining Facebook to do PyTorch engineering with external partners, Mark was a Machine Learning Engineer at Graphcore. Before
The post Machine Learning: The Great Stagnation with Mark Saroufim appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzy Blob]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2472/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2472/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/fuzzy_blob.png" title="If there's no dome, how do you explain the irregularities the board discovered in the zoning permits issued in that area!?" alt="If there's no dome, how do you explain the irregularities the board discovered in the zoning permits issued in that area!?" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Waypoint 0.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-waypoint-0-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-waypoint-0-4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.4 adds significant features, including mutable deployments and platform health reporting, among others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the newest AWS Heroes – June, 2021]]></title>
        <id>7abd88a50e7ca1187d62163688b6b675525deccb</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/gyB86BhvmFk/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We at AWS continue to be impressed by the passion AWS enthusiasts have for knowledge sharing and supporting peer-to-peer learning in tech communities. A select few of the most influential and active community leaders in the world, who truly go above and beyond to create content and help others build better & faster on AWS, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use transforms to track your most recent customer orders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-use-transforms-to-track-your-most-recent-customer-orders</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-use-transforms-to-track-your-most-recent-customer-orders"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an entity-centric index that contains only the latest document for each entity can be useful in a number of situations. For example, maybe you're managing an ecommerce site and you want to track the latest order placed by each of your customers. Or maybe you want to run a campaign targeting customers who haven't been active over a certain period. What's the fastest and most efficient way to compile and organize such data?

Transforms in Elasticsearch enable you to create and maintain an entity-centric index based on the event index and a transforming function. Until recently, the only possible function was pivot, which is a continuous group-by plus aggregations. In version 7.12, we’ve added one more transforming function, called latest. It transforms a source index into a destinat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Przemysław Witek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New policies to restrict personal access token scope and lifespan]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61796</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-policies-to-restrict-personal-access-token-scope-and-lifespan/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T17:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Personal access tokens (PATs) make it easy to authenticate against Azure Devops to integrate with your tools and services. However, leaked tokens could compromise your Azure DevOps account and data, putting your applications and services at significant risk.
The post New policies to restrict personal access token scope and lifespan appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pazand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic License Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-license-update</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-license-update"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January 2021, we announced that starting with version 7.11, we would be changing the Apache 2.0 portions of Elasticsearch and Kibana source code to be dual licensed under Elastic License and SSPL, at the users’ discretion. As part of that change, we created Elastic License 2.0 (ELv2) as a permissive,  fair-code license, which allows free use, redistribution, modification, and derivative works, with only three simple limitations, outlined in our original announcement.  
  
 We've been happy to see the level of community support for this change.  While we would have preferred to collaborate with Amazon, we're glad that with their fork and commitment to rename the Amazon Elasticsearch Service, it means that they will no longer be the cause of confusion in the Elasticsearch and Kibana commu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kearns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Unbelievable Demo]]></title>
        <id>http://www.brendangregg.com/blog/2021-06-04/an-unbelievable-demo.html</id>
        <link href="http://www.brendangregg.com/blog/2021-06-04/an-unbelievable-demo.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the story of the most unbelievable demo I've been given in world of open source. You can't make this stuff up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Gregg's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Special Edition Repeat: AWS Analysis with Corey Quinn]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11027</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/03/special-edition-repeat-aws-analysis-with-corey-quinn/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=special-edition-repeat-aws-analysis-with-corey-quinn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T09:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next week Corey Quinn will be guest hosting on Software Engineering Daily, presenting a Tour of the Cloud. Corey Quinn is the Chief Cloud Economist at The Duckbill Group, where he helps companies fix their AWS bill by making it smaller and less horrifying. If you’re looking to lower your AWS bill or negotiate a
The post Special Edition Repeat: AWS Analysis with Corey Quinn appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: JHipster creator and Microsoft Java Developer Advocacy manager Julien Dubois]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/03/a-bootiful-podcast-jhipster-creator-and-microsoft-java-developer-advocacy-manager-julien-dubois</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/03/a-bootiful-podcast-jhipster-creator-and-microsoft-java-developer-advocacy-manager-julien-dubois"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to JHipster creator and Microsoft Java Developer Advocacy manager Julien Dubois (@juliendubois)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Wiremock" for RSocket]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/02/wiremock-for-rsocket</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/02/wiremock-for-rsocket"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T19:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have an application that connects to an RSocket server at runtime, how do you test it? We need a way for a test to start a server and tell us where it is listening, and then we need to be able to register request and response examples (a.k.a. "contracts"). That’s what this project provides - it’s like Wiremock but for RSocket.



Getting Started



The easiest way to use the project is as a JUnit (Jupiter) extension, e.g:




@SpringBootTest
@ExtendWith(RSocketServerExtension.class)
class SocketsApplicationTests {
	...
}




With this extension installed the Spring Boot tests will run with an RSocket server listening on a port given by test.rsocket.server.port, so the test can connect directly to it, or (more likely) the code that it is testing will connect to it. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cerner depends on Elastic machine learning for a healthy infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/cerner-depends-on-elastic-machine-learning-for-a-healthy-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/cerner-depends-on-elastic-machine-learning-for-a-healthy-infrastructure"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cerner Corp. is a supplier of healthcare information technology systems, services, and devices. The company, with $5.7 billion in annual revenue, empowers people and communities to engage in their own care. A key aspect of the business is surfacing data to enable their clients to make informed decisions about their healthcare. 

The 29,000 Cerner employees in 30 countries are on a mission to shape the healthcare of tomorrow. They believe that their influence goes beyond healthcare, and impacts the world.

Jim Avazpour, Director of Infrastructure, says Cerner was challenged by the massive amount of data that they log — network storage, virtualization, and supporting services — to monitor the health of its infrastructure. In response, Cerner chose Elasticsearch as their logging solution to h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.13.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-13-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-13-1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.13.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
The 7.13.1 patch contains fixes and small enhancements for the stack. Notable bug fixes are:
Kibana: Some "By value" panels not rendering after upgrade from 7.12.1 to 7.13.0 (#100756)
Kibana: "Math" aggregation not working for Table view in TSVB (#100892)
Elasticsearch: Fix illegal access on PIT creation for frozen index (#73517)
Elasticsearch: Fix snapshot shard data lost issue when an index is deleted while the cluster is concurrently taking more than one snapshot (#73456)
For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
7.13.1 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Workplace Search
Elastic Observability
APM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clint Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modeling with Camunda: The Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=21776</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/06/camunda-modeler-cawemo-bpmnio-the-podcast/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T16:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the Camunda Nation podcast is live, and this time we’re talking all things BPMN Modeling with Camunda Platform engineer Maciej Barelkowski.
The post Modeling with Camunda: The Podcast appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Tutorials on HashiCorp Learn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-tutorials-on-hashicorp-learn</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-tutorials-on-hashicorp-learn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From working with providers, to managing resources, to working with Terraform on AWS, we have a lot of new hands-on Terraform exercises to try.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in Elasticsearch 7.13: Even faster aggregations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-in-elasticsearch-7-13-even-faster-aggregations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-in-elasticsearch-7-13-even-faster-aggregations"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our last episode, I wrote about some speed improvements to date_histogram and I was beside myself with excitement to see if I could apply the same principles to other aggregations. I've spent most of the past few months playing a small part developing runtime fields but eventually I found time to take a look at the terms aggregation.
 
It's time for terms!

With the date_histogram aggregation we got a huge performance boost by rewriting it as a filters aggregation internally. Rewriting terms as filters has more mixed results. I often saw a wonderful speed up (454ms -> 131ms). Check the linked PR for more about "often". But now that we've rewritten the agg as filters, we can do much better! 

We landed another optimization that I'm really excited about. It's such a great shortcut it feel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Everett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes – Intro to Bicep]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61789</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-intro-to-bicep/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T14:33:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes – Intro to Bicep appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon: Connecting Ethereum Compatible Blockchain Networks with Denis Ermolin]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11011</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/02/polygon-connecting-ethereum-compatible-blockchain-networks-with-denis-ermolin/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=polygon-connecting-ethereum-compatible-blockchain-networks-with-denis-ermolin"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T09:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Platforms like Ethereum have billions of dollars of market cap and large developer communities. However, it is still a challenge to build widely adopted DApps on it because of current limitations. Blockchain Proof of Work transactions are typically slow, and Proof of Stake transactions trade off decentralization to achieve high throughput. Transaction fees get expensive,
The post Polygon: Connecting Ethereum Compatible Blockchain Networks with Denis Ermolin appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hippo Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2471/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2471/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/hippo_attacks.png" title="It's cool how, when there's a number lots of people are curious about, but which isn't easy to measure, some random guess will get cited everywhere and become the universally quoted value. Unrelatedly, did you know there are 850 trillion waves in the ocean?" alt="It's cool how, when there's a number lots of people are curious about, but which isn't easy to measure, some random guess will get cited everywhere and become the universally quoted value. Unrelatedly, did you know there are 850 trillion waves in the ocean?" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 1st, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/01/this-week-in-spring-june-1st-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/06/01/this-week-in-spring-june-1st-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How’re you doing? I’m doing well! I hope you’re doing well, too. Can you believe we’ve just entered the month of June 2021? WHERE HAS THIS YEAR GONE ALREADY! It’s insane. But, the march of Spring continues, and with each passing week a ton of new stuff to talk about arrives. Let’s get into it!


  
In last week’s episode of A Bootiful Podcast, I talked to Micrometer-lead Tommy Ludwig

  
Announcing the general availability of the Azure Spring Cloud Terraform provider

  
Cool to see an Azure Spring Cloud success story in the MSBuild keynote

  
Get your reactive microservices to Kubernetes with Spring Boot and JHipster

  
Michael Coté asks on Twitter: What’s an API Gateway and why would you use it? Also, what does “business value” mean here? See the full interview with Rita Marinachi, Chris Sterling, and me to hear even more and also a how API gateways fit with service meshes.

  
Providing useful API error messages with Spring Boot

  
Spring Cloud 2020.0.3 (aka Ilford) Is Available

  
Spring Cloud Gateway for Kubernetes lead Chris Sterling on Redmonk

  
Spring Microservices Security Best Practices

  
Spring PetClinic Data JDBC upgraded to Java 16. Records do make a difference 

  
Check out this terminal application for the Spring Initializr: Spring Starter Terminal

  
This is a reasonable JUnit test runner that hides the green test result logs so as to bring the errors to sharp relief

  
I found this old comic book about the amazing adventures of Java mascot Duke, and it is well worth a read: jcp-ec/AmazingAdventuresOfDuke.pdf at master · jcp-org/jcp-ec · GitHub

  
this is an interesting blog on sending HTTP requests with WebClient]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Location Service Is Now Generally Available with New Routing and Satellite Imagery Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>a2bd2230a3cfaa594dc21e5b83c47a560eb39bf2</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/6PBkZP5YxbM/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T19:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December of 2020, we made Amazon Location Service available in preview form for you to start building web and mobile applications with location-based features. Today I’m pleased to announce that we are making Amazon Location generally available along with two new features: routing and satellite imagery. I have been a full-stack developer for over […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Support for Amazon ECS Anywhere in the Terraform AWS Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-day-support-for-amazon-ecs-anywhere-terraform-aws-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-day-support-for-amazon-ecs-anywhere-terraform-aws-provider"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform AWS provider now supports ECS Anywhere, a new capability in Amazon ECS that supports running and managing container-based applications on customers’ on-premises servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Community Steering Committee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-community-steering-committee</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-community-steering-committee"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we all know, Ansible is a well-adapted tool for the end-to-end automation of IT infrastructures. At the same time, due to the addition of new features and developments within the project, the Ansible community is growing at an accelerated rate. To help structure the project and also to facilitate the change in direction, we are launching a Steering Committee for the Ansible Community Project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Ansible Community Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Apply User Interface for Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-apply-user-interface-for-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-apply-user-interface-for-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The redesigned interface for HashiCorp Terraform Cloud brings clarity to how your resources, state, and infrastructure operations are represented during a Terraform run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Outpost Engineering with Joshua Burgin]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11003</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/01/aws-outpost-engineering-with-joshua-burgin/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=aws-outpost-engineering-with-joshua-burgin"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Outposts is a fully managed service that offers the same AWS infrastructure, AWS services, APIs, and tools to virtually any datacenter, co-location space, or on-premises facility for a truly consistent hybrid experience. AWS Outposts is ideal for workloads that require low latency access to on-premises systems, local data processing, data residency, and migration of
The post AWS Outpost Engineering with Joshua Burgin appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter: Native Web and Mobile App Development with Allen Wyma]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11002</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/29/flutter-native-web-and-mobile-app-development-with-allen-wyma/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=flutter-native-web-and-mobile-app-development-with-allen-wyma"/>
        <updated>2021-05-29T15:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter is a UI toolkit developed by Google that helps developers build natively compiled applications for mobile, web, desktop, and embedded devices from a single code base. Development is fast because the screen “hot reloads” as you develop, the architecture is layered for fast and expressive designs, and its widgets incorporate all critical platform differences
The post Flutter: Native Web and Mobile App Development with Allen Wyma appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2020.0.3 (aka Ilford) Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/28/spring-cloud-2020-0-3-aka-ilford-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/28/spring-cloud-2020-0-3-aka-ilford-is-available"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T19:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that Service Release 3 of the Spring Cloud 2020.0 Release Train (2020.0.3) is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2020.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2020.0.3 Release Train

The biggest change in this release was support for Spring Boot 2.5. Besides that, this release is primarily for bug fixes and dependency upgrades.

See all of the included issues and pull requests at the Github project.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Added the possibility to disable load-balancing by property (#940)


Spring Cloud Config


  
Several bug fixes related to spring.config.import with Spring Cloud Config Server


Spring Cloud Consul


  
Fix profile specific behavior relative…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.05.28]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61777</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-05-28/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T17:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Friday, DevOps Friends!  Hope you had a great Microsoft Build, I know I did.  I really enjoyed a lot of the great sessions, Ask The Experts, and of course keynotes that were broadcast throughout the week.  One of my favorite sessions was Ask the Experts: Infra as Code –
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.05.28 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How diverse perspectives create a better workplace — and product]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-diverse-perspectives-create-a-better-workplace-and-product</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-diverse-perspectives-create-a-better-workplace-and-product"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a quality assurance engineer on the Kibana team at Elastic, Bhavya Raju Mandya makes an effort to see things from a different perspective. 

“My job is to break things,” says Bhavya. “I like impersonating a cat, being curious, seeing what happens if I knock something off, or moving something or changing the order to figure out what gives. The end goal is to protect and defend the quality of Kibana and that makes me happy.”

The value Bhavya places on curiosity and diverse perspectives is a direct result of her experiences. Bhavya grew up in the South of India, in a province called Karnataka. She studied software engineering and worked in Bangalore before moving to Montreal with her partner. 
“India is vast and diverse, with many different skin tones and features,” she says. “In South In…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving my US tech job to Australia]]></title>
        <id>http://www.brendangregg.com/blog/2021-05-29/moving-to-australia.html</id>
        <link href="http://www.brendangregg.com/blog/2021-05-29/moving-to-australia.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've moved from the San Francisco Bay Area to Sydney, Australia, where I will continue the best job so far of my career: Performance engineering at Netflix. I'm grateful for the support of Netflix engineering management, Netflix HRBPs, and others for helping to make this happen. While my move is among the first from the Linux cloud teams, Netflix has had staff in Australia for years (for content, marketing, and the FreeBSD OCA).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Gregg's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Process Automation in Government: Challenges, Benefits, Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=21613</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/process-automation-in-government-challenges-benefits-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T10:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we make government tech work better for our citizens and our stakeholders? 
The post Process Automation in Government: Challenges, Benefits, Best Practices appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift ML Is Now Generally Available – Use SQL to Create Machine Learning Models and Make Predictions from Your Data]]></title>
        <id>e2c09f3554087f29b1181cd21535e08f33a1a37d</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/vsIBQ-WoQ8I/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T20:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Amazon Redshift, you can use SQL to query and combine exabytes of structured and semi-structured data across your data warehouse, operational databases, and data lake. Now that AQUA (Advanced Query Accelerator) is generally available, you can improve the performance of your queries by up to 10 times with no additional costs and no code […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing CDK for Terraform 0.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-cdk-for-terraform-0-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-cdk-for-terraform-0-4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cloud Development Kit for Terraform 0.4 introduces experimental Go language support, asset construct, and Terraform Cloud integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Amazon ECS Anywhere – Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>b0c9138fd7857802566b82e31a93ec008da273b7</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/68ocNDKQLfs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T17:13:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) was launched in 2014, AWS has released other options for running Amazon ECS tasks outside of an AWS Region such as AWS Wavelength, an offering for mobile edge devices or AWS Outposts, a service that extends to customers’ environments using hardware owned and fully managed by AWS. But […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics Studio – Quickly Interact with Streaming Data Using SQL, Python, or Scala]]></title>
        <id>5183c1f235442ea38ac6eeec50996b3abd39e531</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/1k3SgVOc2Ag/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T16:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best way to get timely insights and react quickly to new information you receive from your business and your applications is to analyze streaming data. This is data that must usually be processed sequentially and incrementally on a record-by-record basis or over sliding time windows, and can be used for a variety of analytics […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Elasticsearch is an indispensable component of the Adyen stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-elasticsearch-is-an-indispensable-component-of-the-adyen-stack</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-elasticsearch-is-an-indispensable-component-of-the-adyen-stack"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Adyen, we use Elasticsearch to power various parts of our payments platform. This includes payment search, monitoring, and log search. Let’s take a look at how we use Elastic for these different use cases and see how we capitalize on the power of Elasticsearch. 

We recently did a talk about some of our Elasticsearch adventures at an Elastic meetup. You can find a recording here.

Before we look into our different use cases, it helps to get a high-level understanding of Adyen’s architecture.

At Adyen, we do many things, but the core of what we do is payment processing. Our payment platform is built for any business and every customer journey. We process payments across all sales channels. 

Let’s say you want to buy a beer at the local pub (a merchant) and you want to pay with your cre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adyen Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Exploration with a New Python Library with Doris Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10991</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/27/data-exploration-with-a-new-python-library-with-doris-lee/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-exploration-with-a-new-python-library-with-doris-lee"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data exploration uses visual exploration to understand what is in a dataset and the characteristics of the data. Data scientists explore data to understand things like customer behavior and resource utilization. Some common programming languages used for data exploration are Python, R, and Matlab.  Doris Jung-Lin Lee is currently a Graduate Research Assistant at the
The post Data Exploration with a New Python Library with Doris Lee appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Micrometer-lead Tommy Ludwig]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/27/a-bootiful-podcast-micrometer-lead-tommy-ludwig</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/27/a-bootiful-podcast-micrometer-lead-tommy-ludwig"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Micrometer-lead and observability guru Tommy Ludwig (@tommyludwig) about Tokyo, Japan; metrics; tracing; and so much more. 


  
the Micrometer project]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Management Systems and Artificial Intelligence with Arun Kumar]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10990</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/26/data-management-systems-and-artificial-intelligence-with-arun-kumar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-management-systems-and-artificial-intelligence-with-arun-kumar"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T02:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arun Kumar is an Assistant Professor in the Department of Computer Science and Engineering and the Halicioglu Data Science Institute at the University of California, San Diego. His primary research interests are in data management and systems for machine learning/artificial intelligence-based data analytics.  Systems and ideas based on his research have been released as part
The post Data Management Systems and Artificial Intelligence with Arun Kumar appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Tech Preview of Consul Service Mesh for Amazon ECS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-consul-service-mesh-for-amazon-ecs</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-consul-service-mesh-for-amazon-ecs"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS users may now select Consul as their service mesh for ECS deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run a Successful Hacktoberfest Campaign with No Prior Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=21453</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/how-to-run-a-successful-hacktoberfest-campaign-with-no-prior-experience/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T17:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did we see such a great increase in engagement during our busiest season, despite not participating in Hacktoberfest before?
The post How to Run a Successful Hacktoberfest Campaign with No Prior Experience appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[King & Wood Mallesons CISO relies on Elastic to “spot and identify” security threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/king-wood-mallesons-ciso-relies-on-elastic-to-spot-and-identify-security-threats</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/king-wood-mallesons-ciso-relies-on-elastic-to-spot-and-identify-security-threats"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[King & Wood Mallesons (KWM) is among the world’s most innovative law firms and is represented by 2,400 lawyers in 28 locations across the globe. The international law firm, based in Australia, helps clients flourish in Asian markets by helping them understand and navigate local challenges and by delivering solutions that provide clients with a competitive advantage.

The firm believes in taking a partnership approach with clients and in pushing boundaries to connect Asia to the world and the world to Asia. 

To succeed in that mission, John Reeman, the Chief Information Security Officer for KWM, says the firm began leveraging Elastic about two years ago for security operations. The move has provided the firm with fresh insights to quickly pinpoint security events across the enterprise.

“W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiConf Europe Highlights You Don’t Want to Miss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-hashiconf-europe-highlights-you-don-t-want-to-miss</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-hashiconf-europe-highlights-you-don-t-want-to-miss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe 2021 is coming June 8-11. Here are some of the highlights that you don’t want to miss, from customer stories to product deep-dives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Works – AWS Region in the United Arab Emirates (UAE)]]></title>
        <id>06a103b32d7540917020406954100ea849bffe76</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/cPBIIiAjODI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T04:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are currently building AWS regions in Australia, Indonesia, Spain, India, and Switzerland. UAE in the Works I am happy to announce that the AWS Middle East (UAE) Region is in the works and will open in the first half of 2022. The new region is an extension of our existing investment, which already includes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 7.13.0 released: Search and store more data on Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key enhancements include cost-effective search across more data with searchable snapshots and the frozen tier, analyst-driven data enhancements on the fly with runtime fields, and expanded Microsoft integrations
We are pleased to announce the general availability (GA) of Elastic 7.13. This release brings a broad set of new capabilities to our Elastic Enterprise Search, Observability, and Security solutions, which are built into the Elastic Stack — Elasticsearch and Kibana. This release enables customers to search petabytes of data in minutes cost-effectively by leveraging searchable snapshots and the new frozen tier. Analysts can now enhance data on the fly using runtime fields, our implementation of schema on read, in Kibana Lens and Discover. 

And we are building upon our Microsoft part…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kearns,Angelos Kottas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Cloud for 7.13: Microsoft Azure portal integration, Azure Private Link in private beta, and frozen tier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-cloud-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-cloud-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest updates to Elastic Cloud make it easier to deploy and manage Elasticsearch on Microsoft Azure, secure data in motion with Azure Private Link, and cost-effectively store and search more data across all cloud service providers with the frozen tier and searchable snapshots. Keep reading to learn more.
 
Easily find, deploy, and manage Elastic directly within Microsoft Azure

We’re excited to announce the latest development in our ongoing partnership with Microsoft, the public preview of our Azure portal integration, which allows you to find, deploy, and manage Elasticsearch directly within the Azure portal. You can also take advantage of simplified ingestion for Azure platform, resource, and virtual machine logs, accelerating time to value for observability. By adding Workplace Sea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 7.13 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce Elasticsearch 7.13.0, based on Apache Lucene 8.8.2. 

Version 7.13 is the latest stable release of Elasticsearch and is now available for deployment via Elasticsearch Service on Elastic Cloud or via download for use in your own environment(s).

Ready to roll up your sleeves and get started? We have the links you need:

Start Elasticsearch on Elastic Cloud
Download Elasticsearch
Elasticsearch 7.13.0 release notes
Elasticsearch 7.13.0 breaking changes
Search petabytes of data in minutes using low-cost object storage with the frozen tier
We believe that data is a differentiator for businesses and operations. But with exponential data growth, it becomes economically unfeasible to store and search it all.

The frozen tier, now generally available in 7.13, gives the abi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Kibana 7.13: With great power comes great data exploration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-kibana-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-kibana-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kibana 7.13 is now available, bringing new capabilities that give you more flexibility in ad hoc analysis and faster speed in workflows, so you can focus on exploring your data and acting on insights. Highlights include:

Creating, editing, and removing runtime fields in Discover, Kibana Lens, and index patterns via the Kibana runtime fields editor
The general availability of Elastic Maps Server and supervised machine learning
Starting with Kibana Lens as the recommended visualization for ad hoc analysis
See how far you can go in your data exploration with the power of these features (and more) by signing up for a free trial of Elasticsearch Service on Elastic Cloud. You can also download the latest versions of Kibana and the Elastic Stack. 

For a quick list of the new 7.13 features, take…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeline Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Elastic Observability 7.13: Native Azure console integration, Fleet Server, and enhanced APM workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the release of Elastic Observability 7.13. An expanded partnership with Microsoft allows seamless integration between Elastic Observability and your Azure workloads, directly from the Azure console, the new Fleet Server paves the way for better scalability and flexibility, new workflows in APM help speed up root-cause analysis, and more. Let's dive in! 
 Expanded Microsoft partnership enables seamless onboarding to Elastic Cloud via a native Azure console integration
 Through our strategic partnership with Microsoft, we are excited to announce that Elastic Cloud is now available as a native, first-class service, available directly from the Azure console. Now, users can easily discover, procure, and create Elastic deployments directly from the Azure console, just …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Security 7.13: Equip analysts with vital context]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to share Elastic Security 7.13, which connects analysts to the information they need to make smart decisions. The release is a major step forward in our support for osquery, streamlining access to host data from across your environment. Threat intelligence is surfaced in new ways and new detection content spots concerning events. Last but not least, the release shares some developments in the endpoint area and support for new data sources.

Osquery for everybody
Elastic Security 7.13 substantially broadens our support for osquery, the open source host instrumentation framework. Osquery is the not-so-secret weapon of many sophisticated security teams, augmenting numerous security, compliance, and operations use cases, such as:

Unexpected changes in disk free space or memory …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes – Containers and Kubernetes with @brendandburns]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61690</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-containers-and-kubernetes-with-brendandburns/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes – Containers and Kubernetes with @brendandburns appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2020.1 RTW]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61768</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/now-available-azure-devops-server-2020-1-rtw/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T17:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we released Azure DevOps Server 2020.1 RTW. This is our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2020.1. You can upgrade from Azure DevOps Server 2020.1 RC or previous versions of TFS and Azure DevOps. You can find the full details in our release notes.
The post Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2020.1 RTW appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AzureAD Provider Now Supports Microsoft Graph]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-azuread-provider-now-supports-microsoft-graph</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-azuread-provider-now-supports-microsoft-graph"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 1.5.0 of the Terraform AzureAD provider lets you manage your Azure Active Directory resources using the Microsoft Graph API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firebolt: Data Warehouses with Eldad Farkash]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10969</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/25/firebolt-data-warehouses-with-eldad-farkash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=firebolt-data-warehouses-with-eldad-farkash"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud data warehouses are databases hosted in cloud environments. They provide typical benefits of the cloud like flexible data access, scalability, and performance.  The company Firebolt provides a cloud data warehouse built for modern data environments. It decouples storage and compute to operate on top of existing data lakes like S3. It computes orders of
The post Firebolt: Data Warehouses with Eldad Farkash appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 25th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/24/this-week-in-spring-may-25th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/24/this-week-in-spring-may-25th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How’re you doing? I’m still fresh off my little vacation last week, feeling fantastic. I’ve spent the last several days working with Spring Boot and Spring Native and I have to tell you, they’re epic. 

It’s gotten to the point where I sometimes spend time working on enabling Spring Native integrations for other projects - it really makes some third party abstractions come alive! It’s hard to know what the right comparison is. There’s not much you can do in this life that results in such an instantaneous, night-and-day difference in performance and memory profile with so few (user-visibile) changes. Imagine snapping your fingers and having your luxury hypercar (Spring Boot in this metaphor) transform into an equally c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copy Dashboard – Public Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61759</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/copy-dashboard-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T17:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure Reporting and Analytics team is excited to announce the public preview of Copy Dashboard!
The post Copy Dashboard – Public Preview appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Waypoint Runners To Enable GitOps Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-waypoint-runners-to-enable-gitops-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-waypoint-runners-to-enable-gitops-workflows"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint runners perform builds, deployments, poll for Git repository changes, and allow deployments for any platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda Extensions Are Now Generally Available – Get Started with Your Favorite Operations Tools Today]]></title>
        <id>00cf76fbba9108f99f97d0a829f5da99bca9989e</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/Ojzzq6mN-AU/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T16:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In October 2020, we announced the preview of AWS Lambda extensions, which you can use to easily integrate Lambda functions with your favorite tools for monitoring, observability, security, and governance. Today, I’m happy to announce the general availability of AWS Lambda Extensions which comes with new performance improvements and an expanded set of partners. As […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Portainer: Container Management with Neil Cresswell]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10978</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/24/portainer-container-management-with-neil-cresswell/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=portainer-container-management-with-neil-cresswell"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T09:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running applications in containerized environments involves regularly organizing, adding and replacing containers. This complex job may involve managing clusters of containers in different geographic locations with different configuration requirements. Platforms like Kubernetes are great for managing this complexity, but include steep learning curves to efficiently get anything off the ground. The company Portainer provides a
The post Portainer: Container Management with Neil Cresswell appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Observability]]></title>
        <id>http://www.brendangregg.com/blog/2021-05-23/what-is-observability.html</id>
        <link href="http://www.brendangregg.com/blog/2021-05-23/what-is-observability.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a made-up computer word that my word processor decorates with a wiggly red you-can't-spell line. At least it did until I clicked "Add to Dictionary" (it got too annoying as I was writing a book on computer observability).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Gregg's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drafting Your Camunda Cloud Architecture – Part 2: Service Integration Patterns With BPMN And Camunda Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=20841</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/drafting-your-camunda-cloud-architecture-part-2-service-integration-patterns-with-bpmn-and-camunda-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When automating processes you typically integrate systems and services, or in other words you orchestrate various APIs. In order to achieve this you not only have different technical possibilities, but also can choose between various modeling possibilities in BPMN. This post will give you an overview and advice on how to decide between alternatives.
The post Drafting Your Camunda Cloud Architecture – Part 2: Service Integration Patterns With BPMN And Camunda Cloud appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5 is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-5-is-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-5-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T00:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update 2021-05-25: The release contains fixes for Spring Framework CVE-2021-22118.

On behalf of the Spring Boot team and everyone that has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.0 has been released and is available from Maven Central. 

This release adds a significant number of new features and improvements. For full upgrade instructions and new and noteworthy features please see the release notes.
What’s new in 2.5


  
Support for Java 16

  
Support for Gradle 7

  
Enhanced Docker image building

  
New mechanism for Datasource initialization


Additionally, the HTML documentation published by the project has an updated look-and-feel and some new features. There is also support for dark mode! 
Dependency upgrades

Spring Boot 2.5 moves to new versions of several Spring projects:


  
Spring Data 2021.0

  
Spring HATEOAS 1.3

  
Spring Integration 5.5

  
Spring Kafka 2.7

  
Spring Retry 1.3

  
Spring Security 5.5

  
Spring Session 2021.0


We’ve also upgraded to the latest stable releases of other third-party libraries wherever possible. Please see the release notes for details.
Other changes

There’s a whole host of other changes and improvements that are documented in the release notes. You can also find a list of deprecated classes and methods that we plan to remove in the next version.
Thank you

We want to take this opportunity to again thank all our users and contributors.

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask at stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.4.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-4-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-4-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T00:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update 2021-05-25: This release contains fixes for Spring Framework CVE-2021-22118.

On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.4.6 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 84 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: James Ward]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/a-bootiful-podcast-james-ward</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/a-bootiful-podcast-james-ward"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Google Cloud Developer Advocate (and mentor, and friend!) James Ward (@_JamesWard) about his podcast Happy Path Programming (@HappyPathProg), programming, software, Spring Native, and his work at various organizations like Adobe, Heroku, Lightbend, SalesForce, and now Google Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration for AWS 2.5 goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-integration-for-aws-2-5-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-integration-for-aws-2-5-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring (and AWS) Community,



Today it’s my pleasure to announce a release of Spring Integration for Amazon Web Services extension version 2.5.



It is available from Maven Central:




compile "org.springframework.integration:spring-integration-aws:2.5.0"




Mostly this version is a major move from Spring Cloud for AWS project hosted on Spring Cloud side to its own organization.
Plus it includes upgrades to the latest dependencies, including recently released Spring Integration 5.5.



Many thanks to everyone from the Community for all the feedback and contribution to this project.



Spring Integration for AWS resources:



Project Page | Contributing | Help | Chat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.3.11 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-3-11-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-3-11-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.3.11 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 52 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Secure Access Management with Boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/learn-secure-access-management-boundary</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/learn-secure-access-management-boundary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Boundary provides secure access to hosts and services based on user identity with new tutorials on HashiCorp Learn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud Zeebe K8s Operator]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=20493</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/camunda-cloud-zeebe-k8s-operator/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with Cloud Native applications on top of Kubernetes, you might need to make some tough decisions about where to run the services and infrastructure that your applications need, which will directly impact your maintenance costs.
The post Camunda Cloud Zeebe K8s Operator appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mauricio Salatino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preset: Visualizing Big Data with Srini Kadamati]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10968</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/20/preset-visualizing-big-data-with-srini-kadamati/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=preset-visualizing-big-data-with-srini-kadamati"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T09:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Superset is an open-source, fast, lightweight and modern data exploration and visualization platform. It can connect to any SQL based data source through SQLAlchemy at petabyte scale. Its architecture is highly scalable and it ships with a wide array of visualizations. The company Preset provides a powerful, easy to use data exploration and visualization
The post Preset: Visualizing Big Data with Srini Kadamati appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Web Services 3.1.1 is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-web-services-3-1-1-is-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-web-services-3-1-1-is-out"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings Spring community,



The Spring Web Services team has released 3.1.1. This is the first major release under the new versioning schema. Releases will no longer have .RELEASE and snapshots will only be -SNAPSHOT, to better comply with community approaches.



While we strive to maintain alignment with Spring Framework and Spring Security, we also test against Java 8, Java 11, and Java LATEST (JDK 16 as of today).



For more details, read the following release notes for each version:



Release Notes - Spring Web Services - Version 3.1.1.





#1198 - Test against JDK 16 on CI.



#1197 - Upgrade to Spring Framework 5.3.7.



#1187 - Upgrade to Spring Security 5.5.0.



#1199 - Don’t skip main build targets during releases.





Links: Project Page | GitHub | Issues



The artifacts are located on Maven Central. Get it while it’s hot!





SpringOne 2021 is coming



The hottest Spring conference is right around the corner. Spring developers from around the globe will sign in. It’s still not too late to register.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BaseTen: Creating Machine Learning APIs with Tuhin Srivastava and Amir Haghighat]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10963</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/19/baseten-creating-machine-learning-apis-with-tuhin-srivastava-and-amir-haghighat/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=baseten-creating-machine-learning-apis-with-tuhin-srivastava-and-amir-haghighat"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T04:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application Programming Interfaces (APIs) are interfaces that enable multiple software applications to send and retrieve data from one another. They are commonly used for retrieving, saving, editing, or deleting data from databases, transmitting data between apps, and embedding third-party services into apps. The company BaseTen helps companies build and deploy machine learning APIs and applications.
The post BaseTen: Creating Machine Learning APIs with Tuhin Srivastava and Amir Haghighat appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Support for Predictive Scaling Policy in the Terraform AWS Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-support-for-predictive-scaling-policy-in-the-terraform-aws-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-support-for-predictive-scaling-policy-in-the-terraform-aws-provider"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform AWS provider now supports predictive scaling policy, a machine learning based scaling mechanism of Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 4.2.7 and 4.3.3 are out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/19/spring-batch-4-2-7-and-4-3-3-are-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/19/spring-batch-4-2-7-and-4-3-3-are-out"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T21:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 4.2.7 and 4.3.3 have been released and are available now from Maven Central repository. These patch releases come with a number of bug fixes, improvements and dependency updates. You can find the complete change logs here: 4.2.7 and 4.3.3.

I would like to thank all contributors who had a role in these releases!

Spring Batch Home | Source on GitHub | Reference Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fun with private Automation Hub - Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/fun-with-private-automation-hub-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/fun-with-private-automation-hub-part-1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the introduction of Ansible Automation Platform 1.2 at AnsibleFest 2020, Ansible released private Automation Hub. This enables a means to deliver, manage and curate Ansible Automation Platform Certified Content via a central on-premises, self-hosted solution for use by internal automation communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Leroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS App Runner: From Code to a Scalable, Secure Web Application in Minutes]]></title>
        <id>2eb32615b0311b807948f09e866da9700a4494e7</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/95poDWZrIXg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T23:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers have become the default way that I package my web applications. Although I love the speed, productivity, and consistency that containers provide, there is one aspect of the container development workflow that I do not like: the lengthy routine I go through when I deploy a container image for the first time. You might […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Beeby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skynet Labs: Decentralized Internet with Matthew Sevey]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10933</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/18/skynet-labs-decentralized-internet-with-matthew-sevey/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=skynet-labs-decentralized-internet-with-matthew-sevey"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T18:20:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company Skynet Labs provides an open protocol for hosting data and web applications on the decentralized web. Skynet allows for decentralized, censorship-resistant, highly redundant storage and applications that are available around the globe. Developers don’t pay for their application’s storage, can launch apps with access to a user’s data right away, are free from
The post Skynet Labs: Decentralized Internet with Matthew Sevey appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Launch Day Support for AWS App Runner in the Terraform AWS Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-day-support-for-aws-app-runner-in-the-terraform-aws-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-day-support-for-aws-app-runner-in-the-terraform-aws-provider"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform AWS provider now supports AWS AppRunner, a purpose-built container application service that enables customers to build and run containerized web applications in just a few clicks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of HashiCorp Nomad 1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-general-availability-of-hashicorp-nomad-1-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-general-availability-of-hashicorp-nomad-1-1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.1 is now generally available. This release delivers more than 10 new features to enable more flexible scheduling and a simplified operator experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ClickHouse: Data Warehousing with Robert Hodges]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10932</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/17/clickhouse-data-warehousing-with-robert-hodges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=clickhouse-data-warehousing-with-robert-hodges"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Columnar databases store and retrieve columns of data rather than rows of data. Each block of data in a columnar database stores up to 3 times as many records as row-based storage. This means you can read data with a third of the power needed in row-based data, among other advantages. The company Altinity is
The post ClickHouse: Data Warehousing with Robert Hodges appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the New AWS Application Migration Service for Lift-and-Shift Migrations]]></title>
        <id>8b2c4cd789faee0e06adea3f067ac1241363e50a</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/6CDf9qduI2I/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since AWS acquired CloudEndure in 2019, our new colleagues have offered CloudEndure Migration and CloudEndure Disaster Recovery. CloudEndure Migration can move applications from any physical, virtual, or cloud-based infrastructure to AWS at no charge. This complements AWS Server Migration Service (AWS SMS), which is an agentless service for migrating on-premises workloads to AWS. CloudEndure Disaster […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Mechanics: Data Engineering with Jean-Yves Stephan]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10928</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/14/data-mechanics-data-engineering-with-jean-yves-stephan/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-mechanics-data-engineering-with-jean-yves-stephan"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T23:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Spark is a popular open source analytics engine for large-scale data processing. Applications can be written in Java, Scala, Python, R, and SQL. These applications have flexible options to run on like Kubernetes or in the cloud.  The company Data Mechanics is a cloud-native Spark platform for data engineers. It runs continuously optimized Apache
The post Data Mechanics: Data Engineering with Jean-Yves Stephan appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Modules on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-modules-on-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-modules-on-aws"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use best practices-based modules to build production-grade Terraform deployments on AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Azure Resources with TypeScript Using the CDK for Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-azure-resources-with-typescript-using-the-cdk-for-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-azure-resources-with-typescript-using-the-cdk-for-terraform"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn a quick method for getting started with the Cloud Development Kit (CDK) for Terraform using TypeScript as infrastructure code and provisioning on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Route Maps Resource Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-route-maps-resource-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-route-maps-resource-modules"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Engine v2.9 introduced the first set of Resource Modules that make network automation easier and more consistent, especially in multi-vendor environments. These network resource specific and opinionated Ansible modules help us avoid creating overly complex Jinja2 templates to render and push network configurations, thereby easing the adoption of network automation both in green and brownfield environments. The resource modules, along with the tools provided in ansible.utils, are highly focused on allowing the end user to manipulate network configuration as “structured data” and not have to worry about network platform specific details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nilashish Chakraborty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>