<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-07T01:46:28.431Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-06-07T01:46:28.431Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual captions: Using large language models to augment video conferences with dynamic visuals]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/visual-captions-using-large-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/visual-captions-using-large-language.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T16:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ruofei Du, Research Scientist, and Alex Olwal, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Augmented Reality




Recent advances in video conferencing have significantly improved remote video communication through features like live captioning and noise cancellation. However, there are various situations where dynamic visual augmentation would be useful to better convey complex and nuanced information. For example, when discussing what to order at a Japanese restaurant, your friends could share visuals that would help you feel more confident about ordering the “Sukiyaki”. Or when talking about your recent family trip to San Francisco, you may want to show a photo from your personal album.




In “Visual Captions: Augmenting Verbal Communication With On-the-fly Visuals”, presented at …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swift support brings broader mobile application security to GitHub Advanced Security]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-06-swift-support-brings-broader-mobile-application-security-to-github-advanced-security/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-06-swift-support-brings-broader-mobile-application-security-to-github-advanced-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T16:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve launched the beta of code scanning support for Swift. This launch, paired with our launch of Kotlin support in November, means that CodeQL covers both IOS and Android development languages, bringing a heightened level of security to the mobile application development process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring the Vault Secrets Operator with Prometheus and Grafana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/monitoring-the-vault-secrets-operator-with-prometheus-and-grafana</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/monitoring-the-vault-secrets-operator-with-prometheus-and-grafana"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use the Prometheus Operator with the new Vault Secrets Operator for Kubernetes to monitor secrets in a Grafana dashboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.20.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83178&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83178</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/camunda-automation-platform-7-20-0-alpha2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next alpha release of Camunda Automation Runtime 7.20 is here, with new features, security patches and bug fixes.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.20.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Camunda Platform 8 to Orchestrate Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83146&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83146</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/how-to-use-camunda-platform-8-orchestrate-microservices/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this fun example using Camunda Platform 8 to coordinate the use of several popular internet services, providing a nice end-user experience. 
The post How to use Camunda Platform 8 to Orchestrate Microservices appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Paroulek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falling behind]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40764</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/744472427/0/sethsblog~Falling-behind/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T08:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re not in races very often. Usually, what we’re doing is more like a walkathon, or perhaps, a hike. And yet, we’ve been pushed to believe that the only performance that matters is a scarcity-based victory. They close the parkway near my house on Sundays. As people pedal along, you can see the ripple of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 6th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/06/this-week-in-spring-june-6th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/06/this-week-in-spring-june-6th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total Economic Impact of Elasticsearch: Elastic delivers a 293% ROI and drives revenue improvement for customers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/total-economic-impact-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/total-economic-impact-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic customers have seen a 5% revenue improvement within three years, among other benefits, according to a study conducted by Forrester Consulting, commissioned by Elastic. Learn how in this blog post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Riya Juneja,Ben Pruden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total Economic Impact of Elasticsearch: Elastic delivers a 293% ROI and drives revenue improvement for customers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/total-economic-impact-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/total-economic-impact-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic customers have seen a 5% revenue improvement within three years, among other benefits. 

How? Using Elasticsearch, developers can ingest and connect various data sources to provide their companies, employees, customers, and/or public access to information and tune results for faster, more precise answers. Elasticsearch AI/ML powered search is designed to maximize performance and compute resources to deliver applications that can scale as businesses grow. Improving customer and employee experiences with search applications can allow organizations to reap profitability and productivity gains. 

Elastic recently commissioned Forrester to conduct a Total Economic Impact (TEI) study of Elasticsearch in order to help budgetary decision-makers fully understand the impact of partnering w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Riya Juneja,Ben Pruden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Amazon Security Lake Now GA, New Actions on AWS Fault Injection Simulator, and More – June 5, 2023]]></title>
        <id>150a33c67132a6adb31e40c0e37dd808c3b9a192</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-amazon-security-lake-now-ga-new-actions-on-aws-fault-injection-simulator-and-more-june-5-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T20:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Wednesday, I traveled to Cape Town to speak at the .Net Developer User Group. My colleague Francois Bouteruche also gave a talk but joined virtually. I enjoyed my time there—what an amazing community! Join the group in order to learn about upcoming events. Now onto the AWS updates from last week. There was a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REST vs GraphQL vs gRPC: Which API is Right for Your Project?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=82149&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=82149</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/rest-vs-graphql-vs-grpc-which-api-for-your-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T18:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the difference between REST, GraphQL and gRPC. Understand the pros and cons and top use cases of each API to help you choose the right one.
The post REST vs GraphQL vs gRPC: Which API is Right for Your Project? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Frame Rate Playback]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6c87836a948</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/native-frame-rate-playback-6c87836a948?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T16:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article talks about a novel HDMI technology and how it is used within the Netflix Application to improve a user’s experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Stale Repos Action]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-05-announcing-the-stale-repos-action/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-05-announcing-the-stale-repos-action/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T16:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tool to help you keep your open source catalog organized and up to date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.2 EAP #2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=360318</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/06/phpstorm-2023-2-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T14:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this build, you’ll find support for GitLab Merge Requests. The EAP allows you to try new features from the upcoming PhpStorm version, 2023.2. EAP builds are free to use and you can install them side by side with a stable version of PhpStorm. If something doesn’t work correctly, you can quickly switch back to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – June 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=359130</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/06/java-annotated-monthly-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T12:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Java Annotated Monthly! In this edition, we’ll share an abundance of Java news, specifically focusing on the planned features for JDK 21. As always, you’ll find a wide range of tutorials covering Java, Kotlin, and other related technologies.  Additionally, we have thought-provoking blog posts discussing the potential threat that AI poses to developers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Maryasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.2 EAP #3: GitLab Integration, Angular Improvements, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=359077</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/06/webstorm-2023-2-eap3/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T12:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re continuing to work on WebStorm 2023.2 with our third EAP build. To catch up on all of the new features WebStorm 2023.2 will bring, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoid false proxies]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45719</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/744332858/0/sethsblog~Avoid-false-proxies/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T08:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They’re toxic, wasteful and a tempting trap. It’s one of the most important topics in my new book. (And here’s a new podcast on it). We need proxies. You’re not allowed to read the book before you buy it or taste the ketchup before you leave the store. We rely on labels and cultural cues […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy’s New Projects and Topics: June Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=360235</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/06/05/jetbrains-academy-s-new-projects-and-topics-june-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T07:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New projects for Python, Frontend, Kotlin, and Java learners are hot off the press! In the past month, we’ve been busy creating a total of 10 projects and 53 topics for you to dive into. But that’s not all! We’ve also introduced two new tracks: Practicing Algorithms with Python and Kotlin Backend Developer (Spring Boot). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI in financial services: The role of the Elasticsearch Relevance Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/generative-ai-financial-services-elasticsearch-relevance-engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/generative-ai-financial-services-elasticsearch-relevance-engine"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI presents a real opportunity for FSIs. In order to drive this, Elastic recently launched the Elasticsearch Relevance Engine (ESRE), a powerful tool that combines AI and text search capabilities to create smarter search applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of public health depends on data sharing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/public-health-depends-on-data-sharing</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/public-health-depends-on-data-sharing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many US states are setting up prescription drug monitoring programs (PDMPs) to facilitate better patient care and prevent drug abuse. Their success depends on how well data can be shared and utilized — while keeping privacy and security top of mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andres Herrera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI in financial services: The role of the Elasticsearch Relevance Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/generative-ai-financial-services-elasticsearch-relevance-engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/generative-ai-financial-services-elasticsearch-relevance-engine"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Generative artificial intelligence (GAI) is undoubtedly one of the biggest trends across industries in 2023. In a recent survey, almost two-thirds of executives believe generative AI will have a high or extremely high impact on their organization in the next three to five years. Executives anticipate spending the next 6–12 months focused on increasing their understanding of how generative AI works, evaluating internal capabilities, and investing in generative AI tools. 
The financial services community adopted artificial intelligence & machine learning technology early on. AI largely gained prominence with the advent of high-frequency trading in the early 2000s, where financial institutions started using machine learning algorithms to identify patterns in market data and execute trades a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of public health depends on data sharing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/public-health-depends-on-data-sharing</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/public-health-depends-on-data-sharing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For years, state and local government agencies have been focusing on improving public health and the patient experience through technological innovation, such as electronic medical records, patient portals, and telehealth. While those initiatives are gaining ground, the next step in digital healthcare is the ability to easily share relevant data with the right people and at the right time — while adhering to privacy laws.
For example, in the US, many states are setting up prescription drug monitoring programs (PDMPs) to facilitate better patient care as well as prevent drug abuse, specifically opioids. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), a PDMP is an “electronic database that tracks controlled substance prescriptions in a state.”
PDMPs are a critical compon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andres Herrera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marble Run]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2785/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2785/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/marble_run.png" title="I have so many plans. It would incorporate a Galton board, a Ranque-Hilsch marble vortex tube, and a compartment lined with pinball bouncers with a camera-and-servo Maxwell's Demon that separated the balls into fast and slow sides." alt="I have so many plans. It would incorporate a Galton board, a Ranque-Hilsch marble vortex tube, and a compartment lined with pinball bouncers with a camera-and-servo Maxwell's Demon that separated the balls into fast and slow sides." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volition and placebos]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46327</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/744208502/0/sethsblog~Volition-and-placebos/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-04T09:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If a placebo heals your illness, does that mean it was all in your head in the first place? That you weren’t really sick, or didn’t really want to get better? If expensive wine tastes better to you, but you can’t tell wine apart in a double-blind taste test, does that mean it doesn’t really […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Productive assets and useful flows]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46323</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/744065894/0/sethsblog~Productive-assets-and-useful-flows/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-03T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assets are ownable. They are devices, skills, connections or properties that allow us to amplify our effort and do our work with more impact. A drill press is an asset, so is your law degree. The permission you have to talk with your customers, the benefit of the doubt you get from your patients and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 7’s Road to Jakarta EE 10]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83116&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83116</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/camunda-platform-7-road-to-jakarta-ee-10/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-03T00:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the path we've taken to support Jakarta EE 10 on Wildfly 27 as smoothly as possible for our customers.
The post Camunda Platform 7’s Road to Jakarta EE 10 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kelemen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying GitOps principles to your operations]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-02-applying-gitops-principles-to-your-operations/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-02-applying-gitops-principles-to-your-operations/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T17:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could we use our Git repository as the source of truth for operational tasks, and somehow reconcile changes with our real-world view?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVFormer: Injecting vision into frozen speech models for zero-shot AV-ASR]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/avformer-injecting-vision-into-frozen.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/avformer-injecting-vision-into-frozen.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Arsha Nagrani and Paul Hongsuck Seo, Research Scientists, Google Research






Automatic speech recognition (ASR) is a well-established technology that is widely adopted for various applications such as conference calls, streamed video transcription and voice commands. While the challenges for this technology are centered around noisy audio inputs, the visual stream in multimodal videos (e.g., TV, online edited videos) can provide strong cues for improving the robustness of ASR systems — this is called audiovisual ASR (AV-ASR).
 

Although lip motion can provide strong signals for speech recognition and is the most common area of focus for AV-ASR, the mouth is often not directly visible in videos in the wild (e.g., due to egocentric viewpoints, face coverings, and low resolution…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy Plugin 2023.5 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=359862</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/06/02/jetbrains-academy-plugin-2023-5-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T14:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This release is packed with new features for course creators. You can now easily сustomize course structures, task сode highlighting, and the default course opening view. We’ve also made more than 20 bug fixes and improvements across the entire plugin, from Codeforces solution submissions to matching problems for JetBrains Academy and Hyperskill. To check out […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasiia Pogorelova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2023.2 EAP3: Updated RBS Support and Search Everywhere Functionality]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=359379</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2023/06/rubymine-2023-2-eap3-updated-rbs-support-and-search-everywhere-functionality/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T10:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are actively developing RubyMine 2023.2 and have released our third Early Access Program (EAP) build. Here are the notable enhancements included in RubyMine 2023.2 EAP 3. We encourage you to try them and provide your feedback in the comments section or through our issue tracker. You can download the latest build from our website […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iryna Pisklyarova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cecil Phillip – Building payment flows with Stripe and Azure – Webinar Recording]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=359376</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/06/02/cecil-phillip-building-payment-flows-with-stripe-and-azure-webinar-recording/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T10:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The webinar recording for Building payment flows with Stripe and Azure, with Stripe Staff Developer Advocate, Cecil Phillip, is now available on JetBrainsTV. Be sure to like and subscribe on YouTube for more great content like this. Content creators, businesses, and even developers are trying to find ways to connect with their customers and maximize […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab Integration, Improved Main Toolbar Customization, Text Search in Search Everywhere, and More in GoLand 2023.2 EAP #3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=358885</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2023/06/02/gitlab-integration-2023-2-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T08:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third GoLand 2023.2 EAP build is now available! You can get it via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package (for Ubuntu), or from inside GoLand, select Check IDE updates for: Early Access Program in Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System Settings | Updates. Download GoLand 2023.2 EAP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consider the WordWindow]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46138</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/743929832/0/sethsblog~Consider-the-WordWindow/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer adventure games were possible in the 1980s because of a bit of code called a ‘parser’. You could type, “pick up the axe” and the computer would understand the phrase and follow your commands. In italics, because it didn’t understand anything, it simply broke your sentences into bits and changed the state of your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.2 EAP 3: Light Theme With Light Header in the New UI, Single-Click Navigation Between Project Directories, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=358189</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/06/intellij-idea-2023-2-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T07:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third EAP build for IntelliJ IDEA 2023.2 is now available, bringing several UI enhancements and new settings to make it easier to tailor the IDE to your preferences and project requirements. You can get the latest build from our website, the free Toolbox App, or via snaps for Ubuntu. To stay up to date […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Boot team member Moritz Halbritter (@m_halbritter)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/02/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-boot-team-member-moritz-halbritter-m_halbritter</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/02/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-boot-team-member-moritz-halbritter-m_halbritter"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets to successful engineering leadership from Elastic’s Simona Posea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-secrets-successful-engineering-leadership-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-secrets-successful-engineering-leadership-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Simona Posea, visualizing a career in technology came easily. She found she loved learning basic algorithms and languages like C, so she decided to marry her passion with her career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets to successful engineering leadership from Elastic’s Simona Posea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-secrets-successful-engineering-leadership-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-secrets-successful-engineering-leadership-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For Simona Posea, visualizing a career in technology came easily.

“My mother was a role model, as she’s been working with computers since punch cards were a thing,” Simona laughs. “We had our first PC when I was six years old, and she taught us how to operate it. At the time, I would use it to play games.”

This early interest in technology was further reinforced when Simona took programming classes in high school. She found she loved learning basic algorithms and languages like C, so she decided to marry her passion with her career.

17 years later, she’s a director of engineering at Elastic.

We caught up with Simona to hear how she transitioned into management and developed a winning strategy for leading her team. She also shared her top five tips for how other women can grow their t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drainage Basins]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2784/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2784/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/drainage_basins.png" title="After a pail of water was thrown on the Wicked Witch of the West outside Salt Lake City, Utah's Great Salt Lake was measured to be 7 parts per trillion witch by volume." alt="After a pail of water was thrown on the Wicked Witch of the West outside Salt Lake City, Utah's Great Salt Lake was measured to be 7 parts per trillion witch by volume." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS DMS Serverless: Automatically Provisions and Scales Capacity for Migration and Data Replication]]></title>
        <id>11cf7a26044d162c01f7bcb7a694b6e89decc031</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-dms-serverless-automatically-provisions-and-scales-capacity-for-migration-and-data-replication/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T23:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the vast amount of data being created today, organizations are moving to the cloud to take advantage of the security, reliability, and performance of fully managed database services. To facilitate database and analytics migrations, you can use AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS). First launched in 2016, AWS DMS offers a simple migration process […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring the Successful Launch of Ads on Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f99490fdf1ba</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/ensuring-the-successful-launch-of-ads-on-netflix-f99490fdf1ba?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T19:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jose Fernandez, Ed Barker, Hank Jacobs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevating open source contributors to open source maintainers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-01-elevating-open-source-contributors-to-open-source-maintainers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-01-elevating-open-source-contributors-to-open-source-maintainers/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T17:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts explain how to recruit and onboard co-maintainers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The swag is here]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46295</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/743855399/0/sethsblog~The-swag-is-here/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T17:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To celebrate the new book, here are some limited edition swag options to benefit good causes and independent craftspeople. You can find them all at seths.store. I went to Brooklyn and worked with Dan at the Arm to create a set of five handmade letterpress posters. They’re 12 inches square, available framed or unframed, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented visual-language pre-training]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/retrieval-augmented-visual-language-pre.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/retrieval-augmented-visual-language-pre.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ziniu Hu, Student Researcher, and Alireza Fathi, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception Team





Large-scale models, such as T5, GPT-3, PaLM, Flamingo and PaLI, have demonstrated the ability to store substantial amounts of knowledge when scaled to tens of billions of parameters and trained on large text and image datasets. These models achieve state-of-the-art results on downstream tasks, such as image captioning, visual question answering and open vocabulary recognition. Despite such achievements, these models require a massive volume of data for training and end up with a tremendous number of parameters (billions in many cases), resulting in significant computational requirements. Moreover, the data used to train these models can become outdated, requiring re-training…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from Git 2.41]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-01-highlights-from-git-2-41/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-01-highlights-from-git-2-41/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T16:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open-source Git project just released Git 2.41. Take a look at our highlights on what’s new in Git 2.41.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.2 EAP 2: Live Templates for Django Forms and Models, Support for Polars DataFrames]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=359196</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/06/2023-3-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second Early Access Program build brings a bunch of features for both web developers and data scientists. Try new, time-saving live templates for Django forms, models, and views, as well as support for a super-fast Polars DataFrame library and initial GitLab integration.  You can get the latest build from our website, the free Toolbox […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor Your TeamCity Builds with Datadog CI Visibility]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=358607</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/06/monitor-your-teamcity-builds-with-datadog-ci-visibility/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T13:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally written by Nicholas Thomson and Kassen Qian of Datadog and published on the Datadog blog. As the complexity of modern software development lifecycles increases, it’s important to have a comprehensive monitoring solution for your continuous integration (CI) pipelines so that you can quickly pinpoint and triage issues, especially when you have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing chatbot capabilities with NLP and vector search in Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/enhancing-chatbot-capabilities-with-nlp-and-vector-search-in-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/enhancing-chatbot-capabilities-with-nlp-and-vector-search-in-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we will explore how vector search and NLP work to enhance chatbot capabilities and demonstrate how Elasticsearch facilitates the process. Let's begin with a brief overview of vector search.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Priscilla Parodi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing chatbot capabilities with NLP and vector search in Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/enhancing-chatbot-capabilities-with-nlp-and-vector-search-in-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/enhancing-chatbot-capabilities-with-nlp-and-vector-search-in-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Conversational interfaces have been around for a while and are becoming increasingly popular as a means of assisting with various tasks, such as customer service, information retrieval, and task automation. Typically accessed through voice assistants or messaging apps, these interfaces simulate human conversation in order to help users resolve their queries more efficiently.

As technology advances, chatbots are used to handle more complex tasks — and quickly — while still providing a personalized experience for users. Natural language processing (NLP) enables chatbots to process the user's language, identifies the intent behind their message, and extracts relevant information from it. For example, Named Entity Recognition extracts key information in a text by classifying them into a set…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Priscilla Parodi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | June 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=358802</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/06/01/net-annotated-monthly-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T10:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? More than 400 billion PDFs were opened in Adobe products in the last year. Wow! That’s a lot of PDFs! How many did you open last year? .NET news Featured content  Hi folks, it’s me, Khalid, your neighborhood-friendly developer advocate. Rachel has kindly asked me to curate the June 2023 newsletter, as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 77% threshold]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46289</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/743792993/0/sethsblog~The-threshold/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T08:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the gas car was first introduced, it couldn’t compete with horses. After all, we’d had thousands of years to optimize our systems around horseback, and this new technology was still nascent. Roads were rare, gas stations were scarce and the cars themselves were unreliable. The same thing happened again when electric cars made a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Reasons to go Cloud-Native with Your Processes]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=82990&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=82990</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/three-reasons-cloud-native-with-your-processes/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T01:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why more and more companies are investing in cloud-native technology, and how it can benefit you today.
The post Three Reasons to go Cloud-Native with Your Processes appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet the Rainbow Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-rainbow-stack-erg</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-rainbow-stack-erg"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June kicks off Pride season, which started in the U.S and is now celebrated worldwide. It’s an important time for our Rainbow Stack ERG, which welcomes everyone who identifies as LGBTQIA+ and their allies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortifying data security: 5 features your data store must have]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-security-5-features-data-store-must-have</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-security-5-features-data-store-must-have"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One way to help mitigate security risks and avoid reputational damage, financial losses, and lost customer trust? Choose a data store with the right features like access control, audit logging, and data masking, just to name a few.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieve operational resilience with a flexible data store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/achieve-operational-resilience-flexible-data-store</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/achieve-operational-resilience-flexible-data-store"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you prepared for the unexpected? A resilient data store helps to ensure that an application performs optimally and data integrity is maintained. Discover what to look for in your data store solution to help you achieve operational resilience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet the Rainbow Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-rainbow-stack-erg</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-rainbow-stack-erg"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Employee resource groups, or as we like to call them, Elastician resource groups, have been an informal part of Elastic’s culture since 2016. They started as Slack channels and were formalized in 2021 to ensure that the members would have structure, budget, and ultimately, a voice based on any dimension of diversity, identity, allyship, and advocacy. This was an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy.

Our ERGs are aligned to shared identities, interests, affinities, or allyships. The goal is to create a community of people with something in common and to encourage sharing, learning, and networking. Each has visions and goals they are working towards besides building a sense of community and belonging.
Our Core ERGs
We have seven formal ERGs: The Accessibl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortifying data security: 5 features your data store must have]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-security-5-features-data-store-must-have</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-security-5-features-data-store-must-have"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In an era where data is often referred to as the “new oil,” the importance of data security can't be overstated. Breaches can lead to financial losses, reputational damage, and lost trust among customers and stakeholders. One primary step toward mitigating security risks is choosing a data store that has been designed with a robust security framework. 
A data store that offers various security features such as built-in data encryption, access control, audit logging, field-level security controls, and data masking and anonymization capabilities is crucial. Here are some features a robust, scalable, and flexible data store solution must have in order to enhance your security posture and boost overall operational efficiency.
Built-in data encryption: Your first line of defense
At the core o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieve operational resilience with a flexible data store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/achieve-operational-resilience-flexible-data-store</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/achieve-operational-resilience-flexible-data-store"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Are you prepared for the unexpected? In today's rapidly evolving world, operational resilience has never been more critical for businesses to survive and thrive. Resiliency is the ability of a system to maintain its operations under adverse conditions, including system failures, unexpected surges in user demand, or even security breaches. 
The heart of many applications, particularly in this era of data-driven decision-making, is the data store or database. A resilient data store ensures that the application continues to perform optimally and that data integrity is maintained even in the face of unprecedented challenges.
The typical method of making data stores more resilient through a Redundant Array of Independent Disks (RAID) can help protect data by storing it across multiple disks, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Snowball Edge Storage Optimized Devices with More Storage and Bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>bc2108141ac815b7f74d0e72d658b6327572e9bf</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-snowball-edge-storage-optimized-devices-with-more-storage-and-bandwidth/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T20:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Snow Family devices are used to cost-effectively move data to the cloud and to process data at the edge. The enhanced Snowball Edge Storage Optimized devices are designed for your petabyte-scale data migration projects, with 210 terabytes of NVMe storage and the ability to transfer up to 1.5 gigabytes of data per second. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable AI-Powered Process Optimization with ML-Ready Dataset]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=82967&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=82967</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/ai-powered-process-optimization-ml-ready-dataset/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T18:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve enhanced Camunda Optimize to produce more structured data so that it is ready for machine learning, making it easier than ever to take advantage of AI to improve your processes. Learn how.
The post Enable AI-Powered Process Optimization with ML-Ready Dataset appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large sequence models for software development activities]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/large-sequence-models-for-software.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/large-sequence-models-for-software.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:13:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Petros Maniatis and Daniel Tarlow, Research Scientists, Google




Software isn’t created in one dramatic step. It improves bit by bit, one little step at a time — editing, running unit tests, fixing build errors, addressing code reviews, editing some more, appeasing linters, and fixing more errors — until finally it becomes good enough to merge into a code repository. Software engineering isn’t an isolated process, but a dialogue among human developers, code reviewers, bug reporters, software architects and tools, such as compilers, unit tests, linters and static analyzers. 




Today we describe DIDACT (​​Dynamic Integrated Developer ACTivity), which is a methodology for training large machine learning (ML) models for software development. The novelty of DIDACT is that it uses …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown editor for comments (preview)]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67042</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/markdown-editor-for-comments-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T15:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are delighted to announce the long-awaited private preview of the new Markdown editor for the work item discussion. This exciting feature empowers you to utilize the Markdown syntax and editor for all future comments. The Markdown editor aligns with the same experience you encounter in other parts of the product,
The post Markdown editor for comments (preview) appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第230話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361290517894</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361290517894"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who cares?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46177</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/743641313/0/sethsblog~Who-cares/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A question we don’t ask ourselves very often, but a choice we make every day. It’s tempting to not care. If you choose to not care, you’re off the hook. It’s simply to do as little as possible, avoid too much trouble, ask if it will be on the test, try to stay off the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the potential of large language models: Elastic's first code contribution to LangChain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/large-language-models-elastic-code-langchain</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/large-language-models-elastic-code-langchain"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we explore the exciting synergy between Langchain and Elasticsearch, two powerful tools transforming the landscape of large language models. We provide an overview of the collaboration and its potential to shape application development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Vestal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For universities looking to do more with less, start with your data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/universities-do-more-with-less-start-with-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/universities-do-more-with-less-start-with-data"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UK universities are taking on more and more priorities, but government per-student funding in the UK is near an all-time low. Learn how universities can strategically do more with less by examining a fundamental component of their operations: data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Stanley-Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the potential of large language models: Elastic's first code contribution to LangChain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/large-language-models-elastic-code-langchain</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/large-language-models-elastic-code-langchain"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today we’ll be diving into the cutting-edge library, firmly situated in the world of large language models (LLMs), called LangChain and its synergy with Elastic. With LangChain's focus on making large language models more usable and versatile, and Elastic's scalable and fast search and analytics capabilities, this combination is opening new doors in the realm of application development and search application. In this blog, we'll explore what LangChain is, who it's for, and how Elastic fits into this picture, as well as discuss a recent contribution to LangChain by Elastic.
import elasticsearch
from langchain.embeddings.elasticsearch import ElasticsearchEmbeddings# Instantiate ElasticsearchEmbeddings using credentials
embeddings = ElasticsearchEmbeddings.from_credentials(
   model_id,
   …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Vestal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For universities looking to do more with less, start with your data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/universities-do-more-with-less-start-with-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/universities-do-more-with-less-start-with-data"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Universities today are not only centres of academic excellence; they are hubs for student health and well-being, digital innovation, and international research and diplomacy. Despite the fact that higher education is tasked with taking on more and more priorities, government per-student funding in the UK is projected to reach an all-time low by 2024–25.
While it’s tempting to systematically cut out courses in an effort to reduce costs, universities can strategically do more with less by examining one of the most fundamental (yet admittedly unexciting) components of university operations: data.
The unifying role of data in student outcomes
Most education outcomes are reliant, at least partially, on data. This is especially true when you view a university as a “smart campus,” or an “ultra-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Stanley-Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruling Out]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2783/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2783/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/ruling_out.png" title="We were able to replicate and confirm prior authors' detection of a moon orbiting the Earth with high confidence." alt="We were able to replicate and confirm prior authors' detection of a moon orbiting the Earth with high confidence." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 222]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67023</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-222/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T17:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This sprint marked another milestone for New Boards. We successfully activated the “Try the New Boards Hub” message for a large chunk of customers. As a result, a greater number of users have had the opportunity to engage with the New Boards Hub and share feedback.
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 222 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The spark]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45652</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/743443247/0/sethsblog~The-spark/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T08:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how big your backpack is, you can’t carry a bonfire with you when you go on a camping trip. A match is sufficient. Conversations are like that. Conversations are the tools that change our culture. Someone who cares talking with and teaching and learning from someone who was ready to engage. My new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 30th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/30/this-week-in-spring-may-30th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/30/this-week-in-spring-may-30th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – AWS Wickr, Amazon Redshift, Generative AI, and More – May 29, 2023]]></title>
        <id>fe3d1e8a253e9523034a3a21219b3a0a80c584ae</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-aws-wickr-amazon-redshift-generative-ai-and-more-may-29-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T21:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This edition of Week in Review marks the end of the month of May. In addition, we just finished all of the in-person AWS Summits in Asia-Pacific and Japan starting from AWS Summit Sydney and AWS Summit Tokyo in April to AWS Summit ASEAN, AWS Summit Seoul, and AWS Summit Mumbai in May. Thank you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your preference is not universal]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44573</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/743306669/0/sethsblog~Your-preference-is-not-universal/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T08:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re entitled to it, and we will do our best to help you find what you want. But it’s unlikely that what you want is what everyone wants. It’s hard to believe that there is only one appropriate standard for value, observance, speed or performance. The easiest way for us to help you is to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wikipedia Article Titles]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2782/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2782/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/wikipedia_article_titles.png" title="I would never stoop to vandalism, but I'm not above discreetly deleting the occasional 'this article contains excessive amounts of detail' tag." alt="I would never stoop to vandalism, but I'm not above discreetly deleting the occasional 'this article contains excessive amounts of detail' tag." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foundation models for reasoning on charts]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/foundation-models-for-reasoning-on.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/foundation-models-for-reasoning-on.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T19:08:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Julian Eisenschlos, Research Software Engineer, Google Research





Visual language is the form of communication that relies on pictorial symbols outside of text to convey information. It is ubiquitous in our digital life in the form of iconography, infographics, tables, plots, and charts, extending to the real world in street signs, comic books, food labels, etc. For that reason, having computers better understand this type of media can help with scientific communication and discovery, accessibility, and data transparency.
 

While computer vision models have made tremendous progress using learning-based solutions since the advent of ImageNet, the focus has been on natural images, where all sorts of tasks, such as classification, visual question answering (VQA), captioning, det…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Flaky Test Management in Azure Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66961</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/improved-flaky-test-management-in-azure-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T17:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In software development, testing is an integral part of the development process. Tests are used to verify that software behaves as expected, and they ensure that changes made to the code do not break existing functionality. However, there is a problem that often arises when running automated tests: Flaky tests.
The post Improved Flaky Test Management in Azure Pipelines appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravi Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barkour: Benchmarking animal-level agility with quadruped robots]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/barkour-benchmarking-animal-level.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/barkour-benchmarking-animal-level.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T16:58:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ken Caluwaerts and Atil Iscen, Research Scientists, Google





Creating robots that exhibit robust and dynamic locomotion capabilities, similar to animals or humans, has been a long-standing goal in the robotics community. In addition to completing tasks quickly and efficiently, agility allows legged robots to move through complex environments that are otherwise difficult to traverse. Researchers at Google have been pursuing agility for multiple years and across various form factors. Yet, while researchers have enabled robots to hike or jump over some obstacles, there is still no generally accepted benchmark that comprehensively measures robot agility or mobility. In contrast, benchmarks are driving forces behind the development of machine learning, such as ImageNet for computer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differentially private clustering for large-scale datasets]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/differentially-private-clustering-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/differentially-private-clustering-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T23:09:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Vincent Cohen-Addad and  Alessandro Epasto, Research Scientists, Google Research, Graph Mining team




Clustering is a central problem in unsupervised machine learning (ML) with many applications across domains in both industry and academic research more broadly. At its core, clustering consists of the following problem: given a set of data elements, the goal is to partition the data elements into groups such that similar objects are in the same group, while dissimilar objects are in different groups. This problem has been studied in math, computer science, operations research and statistics for more than 60 years in its myriad variants. Two common forms of clustering are metric clustering, in which the elements are points in a metric space, like in the k-means problem, and grap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating Processes from Pega to Camunda: A Step-by-Step Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=82123&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=82123</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/migrating-from-pega-to-camunda-platform-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T20:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to migrate your process flows from Pega to Camunda quickly and easily with this guide, which walks you through how to use our free migration tool.
The post Migrating Processes from Pega to Camunda: A Step-by-Step Tutorial appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Pappas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research at I/O 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/google-research-at-io-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/google-research-at-io-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T17:03:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by James Manyika, SVP Google Research and Technology & Society, and Jeff Dean, Chief Scientist, Google DeepMind and Google Research




Wednesday, May 10th was an exciting day for the Google Research community as we watched the results of months and years of our foundational and applied work get announced on the Google I/O stage. With the quick pace of announcements on stage, it can be difficult to convey the substantial effort and unique innovations that underlie the technologies we presented. So today, we’re excited to reveal more about the research efforts behind some of the many compelling announcements at this year's I/O. 


 

PaLM 2 
PaLM 2, is built on advances in compute-optimal scaling, scaled instruction-fine tuning and improved dataset mixture. By fine-tuning and instruc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2023 Open Source Program Office (OSPO) Survey is live!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-25-the-2023-open-source-program-office-ospo-survey-is-live/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-25-the-2023-open-source-program-office-ospo-survey-is-live/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T17:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Help quantify the state of enterprise open source by taking the 2023 OSPO survey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AWS provider 5.0 adds updates to default tags]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-aws-provider-5-0-adds-updates-to-default-tags</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-aws-provider-5-0-adds-updates-to-default-tags"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 5.0 of the HashiCorp Terraform AWS provider brings improvements to default tags, allowing practitioners to set tags at the provider level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rooting with root cause: finding a variant of a Project Zero bug]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-25-rooting-with-root-cause-finding-a-variant-of-a-project-zero-bug/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-25-rooting-with-root-cause-finding-a-variant-of-a-project-zero-bug/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T16:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, I’ll look at CVE-2022-46395, a variant of CVE-2022-36449 (Project Zero issue 2327), and use it to gain arbitrary kernel code execution and root privileges from the untrusted app domain on an Android phone that uses the Arm Mali GPU. I’ll also explain how root cause analysis of CVE-2022-36449 led to the discovery of CVE-2022-46395.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.3 (aka Kilburn) Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/25/spring-cloud-2022-0-3-aka-kilburn-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/25/spring-cloud-2022-0-3-aka-kilburn-is-available"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Gibb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Java Developer Advocate Billy Korando on the latest and greatest in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/25/a-bootiful-podcast-java-developer-advocate-billy-korando-on-the-latest-and</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/25/a-bootiful-podcast-java-developer-advocate-billy-korando-on-the-latest-and"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.10, 3.0.4 and 3.1.0 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/25/spring-shell-2-1-10-3-0-4-and-3-1-0-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/25/spring-shell-2-1-10-3-0-4-and-3-1-0-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security Kerberos 2.0.0-RC2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/25/spring-security-kerberos-2-0-0-rc2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/25/spring-security-kerberos-2-0-0-rc2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to automate a Microsoft Power Platform deployment using GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-24-how-to-automate-a-microsoft-power-platform-deployment-using-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-24-how-to-automate-a-microsoft-power-platform-deployment-using-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T18:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Low-code enables developers and non-developers to build custom applications and solutions with less effort. In this blog, we show you how to automate your low-code deployments using GitHub Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kelsey Hightower on leadership in open source and the future of Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-24-kelsey-hightower-on-leadership-in-open-source-and-the-future-of-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-24-kelsey-hightower-on-leadership-in-open-source-and-the-future-of-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T16:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this special episode of The ReadME Podcast, dedicated to GitHub’s Maintainer Month, Kelsey Hightower joins hosts Martin Woodward and Neha Batra to discuss his philosophy on fostering thriving open source communities and the importance of empathy to a maintainer’s success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform adds support for Azure Linux container host for Azure Kubernetes Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-adds-support-azure-linux-container-host-azure-kubernetes-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-adds-support-azure-linux-container-host-azure-kubernetes-service"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HashiCorp Terraform supports the deployment of Azure Linux container host for Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp releases a new CI/CD pipeline integration tool and templates for Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-releases-new-ci-cd-pipeline-integration-tool-templates-for-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-releases-new-ci-cd-pipeline-integration-tool-templates-for-terraform"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New CI/CD pipeline templates for GitHub Actions and GitLab CI provide prescriptive guides for integrating with Terraform Cloud, and a new integration tool can help build workflows with other CI/CD platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server is on Spring Initializr!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/24/spring-authorization-server-is-on-spring-initializr</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/24/spring-authorization-server-is-on-spring-initializr"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Riesenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Using OCI artifacts to distribute security profiles for seccomp, SELinux and AppArmor]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/24/oci-security-profiles/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/24/oci-security-profiles/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
The Security Profiles Operator (SPO) makes managing seccomp, SELinux and
AppArmor profiles within Kubernetes easier than ever. It allows cluster
administrators to define the profiles in a predefined custom resource YAML,
which then gets distributed by the SPO into the whole cluster. Modification and
removal of the security profiles are managed by the operator in the same way,
but that’s a small subset of its capabilities.
Another core feature of the SPO is being able to stack seccomp profiles. This
means that users can define a baseProfileName in the YAML specification, which
then gets automatically resolved by the operator and combines the syscall rules.
If a base profile has another baseProfileName, then the operator will
recursively resolve the profiles up to a ce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resolving code review comments with ML]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/resolving-code-review-comments-with-ml.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/resolving-code-review-comments-with-ml.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T17:51:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alexander Frömmgen, Staff Software Engineer, and Lera Kharatyan, Senior Software Engineer, Core Systems & Experiences


  

Code-change reviews are a critical part of the software development process at scale, taking a significant amount of the code authors’ and the code reviewers’ time. As part of this process, the reviewer inspects the proposed code and asks the author for code changes through comments written in natural language. At Google, we see millions of reviewer comments per year, and authors require an average of ~60 minutes active shepherding time between sending changes for review and finally submitting the change. In our measurements, the required active work time that the code author must do to address reviewer comments grows almost linearly with the number of comme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer improves channels and furthers integration with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-improves-channels-and-furthers-integration-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-improves-channels-and-furthers-integration-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer’s latest additions to channels give platform teams more visibility into their artifact estate, shorten times to remediation, and unify workflows with Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the public preview of GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-23-announcing-the-public-preview-of-github-advanced-security-for-azure-devops/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-23-announcing-the-public-preview-of-github-advanced-security-for-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T15:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps is now available for public preview, making GitHub’s same application security testing tools natively available on Azure Repos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-Driven Ansible is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-is-here</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-is-here"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T13:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may recall, we introduced Event-Driven Ansible in developer preview last fall at AnsibleFest. Since that time, much work has been done across the community, the Red Hat development teams, customers, and last but not least, Red Hat partners. Today, we are pleased to announce that Event-Driven Ansible will be concluding its developer preview and will become generally available as part of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Pisciotta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arriving soon: Red Hat Ansible Certified and validated Content Collections for Event-Driven Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-partner-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-partner-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since we announced Event-Driven Ansible in developer preview at AnsibleFest last October, we have been working with a number of technology partners to provide integrated offerings via Ansible Content Collections for Event-Driven Ansible. We know that partner integrations are an important source of event intelligence that can be used to create full end-to-end event-driven automation across your Day 2 operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Bock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-Driven Ansible: Driving Innovations at the Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-driving-innovations-at-the-edge</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-driving-innovations-at-the-edge"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T12:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The introduction of Event-Driven Ansible is especially exciting when considering the impacts to edge environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michele Null</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps public preview starts now!]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66951</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/github-advanced-security-for-azure-devops-public-preview-starts-now/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T08:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In October of last year we announced that GitHub Advanced Security was coming to Azure DevOps, starting with a private preview in November. Since then, we’ve been working hard on the product and incorporating feedback from our private preview customers. Today,
The post GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps public preview starts now! appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Hallberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash Spring apps in a flex environment with Azure Spring Apps Consumption and Dedicated plans]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/23/unleash-spring-apps-in-a-flex-environment-with-azure-spring-apps-consumption</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/23/unleash-spring-apps-in-a-flex-environment-with-azure-spring-apps-consumption"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 23rd, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/23/this-week-in-spring-may-23rd-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/23/this-week-in-spring-may-23rd-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prioritizing Our DevRel Backlog with Form Builder, DMN, and a Process Model]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=81782&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=81782</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/prioritizing-devrel-backlog-form-builder-dmn-process-model/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T19:32:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the backlog grows too fast, how do we prioritize the work that’s in front of us? See how we do it at Camunda.
The post Prioritizing Our DevRel Backlog with Form Builder, DMN, and a Process Model appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Thengvall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – AWS Documentation Updates, Amazon EventBridge is Faster, and More – May 22, 2023]]></title>
        <id>658cfdbc2595cff97d4c304cdbe5a812aa8aa957</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-aws-documentation-updates-amazon-eventbridge-is-faster-and-more-may-22-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T18:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are your AWS updates from the previous 7 days. Last week I was in Turin, Italy for CloudConf, a conference I’ve had the pleasure to participate in for the last 10 years. AWS Hero Anahit Pogosova was also there sharing a few serverless tips in front of a full house. Here’s a picture I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YOU are the community]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/you-are-the-community</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/you-are-the-community"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New year, new role, new strategy…2023 is officially the year when I return to my roots. Back in 2014, I officially became part of the Ansible community. Admittingly, back then my focus was solely on figuring out how to best demonstrate to my customers the power of having a OpenStack private cloud. Anyone who has ever stood up or experimented with OpenStack knows that this is a tall order. Imagine having to stand up that platform over and over again on a daily basis. My focus was to find a way—a tool—that could help me do that, so I could focus on helping solve the customers' true challenges. Fast forward to now, and the decision to do it with Ansible still stands as the best choice hands down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wbentley@redhat.com (Walter Bentley)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging a FUSE deadlock in the Linux kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c75cd7989b6d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/debugging-a-fuse-deadlock-in-the-linux-kernel-c75cd7989b6d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T19:21:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tycho Andersen]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making ML models differentially private: Best practices and open challenges]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/making-ml-models-differentially-private.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/making-ml-models-differentially-private.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T16:59:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Natalia Ponomareva and Alex Kurakin, Staff Software Engineers, Google Research






Large machine learning (ML) models are ubiquitous in modern applications: from spam filters to recommender systems and virtual assistants. These models achieve remarkable performance partially due to the abundance of available training data. However, these data can sometimes contain private information, including personal identifiable information, copyright material, etc. Therefore, protecting the privacy of the training data is critical to practical, applied ML.  



Differential Privacy (DP) is one of the most widely accepted technologies that allows reasoning about data anonymization in a formal way. In the context of an ML model, DP can guarantee that each individual user's contribution will …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Geospatial Capabilities Now Generally Available with Security Updates and More Use Case Samples]]></title>
        <id>efedd5b45420d25bd006433406be72b45697a562</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-geospatial-capabilities-now-generally-available-with-security-updates-and-more-use-case-samples/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2022, we previewed Amazon SageMaker geospatial capabilities, allowing data scientists and machine learning (ML) engineers to build, train, and deploy ML models using geospatial data. Geospatial ML with Amazon SageMaker supports access to readily available geospatial data, purpose-built processing operations and open source libraries, pre-trained ML models, and built-in visualization tools with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABAC on SpiceDB: Enabling Netflix’s Complex Identity Types]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c118f374fa89</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/abac-on-spicedb-enabling-netflixs-complex-identity-types-c118f374fa89?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T12:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Chris Wolfe, Joey Schorr, and Victor Roldán Betancort]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sparse video tubes for joint video and image vision transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/sparse-video-tubes-for-joint-video-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/sparse-video-tubes-for-joint-video-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T21:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by AJ Piergiovanni and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google








Video understanding is a challenging problem that requires reasoning about both spatial information (e.g., for objects in a scene, including their locations and relations) and temporal information for activities or events shown in a video. There are many video understanding applications and tasks, such as understanding the semantic content of web videos and robot perception. However, current works, such as ViViT and TimeSFormer, densely process the video and require significant compute, especially as model size plus video length and resolution increase. 



In “Rethinking Video ViTs: Sparse Video Tubes for Joint Image and Video Learning”, to be presented at CVPR 2023, we introduce a simple technique that tur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Simplify the Investigation of AWS Security Findings with Amazon Detective]]></title>
        <id>c2ef7c334d9e453399d2e4811e7ab0a933504eb3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-simplify-the-investigation-of-aws-security-findings-with-amazon-detective/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T20:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Amazon Detective, you can analyze and visualize security data to investigate potential security issues. Detective collects and analyzes events that describe IP traffic, AWS management operations, and malicious or unauthorized activity from AWS CloudTrail logs, Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Flow Logs, Amazon GuardDuty findings, and, since last year, Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about Edge Automation at Red Hat Summit and AnsibleFest 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-edge-automation-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-edge-automation-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T20:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about what is happening around Edge Automation at Red Hat Summit and AnsibleFest 2023!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michele Null</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: PAIR]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/responsible-ai-at-google-research-pair.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/responsible-ai-at-google-research-pair.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T17:12:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lucas Dixon and Michael Terry, co-leads, PAIR, Google Research




PAIR (People + AI Research) first launched in 2017 with the belief that “AI can go much further — and be more useful to all of us — if we build systems with people in mind at the start of the process.” We continue to focus on making AI more understandable, interpretable, fun, and usable by more people around the world. It’s a mission that is particularly timely given the emergence of generative AI and chatbots.



Today, PAIR is part of the Responsible AI and Human-Centered Technology team within Google Research, and our work spans this larger research space: We advance foundational research on human-AI interaction (HAI) and machine learning (ML); we publish educational materials, including the PAIR Guidebook and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying securely into Azure architecture with Terraform Cloud and HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploying-securely-into-azure-architecture-with-terraform-cloud-and-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploying-securely-into-azure-architecture-with-terraform-cloud-and-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build a secure infrastructure as code workflow with Terraform Cloud dynamic provider credentials, Microsoft Defender for Cloud, and HCP Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game on! Join Us in the Play Alpha-Testing Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=81486&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=81486</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/join-play-alpha-testing-contest/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve made process development fun and exciting for your team with Play. Share your feedback to help us make it better.
The post Game on! Join Us in the Play Alpha-Testing Contest appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Inozemtceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Having fun with seccomp profiles on the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/18/seccomp-profiles-edge/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/18/seccomp-profiles-edge/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
The Security Profiles Operator (SPO) is a feature-rich
operator for Kubernetes to make managing seccomp, SELinux and
AppArmor profiles easier than ever. Recording those profiles from scratch is one
of the key features of this operator, which usually involves the integration
into large CI/CD systems. Being able to test the recording capabilities of the
operator in edge cases is one of the recent development efforts of the SPO and
makes it excitingly easy to play around with seccomp profiles.
Recording seccomp profiles with spoc record
The v0.8.0 release of the Security Profiles Operator shipped a new
command line interface called spoc, a little helper tool for recording and
replaying seccomp profiles among various other things that are out of scope of
this blog post.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retiring the AWS Documentation on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>b7080422d9b11a447cfc260dc7cce95c30bddad8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/retiring-the-aws-documentation-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T23:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About five years ago I announced that AWS Documentation is Now Open Source and on GitHub. After a prolonged period of experimentation we will archive most of the repos starting the week of June 5th, and will devote all of our resources to directly improving the AWS documentation and website. The primary source for most […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Draft to Perfection: Creating Effective Forms for Human Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=81100&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=81100</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/draft-to-perfection-effective-forms-human-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With our Form Editor you can draft, refine, and validate forms with ease. Learn how to design forms to perfectly fit your business needs.
The post From Draft to Perfection: Creating Effective Forms for Human Workflows appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Konrad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using reinforcement learning for dynamic planning in open-ended conversations]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/using-reinforcement-learning-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/using-reinforcement-learning-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T19:22:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Deborah Cohen, Staff Research Scientist, and Craig Boutilier, Principal Scientist, Google Research




As virtual assistants become ubiquitous, users increasingly interact with them to learn about new topics or obtain recommendations and expect them to deliver capabilities beyond narrow dialogues of one or two turns. Dynamic planning, namely the capability to look ahead and replan based on the flow of the conversation, is an essential ingredient for the making of engaging conversations with the deeper, open-ended interactions that users expect.
 

While large language models (LLMs) are now beating state-of-the-art approaches in many natural language processing benchmarks, they are typically trained to output the next best response, rather than planning ahead, which is required fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud updates plans with an enhanced Free tier and more flexibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-updates-plans-with-an-enhanced-free-tier-and-more-flexibility</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-updates-plans-with-an-enhanced-free-tier-and-more-flexibility"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud’s Free tier now offers new features — including SSO, policy as code, and cloud agents — while new paid offerings update scaling concurrency and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Achieves ISO 26262 ASIL D level of Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66945</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-achieves-iso-26262-asil-d-level-of-certification/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T15:27:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce that Azure DevOps has successfully passed the ISO 26262 ASIL D certification, the highest level of Functional Safety management process, by TÜV SUD, an international independent third-party testing and certification company. This certification demonstrates Microsoft’s commitment to providing our Automotive customers with the highest level of quality and safety in their software development projects.
The post Azure DevOps Achieves ISO 26262 ASIL D level of Certification appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jorge Minana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: KMS V2 Moves to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/16/kms-v2-moves-to-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/16/kms-v2-moves-to-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Anish Ramasekar, Mo Khan, and Rita Zhang (Microsoft)
With Kubernetes 1.27, we (SIG Auth) are moving Key Management Service (KMS) v2 API to beta.
What is KMS?
One of the first things to consider when securing a Kubernetes cluster is encrypting etcd data at
rest. KMS provides an interface for a provider to utilize a key stored in an external key service to
perform this encryption.
KMS v1 has been a feature of Kubernetes since version 1.10, and is currently in beta as of version
v1.12. KMS v2 was introduced as alpha in v1.25.
Note
the previous blog post
was written and it is not compatible with the design in this blog post. Attempting to upgrade from
old versions with the alpha feature enabled will result in data loss.

What’s new in v2beta1?
The KMS encryption provider uses an envel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Larger language models do in-context learning differently]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/larger-language-models-do-in-context.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/larger-language-models-do-in-context.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T20:59:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jerry Wei, Student Researcher, and Denny Zhou, Principal Scientist, Google Research




There have recently been tremendous advances in language models, partly because they can perform tasks with strong performance via in-context learning (ICL), a process whereby models are prompted with a few examples of input-label pairs before performing the task on an unseen evaluation example. In general, models’ success at in-context learning is enabled by:
 


Their use of semantic prior knowledge from pre-training to predict labels while following the format of in-context examples (e.g., seeing examples of movie reviews with “positive sentiment” and “negative sentiment” as labels and performing sentiment analysis using prior knowledge).


Learning the input-label mappings in context from …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review –  New Open-Source Updates for Snapchange, Cedar, and Jupyter Community Contributions – May 15, 2023]]></title>
        <id>e8903c7f01bbcc4d30acec4eca295aa082db9119</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-new-open-source-updates-for-snapchange-cedar-and-jupyter-community-contributions-may-15-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T20:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new week has begun. Last week, there was a lot of news related to AWS. I have compiled a few announcements you need to know. Let’s get started right away! Last Week’s Launches Let’s take a look at some launches from the last week that I want to remind you of: New Amazon EC2 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Global 2023 scholarship program open for applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-scholarship-program-open-for-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-scholarship-program-open-for-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now is your chance to apply for a scholarship to attend the HashiConf Global conference in San Francisco, Oct. 10-12.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consensus and subjectivity of skin tone annotation for ML fairness]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/consensus-and-subjectivity-of-skin-tone_15.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/consensus-and-subjectivity-of-skin-tone_15.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T17:16:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Candice Schumann, Software Engineer, and Gbolahan O. Olanubi, User Experience Researcher, Google Research




Skin tone is an observable characteristic that is subjective, perceived differently by individuals (e.g., depending on their location or culture) and thus is complicated to annotate. That said, the ability to reliably and accurately annotate skin tone is highly important in computer vision. This became apparent in 2018, when the Gender Shades study highlighted that computer vision systems struggled to detect people with darker skin tones, and performed particularly poorly for women with darker skin tones. The study highlights the importance for computer researchers and practitioners to evaluate their technologies across the full range of skin tones and at intersections of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New version of ServiceNow Terraform Catalog enhances workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-of-servicenow-terraform-catalog-enhances-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-of-servicenow-terraform-catalog-enhances-workflows"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ServiceNow Service Catalog integration for Terraform now allows you to select the execution mode for your Terraform workspaces — along with other enhancements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about Network Automation at Red Hat Summit and AnsibleFest 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-network-automation-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-network-automation-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may have heard, AnsibleFest will be taking place at Red Hat Summit in Boston May 23-25. This change will allow you to harness everything that Red Hat technology has to offer in a single place and will give you even more tools to address your automation needs. Join Ansible and automation-focused audiences to hear from Red Hat and Ansible leaders, customers, and partners while getting the latest on the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform product roadmap, community projects, and what’s coming in IT automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: updates on speeding up Pod startup]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/15/speed-up-pod-startup/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/15/speed-up-pod-startup/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Paco Xu (DaoCloud), Sergey Kanzhelev (Google), Ruiwen Zhao (Google)
How can Pod start-up be accelerated on nodes in large clusters? This is a common issue that
cluster administrators may face.
This blog post focuses on methods to speed up pod start-up from the kubelet side. It does not
involve the creation time of pods by controller-manager through kube-apiserver, nor does it
include scheduling time for pods or webhooks executed on it.
We have mentioned some important factors here to consider from the kubelet's perspective, but
this is not an exhaustive list. As Kubernetes v1.27 is released, this blog highlights
significant changes in v1.27 that aid in speeding up pod start-up.
Parallel container image pulls
Pulling images always takes some time and what's worse is that image pull…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F-VLM: Open-vocabulary object detection upon frozen vision and language models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/f-vlm-open-vocabulary-object-detection.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/f-vlm-open-vocabulary-object-detection.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Weicheng Kuo and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research






Detection is a fundamental vision task that aims to localize and recognize objects in an image. However, the data collection process of manually annotating bounding boxes or instance masks is tedious and costly, which limits the modern detection vocabulary size to roughly 1,000 object classes. This is orders of magnitude smaller than the vocabulary people use to describe the visual world and leaves out many categories. Recent vision and language models (VLMs), such as CLIP, have demonstrated improved open-vocabulary visual recognition capabilities through learning from Internet-scale image-text pairs. These VLMs are applied to zero-shot classification using frozen model weights without the need for fine-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Modernize Your Applications at AWS Serverless Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>ee829d9b822332b77c6c37976dab86517e596799</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/learn-how-to-modernize-your-applications-at-aws-serverless-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T18:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on Wednesday, May 17, for AWS Serverless Innovation Day, a free full-day virtual event. You will learn about AWS Serverless technologies and event-driven architectures from customers, experts, and leaders. AWS Serverless Innovation Day is an event to empower builders and technical decision-makers with different AWS Serverless technologies, including AWS Lambda, Amazon Elastic Container […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling conversational interaction on mobile with LLMs]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/enabling-conversational-interaction-on.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/enabling-conversational-interaction-on.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:03:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bryan Wang, Student Researcher, and Yang Li, Research Scientist, Google Research





Intelligent assistants on mobile devices have significantly advanced language-based interactions for performing simple daily tasks, such as setting a timer or turning on a flashlight. Despite the progress, these assistants still face limitations in supporting conversational interactions in mobile user interfaces (UIs), where many user tasks are performed. For example, they cannot answer a user's question about specific information displayed on a screen. An agent would need to have a computational understanding of graphical user interfaces (GUIs) to achieve such capabilities. 



Prior research has investigated several important technical building blocks to enable conversational interaction with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: In-place Resource Resize for Kubernetes Pods (alpha)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/12/in-place-pod-resize-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/12/in-place-pod-resize-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Vinay Kulkarni (Kubescaler Labs)
If you have deployed Kubernetes pods with CPU and/or memory resources
specified, you may have noticed that changing the resource values involves
restarting the pod. This has been a disruptive operation for running
workloads... until now.
In Kubernetes v1.27, we have added a new alpha feature that allows users
to resize CPU/memory resources allocated to pods without restarting the
containers. To facilitate this, the resources field in a pod's containers
now allow mutation for cpu and memory resources. They can be changed
simply by patching the running pod spec.
This also means that resources field in the pod spec can no longer be
relied upon as an indicator of the pod's actual resources. Monitoring tools
and other such applications must now look at n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon Aurora I/O-Optimized Cluster Configuration with Up to 40% Cost Savings for I/O-Intensive Applications]]></title>
        <id>5ec1a9f67d502ffa32d8252cb12b71e213171571</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-aurora-i-o-optimized-cluster-configuration-with-up-to-40-cost-savings-for-i-o-intensive-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T20:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Amazon Aurora launched in 2014, hundreds of thousands of customers have chosen Aurora to run their most demanding applications. Aurora provides unparalleled high performance and availability at global scale with full MySQL and PostgreSQL compatibility at up to one-tenth the cost of commercial databases. Many customers benefit from the cost-effectiveness of Aurora’s current simple, pay-per-request […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform integrations from Dell, Fortinet, GitHub, Harness, Snyk, Splunk, and Zscaler]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-from-dell-fortinet-github-harness-snyk-splunk-and-zsca</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-from-dell-fortinet-github-harness-snyk-splunk-and-zsca"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 24 new Terraform partner integrations make their debut on the Terraform registry, simplifying customers’ cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Avoid Collisions Assigning Ports to NodePort Services]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/11/nodeport-dynamic-and-static-allocation/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/11/nodeport-dynamic-and-static-allocation/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Xu Zhenglun (Alibaba)
In Kubernetes, a Service can be used to provide a unified traffic endpoint for
applications running on a set of Pods. Clients can use the virtual IP address (or VIP) provided
by the Service for access, and Kubernetes provides load balancing for traffic accessing
different back-end Pods, but a ClusterIP type of Service is limited to providing access to
nodes within the cluster, while traffic from outside the cluster cannot be routed.
One way to solve this problem is to use a type: NodePort Service, which sets up a mapping
to a specific port of all nodes in the cluster, thus redirecting traffic from the
outside to the inside of the cluster.
How Kubernetes allocates node ports to Services?
When a type: NodePort Service is created, its corresponding port(s) are al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell, Marvell, NetApp, and SUSE expand Vault support with new integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dell-marvell-netapp-and-suse-expand-vault-support-with-new-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dell-marvell-netapp-and-suse-expand-vault-support-with-new-integrations"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Vault partner ecosystem continues to show strong growth with the addition of more than a dozen new Vault integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building better pangenomes to improve the equity of genomics]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/building-better-pangenomes-to-improve.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/building-better-pangenomes-to-improve.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:03:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Andrew Carroll, Product Lead, and Kishwar Shafin, Research Scientist, Genomics






For decades, researchers worked together to assemble a complete copy of the molecular instructions for a human — a map of the human genome. The first draft was finished in 2000, but with several missing pieces.  Even when a complete reference genome was achieved in 2022, their work was not finished. A single reference genome can’t incorporate known genetic variations, such as the variants for the gene determining whether a person has a blood type A, B, AB or O. Furthermore, the reference genome didn’t represent the vast diversity of human ancestries, making it less useful for detecting disease or finding cures for people from some backgrounds than others. For the past three years, we have been pa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about Event-Driven Ansible at Red Hat Summit and AnsibleFest 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-event-driven-ansible-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-event-driven-ansible-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may have heard, AnsibleFest will be taking place at Red Hat Summit in Boston May 23-25. This change will allow you to harness everything that Red Hat technology has to offer in a single place and give you even more tools to address your automation needs. Join Ansible and automation-focused audiences to hear from Red Hat and Ansible leaders, customers, and partners while getting the latest on future Ansible product updates, community projects, and what’s coming in IT automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Storage-Optimized Amazon EC2 I4g Instances: Graviton Processors and AWS Nitro SSDs]]></title>
        <id>fa9f4d36a6cc0d15999ca03edf1ef668d2028f09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-storage-optimized-amazon-ec2-i4g-instances-graviton-processors-and-aws-nitro-ssds/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T21:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are launching I4g instances powered by AWS Graviton2 processors that deliver up to 15% better compute performance than our other storage-optimized instances. With up to 64 vCPUs, 512 GiB of memory, and 15 TB of NVMe storage, one of the six instance sizes is bound to be a great fit for your storage-intensive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66918</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/now-available-azure-devops-server-2022-0-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T17:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we released Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RTW. This is our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1. You can directly install Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 or upgrade from Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC, Azure DevOps Server 2022, Team Foundation Server 2015 or newer versions of the product.
The post Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Safer, More Performant Pruning in kubectl apply]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/09/introducing-kubectl-applyset-pruning/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/09/introducing-kubectl-applyset-pruning/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Katrina Verey (independent) and Justin Santa Barbara (Google)
Declarative configuration management with the kubectl apply command is the gold standard approach
to creating or modifying Kubernetes resources. However, one challenge it presents is the deletion
of resources that are no longer needed. In Kubernetes version 1.5, the --prune flag was
introduced to address this issue, allowing kubectl apply to automatically clean up previously
applied resources removed from the current configuration.
Unfortunately, that existing implementation of --prune has design flaws that diminish its
performance and can result in unexpected behaviors. The main issue stems from the lack of explicit
encoding of the previously applied set by the preceding apply operation, necessitating
error-prone dynam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – AWS User Notifications, Serverless event, and More – May 8, 2023]]></title>
        <id>4e74355f2ac25e5c1b2a61d6decd0116b526557f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-aws-notifications-serverless-event-and-more-may-8-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T21:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of this week, I’m flying to Seattle to take part in the AWS Serverless Innovation Day. Along with many customers and colleagues from AWS, we are going to be live on May 17 at a virtual free event. During the AWS Serverless Innovation Day we will share best practices related to building […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>