<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-13T00:20:01.106Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-13T00:20:01.106Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Winning Process Orchestration Plays for Media & Entertainment]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=98075</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/01/four-winning-process-orchestration-plays-media-entertainment/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T20:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Media and entertainment businesses have to change quickly. Learn four different ways these companies are benefitting from the power of process orchestration with Camunda.
The post Four Winning Process Orchestration Plays for Media & Entertainment appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason English</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMIE: A research AI system for diagnostic medical reasoning and conversations]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/01/amie-research-ai-system-for-diagnostic_12.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/01/amie-research-ai-system-for-diagnostic_12.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alan Karthikesalingam and Vivek Natarajan, Research Leads, Google Research




The physician-patient conversation is a cornerstone of medicine, in which skilled and intentional communication drives diagnosis, management, empathy and trust. AI systems capable of such diagnostic dialogues could increase availability, accessibility, quality and consistency of care by being useful conversational partners to clinicians and patients alike. But approximating clinicians’ considerable expertise is a significant challenge. 





Recent progress in large language models (LLMs) outside the medical domain has shown that they can plan, reason, and use relevant context to hold rich conversations. However, there are many aspects of good diagnostic dialogue that are unique to the medical domain. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for a handle]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46542</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/860389337/0/sethsblog~Looking-for-a-handle/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if your boots don’t have any straps? Bootstrapping is logically impossible. You can’t pick yourself up into the air by lifting on your boots, no matter how hard you try, because gravity isn’t just a good idea, it’s the law. But it’s significantly more difficult if your boots don’t have straps. The word “purchase” […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Web Services 4.0.10 is released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/12/spring-web-services-4-0-10-is-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/12/spring-web-services-4-0-10-is-released"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corneil du Plessis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2023.1.2 and 2023.0.8 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/12/spring-data-2023-1-2-and-2023-0-8-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/12/spring-data-2023-1-2-and-2023-0-8-available"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sheet Bend]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2880/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2880/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/sheet_bend.png" title="A left-handed sheet bend creates a much weaker connection, especially under moderate loads." alt="A left-handed sheet bend creates a much weaker connection, especially under moderate loads." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can large language models identify and correct their mistakes?]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/01/can-large-language-models-identify-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/01/can-large-language-models-identify-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T22:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Gladys Tyen, Intern, Google Research




LLMs are increasingly popular for reasoning tasks, such as multi-turn QA, task completion, code generation, or mathematics. Yet much like people, they do not always solve problems correctly on the first try, especially on tasks for which they were not trained. Therefore, for such systems to be most useful, they should be able to 1) identify where their reasoning went wrong and 2) backtrack to find another solution.



This has led to a surge in methods related to self-correction, where an LLM is used to identify problems in its own output, and then produce improved results based on the feedback. Self-correction is generally thought of as a single process, but we decided to break it down into two components, mistake finding and output corre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon ECS supports a native integration with Amazon EBS volumes for data-intensive workloads]]></title>
        <id>aa651b9a68332fa0b11be808f87f4175a6e2ddba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ecs-supports-a-native-integration-with-amazon-ebs-volumes-for-data-intensive-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T22:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing that Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) supports an integration with Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS), making it easier to run a wider range of data processing workloads. You can provision Amazon EBS storage for your ECS tasks running on AWS Fargate and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) without […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering Uruguay’s future workforce with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-11-empowering-uruguays-future-workforce-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-11-empowering-uruguays-future-workforce-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T20:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>During the second cycle of Git Commit Uruguay, students learned the basics of AI and built their own AI-powered projects.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-11-empowering-uruguays-future-workforce-with-ai/">Empowering Uruguay’s future workforce with AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf 2024 scholarship program now open for applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-2024-scholarship-program-now-open-for-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-2024-scholarship-program-now-open-for-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is your chance to apply for a scholarship to attend HashiConf in Boston, October 14-16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for a Next-Generation C++ IDE? Find Out More in The CLion 2024.1 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=433277</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2024/01/clion-2024-1-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T16:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2023 brought many enhancements to CLion, including AI Assistant, dozens of smart C++ code analysis checks, Meson and Bazel support, the Assembly view, device tree file support and enhanced PlatformIO integration for embedded developers, vcpkg support and updates to the Conan plugin, a new UI, and many other improvements. Check out the key […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Livestream: Virtual Threads in Action!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=420225</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/01/new-livestream-virtual-threads-in-action/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T09:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for the new IntelliJ IDEA Livestream episode with Dmitry Aleksandrov to learn about the world’s first web framework fully based on virtual threads. Date: January 25, 2024 Time: 3:00 pm – 4:00 pm UTC REGISTER FOR THE LIVESTREAM Session abstract Helidon 4 became the world’s first web framework fully based on virtual threads […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Rovinskaia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kash’s garden]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46521</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/860283290/0/sethsblog~Kashs-garden/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[She doesn’t grow plants. The plants grow themselves. Her job is to create conditions for the plants to grow. The soil, the water, the light, the weeds… these are the conditions. But none of it happens if the plants don’t do the thing they want to do in the first place. This is always true, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Ways to Learn Java]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=432869</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/01/the-best-ways-to-learn-java/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T08:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting with Java can feel overwhelming – there are so many options and so little time. That’s where this article comes in handy – consider it your roadmap to learning Java with ease. Whether you’re just starting out or have watched every Java tutorial in existence but still feel stuck, we’ve compiled interesting resources and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Maryasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.11.2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/11/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-11-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/11/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-11-2-released"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Renfro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.1.3 and 6.0.16 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/11/spring-framework-6-1-3-and-6-0-16-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/11/spring-framework-6-1-3-and-6-0-16-available-now"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stéphane Nicoll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Apache Skywalking’s Sheng Wu and Apache ShardingSphere’s Trista Pan]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/11/a-bootiful-podcast-apache-skywalkings-sheng-wu-and-apache-shardingspheres</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/11/a-bootiful-podcast-apache-skywalkings-sheng-wu-and-apache-shardingspheres"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diana Todea pivoted from political philosophy to engineering. Here’s how she broke into tech.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-pivoting-philosophy-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-pivoting-philosophy-engineering"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diana Todea shares her story of becoming a site reliability engineer and how she used engineering certifications to advance her career. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionizing telco procurement with the Elasticsearch Platform: A comprehensive approach to unifying licensing and reducing costs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/revolutionizing-telco-procurement-with-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/revolutionizing-telco-procurement-with-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic helps telco procurement teams unify software solutions and reduce operational and licensing costs. Learn about the benefits of using the Elasticsearch Platform for your organization....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Kobziakowski,Jürgen Obermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-4-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-4-released"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Snehal Adlinge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diana Todea pivoted from political philosophy to engineering. Here’s how she broke into tech.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-pivoting-philosophy-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-pivoting-philosophy-engineering"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After completing a degree in political philosophy, Diana Todea pivoted to a role in IT customer service. While it seems like a big leap, it made sense for her. She comes from a family of engineers. 

“Asking questions is a part of who I am,” she says. “I’m an engineer at heart, I like seeing how things are constructed.”
Diana started her tech career in her home country of Romania after she graduated from a postgraduate program in philosophy — she is a published philosopher and poetess and also speaks five different languages. 
“They hired me because I spoke different languages,” she says. “I was really attracted to the technical side and wanted to get more involved in the technical projects.” 
Her first project was in telecom customer service on networking. She then moved on to contract pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionizing telco procurement with the Elasticsearch Platform: A comprehensive approach to unifying licensing and reducing costs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/revolutionizing-telco-procurement-with-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/revolutionizing-telco-procurement-with-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fast-evolving landscape of business operations, telecommunications procurement departments are pivotal in spearheading cost efficiencies and technological advancements. A significant challenge in this realm is the management of disparate software solutions from multiple vendors. Telecom companies deal with complex systems, and having multiple tools that don't integrate well can lead to inefficiencies. This often results in overlapping data and functionalities, leading to inflated costs and complexities in maintenance, integration, and training. The diverse renewal cycles, compliance demands, and disparate usage tracking methodologies further complicate the formulation of an efficient and cost-effective IT strategy.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.

In this blog post, we may have used or referred to third party generative AI tools, which are owned and operated by their respective owners. Elastic does not have any control over the third party tools and we have no responsibility or liability for their content, operation or use, nor for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of such tools. Please exercise caution when using AI tools with personal, sensitive or confidential information. Any data you submit may be used for AI training or other purposes. There is no guarantee that information you provide will be kept secure or confidential. You should familiarize yourself with the privacy practices and terms of use of any generative AI tools prior to use.

Elastic, Elasticsearch, ESRE, Elasticsearch Relevance Engine and associated marks are trademarks, logos or registered trademarks of Elasticsearch N.V. in the United States and other countries. All other company and product names are trademarks, logos or registered trademarks of their respective owners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Kobziakowski,Jürgen Obermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-4-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-4-released"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.11.4 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.11.4 over 8.11.3 and 8.10.x releases.
The 8.11.4 patch release contains a performance issue fix in the Elastic Security Solution. Please see our Elastic Security Solution release notes for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Snehal Adlinge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding Netflix Video Processing Pipeline with Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4e5e6310e359</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/rebuilding-netflix-video-processing-pipeline-with-microservices-4e5e6310e359?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T23:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first blog in a multi-part series on how Netflix rebuilt its video processing pipeline with microservices, so we can maintain…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decision Engines: What They Are and What They Do]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=98025&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=98025</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/01/decision-engines-what-they-are-what-they-do/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T17:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is a decision engine? Why is a decision engine important? Learn how they work in this guide.
The post Decision Engines: What They Are and What They Do appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Results of Google Summer of Code With Kotlin]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=433033</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2024/01/google-summer-of-code-with-kotlin-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T17:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 marked Kotlin’s first-ever participation in Google Summer of Code (GSoC), a global online program focused on bringing new contributors into open-source development. Contributors worked on 12-week programming projects with the Kotlin Foundation under the guidance of mentors from JetBrains, Google, and Gradle, and gained experience on real-world projects. We would like to share the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ksenia Shneyveys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDKTF 0.20 improves implementation of iterators and enables HCL output]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdktf-0-20-improves-implementation-of-iterators-and-enables-hcl-output</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdktf-0-20-improves-implementation-of-iterators-and-enables-hcl-output"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.20 improves the existing implementation of iterators, allowing developers to handle complex scenarios related to dynamic resource creation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad JWT auth with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-jwt-auth-with-github-actions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-jwt-auth-with-github-actions"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how JWT-based authentication works in HashiCorp Nomad using a custom GitHub Action as an example of machine-to-machine authentication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the Livestream: How to work with SQL and Databases in DataSpell]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=432842</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2024/01/join-the-webinar-how-to-work-with-sql-and-databases-in-dataspell/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T14:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We invite you to join our livestream How to work with SQL and Databases in DataSpell. The event will take place on Monday, January 22, at 1:00 PM UTC. Date: January 22, 2024 Time: 1:00 pm UTC (2:00 pm CET / 8:00 am EST) Register In this livestream, we’ll show you how to write SQL queries and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanislav Garkusha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use JetBrains AI Assistant To Help You Understand Changes In Your Code]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=423734</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/01/10/use-jetbrains-ai-assistant-to-help-you-understand-changes-in-your-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T13:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll spend most of your time reading and understanding a codebase as a software developer. Reading and comprehending a rapidly evolving codebase may feel overwhelming, especially in situations with limited access to original authors and outdated documentation. Luckily, code never lies, and with the growing capabilities of LLMs and AI Assistants to parse and summarize […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Livestream Alert: How To Prepare for a Programming Contest?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=432800</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2024/01/10/livestream-alert-how-to-prepare-for-a-programming-contest/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T13:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on January 16, 2024, for a livestream about preparing for a programming contest. Software Engineer at the JetBrains Applied Program Analysis Lab, two-time ICPC world champion (2012 and 2013), and coach for ICPC at Constructor University Bremen and Neapolis University Pafos, Niyaz Nigmatullin will share his expertise on preparing for and competing in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Gupaisova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consequences]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44766</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/860117186/0/sethsblog~Consequences/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frederick Lewis Donaldson created a list of seven social sins that was soon popularized by Gandhi. One hundred years later, it’s more relevant and more urgent than ever. Wealth without work.Pleasure without conscience.Knowledge without character.Commerce without morality.Science without humanity.Religion without sacrifice.Politics without principle. When we create these imbalances, we pay for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Spring Data JDBC]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/10/spring-tips-spring-data-jdbc</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/10/spring-tips-spring-data-jdbc"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like This One]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2879/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2879/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/like_this_one.png" title="A lot of sentences undergo startling shifts in mood if you add 'like this one' to the end, but high on the list is 'I'm a neurologist studying dreams.'" alt="A lot of sentences undergo startling shifts in mood if you add 'like this one' to the end, but high on the list is 'I'm a neurologist studying dreams.'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Off 2023 results 🏆]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-09-game-off-2023-results/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-09-game-off-2023-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T20:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The GitHub Game Off results are in! All games have been rated, ranked, and reviewed. Read on for a look at the 10 highest-rated submissions overall.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-09-game-off-2023-results/">Game Off 2023 results 🏆</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use the Backstage HCP Consul plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-use-the-backstage-hcp-consul-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-use-the-backstage-hcp-consul-plugin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating HCP Consul Central with Backstage can enhance your organization’s infrastructure-management capabilities. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Connect Django With MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=422663</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2024/01/how-to-connect-django-with-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T14:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most popular web frameworks, Django, has adopted the “batteries included” philosophy. This means that you can build a production-ready application using only the vanilla Django with no extensions or other frameworks. Even the database SQLite is available out of the box. SQLite is great for learning and developing small applications, but has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denis Mashutin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda 8.4: Simplifying Installation and Enhancing the User Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=97969&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=97969</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/01/camunda-8-4-simplifying-installation-enhancing-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know everything that's new in the 8.4 release of Camunda, from improved multi-tenancy experience to new components and more.
The post Camunda 8.4: Simplifying Installation and Enhancing the User Experience appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Now Available on the AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=97923&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=97923</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/01/camunda-aws-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T13:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Self-Managed is available on the AWS Marketplace. You can now purchase it there with just a few clicks and start orchestrating quickly.
The post Camunda Now Available on the AWS Marketplace appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Research Digest 2023: Volume 3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=research&amp;p=431798</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/research/2024/01/jetbrains-research-digest-2023-volume-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T13:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Volume 3 of the JetBrains Research Digest, we’re presenting the latest news from two JetBrains Research labs. Mobile Robotics Algorithms Lab The Mobile Robotics Algorithms Lab works on developing intelligent, fully autonomous mobile robots, as well as educational programs in robotics. In November, J. Meghana and J. Hanumanthappa from the University of Mysore, Mysuru, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Artamonova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customer service is a choice]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48235</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/859802132/0/sethsblog~Customer-service-is-a-choice/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T09:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s either part of your strategy or you’re paying for your mistake. 800 numbers changed the way large brands dealt with the public. Instantly, and for free, a consumer could contact a company about a product or service and they would work to make it right. It was more than fodder for an infinite number […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - January 9th, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/09/this-week-in-spring-january-9th-2024</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/09/this-week-in-spring-january-9th-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: User Experience Team]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/01/responsible-ai-at-google-research-user.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/01/responsible-ai-at-google-research-user.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T22:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ayça Çakmakli, UX Lead, Google Research, Responsible AI and Human Centered Technology Team




Google’s Responsible AI User Experience (Responsible AI UX) team is a product-minded team embedded within Google Research. This unique positioning requires us to apply responsible AI development practices to our user-centered user experience (UX) design process. In this post, we describe the importance of UX design and responsible AI in product development, and share a few examples of how our team’s capabilities and cross-functional collaborations have led to responsible development across Google.



First, the UX part. We are a multi-disciplinary team of product design experts: designers, engineers, researchers, and strategists who manage the user-centered UX design process from early-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Certifications are generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-08-github-certifications-are-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-08-github-certifications-are-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T20:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your full potential with GitHub Certifications! Earning a GitHub certification will give you the competitive advantage of showing up as a GitHub expert.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-08-github-certifications-are-generally-available/">GitHub Certifications are generally available</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! AWS Weekly Roundup – January 8, 2024]]></title>
        <id>cfad3721391555e841453d11e345c33fc090054d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-new-year-aws-weekly-roundup-january-8-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T20:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! Cloud technologies, machine learning, and generative AI have become more accessible, impacting nearly every aspect of our lives. Amazon CTO Dr. Werner Vogels offers four tech predictions for 2024 and beyond: Generative AI becomes culturally aware FemTech finally takes off AI assistants redefine developer productivity Education evolves to match the speed of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub and the Ekoparty 2023 Capture the Flag]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-08-github-and-the-ekoparty-2023-capture-the-flag/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-08-github-and-the-ekoparty-2023-capture-the-flag/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The GitHub Security Lab teamed up with Ekoparty once again to create some challenges for its yearly Capture the Flag competition!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-08-github-and-the-ekoparty-2023-capture-the-flag/">GitHub and the Ekoparty 2023 Capture the Flag</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Target CLI: The context switcher for HashiCorp tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/target-cli-the-context-switcher-for-hashicorp-tools</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/target-cli-the-context-switcher-for-hashicorp-tools"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing multiple clusters of HashiCorp tools can be complicated. Target CLI eases the burden by using context profiles to easily switch between different clusters and environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frenemies to friends: Developers and security tools]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-08-frenemies-to-friends-developers-and-security-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-08-frenemies-to-friends-developers-and-security-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T15:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When socializing a new security tool, it IS possible to build a bottom-up security culture where engineering has a seat at the table. Let's explore some effective strategies witnessed by the GitHub technical sales team to make this shift successful.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-08-frenemies-to-friends-developers-and-security-tools/">Frenemies to friends: Developers and security tools</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy: New Learning Content in January]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=431426</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2024/01/08/jetbrains-academy-new-learning-content-in-january/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T13:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a new year, and new learning adventures await you! There’s no better moment to start something new than the beginning of a fresh year. Why not kickstart your learning journey with JetBrains Academy? This month we’ve prepared a new Go project – perfect for those craving a fresh language experience. Additionally, four projects have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Regina Muradova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Digest | January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=424111</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/01/08/net-digest-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T12:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to JetBrains .NET Digest! Yes, this newsletter used to be called JetBrains .NET Annotated, but we’ve Rename Refactored and refreshed the newsletter. 🎉 🌟 Featured Content Happy new year, everyone! 🎉For 2024 and beyond we’ll continue to highlight educational, interesting, and fun content from the .NET and software development communities. We’ll also occasionally showcase […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The opposite of insubordination]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48222</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/859541828/0/sethsblog~The-opposite-of-insubordination/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T09:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Do as I say.” That’s industrial management in four words. If you don’t follow the instructions to the letter, you’re insubordinate. Not subordinate. Complete subordination might have been the goal in an industrial setting. But now, it’s dangerous, expensive and inefficent. Because people close to the work know exactly what needs to be done. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing the power of generative AI in telecom with Elastic Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-generative-ai-telecommunication</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-generative-ai-telecommunication"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration of Elastic and generative AI is ushering in a new era of operational efficiency and innovation. Learn how these technologies are augmenting network operations and revolutionizing inter...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Kobziakowski,Jürgen Obermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing the power of generative AI in telecom with Elastic Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-generative-ai-telecommunication</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-generative-ai-telecommunication"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic landscape of telecommunications, the integration of the Elastic® Stack and generative AI is ushering in a new era of operational efficiency and innovation. These technologies are not just augmenting network operations but are also revolutionizing internal processes across various departments. Below, we’ll delve into their impact on different facets of telecom operations.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt79345f72a075eb00/659597f09fa6cf4b49288e6c/1-blog-elastic-gai-telecom.png,1-blog-elastic-gai-telecom.pnghttps://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt5a0b3cda7437451a/659597f833550e6fa1d5cb73/2-blog-elastic-gai-telecom.png,2-blog-elastic-gai-telecom.pnghttps://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltaf02bf140b5e17d7…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Kobziakowski,Jürgen Obermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supernova]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2878/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2878/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/supernova.png" title="They're a little cagey about exactly where the crossover point lies relative to the likelihood of devastating effects on the planet." alt="They're a little cagey about exactly where the crossover point lies relative to the likelihood of devastating effects on the planet." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoiding technology]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44769</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/859398917/0/sethsblog~Avoiding-technology/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T10:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Caro never learned to type. He pecks out his books two fingers at a time on an electric typewriter. There are two reasons to avoid learning a proven new technology: You know what it can do and how it will change your life and you don’t want it. You don’t know what it can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying harder]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46509</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/859301198/0/sethsblog~Trying-harder/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T09:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Or trying better? Fast runners aren’t the same as slow runners, but with more effort. And great chefs or violinists or actors… it’s not about doing what you did yesterday, but more of that. It’s something different.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PW 5: Measuring the right thing]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48109</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/859299413/0/sethsblog~PW-Measuring-the-right-thing/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last in the series… Most of us were indoctrinated to believe that completing chores is the appropriate measure of productivity. “I did all my homework.” Doing all your homework is a measure for industrial bosses. But what, precisely, did your homework ever do for you? The actual measures of productivity that might be useful range […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Engaging Trivia Experiences: A Developer’s Perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=97837</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/01/creating-engaging-trivia-experiences-developers-perspective/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T17:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a trivia game live was not only a lot of fun, but ended up with surprising new features inspired by the players themselves.
The post Creating Engaging Trivia Experiences: A Developer’s Perspective appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 ways to make your DevSecOps strategy developer-friendly]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-05-5-ways-to-make-your-devsecops-strategy-developer-friendly/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-05-5-ways-to-make-your-devsecops-strategy-developer-friendly/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T15:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Developers care about security, but poorly integrated tools and other factors can cause frustration. Here are five best practices to reduce friction.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-05-5-ways-to-make-your-devsecops-strategy-developer-friendly/">5 ways to make your DevSecOps strategy developer-friendly</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top PKI use cases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/top-pki-use-cases</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/top-pki-use-cases"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PKI provides a flexible and scalable identity-first security solution that aligns with zero trust and secures a wide variety of enterprise use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=423704</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/01/java-annotated-monthly-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T12:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year and welcome to the January edition of Java Annotated Monthly! As we step into 2024, we’re excited to bring you the latest news and tutorials from the tech world. This issue’s highlight is the release of IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 – a real game-changer that introduces an AI Assistant feature that revolutionizes coding […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Maryasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PW 4: Productivity and tools]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48107</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/859152557/0/sethsblog~PW-Productivity-and-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T09:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Smith and Karl Marx both wrote about the pin-making machine. Not too long ago, pins (for hats, to hold shirts in place, etc.) were incredibly expensive. They were a luxury item, and a handmade pin might cost more than buying lunch. The pin-making machine changed this. It transformed the labor of four trained workers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fever]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2877/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2877/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/fever.png" title="Hypothermia of below 98.6 K should be treated by leaving the giant molecular cloud and moving to the vicinity of a star." alt="Hypothermia of below 98.6 K should be treated by leaving the giant molecular cloud and moving to the vicinity of a star." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Productivity week: Bonus]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48193</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/858786254/0/sethsblog~Productivity-week-Bonus/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T17:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an economy built on skill, knowledge, and attitude, the single most powerful way to improve your productivity is to learn something. You put in the effort once and it pays off for decades. There are more ways for an adult to learn now than at any time in our history, and all of it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Kubernetes guru Leigh Capili helps us ring in the new year]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/04/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-guru-leigh-capili-helps-us-ring-in-the-new</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/04/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-guru-leigh-capili-helps-us-ring-in-the-new"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 year in review]]></title>
        <id>http://martin.kleppmann.com/2024/01/04/year-in-review.html</id>
        <link href="http://martin.kleppmann.com/2024/01/04/year-in-review.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot has happened in the last year, so I thought it would be good to write up a review. My biggest change in 2023 was that my wife and I had a baby! This has brought a mixture of joys and frustrations, but overall it has been very good....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Kleppmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Build a Custom Connector Using the Connector SDK]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=97620</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/01/tutorial-custom-connector-using-connector-sdk/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T21:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use the Connector SDK to build a custom Connector.
The post Tutorial: Build a Custom Connector Using the Connector SDK appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds aggregated VCS reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-aggregated-vcs-reviews</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-aggregated-vcs-reviews"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline the verification process across multiple workspaces by aggregating status checks directed to external VCS providers and review changes that affect multiple workspaces on a single page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our move to generated SDKs]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-03-our-move-to-generated-sdks/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-03-our-move-to-generated-sdks/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T15:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub SDKs: software generated meets hand curated.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-03-our-move-to-generated-sdks/">Our move to generated SDKs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 3.1.7 and 3.2.0 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/03/spring-shell-3-1-7-and-3-2-0-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/03/spring-shell-3-1-7-and-3-2-0-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - January 2nd, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/02/this-week-in-spring-january-1st-2024</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/02/this-week-in-spring-january-1st-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[年賀イラスト] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755593132482</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755593132482"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Chat now generally available for organizations and individuals]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-29-github-copilot-chat-now-generally-available-for-organizations-and-individuals/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-29-github-copilot-chat-now-generally-available-for-organizations-and-individuals/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T17:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>All GitHub Copilot users can now enjoy natural language-powered coding with Copilot Chat at no additional cost.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-29-github-copilot-chat-now-generally-available-for-organizations-and-individuals/">GitHub Copilot Chat now generally available for organizations and individuals</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub’s top blog posts of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-27-githubs-top-blog-posts-of-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-27-githubs-top-blog-posts-of-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T17:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As the year winds down, we're highlighting some of the incredible work from GitHub’s engineers, product teams, and security researchers.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-27-githubs-top-blog-posts-of-2023/">GitHub’s top blog posts of 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Intelligent Process Automation (IPA) and how can it help your business?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=97334</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/12/what-is-intelligent-process-automation-ipa-and-how-can-it-help-your-business/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T15:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a quick overview of what Intelligent Process Automation (IPA) is, what workflows should look like, and the technologies you’ll need to get started.
The post What is Intelligent Process Automation (IPA) and how can it help your business? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第244話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755604769484</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755604769484"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benefits of CI/CD]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=97325</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/12/benefits-of-ci-cd/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T15:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn some of the benefits of using CI/CD on your projects in this deep dive.
The post Benefits of CI/CD appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023: A year of groundbreaking advances in AI and computing]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/2023-year-of-groundbreaking-advances-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/2023-year-of-groundbreaking-advances-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T18:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeff Dean, Chief Scientist, Google DeepMind & Google Research, Demis Hassabis, CEO, Google DeepMind, and James Manyika, SVP, Google Research, Technology & Society





This has been a year of incredible progress in the field of Artificial Intelligence (AI) research and its practical applications. 



As ongoing research pushes AI even farther, we look back to our perspective published in January of this year, titled “Why we focus on AI (and to what end),” where we noted:





    We are committed to leading and setting the standard in developing and shipping useful and beneficial applications, applying ethical principles grounded in human values, and evolving our approaches as we learn from research, experience, users, and the wider community.


   We also believe that getting AI…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collaborate and Innovate by Joining Camunda Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=97317</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/12/collaborate-and-innovate-by-joining-camunda-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover pre-built Connectors for everything from protocols like REST and GraphQL to enterprise applications and productivity apps with Camunda Marketplace.
The post Collaborate and Innovate by Joining Camunda Marketplace appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your MySQL 5.7 and PostgreSQL 11 databases will be automatically enrolled into Amazon RDS Extended Support]]></title>
        <id>b5cdd71e80db076a8254fccd5b55346635929927</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/your-mysql-5-7-and-postgresql-11-databases-will-be-automatically-enrolled-into-amazon-rds-extended-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T22:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing that your MySQL 5.7 and PostgreSQL 11 database instances running on Amazon Aurora and Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) will be automatically enrolled into Amazon RDS Extended Support starting on February 29, 2024. This will help avoid unplanned downtime and compatibility issues that can arise with automatically upgrading to a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp 2023 year in review: Community]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2023-year-in-review-community</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2023-year-in-review-community"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year saw tens of thousands of people engage with HashiCorp to achieve HashiCorp certifications, while hundreds of millions downloaded HashiCorp community software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Process Orchestration Maturity Model: Level 4]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=97161</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/12/process-orchestration-maturity-model-level-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T20:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does your organization need to do to achieve Level 4 of the Process Orchestration Maturity Model? Learn how in the final post in our series on process orchestration maturity.
The post Process Orchestration Maturity Model: Level 4 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNS over HTTPS is now available in Amazon Route 53 Resolver]]></title>
        <id>4694b932095b5a1012286d52e7559c670fe69489</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/dns-over-https-is-now-available-in-amazon-route-53-resolver/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T18:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, Amazon Route 53 Resolver supports using the DNS over HTTPS (DoH) protocol for both inbound and outbound Resolver endpoints. As the name suggests, DoH supports HTTP or HTTP/2 over TLS to encrypt the data exchanged for Domain Name System (DNS) resolutions. Using TLS encryption, DoH increases privacy and security by preventing eavesdropping and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contextual logging in Kubernetes 1.29: Better troubleshooting and enhanced logging]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/20/contextual-logging-in-kubernetes-1-29/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/20/contextual-logging-in-kubernetes-1-29/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Mengjiao Liu (DaoCloud), Patrick Ohly (Intel)
On behalf of the Structured Logging Working Group
and SIG Instrumentation,
we are pleased to announce that the contextual logging feature
introduced in Kubernetes v1.24 has now been successfully migrated to
two components (kube-scheduler and kube-controller-manager)
as well as some directories. This feature aims to provide more useful logs
for better troubleshooting of Kubernetes and to empower developers to enhance Kubernetes.
What is contextual logging?
Contextual logging
is based on the go-logr API.
The key idea is that libraries are passed a logger instance by their caller
and use that for logging instead of accessing a global logger.
The binary decides the logging implementation, not the libraries.
The go-logr API is designed arou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp 2023 year in review: Customers and partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2023-year-in-review-customers-and-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2023-year-in-review-customers-and-partners"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a look back at HashiCorp’s new customers, new customer stories, and partner ecosystem milestones from the past year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Canada West (Calgary) Region is now available]]></title>
        <id>6b3cea87b782c16878fbdb2c69ae9048a41b26a5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/the-aws-canada-west-calgary-region-is-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T11:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update: December 20, 2023 — The list of services available today at launch is now updated with AWS Artifact, AWS Cloud Control API, AWS Directory Services, EC2 Image Builder, and AWS Transit Gateway for a new total of 70 services.   Today, we are opening a new Region in Canada. AWS Canada West (Calgary), also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US federal agencies and AI: The race is on]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-federal-agencies-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-federal-agencies-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new audit from the US government shows that federal agencies are rapidly increasing their use of AI. Here, we unpack agencies’ AI use cases and top considerations for AI implementation in government...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 reasons to upgrade Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-reasons-to-upgrade-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-reasons-to-upgrade-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic upgrades come quickly, and it can be a challenge to schedule upgrades. Here we’ll take a quick look at the top five new features in Elastic Security that’ll help you reduce risk and control co...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dain Perkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US federal agencies and AI: The race is on]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-federal-agencies-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-federal-agencies-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI revolution in federal agencies has begun
Federal agencies are ramping up their use of artificial intelligence significantly, according to a US Government Accountability Office (GAO) audit. The report noted that there were 228 different AI use cases in operation, with over 500 more in planning and approximately another 500 in research or exploration phases. These numbers are likely conservative, considering the rapid advancement in AI since the report compiled its data for Fiscal Year 2022. 

Agencies are employing AI for diverse purposes to enhance their agency’s mission — from analyzing surveillance data for border activities to interpreting drone images to detecting cybersecurity threats and processing large data sets. Notably, NASA and the Department of Commerce are leading in AI…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 reasons to upgrade Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-reasons-to-upgrade-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-reasons-to-upgrade-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fear of missing out, or fear of missing logs?
Let’s start with assurances that we’re not here to heap anxiety on anyone’s fear of missing out. That being said, we do want to make sure you’re aware of all the goodness that is available in Elastic Security, especially if you’re on an older version. It can be hard to find time to dig into every new release, to see what new features might be available, or check on ways to stretch your budget in order to pick up all the logs you might be missing.

Elastic® releases new versions fairly quickly, driven by new features, user submitted enhancement requests, and of course, the occasional bug fix. It can be challenging to schedule upgrades for every new release, particularly when we’re talking about a SIEM platform that needs to be running 24/7/365, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dain Perkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VideoPoet: A large language model for zero-shot video generation]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/videopoet-large-language-model-for-zero.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/videopoet-large-language-model-for-zero.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T21:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dan Kondratyuk and David Ross, Software Engineers, Google Research




A recent wave of video generation models has burst onto the scene, in many cases showcasing stunning picturesque quality. One of the current bottlenecks in video generation is in the ability to produce coherent large motions. In many cases, even the current leading models either generate small motion or, when producing larger motions, exhibit noticeable artifacts.
 

To explore the application of language models in video generation, we introduce VideoPoet (website, research paper), a large language model (LLM) that is capable of a wide variety of video generation tasks, including text-to-video, image-to-video, video stylization, video inpainting and outpainting, and video-to-audio. One notable observation is t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS India customers can now save card information for monthly AWS billing]]></title>
        <id>1cd93eb93a4a6344bc1ea2d4e334af63f84faf21</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-india-customers-can-now-save-card-information-for-monthly-aws-billing/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T20:11:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, AWS India customers can now securely save their credit or debit cards in their AWS accounts according to the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) guidelines. Customers can use their saved cards to make payments for their AWS invoices. Previously, customers needed to manually enter their card information in the payments console for each payment. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we organize and get things done with SERVICEOWNERS]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-19-how-we-organize-and-get-things-done-with-serviceowners/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-19-how-we-organize-and-get-things-done-with-serviceowners/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T18:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Take CODEOWNERS and GitHub teams to the next level. Learn about how GitHub engineering solves the age old problem of who owns what.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-19-how-we-organize-and-get-things-done-with-serviceowners/">How we organize and get things done with SERVICEOWNERS</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp 2023 year in review: Product innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2023-year-in-review-product-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2023-year-in-review-product-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking back on a busy year, we’re proud of so many technical accomplishments. We’re even more excited about the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simulations illuminate the path to post-event traffic flow]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/simulations-illuminate-path-to-post.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/simulations-illuminate-path-to-post.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yechen Li and Neha Arora, Software Engineers, Google Research




Fifteen minutes. That’s how long it took to empty the Colosseum, an engineering marvel that’s still standing as the largest amphitheater in the world. Two thousand years later, this design continues to work well to move enormous crowds out of sporting and entertainment venues.





But of course, exiting the arena is only the first step. Next, people must navigate the traffic that builds up in the surrounding streets. This is an age-old problem that remains unsolved to this day. In Rome, they addressed the issue by prohibiting private traffic on the street that passes directly by the Colosseum. This policy worked there, but what if you’re not in Rome? What if you’re at the Superbowl? Or at a Taylor Swift concert?

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M-21-31 logging compliance: Overcoming the 3 top challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/m-21-31-logging-compliance-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/m-21-31-logging-compliance-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US federal agencies have made progress in adhering to M-21-31’s cyber threat response requirements but lag in advanced event logging requirements. Learn how Elastic can help agencies overcome three ma...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link,Richard Im</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do customers choose Elastic for logs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-do-customers-choose-elastic-for-logs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-do-customers-choose-elastic-for-logs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic helped define centralized logging; now we’re redefining the value modern logging tools can bring. We discuss how ES|QL, ML, AI, and OTel enable customers to transform logging from a reactive d...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ty Bekiares</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU AI Act: What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/eu-ai-act</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/eu-ai-act"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EU’s AI Act, which sets regulations for artificial intelligence, is the first of its kind — but it likely will not be the last. Here’s what it means for global organizations and what you can do to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M-21-31 logging compliance: Overcoming the 3 top challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/m-21-31-logging-compliance-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/m-21-31-logging-compliance-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, the US Government Accountability Office (GAO) released a study tracking US federal agencies’ progress on meeting the requirements set out in OMB M-21-31. Released in 2021, the Office of Management and Budget (OMB)’s M-21-31 memorandum provided guidance and requirements for federal agencies in order to improve centralized visibility into logging data before, during, and after cybersecurity incidents. The memo outlined a logging maturity model with four tiers (E0-3) to guide agencies in their compliance process.

In the new study, GAO found that agencies “have made progress in preparing for and responding to cyber threats.” At the same time, however, the study noted that 20 of the 23 agencies did not meet M-21-31’s tier 3 advanced event logging (“advanced EL3”) August deadline for tracking, storing, and managing event logs.

The study highlighted three challenges agencies are facing as they work to meet M-21-31 event logging requirements: 


Lack of staff

Event logging technical challenges

Limitations in cyber event information sharing


In this post, we’ll walk through these challenges and share how we’ve seen federal customers address them using Elasticsearch®.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link,Richard Im</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do customers choose Elastic for logs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-do-customers-choose-elastic-for-logs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-do-customers-choose-elastic-for-logs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the absence of other observability signals, generally everything in your infrastructure (hardware, software, and services) emits log lines. Logs, however, are often structured at a developer’s whim and, first and foremost, serve the developer’s needs (e.g., debugging). Once in production, these same log lines are inherently promoted to a first-class means of observing your applications and infrastructure, regardless of their original intent. This makes logs a notoriously noisy observability signal whose rate can swing wildly with errors and scale.

The simplicity of the log line as an observability signal (fundamentally, it’s just text!) makes it deceivingly simple to observe. On the other hand, its noisy, unstructured nature and unpredictable rate make it among the most difficult of si…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ty Bekiares</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU AI Act: What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/eu-ai-act</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/eu-ai-act"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On December 8, 2023, the European Union made a significant step in digital governance by introducing the first set of comprehensive artificial intelligence (AI) regulations. This legislation, poised for a European Parliament vote by early 2024, is first out of the gate in regulating AI. As organizations look to comply with this act (and the additional regulations likely to come on its heels), one thing is for sure: The ability to have access and insight into all data will be essential. And the stakes have never been higher.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.

In this blog post, we may have used or referred to third party generative AI tools, which are owned and operated by their respective owners. Elastic does not have any control over the third party tools and we have no responsibility or liability for their content, operation or use, nor for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of such tools. Please exercise caution when using AI tools with personal, sensitive or confidential information. Any data you submit may be used for AI training or other purposes. There is no guarantee that information you provide will be kept secure or confidential. You should familiarize yourself with the privacy practices and terms of use of any generative AI tools prior to use.

Elastic, Elasticsearch, ESRE, Elasticsearch Relevance Engine and associated marks are trademarks, logos or registered trademarks of Elasticsearch N.V. in the United States and other countries. All other company and product names are trademarks, logos or registered trademarks of their respective owners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.29: Decoupling taint-manager from node-lifecycle-controller]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/19/kubernetes-1-29-taint-eviction-controller/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/19/kubernetes-1-29-taint-eviction-controller/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Yuan Chen (Apple), Andrea Tosatto (Apple)
This blog discusses a new feature in Kubernetes 1.29 to improve the handling of taint-based pod eviction.
Background
In Kubernetes 1.29, an improvement has been introduced to enhance the taint-based pod eviction handling on nodes.
This blog discusses the changes made to node-lifecycle-controller
to separate its responsibilities and improve overall code maintainability.
Summary of changes
node-lifecycle-controller previously combined two independent functions:
Adding a pre-defined set of NoExecute taints to Node based on Node's condition.
Performing pod eviction on NoExecute taint.
With the Kubernetes 1.29 release, the taint-based eviction implementation has been
moved out of node-lifecycle-controller into a separate and independent compone…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.29: PodReadyToStartContainers Condition Moves to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/19/pod-ready-to-start-containers-condition-now-in-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/19/pod-ready-to-start-containers-condition-now-in-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Zefeng Chen (independent), Kevin Hannon (Red Hat)
With the recent release of Kubernetes 1.29, the PodReadyToStartContainers
condition is
available by default.
The kubelet manages the value for that condition throughout a Pod's lifecycle,
in the status field of a Pod. The kubelet will use the PodReadyToStartContainers
condition to accurately surface the initialization state of a Pod,
from the perspective of Pod sandbox creation and network configuration by a container runtime.
What's the motivation for this feature?
Cluster administrators did not have a clear and easily accessible way to view the completion of Pod's sandbox creation
and initialization. As of 1.28, the Initialized condition in Pods tracks the execution of init containers.
However, it has limitations in accurately re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — AWS Lambda, AWS Amplify, Amazon OpenSearch Service, Amazon Rekognition, and more — December 18, 2023]]></title>
        <id>2dacccda6aac8e12d9d28e3e086b8d65dbbd17b8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-lambda-aws-amplify-amazon-opensearch-service-amazon-rekognition-and-more-december-18-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T17:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My memories of Amazon Web Services (AWS) re:Invent 2023 are still fresh even when I’m currently wrapping up my activities in Jakarta after participating in AWS Community Day Indonesia. It was a great experience, from delivering chalk talks and having thoughtful discussions with AWS service teams, to meeting with AWS Heroes, AWS Community Builders, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The benefits of using a Verified MSP for your Elastic deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/verified-msp-elastic-deployments-benefits</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/verified-msp-elastic-deployments-benefits"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the benefits of a managed service provider and learn about Elastic’s new MSP designation, Verified. Explore eight considerations for choosing the right MSP for your business. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabelle Li,David Kosman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The benefits of using a Verified MSP for your Elastic deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/verified-msp-elastic-deployments-benefits</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/verified-msp-elastic-deployments-benefits"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why choose a Managed Service Provider (MSP)? 
Using an MSP allows you to focus on your core business instead of your IT infrastructure. The right MSP not only provides deep technical expertise and 24/7 monitoring and management of your infrastructure, but it can also improve core operational and procedural challenges over time to help you reduce costs and streamline operations, so your IT team can focus on projects that accelerate your business.
Ready to engage with an Elastic Verified MSP?
Whether you want to leverage Elastic within your data center or via the cloud, here are eight areas to consider when selecting a MSP:

Support: Ensure that your preferred MSP offers 24/7 support and security operation center(s) across time zones.

Pricing: Review pricing models to make sure it fits within your resources.

Breadth of services: Consider your needs today, but also what you might need in one, three, or five years. Choose an MSP with a wide range of services so you’re able to grow together and build a lasting partnership. 

Cloud or hybrid posture: What is your current environment? Make sure your MSP supports your model.

Service offerings: Inquire about additional offerings, like consulting or migration services.

References: Ask to see validated customer references and testimonials.

Certifications and clearances: If your industry is regulated, ensure that your MSP has the right certifications and clearances. 

Verified: Consider choosing an MSP who is Elastic Verified. This ensures the MSP has the correct architecture design, proof of 24/7 support, Elastic-certified engineers, successful customer deployments, and more.

Our current list of our Verified MSP partners includes:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabelle Li,David Kosman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.29: New (alpha) Feature, Load Balancer IP Mode for Services]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/18/kubernetes-1-29-feature-loadbalancer-ip-mode-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/18/kubernetes-1-29-feature-loadbalancer-ip-mode-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aohan Yang
This blog introduces a new alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.29.
It provides a configurable approach to define how Service implementations,
exemplified in this blog by kube-proxy,
handle traffic from pods to the Service, within the cluster.
Background
In older Kubernetes releases, the kube-proxy would intercept traffic that was destined for the IP
address associated with a Service of type: LoadBalancer. This happened whatever mode you used
for kube-proxy.
The interception implemented the expected behavior (traffic eventually reaching the expected
endpoints behind the Service). The mechanism to make that work depended on the mode for kube-proxy;
on Linux, kube-proxy in iptables mode would redirecting packets directly to the endpoint; in ipvs mode,
kube-proxy would configure t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.29: Single Pod Access Mode for PersistentVolumes Graduates to Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/18/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/18/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chris Henzie (Google)
With the release of Kubernetes v1.29, the ReadWriteOncePod volume access mode
has graduated to general availability: it's part of Kubernetes' stable API. In
this blog post, I'll take a closer look at this access mode and what it does.
What is ReadWriteOncePod?
ReadWriteOncePod is an access mode for
PersistentVolumes (PVs)
and PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs)
introduced in Kubernetes v1.22. This access mode enables you to restrict volume
access to a single pod in the cluster, ensuring that only one pod can write to
the volume at a time. This can be particularly useful for stateful workloads
that require single-writer access to storage.
For more context on access modes and how ReadWriteOncePod works read
What are access modes and why are they important?
in the Intr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advancements in machine learning for machine learning]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/advancements-in-machine-learning-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/advancements-in-machine-learning-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Phitchaya Mangpo Phothilimthana, Staff Research Scientist, Google DeepMind, and Bryan Perozzi, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Research





With the recent and accelerated advances in machine learning (ML), machines can understand natural language, engage in conversations, draw images, create videos and more. Modern ML models are programmed and trained using ML programming frameworks, such as TensorFlow, JAX, PyTorch, among many others. These libraries provide high-level instructions to ML practitioners, such as linear algebra operations (e.g., matrix multiplication, convolution, etc.) and neural network layers (e.g., 2D convolution layers, transformer layers). Importantly, practitioners need not worry about how to make their models run efficiently on hardware because an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[StyleDrop: Text-to-image generation in any style]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/styledrop-text-to-image-generation-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/styledrop-text-to-image-generation-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kihyuk Sohn and Dilip Krishnan, Research Scientists, Google Research




Text-to-image models trained on large volumes of image-text pairs have enabled the creation of rich and diverse images encompassing many genres and themes. Moreover, popular styles such as “anime” or “steampunk”, when added to the input text prompt, may translate to specific visual outputs. While many efforts have been put into prompt engineering, a wide range of styles are simply hard to describe in text form due to the nuances of color schemes, illumination, and other characteristics. As an example, “watercolor painting” may refer to various styles, and using a text prompt that simply says “watercolor painting style” may either result in one specific style or an unpredictable mix of several.
 




When we …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.29: CSI Storage Resizing Authenticated and Generally Available in v1.29]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/csi-node-expand-secret-support-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/csi-node-expand-secret-support-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Humble Chirammal (Vmware), Louis Koo (deeproute.ai)
Kubernetes version v1.29 brings generally available support for authentication
during CSI (Container Storage Interface) storage resize operations.
Let's embark on the evolution of this feature, initially introduced in alpha in
Kubernetes v1.25, and unravel the changes accompanying its transition to GA.
Authenticated CSI storage resizing unveiled
Kubernetes harnesses the capabilities of CSI to seamlessly integrate with third-party
storage systems, empowering your cluster to seamlessly expand storage volumes
managed by the CSI driver. The recent elevation of authentication secret support
for resizes from Beta to GA ushers in new horizons, enabling volume expansion in
scenarios where the underlying storage operation demands credenti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.29: VolumeAttributesClass for Volume Modification]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/kubernetes-1-29-volume-attributes-class/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/kubernetes-1-29-volume-attributes-class/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sunny Song (Google)
The v1.29 release of Kubernetes introduced an alpha feature to support modifying a volume
by changing the volumeAttributesClassName that was specified for a PersistentVolumeClaim (PVC).
With the feature enabled, Kubernetes can handle updates of volume attributes other than capacity.
Allowing volume attributes to be changed without managing it through different
provider's APIs directly simplifies the current flow.
You can read about VolumeAttributesClass usage details in the Kubernetes documentation
or you can read on to learn about why the Kubernetes project is supporting this feature.
VolumeAttributesClass
The new storage.k8s.io/v1alpha1 API group provides two new types:
VolumeAttributesClass
Represents a specification of mutable volume attributes defined by th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitchell reflects as he departs HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mitchell-reflects-as-he-departs-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mitchell-reflects-as-he-departs-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After more than 11 years, HashiCorp Co-Founder Mitchell Hashimoto pens a heartfelt goodbye letter to the company he helped create.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.29: Cloud Provider Integrations Are Now Separate Components]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/14/cloud-provider-integration-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/14/cloud-provider-integration-changes/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Michael McCune (Red Hat), Andrew Sy Kim (Google)
For Kubernetes v1.29, you need to use additional components to integrate your
Kubernetes cluster with a cloud infrastructure provider. By default, Kubernetes
v1.29 components abort if you try to specify integration with any cloud provider using
one of the legacy compiled-in cloud provider integrations. If you want to use a legacy
integration, you have to opt back in - and a future release will remove even that option.
In 2018, the Kubernetes community agreed to form the Cloud Provider Special
Interest Group (SIG), with a mission to externalize all cloud provider
integrations and remove all the existing in-tree cloud provider integrations.
In January 2019, the Kubernetes community approved the initial draft of
KEP-2395: Removing In-T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to Azure DevOps Demo Generator and Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67966</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/updates-to-azure-devops-demo-generator-and-labs/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that we have published new content to the Azure DevOps Demo Generator and Azure DevOps Labs!
The Azure DevOps Labs is a great tool to help you learn about the integrated features offered in Azure DevOps.
The post Updates to Azure DevOps Demo Generator and Labs appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our First Netflix Data Engineering Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f326b0589102</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/our-first-netflix-data-engineering-summit-f326b0589102?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holden Karau Elizabeth Stone Pedro Duarte Chris Stephens Pallavi Phadnis Lee Woodridge Mark Cho Guil Pires Sujay Jain Tristan Reid…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds on-demand policy evaluation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-on-demand-policy-evaluation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-on-demand-policy-evaluation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-demand policy evaluation improves visibility and control by letting users evaluate the effects of policy changes in Terraform Cloud before they are enforced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>