<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-08T01:10:06.432Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-08T01:10:06.432Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Aurora MySQL zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>2308f549d5548edd37c9cee34f1a4c94a050db99</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-aurora-mysql-zero-etl-integration-with-amazon-redshift-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T21:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Data is at the center of every application, process, and business decision,” wrote Swami Sivasubramanian, VP of Database, Analytics, and Machine Learning at AWS, and I couldn’t agree more. A common pattern customers use today is to build data pipelines to move data from Amazon Aurora to Amazon Redshift. These solutions help them gain insights […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Create application-consistent snapshots using Amazon Data Lifecycle Manager and custom scripts]]></title>
        <id>21819ebcd771021186ce58ee87af26de0e9b8d27</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-create-application-consistent-snapshots-using-amazon-data-lifecycle-manager-and-custom-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T20:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Data Lifecycle Manager now supports the use of pre-snapshot and post-snapshot scripts embedded in AWS Systems Manager documents. You can use these scripts to ensure that Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) snapshots created by Data Lifecycle Manager are application-consistent. Scripts can pause and resume I/O operations, flush buffered data to EBS volumes, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternating updates for efficient transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/alternating-updates-for-efficient.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/alternating-updates-for-efficient.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T20:34:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xin Wang, Software Engineer, and Nishanth Dikkala, Research Scientist, Google Research




Contemporary deep learning models have been remarkably successful in many domains, ranging from natural language to computer vision. Transformer neural networks (transformers) are a popular deep learning architecture that today comprise the foundation for most tasks in natural language processing and also are starting to extend to applications in other domains, such as computer vision, robotics, and autonomous driving. Moreover, they form the backbone of all the current state-of-the-art language models.
 

Increasing scale in Transformer networks has led to improved performance and the emergence of behavior not present in smaller networks. However, this increase in scale often comes with pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Process Orchestration Strengthens Operational Resilience]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93926</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/11/process-orchestration-operational-resilience/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T19:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banking CEOs are now on notice: They need to demonstrate operational resiliency.
The post How Process Orchestration Strengthens Operational Resilience appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Grund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud now supports dynamic provider credentials for Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-now-supports-dynamic-provider-credentials-for-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-now-supports-dynamic-provider-credentials-for-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud dynamic provider credentials now enable automated authentication for Kubernetes via EKS and GKE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Operator v2 for Kubernetes is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-operator-v2-for-kubernetes-is-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-operator-v2-for-kubernetes-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Operator v2 for Kubernetes is now generally available, enhancing resource management and scaling of Terraform Cloud agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome Fleet with Kotlin Multiplatform Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=403389</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/11/kotlin-multiplatform-tooling-in-fleet/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T14:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP) is an open-source technology built by JetBrains that allows you to share code across multiple platforms while retaining the benefits of native programming. Supported platforms include iOS, Android, desktop, web, and others. Today, we’re launching a preview for Kotlin Multiplatform support in Fleet, which simplifies the development of multiplatform applications, adding to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hadi Hariri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 use cases for automating your infrastructure with Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/5-use-cases-for-automating-your-infrastructure-with-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/5-use-cases-for-automating-your-infrastructure-with-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure automation is an area where systems administrators and  IT operations teams can see some of the biggest benefits from automation, including time savings, reducing tedious manual work, and improving the overall health of their systems. In this blog, I've identified the top 5 infrastructure automation use cases for Ansible Automation Platform that you can deploy in your own environment, and I've incorporated new capabilities like Event-Driven Ansible to make managing your infrastructure even easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>trmcconn@redhat.com (Tricia McConnell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JetBrains Rider Implemented .NET WebAssembly Debugging]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=399743</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/11/07/how-jetbrains-rider-implemented-net-webassembly-debugging/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blazor is part of a .NET technology that lets you build full-stack web applications using C# without the need to write JavaScript code. There’s server-side Blazor, client-side Blazor (which uses WebAssembly (WASM) to run in the browser and interact with the DOM), and other hosting models. Our .NET IDE, JetBrains Rider, helps you develop Blazor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maarten Balliauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project resistance]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47657</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/818261723/0/sethsblog~Project-resistance/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T09:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Steven Pressfield’s classic The War of Art, he introduces the idea of Resistance. It’s the internal force that keeps us from doing our most important creative work. If an instinct, a habit or a feeling gets in the way of the work, it’s Pressfield’s Resistance. Things we would never choose to add to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - November 7th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/07/this-week-in-spring-november-7th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/07/this-week-in-spring-november-7th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSL hot reload in Spring Boot 3.2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/07/ssl-hot-reload-in-spring-boot-3-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/07/ssl-hot-reload-in-spring-boot-3-2-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with ES|QL (Elasticsearch Query Language)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-elasticsearch-query-language</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-elasticsearch-query-language"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with ES|QL and learn how to use it to analyze, visualize, and get insights from your data. ES|QL accelerates your workflows by allowing you to create visualizations, calculations, and aggregations directly from one screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ninoslav Miskovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Security 8.11: Piped queries, AI assistance, and cloud and user data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-11-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-11-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 8.11 brings ES|QL piped queries, AI Assistant upgrades, and data integrations for Okta, Microsoft Entra ID, Wiz, and Palo Alto Prisma Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Paquette,James Spiteri,Jamie Hynds,Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11: Introducing a new powerful query language, ES|QL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-platform-8-11-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-platform-8-11-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11 introduces an advanced query language known as ES|QL in the Discover application, making data exploration more straightforward and user friendly. The Elastic Learned Sparse EncodeR (ELSER) is now generally available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Perkins,Ninoslav Miskovic,Gilad Gal,Teresa Soler,Shani Sagiv,Jason Burns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantifying the value of AI-powered observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/quantifying-the-value-of-ai-powered-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/quantifying-the-value-of-ai-powered-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic commissioned Forrester to provide objective research based on the value of AI-powered observability. The study found that organizations leveraging Elastic Observability see a 243% ROI and $1.2 million in savings over three years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Observability with ES|QL: Streamlining SRE operations and issue resolution for Kubernetes and OTel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-kubernetes-problem-resolution-elastic-observability-esql</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-kubernetes-problem-resolution-elastic-observability-esql"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ES|QL enhances operational efficiency, data analysis, and issue resolution for SREs. This blog covers the advantages of ES|QL in Elastic Observability and how it can apply to managing issues instrumented with OpenTelemetry and running on Kubernetes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.11: ES|QL, Universal profiling in APM, and enhanced SLOs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-11-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-11-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability introduces ES|QL for Observability, Universal Profiling and Elastic APM integration, and new SLO enhancements for Elastic Observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Grabowski,Katrin Freihofner,Israel Ogbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch and LangChain collaborate on production-ready RAG templates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-langchain-production-ready-rag-templates</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-langchain-production-ready-rag-templates"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about how Elasticsearch and LangChain have collaborated on production-ready RAG templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why public sector needs AI-powered observability: Cost savings, ROI, and analyst efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/public-sector-ai-observability-cost-savings-roi-analyst-efficiency</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/public-sector-ai-observability-cost-savings-roi-analyst-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability helps public sector customers solve problems like IT modernization, data silos, and data inaccessibility. Customers gain significant value from Elastic Observability, including increased ROI, analyst efficiency and cost savings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 8.11: Preview of ES|QL, GA of Elastic Learned Sparse EncodeR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-11-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-11-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 8.11 includes the GA of the Elastic Learned Sparse EncodeR (ELSER), tech preview of ES|QL, Elastic AI Assistant support for Amazon Bedrock, and Elasticsearch Relevance Engine (ESRE) improvements in vector search.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From pipe dreams to reality: Announcing Elastic’s piped query language, ES|QL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/esql-elasticsearch-piped-query-language</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/esql-elasticsearch-piped-query-language"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing ES|QL: Elastic's piped query language. Transform, enrich, and simplify data investigations with concurrent processing, efficient searches across data, and all-in-one screen aggregations and visualizations delivering iterative workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar,Bahubali Shetti,Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with ES|QL (Elasticsearch Query Language)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-elasticsearch-query-language</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-elasticsearch-query-language"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is ES|QL (Elasticsearch Query Language)?,
ES|QL (Elasticsearch Query Language) is Elastic®'s new innovative piped query language, designed to speed up your data analysis and investigation processes by offering powerful computing and aggregation capabilities. 

Navigate through the complexities of identifying unfolding cyber attacks or pinpointing production issues with enhanced ease and efficiency. 

ES|QL not only simplifies searching, aggregating, and visualizing massive data sets but also empowers users with advanced features like lookups and real-time processing, all from a single screen in Discover.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltf1ba0812b74b1ada/65428eb908cc0104077cd28a/elastic-blog-1-how-to-get-started.png,elastic-blog-1-how-to-get-started.png,
T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ninoslav Miskovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Security 8.11: Piped queries, AI assistance, and cloud and user data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-11-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-11-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Security 8.11 introduces pipe queries with Elasticsearch Query Language (ES|QL), an Elastic AI Assistant connector for AWS Bedrock, and data integrations for Okta, Microsoft Entra ID, Wiz, and Palo Alto Prisma Cloud. Together, these enhancements deliver vital guidance and context to threat hunters and investigators.

Elastic Security 8.11 is available now on Elastic Cloud — the only hosted Elasticsearch® offering to include all of the new features in this latest release. You can also download the Elastic Stack and our cloud orchestration products, Elastic Cloud Enterprise and Elastic Cloud for Kubernetes, for a self-managed experience.

What else is new? Check out the Elastic 8.11 announcement post to learn more.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltcf34…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Paquette,James Spiteri,Jamie Hynds,Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11: Introducing a new powerful query language, ES|QL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-platform-8-11-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-platform-8-11-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic® Stack 8.11 introduces data stream lifecycle, a simple way to configure retention and downsampling for data streams (tech preview), plus details about the cross-cluster search response in the Kibana® Inspector and general availability for the reroute ingest processor. 
These new features allow customers to:

Manage data stream retention directly in the data stream without needing an ILM policy
See more information about their remote searches so they can triage any potential issues
Route documents to the right index based on values in their fields

Elastic Stack 8.11 is available now on Elastic Cloud — the only hosted Elasticsearch® offering to include all of the new features in this latest release. You can also download the Elastic Stack and our cloud orchestration products, Elas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Perkins,Ninoslav Miskovic,Gilad Gal,Teresa Soler,Shani Sagiv,Jason Burns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantifying the value of AI-powered observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/quantifying-the-value-of-ai-powered-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/quantifying-the-value-of-ai-powered-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In today’s complex and distributed IT environments, traditional monitoring falls short. Legacy tools often provide limited visibility across an organization’s tech stack and often at a high cost, resulting in selective monitoring. Many companies are therefore realizing the need for true, affordable end-to-end observability, which eliminates blind spots and improves visibility across their ecosystem. In particular, organizations are seeking tools that leverage AI for drawing insights from the data and connecting the dots — helping teams collaborate, innovate, and solve problems faster.
,To better understand the benefits, costs, and risks associated with this investment, Elastic® commissioned Forrester to provide a business value analysis to understand the financial impact of an investment into Elastic Observability. Forrester Consulting interviewed seven representatives from five organizations with experience using Elastic's own AI-powered observability solution. For this study, Forrester aggregated the interviewees' experiences and combined the results into a single composite organization — an online services organization with 10 million customers and revenue of $1 billion per year.
,The study has shown that deploying a unified full-stack observability platform can help organizations obtain greater visibility across the ecosystem, while reducing costs and driving efficiencies. Interested in learning more? Read the study report.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Observability with ES|QL: Streamlining SRE operations and issue resolution for Kubernetes and OTel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-kubernetes-problem-resolution-elastic-observability-esql</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-kubernetes-problem-resolution-elastic-observability-esql"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As an operations engineer (SRE, IT Operations, DevOps), managing technology and data sprawl is an ongoing challenge. Simply managing the large volumes of high dimensionality and high cardinality data is overwhelming.
As a single platform, Elastic® helps SREs unify and correlate limitless telemetry data, including metrics, logs, traces, and profiling, into a single datastore — Elasticsearch®. By then applying the power of Elastic’s advanced machine learning (ML), AIOps, AI Assistant, and analytics, you can break down silos and turn data into insights. As a full-stack observability solution, everything from infrastructure monitoring to log monitoring and application performance monitoring (APM) can be found in a single, unified experience.
In Elastic 8.11, a technical preview is now availa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.11: ES|QL, Universal profiling in APM, and enhanced SLOs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-11-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-11-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Observability 8.11 introduces ES|QL for Observability (technical preview), Universal ProfilingTM and Elastic APM integration, and new SLO enhancements for Elastic Observability:

ES|QL for Elastic Observability: Now in tech preview, Elasticsearch Query Language (ES|QL) transforms, enriches, and simplifies data investigations. Read about how ES|QL integrates with Elastic AI Assistant, easily creates alerts, and creates contextual insights with a single query.
Universal Profiling with Elastic APM: Correlate application performance issues with underlying system functions in APM without having to switch context. This helps SREs increase visibility and reduce time to resolution.
New capabilities added to the SLO tech preview enhancing operational experience, which include adding dashb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Grabowski,Katrin Freihofner,Israel Ogbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch and LangChain collaborate on production-ready RAG templates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-langchain-production-ready-rag-templates</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-langchain-production-ready-rag-templates"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For the past few months, we’ve been working closely with the LangChain team as they made progress on launching LangServe and LangChain Templates! LangChain Templates is a set of reference architectures to build production-ready generative AI applications. You can read more about the launch here.
Thanks to our community, Elasticsearch® is one of the most popular vector stores on LangChain. Elasticsearch has production-ready vector database capabilities that developers can use to build interesting use cases. This collaboration with LangChain brings together the power of LangSmith — designed to help you create production-ready generative AI apps — and Elasticsearch to enable you — and companies like Labelbox and Cisco — to build better AI products, at scale.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.
In this blog post, we may have used or referred to third party generative AI tools, which are owned and operated by their respective owners. Elastic does not have any control over the third party tools and we have no responsibility or liability for their content, operation or use, nor for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of such tools. Please exercise caution when using AI tools with personal, sensitive or confidential information. Any data you submit may be used for AI training or other purposes. There is no guarantee that information you provide will be kept secure or confidential. You should familiarize yourself with the privacy practices and terms of use of any generative AI tools prior to use. 
Elastic, Elasticsearch, ESRE, Elasticsearch Relevance Engine and associated marks are trademarks, logos or registered trademarks of Elasticsearch N.V. in the United States and other countries. All other company and product names are trademarks, logos or registered trademarks of their respective owners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why public sector needs AI-powered observability: Cost savings, ROI, and analyst efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/public-sector-ai-observability-cost-savings-roi-analyst-efficiency</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/public-sector-ai-observability-cost-savings-roi-analyst-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For government and education organizations around the world, facilitating an efficient, reliable customer experience is essential when providing critical services and building trust with stakeholders. As technology infrastructure expands and the IT landscape becomes a complex mix of private cloud, public cloud, and air-gapped environments, the ability to see across all systems and data is challenging yet critical. With an AI-powered observability solution, organizations can strengthen operational resilience by improving real-time visibility, generating AI-powered insights, and detecting and resolving IT issues faster.

This week, Forrester Consulting released the The Total Economic Impact™ (TEI) of Elastic Observability study, commissioned by Elastic, which quantifies the benefits, costs, and risks that Elastic customers have seen from Elastic Observability. To calculate these numbers, Forrester aggregated the experiences and results from five organizations — including one from public sector — into a single composite organization.
The study found that, based on a three-year, risk-adjusted present value, the composite organization experienced the following quantifiable benefits: 


243% return on investment (ROI) 
85% less time spent monitoring and resolving incidents 
105,000 hours saved by developers with more efficient application deployment
90% increase in data analyst efficiency
$1.2 million in savings over three years


In addition to measuring quantifiable benefits, the study also highlights significant qualitative benefits that come from Elastic Observability, such as:


Faster and higher quality, data-driven decision making
Improved application performance and service quality
Improved employee collaboration
Improved security and compliance 
Better flexibility and scalability
,
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 8.11: Preview of ES|QL, GA of Elastic Learned Sparse EncodeR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-11-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-11-0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today, we are pleased to announce the general availability of Elastic® 8.11.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From pipe dreams to reality: Announcing Elastic’s piped query language, ES|QL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/esql-elasticsearch-piped-query-language</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/esql-elasticsearch-piped-query-language"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today, we are pleased to announce the technical preview of Elastic®’s new piped query language, ES|QL (Elasticsearch Query Language), which transforms, enriches, and simplifies data investigations. Powered by a new query engine, ES|QL delivers advanced search capabilities with concurrent processing, improving speed and efficiency irrespective of data source and structure. Quickly resolve issues by creating aggregations and visualizations all from a single screen for an iterative and smooth workflow.
Evolution in Elasticsearch,
Over the past 13 years, Elasticsearch® has significantly evolved, adapting to user needs and the shifting digital landscape. Originally for full-text search, Elasticsearch expanded to support a broader set of use cases based on user feedback. Throughout this journe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar,Bahubali Shetti,Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing SIG etcd]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/07/introducing-sig-etcd/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/07/introducing-sig-etcd/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Han Kang (Google), Marek Siarkowicz (Google), Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
Special Interest Groups (SIGs) are a fundamental part of the Kubernetes project, with a substantial share of the community activity happening within them. When the need arises, new SIGs can be created, and that was precisely what happened recently.
SIG etcd is the most recent addition to the list of Kubernetes SIGs. In this article we will get to know it a bit better, understand its origins, scope, and plans.
The critical role of etcd
If we look inside the control plane of a Kubernetes cluster, we will find etcd, a consistent and highly-available key value store used as Kubernetes' backing store for all cluster data -- this description alone highlights the critical role that etcd plays, and the importanc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup—Reserve GPU capacity for short ML workloads, Finch is GA, and more—November 6, 2023]]></title>
        <id>6197b88286f499261431394fa5bffcd56d9d07ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-reserve-gpu-capacity-for-short-ml-workloads-finch-is-ga-and-more-november-6-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year is coming to an end, and there are only 50 days until Christmas and 21 days to AWS re:Invent! If you are in Las Vegas, come and say hi to me. I will be around the Serverlesspresso booth most of the time. Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention during […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building In-Video Search]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/936766f0017c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/building-in-video-search-936766f0017c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering video editors with multimodal machine learning to discover perfect moments across the entire Netflix catalog]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 Instance Metadata Service IMDSv2 by default]]></title>
        <id>bdbe7a12163ea18b9aae7bd0f333ec6c3ee2eb08</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-instance-metadata-service-imdsv2-by-default/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effective mid-2024, newly released Amazon EC2 instance types will use only version 2 of the EC2 Instance Metadata Service (IMDSv2). We are also taking a series of steps to make IMDSv2 the default choice for AWS Management Console Quick Starts and other launch pathways. Background This service is accessible from within an EC2 instance at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault adds 3 new observability integrations and HTTP streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-adds-3-new-observability-integrations-and-http-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-adds-3-new-observability-integrations-and-http-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault gains 3 new observability integrations with AWS Cloudwatch, Elasticsearch, and New Relic, as well as a generic HTTP endpoint for flexible metrics streaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.3 EAP Digest #3: Angular, React, and Vue Improvements and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=403372</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/11/webstorm-2023-3-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T13:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for our last EAP digest to walk you through the new features and improvements coming in WebStorm 2023.3! For more information, check out our previous blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. You can also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first nine minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44591</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/817819451/0/sethsblog~The-first-nine-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T09:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mixing up a batch of homemade vegan marshmallow Fluff® is an exercise in patience. For the first nine minutes of the ten minutes it takes in the mixer, not much happens. And then, it transforms into something fluffy and delightful. Without the recipe, it’s unlikely that most folks would make it to minute five, never […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.2.4 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=403357</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/11/2023-2-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T07:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released another update for v2023.2.  You can update to this version from inside the IDE, using the Toolbox App, or by using snaps if you are a Ubuntu user. You can also download it from our website. This version brings the following refinements:  To see the full list of issues addressed in this version, please […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Messier Objects]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2851/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2851/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/messier_objects.png" title="The debate over the correct Messier number for the Ship of Theseus is ongoing." alt="The debate over the correct Messier number for the Ship of Theseus is ongoing." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patience]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47720</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/814167062/0/sethsblog~Patience/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-05T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s worth the most when it’s the most difficult to find.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The power of expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44672</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/810930158/0/sethsblog~The-power-of-expectations/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-04T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we raise our expectations for a student, a friend or a co-worker, we open the door to possibility. We offer them dignity and a chance to grow. We are offering them trust. But if we become attached to those expectations, if the expectation unmet leads us to distress or unhappiness, then that attachment undermines […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streaming SQL in Data Mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/0d83f5a00d08</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/streaming-sql-in-data-mesh-0d83f5a00d08?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T21:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratizing Stream Processing @ Netflix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevEx at Camunda Turns 3!]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93602</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/11/devex-camunda-3-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T18:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Developer Experience team at Camunda aims to lower barriers for developers working in the Camunda ecosystem so they can be more effective.
The post DevEx at Camunda Turns 3! appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amara Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of both worlds: Achieving scalability and quality in text clustering]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/best-of-both-worlds-achieving.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/best-of-both-worlds-achieving.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T18:23:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Ahmadian and Mehran Kazemi, Research Scientists, Google Research




Clustering is a fundamental, ubiquitous problem in data mining and unsupervised machine learning, where the goal is to group together similar items. The standard forms of clustering are metric clustering and graph clustering. In metric clustering, a given metric space defines distances between data points, which are grouped together based on their separation. In graph clustering, a given graph connects similar data points through edges, and the clustering process groups data points together based on the connections between them. Both clustering forms are particularly useful for large corpora where class labels can’t be defined. Examples of such corpora are the ever-growing digital text collections of variou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy: New Projects and Topics in November]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=403307</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/11/03/jetbrains-academy-new-projects-and-topics-in-november-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T17:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s already November, and we’re excited to share all of the new topics and projects on offer this month. Each comes with its own exciting challenges and learning opportunities to explore. This month we released new projects for Python, Go, ML, and frontend learners! Beyond that, there are also 110 new topics for you to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Regina Muradova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate networking across Google Cloud runtimes with Consul and Apigee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/automate-networking-across-google-cloud-runtimes-with-consul-and-apigee</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/automate-networking-across-google-cloud-runtimes-with-consul-and-apigee"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to manage service-to-service communication across environments using Consul and the Apigee adapter for Envoy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2023.3 EAP Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=399012</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2023/11/rubymine-2023-3-eap-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T12:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! We’re back with an update on the state of the 2023.3 Early Access Program. You can download the latest EAP build from our website, via the free Toolbox App, or by using snaps for Ubuntu. Here are the biggest highlights of this release: Performance improvements As we mentioned in our previous blog post, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Zykova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – November 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=402882</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/11/java-annotated-monthly-november-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T11:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Java Annotated Monthly – November 2023! As the Java world keeps on spinning, we’ve gathered a treasure trove of articles, talks, and insights to warm your Java developers’ hearts. This month’s edition features a delightful blend of the latest technological advancements and the ever-inspiring soft-skills discussions. We’ve also selected several talks recorded […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains at Unite Amsterdam]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=402934</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/11/03/jetbrains-at-unite-amsterdam/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T11:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time in four years, the Unite conference will take place in person, and it will be in Amsterdam on November 15–16. JetBrains couldn’t miss the opportunity to be there! Our involvement doesn’t end at our booth at the expo – we are also hosting the JetBrains Pre-Unite Borrel Party! Join us at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Ruban</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Bug Fixes: ReSharper 2023.2.3 and Rider 2023.2.3 Are Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=401379</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/11/03/resharper-rider-2023-2-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T11:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper and Rider have just received their third set of bug-fix updates for the 2023.2 release! Let’s take a look at the most important issues that have been resolved in this update. ReSharper  For the full list of resolved issues, please refer to our issue tracker. Rider For the full list of resolved issues, please […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The community orchestra]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45678</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/809258474/0/sethsblog~The-community-orchestra/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T08:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are people who get paid to play the flute or bassoon. There are far more people who volunteer to participate in a community orchestra. For many, rehearsals or performances are the high points of their day. The metaphor is powerful, because it teaches us that we all benefit from having a community orchestra in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.3 EAP6: Support for Intel Syntax in Assembly Views]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=402786</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/11/clion-2023-3-eap6-support-for-intel-syntax-in-assembly-views/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T01:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grab the fresh CLion 2023.3 EAP5 build (233.11555.2) from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package if you are using Ubuntu, or update via a patch if you’re using the previous EAP build. DOWNLOAD CLION EAP Intel syntax in the Assembly view Previously, CLion 2023.3 EAP added an Assembly view for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.1 RC2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/03/spring-modulith-1-1-rc2-release</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/03/spring-modulith-1-1-rc2-release"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.0-RC2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/03/spring-boot-3-2-0-rc2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/03/spring-boot-3-2-0-rc2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Webb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doctor's Office]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2850/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2850/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/doctors_office.png" title="&quot;The police told me I can't be a doctor, but whenever they show up I just go into the Google Maps settings page I found and change the house to 'Police Headquarters' and then they have to do what I say.&quot;" alt="&quot;The police told me I can't be a doctor, but whenever they show up I just go into the Google Maps settings page I found and change the house to 'Police Headquarters' and then they have to do what I say.&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Contributor Summit: Behind-the-scenes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/03/k8s-contributor-summit-behind-the-scenes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/03/k8s-contributor-summit-behind-the-scenes/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author : Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
Every year, just before the official start of KubeCon+CloudNativeCon, there's a special event that
has a very special place in the hearts of those organizing and participating in it: the Kubernetes
Contributor Summit. To find out why, and to provide a behind-the-scenes perspective, we interview
Noah Abrahams, whom amongst other roles was the co-lead for the Kubernetes Contributor Summit in
2023.
Frederico Muñoz (FSM): Hello Noah, and welcome. Could you start by introducing yourself and
telling us how you got involved in Kubernetes?
Noah Abrahams (NA): I’ve been in this space for quite a while.  I got started in IT in the mid
90's, and I’ve been working in the "Cloud" space for about 15 years.  It was, frankly, through a
combination of sheer luck (be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is IT Automation?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93637</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/11/what-is-it-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T23:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how IT automation can boost efficiency, reduce costs, and streamline processes for your business, whether you're provisioning new servers to securing your infrastructure.
The post What is IT Automation? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-shot adaptive prompting of large language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/zero-shot-adaptive-prompting-of-large.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/zero-shot-adaptive-prompting-of-large.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T22:01:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xingchen Wan, Student Researcher, and Ruoxi Sun, Research Scientist, Cloud AI Team




Recent advances in large language models (LLMs) are very promising as reflected in their capability for general problem-solving in few-shot and zero-shot setups, even without explicit training on these tasks. This is impressive because in the few-shot setup, LLMs are presented with only a few question-answer demonstrations prior to being given a test question. Even more challenging is the zero-shot setup, where the LLM is directly prompted with the test question only. 




Even though the few-shot setup has dramatically reduced the amount of data required to adapt a model for a specific use-case, there are still cases where generating sample prompts can be challenging. For example, handcrafting…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Process Orchestration Maturity Model Introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93592</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/11/process-orchestration-maturity-model-intro/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T19:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know the Process Orchestration Maturity Model and learn about the first two levels in this first post in our series.
The post Process Orchestration Maturity Model Introduction appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.3 EAP 5 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=402559</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/11/2023-3-eap-5/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T16:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can download the build from our website, get it from the free Toolbox App, or update to it using snaps if you’re an Ubuntu user. Download PyCharm 2023.3 EAP The fifth build of the Early Access Program for PyCharm 2023.3 introduces: You can download the build from our website, get it from the free Toolbox App, or update […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging AI to empower all developers at GitHub Universe 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-02-leveraging-ai-to-empower-all-developers-at-github-universe-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-02-leveraging-ai-to-empower-all-developers-at-github-universe-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T16:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub Universe 2023 is just around the corner! Join us and learn how GitHub is leveraging AI to empower all developers, including developers with disabilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-02-leveraging-ai-to-empower-all-developers-at-github-universe-2023/">Leveraging AI to empower all developers at GitHub Universe 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 EAP 7: More Updates For Kubernetes, Improvements For Java, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=401284</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/11/intellij-idea-2023-3-eap-7/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T15:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 Early Access Program is nearing its end, and we’re switching our focus to refining the new features for the final release. However, there are still significant improvements, and you have the opportunity to test them in the latest EAP build before the major release. You can download the latest build from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating the first round of GitHub Accelerator and what&#8217;s next]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-02-celebrating-the-first-round-of-github-accelerator-and-whats-next/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-02-celebrating-the-first-round-of-github-accelerator-and-whats-next/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T14:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Celebrate the maintainers of the first GitHub Accelerator cohort, learn what they have been up to since, and hear what’s next for GitHub Accelerator.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-02-celebrating-the-first-round-of-github-accelerator-and-whats-next/">Celebrating the first round of GitHub Accelerator and what&#8217;s next</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fact-Gathering with Event-Driven Ansible for Microsoft Windows ITSM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/fact-gathering-with-event-driven-ansible-and-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/fact-gathering-with-event-driven-ansible-and-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The use of Event-Driven Ansible to enable fact gathering from events is considered a “Getting Started” type of use case, but it can be extremely powerful. This use case is simple and it is what we consider a “Read Only” type of action, meaning that we are not making any changes, but we are using the event to trigger a fact gathering process which we can later publish to the IT Service Management system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commonplace technology]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47711</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/806454458/0/sethsblog~Commonplace-technology/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not all tech is new tech. The ballpoint pen was a revelation, and a bit controversial. Now, it’s disposable and obvious. Different industries go through tech spurts. My desk is covered with items I use every day (a mouse, headphones, a solid-state drive, transparent tape, and even a Star Trek communicator) that were risky breakthroughs, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: GraalVM founder and Oracle vice president Thomas Wuerthinger]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/02/a-bootiful-podcast-graalvm-founder-and-oracle-vice-president-thomas</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/02/a-bootiful-podcast-graalvm-founder-and-oracle-vice-president-thomas"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2023.0.0-RC1 (aka Leyton) Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/02/spring-cloud-2023-0-0-rc1-aka-leyton-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/02/spring-cloud-2023-0-0-rc1-aka-leyton-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Baxter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Architecture: Production Readiness]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/02/sig-architecture-production-readiness-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/02/sig-architecture-production-readiness-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
This is the second interview of a SIG Architecture Spotlight series that will cover the different
subprojects. In this blog, we will cover the SIG Architecture: Production Readiness
subproject.
In this SIG Architecture spotlight, we talked with Wojciech Tyczynski
(Google), lead of the Production Readiness subproject.
About SIG Architecture and the Production Readiness subproject
Frederico (FSM): Hello Wojciech, could you tell us a bit about yourself, your role and how you
got involved in Kubernetes?
Wojciech Tyczynski (WT): I started contributing to Kubernetes in January 2015. At that time,
Google (where I was and still am working) decided to start a Kubernetes team in the Warsaw office
(in addition to already existing teams in California and Seattle…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestration with Camunda and Kafka Confluent Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93624</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/11/orchestration-camunda-kafka/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would you use both Camunda and Kafka in your architecture? Learn why and how to do it in this easy to follow tutorial.
The post Orchestration with Camunda and Kafka Confluent Cloud appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Game Off 2023 theme announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-01-github-game-off-2023-theme-announcement/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-01-github-game-off-2023-theme-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It’s the moment you’ve all been waiting for. Are you ready?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-01-github-game-off-2023-theme-announcement/">GitHub Game Off 2023 theme announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.7 beta improves Vault and Consul integrations, adds NUMA support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.7 — now in beta — introduces improved workload identity, improved Vault and Consul integrations, NUMA support, Nomad actions, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetNet-3: A state-of-the-art neural weather model available in Google products]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/metnet-3-state-of-art-neural-weather.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/metnet-3-state-of-art-neural-weather.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T17:30:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Samier Merchant, Google Research, and Nal Kalchbrenner, Google DeepMind






Forecasting weather variables such as precipitation, temperature, and wind is key to numerous aspects of society, from daily planning and transportation to energy production. As we continue to see more extreme weather events such as floods, droughts, and heat waves, accurate forecasts can be essential to preparing for and mitigating their effects. The first 24 hours into the future are especially important as they are both highly predictable and actionable, which can help people make informed decisions in a timely manner and stay safe. 
 

Today we present a new weather model called MetNet-3, developed by Google Research and Google DeepMind. Building on the earlier MetNet and MetNet-2 models, MetNet-3 p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul tips and tricks for cloud transformation at HashiConf 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-tips-and-tricks-for-cloud-transformation-at-hashiconf-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-tips-and-tricks-for-cloud-transformation-at-hashiconf-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch our key Consul networking sessions from HashiConf 2023 and give us your feedback on the talks and the future direction of Consul.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Partial Clone Now Supported in Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67877</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/git-partial-clone-now-supported-in-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T17:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git Partial Clone
The post Git Partial Clone Now Supported in Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Carlson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diversity, inclusion, and belonging at GitHub in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-01-diversity-inclusion-and-belonging-at-github-in-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-01-diversity-inclusion-and-belonging-at-github-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We expanded diversity of our employee base, launched several new employee engagement programs, made investments to improve accessibility, and more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-01-diversity-inclusion-and-belonging-at-github-in-2023/">Diversity, inclusion, and belonging at GitHub in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第240話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755396392866</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755396392866"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two ways to defend the status quo]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46032</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/805183556/0/sethsblog~Two-ways-to-defend-the-status-quo/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T08:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neither is true, helpful or generous. Both happen all the time. Call it out when you see it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.20.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/01/spring-tools-4-20-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/01/spring-tools-4-20-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lippert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Under the Stars]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2849/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2849/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/under_the_stars.png" title="If you live in Los Angeles (around 33°52'N, roughly the latitude of Hermosa Beach) the black hole in V404 Cygni passes over you each day. On Christmas Day it will be directly overhead around 2pm." alt="If you live in Los Angeles (around 33°52'N, roughly the latitude of Hermosa Beach) the black hole in V404 Cygni passes over you each day. On Christmas Day it will be directly overhead around 2pm." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon EC2 Capacity Blocks for ML to reserve GPU capacity for your machine learning workloads]]></title>
        <id>4c52f5324f0331091a5829e03f9cf90f4f2d5bfb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-ec2-capacity-blocks-for-ml-to-reserve-gpu-capacity-for-your-machine-learning-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T23:02:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent advancements in machine learning (ML) have unlocked opportunities for customers across organizations of all sizes and industries to reinvent new products and transform their businesses. However, the growth in demand for GPU capacity to train, fine-tune, experiment, and inference these ML models has outpaced industry-wide supply, making GPUs a scarce resource. Access to GPU […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Play When You Have Connectors in Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93522</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/using-play-connectors-in-your-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T21:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Camunda's Play feature functions and how to test processes without disrupting your Zeebe cluster.
The post Using Play When You Have Connectors in Your Process appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the GitHub transparency center]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-31-introducing-the-github-transparency-center/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-31-introducing-the-github-transparency-center/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T19:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It’s time for our biannual transparency report, where we share how we approach content moderation and disclosure of user information. This year, we’re introducing the transparency center, a new platform for our transparency reporting data.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-31-introducing-the-github-transparency-center/">Introducing the GitHub transparency center</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC2 now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67838</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-1-rc2-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T18:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC2. This is our last planned prerelease before our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2022.1. A direct upgrade is supported from Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC1, any version of TFS, including Team Foundation Server 2015 and newer.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC2 now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Gateway API v1.0: GA Release]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/31/gateway-api-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/31/gateway-api-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Shane Utt (Kong), Nick Young (Isovalent), Rob Scott (Google)
On behalf of Kubernetes SIG Network, we are pleased to announce the v1.0 release of Gateway
API! This release marks a huge milestone for
this project. Several key APIs are graduating to GA (generally available), while
other significant features have been added to the Experimental channel.
What's new
Graduation to v1
This release includes the graduation of
Gateway,
GatewayClass, and
HTTPRoute to v1, which
means they are now generally available (GA). This API version denotes a high
level of confidence in the API surface and provides guarantees of backwards
compatibility. Note that although, the version of these APIs included in the
Standard channel are now considered stable, that does not mean that they are
complete. These…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Boards + GitHub Integration Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67897</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-boards-github-integration-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T16:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The existing Azure Boards + GitHub integration has been in place for several years now. This integration was a great starting point, but it does not offer the level of traceability that our customers have grown accustomed to. Based on your feedback,
The post Azure Boards + GitHub Integration Improvements appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confronting consciousness]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47611</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/804250295/0/sethsblog~Confronting-consciousness/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T08:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone knows what it is to be conscious, and we imagine that other people are also aware. That we have a voice in our heads, apparent agency and free will, a little person inside who is commenting, making decisions and in charge. We’re not sure if dogs have this, and we’re pretty sure that sunflowers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · Hacktoberfest 2023 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-30-release-radar-hack-23/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-release-radar-hack-23/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T06:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As Hacktoberfest comes to a close, you still have a day or so left to complete and submit your pull requests. If you&#8217;re struggling to think of projects to contribute to, our picks below might help you. This edition of the Release Radar covers a few projects that shipped major version updates this August and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-release-radar-hack-23/">Release Radar · Hacktoberfest 2023 Edition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda 8.3 Release Webinar, Recap and Extended Q&A]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93435</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/camunda-8-3-webinar-recap-q-a/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T01:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch all the highlights from our latest release webinar, as well as detailed answers to all the questions we couldn't get to live.
The post Camunda 8.3 Release Webinar, Recap and Extended Q&A appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Montalvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What new is coming in reactor-core 3.6.0?]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/31/what-new-is-coming-in-reactor-core-3-6-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/31/what-new-is-coming-in-reactor-core-3-6-0"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleh Dokuka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - October 31st, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/31/this-week-in-spring-october-31st-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/31/this-week-in-spring-october-31st-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The architecture of today&#8217;s LLM applications]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-30-the-architecture-of-todays-llm-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-the-architecture-of-todays-llm-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here’s everything you need to know to build your first LLM app and problem spaces you can start exploring today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-the-architecture-of-todays-llm-applications/">The architecture of today&#8217;s LLM applications</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – re:Post Selections, SNS and SQS FIFO improvements, multi-VPC ENI attachments, and more – October 30, 2023]]></title>
        <id>c693bec204bcea0b124466b9876c223fba395649</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-repost-selections-sns-and-sqs-fifo-improvements-multi-vpc-eni-attachments-and-more-october-30-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s less than a month to AWS re:Invent, but interesting news doesn’t slow down in the meantime. This week is my turn to help keep you up to date! Last week’s launches Here are some of the launches that caught my attention last week: AWS re:Post – With re:Post, you have access to a community […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2 x 4 lessons]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46036</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/803673851/0/sethsblog~The-x-lessons/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T08:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll need two 8-foot boards and six five-gallon buckets. Each board is a standard 2 x 4, about two inches by four inches in size. And the bucket is about two feet deep. The first lesson is simple: Put the board on the floor and have a colleague walk from one end to the other. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackable Halloween games MMXXIII]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-30-hackable-halloween-games-mmxxiii/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-hackable-halloween-games-mmxxiii/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T08:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>13 spooktacular games plus source code for readers to jam on.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-30-hackable-halloween-games-mmxxiii/">Hackable Halloween games MMXXIII</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Statemachine 4.0.0-M1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/30/spring-statemachine-4-0-0-m1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/10/30/spring-statemachine-4-0-0-m1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaker Box]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2848/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2848/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/breaker_box.png" title="Any electrician will warn you to first locate and flip the house's CAUSALITY circuit breaker before touching the CIRCUIT BREAKERS one." alt="Any electrician will warn you to first locate and flip the house's CAUSALITY circuit breaker before touching the CIRCUIT BREAKERS one." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three things about innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46034</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/803519273/0/sethsblog~Three-things-about-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New approaches will never be embraced by everyone at first. If you need unanimous consent, you’re not going to move forward. And it’s not convenient. If it were, someone would have done it already. Finally, it’s not sure to work. If you need any or all three of these things for your project to move […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audioplethysmography for cardiac monitoring with hearable devices]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/audioplethysmography-for-cardiac.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/audioplethysmography-for-cardiac.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T20:22:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xiaoran "Van" Fan, Experimental Scientist, and Trausti Thormundsson, Director, Google





The market for true wireless stereo (TWS) active noise canceling (ANC) hearables (headphones and earbuds) has been soaring in recent years, and the global shipment volume will nearly double that of smart wristbands and watches in 2023. The on-head time for hearables has extended significantly due to the recent advances in ANC, transparency mode, and artificial intelligence. Users frequently wear hearables not just for music listening, but also for exercising, focusing, or simply mood adjustment. However, hearable health is still mostly uncharted territory for the consumer market. 



In “APG: Audioplethysmography for Cardiac Monitoring in Hearables,” presented at MobiCom 2023, we introduce …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying LLMs: How they can do things they weren&#8217;t trained to do]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-27-demystifying-llms-how-they-can-do-things-they-werent-trained-to-do/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-27-demystifying-llms-how-they-can-do-things-they-werent-trained-to-do/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T16:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore how LLMs generate text, why they sometimes hallucinate information, and the ethical implications surrounding their incredible capabilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-27-demystifying-llms-how-they-can-do-things-they-werent-trained-to-do/">Demystifying LLMs: How they can do things they weren&#8217;t trained to do</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes And Kernel Panics]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ed620b9c6225</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/kubernetes-and-kernel-panics-ed620b9c6225?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T16:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Netflix’s Container Platform Connects Linux Kernel Panics to Pods]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is public key infrastructure (PKI)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-is-public-key-infrastructure-pki</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-is-public-key-infrastructure-pki"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public key infrastructure (PKI) governs the provisioning of digital certificates to protect sensitive data, establish digital identities, and secure communications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are the first group to adopt AI at work. Here’s why that matters.]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-10-27-developers-are-the-first-group-to-adopt-ai-at-work-heres-why-that-matters/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-10-27-developers-are-the-first-group-to-adopt-ai-at-work-heres-why-that-matters/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From starting at GitHub over 10 years ago as a developer to becoming the Chief Operating Officer, I’ve learned that developers are often bellwethers for change across the rest of their organizations. That makes investing in—and learning from—them critical. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-10-27-developers-are-the-first-group-to-adopt-ai-at-work-heres-why-that-matters/">Developers are the first group to adopt AI at work. Here’s why that matters.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Your Camunda Process from an External Form]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93419</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/start-camunda-process-external-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T14:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now you can launch your Camunda processes from an external URL, simplifying collaboration and adoption.
The post Start Your Camunda Process from an External Form appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-secondary performance replication is now available on HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multi-secondary-performance-replication-is-now-available-on-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multi-secondary-performance-replication-is-now-available-on-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Plus clusters can now have more than one additional performance secondary cluster per primary cluster within the same cloud provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting benchmarks for AI safety with MLCommons]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/supporting-benchmarks-for-ai-safety.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/supporting-benchmarks-for-ai-safety.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Anoop Sinha, Technology and Society, and Marian Croak, Google Research, Responsible AI and Human Centered Technology team





Standard benchmarks are agreed upon ways of measuring important product qualities, and they exist in many fields. Some standard benchmarks measure safety: for example, when a car manufacturer touts a “five-star overall safety rating,” they’re citing a benchmark. Standard benchmarks already exist in machine learning (ML) and AI technologies: for instance, the MLCommons Association operates the MLPerf benchmarks that measure the speed of cutting edge AI hardware such as Google’s TPUs. However, though there has been significant work done on AI safety, there are as yet no similar standard benchmarks for AI safety.
 

We are excited to support a new effort by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spoken question answering and speech continuation using a spectrogram-powered LLM]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/spoken-question-answering-and-speech.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/spoken-question-answering-and-speech.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T15:57:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eliya Nachmani, Research Scientist, and Alon Levkovitch, Student Researcher, Google Research




The goal of natural language processing (NLP) is to develop computational models that can understand and generate natural language. By capturing the statistical patterns and structures of text-based natural language, language models can predict and generate coherent and meaningful sequences of words. Enabled by the increasing use of the highly successful Transformer model architecture and with training on large amounts of text (with proportionate compute and model size), large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable success in NLP tasks. 

 


However, modeling spoken human language remains a challenging frontier. Spoken dialog systems have conventionally been built as a c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a new HashiCorp Women in Tech podcast series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-a-new-hashicorp-women-in-tech-podcast-series</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-a-new-hashicorp-women-in-tech-podcast-series"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our new Women in Tech podcast debuts alongside our Fortune Best Workplaces for Women recognition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking back at wildfire research in 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/looking-back-at-wildfire-research-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/looking-back-at-wildfire-research-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T22:10:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yi-Fan Chen, Software Engineer, and Carla Bromberg, Program Lead, Google Research

Wildfires are becoming larger and affecting more and more communities around the world, often resulting in large-scale devastation. Just this year, communities have experienced catastrophic wildfires in Greece, Maui, and Canada to name a few. While the underlying causes leading to such an increase are complex — including changing climate patterns, forest management practices, land use development policies and many more — it is clear that the advancement of technologies can help to address the new challenges.
 
At Google Research, we’ve been investing in a number of climate adaptation efforts, including the application of machine learning (ML) to aid in wildfire prevention and provide information to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claims Processing Automation in Insurance: A Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93359</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/claims-processing-automation-insurance-complete-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Camunda and process orchestration, insurance organizations can scale processes to any level. Learn how and enable claims processing automation today.
The post Claims Processing Automation in Insurance: A Complete Guide appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing ingress2gateway; Simplifying Upgrades to Gateway API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/25/introducing-ingress2gateway/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/25/introducing-ingress2gateway/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Lior Lieberman (Google), Kobi Levi (independent)
Today we are releasing ingress2gateway, a tool
that can help you migrate from Ingress to Gateway
API. Gateway API is just weeks away from graduating to GA, if you
haven't upgraded yet, now's the time to think about it!
Background
In the ever-evolving world of Kubernetes, networking plays a pivotal role. As more applications are
deployed in Kubernetes clusters, effective exposure of these services to clients becomes a critical
concern. If you've been working with Kubernetes, you're likely familiar with the Ingress API,
which has been the go-to solution for managing external access to services.
The Ingress API provides a way to route external traffic to your applications within the cluster,
making it an indispensable tool for many Kub…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grammar checking at Google Search scale]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/grammar-checking-at-google-search-scale.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/grammar-checking-at-google-search-scale.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eric Malmi, Senior Research Scientist, and Jakub Adamek, Senior Software Engineer, Google, Bard Team





Many people with questions about grammar turn to Google Search for guidance. While existing features, such as “Did you mean”, already handle simple typo corrections, more complex grammatical error correction (GEC) is beyond their scope. What makes the development of new Google Search features challenging is that they must have high precision and recall while outputting results quickly.



The conventional approach to GEC is to treat it as a translation problem and use autoregressive Transformer models to decode the response token-by-token, conditioning on the previously generated tokens. However, although Transformer models have proven to be effective at GEC, they aren’t part…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving PCI compliance: Leveraging HashiCorp Vault to protect payment data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/achieving-pci-compliance-leveraging-hashicorp-vault-to-protect-payment-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/achieving-pci-compliance-leveraging-hashicorp-vault-to-protect-payment-data"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to address key PCI DSS 4.0 requirements with HashiCorp Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible can help with the Cisco IOS XE Software Web UI Privilege Escalation Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-can-help-with-the-cisco-ios-xe-software-web-ui-privilege-escalation-vulnerability</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-can-help-with-the-cisco-ios-xe-software-web-ui-privilege-escalation-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-20198]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Dubiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Works – AWS European Sovereign Cloud]]></title>
        <id>eaa67c5d06a038a223f4382ed88baf0665d77ef5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/in-the-works-aws-european-sovereign-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T05:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS European Sovereign Cloud will allow government agencies, regulated industries, and the independent software vendors (ISVs) that support them to store sensitive data and run critical workloads on AWS infrastructure that is operated and supported by AWS employees located in and residents of the European Union (EU). The first Region will be located in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the Power of Effective Microservices Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=93258</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/10/unlocking-the-power-of-effective-microservices-communication/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T18:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is microservices communication? Learn the difference between synchronous and asynchronous communication and how to choose which is right for your processes.  
The post Unlocking the Power of Effective Microservices Communication appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – CodeWhisperer, CodeCatalyst, RDS, Route53, and more – October 24, 2023]]></title>
        <id>7f6cef8aa03c93e83348e6f22c7a6ae96831967e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-codewhisperer-codecatalyst-rds-route53-and-more-october-23-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T17:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The entire AWS News Blog team is fully focused on writing posts to announce the new services and features during our annual customer conference in Las Vegas, AWS re:Invent! And while we prepare content for you to read, our services teams continue to innovate. Here is my summary of last week’s launches. Last week’s launches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Work Item Chart Filtering in Azure DevOps Dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67602</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-work-item-chart-filtering-in-azure-devops-dashboards/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T08:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce the release of Work Item Chart Filtering in Azure DevOps Dashboards. This enhanced filtering streamlines your workflow just a click away.
With this new feature, not only can you hover over a work item chart,
The post Introducing Work Item Chart Filtering in Azure DevOps Dashboards appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jihye Eom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Plants, process and parties: the Kubernetes 1.28 release interview]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/24/plants-process-and-parties-the-kubernetes-1.28-release-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/24/plants-process-and-parties-the-kubernetes-1.28-release-interview/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Craig Box
Since 2018, one of my favourite contributions to the Kubernetes community has been to share the story of each release. Many of these stories were told on behalf of a past employer; by popular demand, I've brought them back, now under my own name. If you were a fan of the old show, I would be delighted if you would subscribe.
Back in August, we welcomed the release of Kubernetes 1.28. That release was led by Grace Nguyen, a CS student at the University of Waterloo. Grace joined me for the traditional release interview, and while you can read her story below, I encourage you to listen to it if you can.
This transcript has been lightly edited and condensed for clarity.
You're a student at the University of Waterloo, so I want to spend the first two minutes of this interview …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW!!! Getting started landing page for Ansible Automation Platform on Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-getting-started-landing-page-for-ansible-automation-platform-on-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-getting-started-landing-page-for-ansible-automation-platform-on-azure"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is co-authored by Tomas Znamenacek and Hicham (he-sham) Mourad]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas Znamenacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five trends in cloud infrastructure and what they mean]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/five-trends-in-cloud-infrastructure-and-what-they-mean</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/five-trends-in-cloud-infrastructure-and-what-they-mean"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T07:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From AI to the edge, HashiCorp Co-Founder and CTO Armon Dadgar shares his insights on where the cloud is headed, and what that means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: PersistentVolume Last Phase Transition Time in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/23/persistent-volume-last-phase-transition-time/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/23/persistent-volume-last-phase-transition-time/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Roman Bednář (Red Hat)
In the recent Kubernetes v1.28 release, we (SIG Storage) introduced a new alpha feature that aims to improve PersistentVolume (PV)
storage management and help cluster administrators gain better insights into the lifecycle of PVs.
With the addition of the lastPhaseTransitionTime field into the status of a PV,
cluster administrators are now able to track the last time a PV transitioned to a different
phase, allowing for more efficient
and informed resource management.
Why do we need new PV field?
PersistentVolumes in Kubernetes play a crucial role in providing storage resources to workloads running in the cluster.
However, managing these PVs effectively can be challenging, especially when it comes
to determining the last time a PV transitioned between different…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answering billions of reporting queries each day with low latency]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/answering-billions-of-reporting-queries.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/answering-billions-of-reporting-queries.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T17:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jagan Sankaranarayanan, Senior Staff Software Engineer, and Indrajit Roy, Head of Napa Product, Google




Google Ads infrastructure runs on an internal data warehouse called Napa. Billions of reporting queries, which power critical dashboards used by advertising clients to measure campaign performance, run on tables stored in Napa. These tables contain records of ads performance that are keyed using particular customers and the campaign identifiers with which they are associated. Keys are tokens that are used both to associate an ads record with a particular client and campaign (e.g., customer_id, campaign_id) and for efficient retrieval. A record contains dozens of keys, so clients use reporting queries to specify keys needed to filter the data to understand ads performance (e.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rotate Your SSL/TLS Certificates Now – Amazon RDS and Amazon Aurora Expire in 2024]]></title>
        <id>f73464fad068270f248da400702f12effc2a0f1f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/rotate-your-ssl-tls-certificates-now-amazon-rds-and-amazon-aurora-expire-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T15:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t be surprised if you have seen the Certificate Update in the Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) console. If you use or plan to use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) or Transport Layer Security (TLS) with certificate verification to connect to your database instances of Amazon RDS for MySQL, MariaDB, SQL Server, Oracle, PostgreSQL, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: A Quick Recap of 2023 China Kubernetes Contributor Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/20/kcs-shanghai/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/20/kcs-shanghai/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Paco Xu and Michael Yao (DaoCloud)
On September 26, 2023, the first day of
KubeCon + CloudNativeCon + Open Source Summit China 2023,
nearly 50 contributors gathered in Shanghai for the Kubernetes Contributor Summit.
 
All participants in the 2023 Kubernetes Contributor Summit
This marked the first in-person offline gathering held in China after three years of the pandemic.
A joyful meetup
The event began with welcome speeches from Kevin Wang from Huawei Cloud,
one of the co-chairs of KubeCon, and Puja from Giant Swarm.
Following the opening remarks, the contributors introduced themselves briefly. Most attendees were from China,
while some contributors had made the journey from Europe and the United States specifically for the conference.
Technical experts from companies such as Mic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English learners can now practice speaking on Search]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/google-search-can-now-help-with-english-speaking-practice.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/google-search-can-now-help-with-english-speaking-practice.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T16:24:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Christian Plagemann, Director, and Katya Cox, Product Manager, Google Research




Learning a language can open up new opportunities in a person’s life. It can help people connect with those from different cultures, travel the world, and advance their career. English alone is estimated to have 1.5 billion learners worldwide. Yet proficiency in a new language is difficult to achieve, and many learners cite a lack of opportunity to practice speaking actively and receiving actionable feedback as a barrier to learning.




We are excited to announce a new feature of Google Search that helps people practice speaking and improve their language skills. Within the next few days, Android users in Argentina, Colombia, India (Hindi), Indonesia, Mexico, and Venezuela can get even more langua…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Code Coverage Tab Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67794</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/improved-code-coverage-tab-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T09:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re using Azure DevOps for your CI/CD pipeline, you may be interested in our recent improvements to code coverage testing. Code coverage tests can help you identify areas of your code that are not tested, or not tested enough, and improve the quality of your automated tests and overall code quality.
The post Improved Code Coverage Tab Experience appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinayak Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP expands IAM enterprise capabilities by introducing groups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-expands-iam-enterprise-capabilities-by-introducing-groups</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-expands-iam-enterprise-capabilities-by-introducing-groups"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Groups offer a new approach for managing identities and their access to HashiCorp Cloud Platform (HCP) resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measurement-induced entanglement phase transitions in a quantum circuit]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/measurement-induced-entanglement-phase.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/measurement-induced-entanglement-phase.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jesse Hoke, Student Researcher, and Pedram Roushan, Senior Research Scientist, Quantum AI Team




Quantum mechanics allows many phenomena that are classically impossible: a quantum particle can exist in a superposition of two states simultaneously or be entangled with another particle, such that anything you do to one seems to instantaneously also affect the other, regardless of the space between them. But perhaps no aspect of quantum theory is as striking as the act of measurement. In classical mechanics, a measurement need not affect the system being studied. But a measurement on a quantum system can profoundly influence its behavior. For example, when a quantum bit of information, called a qubit, that is in a superposition of both “0” and “1” is measured, its state will sudde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon MSK Replicator – Fully Managed Replication across MSK Clusters in Same or Different AWS Regions]]></title>
        <id>c1324a25314db12bed4d7242f05c870d0bdde108</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-msk-replicator-fully-managed-replication-across-msk-clusters-in-same-or-different-aws-regions/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T17:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka (Amazon MSK) provides a fully managed and highly available Apache Kafka service simplifying the way you process streaming data. When using Apache Kafka, a common architectural pattern is to replicate data from one cluster to another. Cross-cluster replication is often used to implement business continuity and disaster recovery plans […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第239話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755331321453</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755331321453"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform provider code generation now in tech preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-provider-code-generation-now-in-tech-preview</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-provider-code-generation-now-in-tech-preview"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T07:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform provider code generation is an extensible solution that lets developers automate portions of their provider development workflow — now in tech preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Customization Capability in Amazon CodeWhisperer Generates Even Better Suggestions (Preview)]]></title>
        <id>70dd1e1fe2691c02993fd47419de9212cf2249dd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-customization-capability-in-amazon-codewhisperer-generates-even-better-suggestions-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An AI coding companion, such as Amazon CodeWhisperer, aims to improve developers’ productivity by helping them write code quickly and securely. However, in particular cases, developers need to have code recommendations based on their internal libraries and APIs they extensively use every day. As most of the existing AI coding companion tools are trained only […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PKI hosting: Cloud-based PKI vs. self managed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pki-hosting-cloud-based-pki-vs-self-managed</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pki-hosting-cloud-based-pki-vs-self-managed"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T07:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the differences between hosting (public key infrastructure) PKI workloads in the cloud versus on-premises?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDKTF 0.19 adds support for config-driven import and refactoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdktf-0-19-adds-support-for-config-driven-import-and-refactoring</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdktf-0-19-adds-support-for-config-driven-import-and-refactoring"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T07:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.19 adds support for importing existing resources with  auto-generated configuration in CDKTF projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Seventh Generation Memory-optimized Amazon EC2 Instances (R7i)]]></title>
        <id>c59c1841d9d6b3e95d0210c06dd38a524d0993dc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-seventh-generation-memory-optimized-amazon-ec2-instances-r7i/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T18:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier, we introduced a duo of Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances to our lineup: the general-purpose Amazon EC2 M7i instances and the compute-optimized Amazon EC2 C7i instances. Today, I’m happy to share that we’re expanding these seventh-generation x86-based offerings to include memory-optimized Amazon EC2 R7i instances. These instances are powered by custom 4th […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – EBS Status Check, Textract Custom Queries, Amazon Linux 2, and more – October 16, 2023]]></title>
        <id>d9629e933b3b25778325dd23875967d8638a39da</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-ebs-status-check-textract-custom-queries-amazon-linux-2-and-more-october-16-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T18:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With just 41 days until AWS re:Invent 2023 opens, I’m doing my best to stay heads-down and focused on working with the entire AWS News Blog team to create plenty of awesome new posts for your reading pleasure! I’ll take a short break this morning to share some of the most exciting launches and other […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving traffic evacuations: A case study]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/improving-traffic-evacuations-case-study.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/improving-traffic-evacuations-case-study.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T17:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Damien Pierce, Software Engineer, and John Anderson, Senior Research Director, Google Research




Some cities or communities develop an evacuation plan to be used in case of an emergency. There are a number of reasons why city officials might enact their plan, a primary one being a natural disaster, such as a tornado, flood, or wildfire. An evacuation plan can help the community more effectively respond to an emergency, and so could help save lives. However, it can be difficult for a city to evaluate such a plan because it is not practical to have an entire town or city rehearse a full blown evacuation. For example, Mill Valley, a city in northern California, created a wildfire evacuation plan but lacked an estimate for how long the evacuation would take.


Today we describe a c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Linux package archive site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-linux-package-archive-site</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-linux-package-archive-site"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp will cease publishing packages of our products for end-of-life (EoL) distributions to our production packaging sites and migrate EoL versions to our new archive site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Batch calibration: Rethinking calibration for in-context learning and prompt engineering]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/batch-calibration-rethinking.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/batch-calibration-rethinking.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Han Zhou, Student Researcher, and Subhrajit Roy, Senior Research Scientist, Google Research





Prompting large language models (LLMs) has become an efficient learning paradigm for adapting LLMs to a new task by conditioning on human-designed instructions. The remarkable in-context learning (ICL) ability of LLMs also leads to efficient few-shot learners that can generalize from few-shot input-label pairs. However, the predictions of LLMs are highly sensitive and even biased to the choice of templates, label spaces (such as yes/no, true/false, correct/incorrect), and demonstration examples, resulting in unexpected performance degradation and barriers for pursuing robust LLM applications. To address this problem, calibration methods have been developed to mitigate the effects of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2023 HashiCorp Systems Integrator Award winners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2023-hashicorp-systems-integrator-award-winners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2023-hashicorp-systems-integrator-award-winners"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2023 HashiCorp Partner Network Awards for Systems Integrators have been announced. Meet the 13 winners in 5 categories around the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2023 HashiCorp Technology Partner Award winners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2023-hashicorp-technology-partner-award-winners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2023-hashicorp-technology-partner-award-winners"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2023 HashiCorp Technology Partner Awards have been announced. Congratulations to Palo Alto Networks, Datadog, Zscaler, and Tines!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing industrial use cases for physical simulation on future error-corrected quantum computers]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/developing-industrial-use-cases-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/developing-industrial-use-cases-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T20:56:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nicholas Rubin, Senior Research Scientist, and Ryan Babbush, Head of Quantum Algorithms, Quantum AI Team





If you’ve paid attention to the quantum computing space, you’ve heard the claim that in the future, quantum computers will solve certain problems exponentially more efficiently than classical computers can. They have the potential to transform many industries, from pharmaceuticals to energy.



For the most part, these claims have rested on arguments about the asymptotic scaling of algorithms as the problem size approaches infinity, but this tells us very little about the practical performance of quantum computers for finite-sized problems. We want to be more concrete: Exactly which problems are quantum computers more suited to tackle than their classical counterparts, an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Bootstrap an Air Gapped Cluster With Kubeadm]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/12/bootstrap-an-air-gapped-cluster-with-kubeadm/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/12/bootstrap-an-air-gapped-cluster-with-kubeadm/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Rob Mengert (Defense Unicorns)
Ever wonder how software gets deployed onto a system that is deliberately disconnected from the Internet and other networks? These systems are typically disconnected due to their sensitive nature. Sensitive as in utilities (power/water), banking, healthcare, weapons systems, other government use cases, etc. Sometimes it's technically a water gap, if you're running Kubernetes on an underwater vessel. Still, these environments need software to operate. This concept of deployment in a disconnected state is what it means to deploy to the other side of an air gap.
Again, despite this posture, software still needs to run in these environments. Traditionally, software artifacts are physically carried across the air gap on hard drives, USB sticks, CDs, or flo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure and security releases open HashiConf 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/infrastructure-security-lifecycle-releases-open-hashiconf-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/infrastructure-security-lifecycle-releases-open-hashiconf-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf 2023 unveils key announcements covering infrastructure and workflow enhancements as well as new security lifecycle management capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer now supports webhooks and streamlined run task reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-now-supports-webhooks-and-streamlined-run-task-reviews</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-now-supports-webhooks-and-streamlined-run-task-reviews"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Webhooks automatically notify external systems about image-related events. Streamlined run task reviews offer meaningful context on HCP Packer run task evaluations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67748</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/october-patches-for-azure-devops-server-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T17:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 Patch 4
Note: If you have Azure DevOps Server 2022,
The post October patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Insights Collection for Event-Driven Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-insights-collection-for-event-driven-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-insights-collection-for-event-driven-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-Driven Ansible became generally available in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4. As part of the release, Red Hat Insights and Ansible teams collaborated to implement and certify a Red Hat Insights collection integrating Insights events as a source of events for Ansible Automation Platform. This provides a consistent way to receive and handle events triggered from Insights to drive and track automation within the Ansible Automation Platform. The collection is available for installation on Ansible automation hub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerome Marc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: CRI-O is moving towards pkgs.k8s.io]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/10/cri-o-community-package-infrastructure/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/10/cri-o-community-package-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
The Kubernetes community recently announced
that their legacy package repositories are frozen, and now they moved to
introduced community-owned package repositories powered by the
OpenBuildService (OBS).
CRI-O has a long history of utilizing
OBS for their package builds,
but all of the packaging efforts have been done manually so far.
The CRI-O community absolutely loves Kubernetes, which means that they're
delighted to announce that:
All future CRI-O packages will be shipped as part of the officially supported
Kubernetes infrastructure hosted on pkgs.k8s.io!
There will be a deprecation phase for the existing packages, which is currently
being discussed in the CRI-O community.
The new infrastructure will only support releases of CRI-O >= v1.28.2 as well as
release br…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANPO: A Scene understanding, Accessibility, Navigation, Pathfinding, & Obstacle avoidance dataset]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/10/sanpo-scene-understanding-accessibility.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/10/sanpo-scene-understanding-accessibility.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T19:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sagar M. Waghmare, Senior Software Engineer, and Kimberly Wilber, Software Engineer, Google Research, Perception Team




As most people navigate their everyday world, they process visual input from the environment using an eye-level perspective. Unlike robots and self-driving cars, people don't have any "out-of-body" sensors to help guide them. Instead, a person’s sensory input is completely "egocentric", or "from the self." This also applies to new technologies that understand the world around us from a human-like perspective, e.g., robots navigating through unknown buildings, AR glasses that highlight objects, or assistive technology to help people run independently.





In computer vision, scene understanding is the subfield that studies how visible objects relate to the sce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Control Tower, Amazon Bedrock, Amazon OpenSearch Service, and More (October 9, 2023)]]></title>
        <id>196aa0e7b4449c650c1db86dcc60997ea5c34699</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-control-tower-amazon-bedrock-amazon-opensearch-service-and-more-october-9-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T19:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Northern Hemisphere enjoys early fall and pumpkins take over the local farmers markets and coffee flavors here in the United States, we’re also just 50 days away from re:Invent 2023! But before we officially enter pre:Invent sea­­son, let’s have a look at some of last week’s exciting news and announcements. Last Week’s Launches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>