<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-22T00:19:27.198Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-22T00:19:27.198Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your MySQL 5.7 and PostgreSQL 11 databases will be automatically enrolled into Amazon RDS Extended Support]]></title>
        <id>b5cdd71e80db076a8254fccd5b55346635929927</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/your-mysql-5-7-and-postgresql-11-databases-will-be-automatically-enrolled-into-amazon-rds-extended-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T22:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing that your MySQL 5.7 and PostgreSQL 11 database instances running on Amazon Aurora and Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) will be automatically enrolled into Amazon RDS Extended Support starting on February 29, 2024. This will help avoid unplanned downtime and compatibility issues that can arise with automatically upgrading to a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drama at work]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48071</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/852413975/0/sethsblog~Drama-at-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T09:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A divo (or diva) is an opera singer with skill. Sometimes, though, that skill comes in a package that also includes imperiousness, skittishness and a fair amount of unpredictable drama. It’s tempting to imagine that CEOs, painters or poets that bring the noise must also have skill. But burning your guitar doesn’t make you Jimi […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.0.4 and 1.1.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/21/spring-modulith-1-0-4-and-1-1-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/21/spring-modulith-1-0-4-and-1-1-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/21/spring-boot-3-2-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/21/spring-boot-3-2-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.7 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/21/spring-boot-3-1-7-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/21/spring-boot-3-1-7-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.3.2 Bug-Fix Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=421855</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/12/clion-2023-3-2-bug-fix-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CLion 2023.3.2 bug-fix update is here! The fixes included in this update are listed below. Download build 233.13135.93 from our website, through the Toolbox App, as a snap package for Ubuntu, or via a patch from inside the IDE. DOWNLOAD CLION While bug-fix update 2023.3.1 was mostly focused on addressing AI Assistant licensing issues, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNS over HTTPS is now available in Amazon Route 53 Resolver]]></title>
        <id>4694b932095b5a1012286d52e7559c670fe69489</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/dns-over-https-is-now-available-in-amazon-route-53-resolver/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T18:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, Amazon Route 53 Resolver supports using the DNS over HTTPS (DoH) protocol for both inbound and outbound Resolver endpoints. As the name suggests, DoH supports HTTP or HTTP/2 over TLS to encrypt the data exchanged for Domain Name System (DNS) resolutions. Using TLS encryption, DoH increases privacy and security by preventing eavesdropping and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3.2 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=421826</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/12/intellij-idea-2023-3-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second bug-fix update for v2023.3 is now available. You can update to this version from inside the IDE, using the Toolbox App, or using snaps if you are a Ubuntu user. You can also download it from our website. Here are the most notable fixes and updates that IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3.2 brings: For more information about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Contextual logging in Kubernetes 1.29: Better troubleshooting and enhanced logging]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/20/contextual-logging-in-kubernetes-1-29/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/20/contextual-logging-in-kubernetes-1-29/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Mengjiao Liu (DaoCloud), Patrick Ohly (Intel)
On behalf of the Structured Logging Working Group
and SIG Instrumentation,
we are pleased to announce that the contextual logging feature
introduced in Kubernetes v1.24 has now been successfully migrated to
two components (kube-scheduler and kube-controller-manager)
as well as some directories. This feature aims to provide more useful logs
for better troubleshooting of Kubernetes and to empower developers to enhance Kubernetes.
What is contextual logging?
Contextual logging
is based on the go-logr API.
The key idea is that libraries are passed a logger instance by their caller
and use that for logging instead of accessing a global logger.
The binary decides the logging implementation, not the libraries.
The go-logr API is designed arou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp 2023 year in review: Customers and partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2023-year-in-review-customers-and-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2023-year-in-review-customers-and-partners"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a look back at HashiCorp’s new customers, new customer stories, and partner ecosystem milestones from the past year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy Youth Challenge: The Ultimate Coding and Math Showdown!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=421929</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/12/20/jetbrains-academy-youth-challenge-the-ultimate-coding-and-math-showdown/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T16:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready for the JetBrains Academy Youth Challenge, a brand-new competition for young coders and mathematicians. If you’re passionate about these fields, this is your stage to shine, compete, and win. Choose your track The challenge consists of two tracks: math and coding. Feel free to participate in both or choose your favorite.  Don’t forget […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Gupaisova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Common Rust Compiler Errors as Encountered in RustRover: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rust&amp;p=421518</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rust/2023/12/20/the-most-common-rust-compiler-errors-as-encountered-in-rustrover-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T15:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this blog series, we dug into our list of the top 10 most common Rust compiler errors according to RustRover’s usage data, and we made it halfway through the list. In this part, we’ll explore the top five most frequently occurring errors and then make some more general observations regarding the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vitaly Bragilevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper and Rider 2023.3.2 – Bug Fixes Have Landed!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=421246</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/12/20/resharper-and-rider-2023-3-2-bug-fix/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T14:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A second set of bug fixes for the 2023.3 versions of ReSharper and Rider has just been released.  Let’s take a look at what’s been improved. ReSharper  ReSharper 2023.3.2 comes with the following bug fixes: For the full list of resolved issues, please refer to our issue tracker. Rider  Rider 2023.3.2 comes with the following […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Canada West (Calgary) Region is now available]]></title>
        <id>6b3cea87b782c16878fbdb2c69ae9048a41b26a5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/the-aws-canada-west-calgary-region-is-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T11:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update: December 20, 2023 — The list of services available today at launch is now updated with AWS Artifact, AWS Cloud Control API, AWS Directory Services, EC2 Image Builder, and AWS Transit Gateway for a new total of 70 services.   Today, we are opening a new Region in Canada. AWS Canada West (Calgary), also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The clamp and the mallet]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46341</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/852306803/0/sethsblog~The-clamp-and-the-mallet/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T09:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While building a project, I found that a key part was stuck. I tapped it with a mallet, then harder, and eventually whacked at it. No luck. Then I got smart and put three clamps around the part, gently turning each one, increasing the pressure, until it simply popped out. Persistent, gentle pressure almost always […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.9 (aka Jubilee) Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/20/spring-cloud-2021-0-9-aka-jubilee-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/20/spring-cloud-2021-0-9-aka-jubilee-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Baxter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 reasons to upgrade Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-reasons-to-upgrade-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-reasons-to-upgrade-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic upgrades come quickly, and it can be a challenge to schedule upgrades. Here we’ll take a quick look at the top five new features in Elastic Security that’ll help you reduce risk and control costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dain Perkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US federal agencies and AI: The race is on]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-federal-agencies-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-federal-agencies-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new audit from the US government shows that federal agencies are rapidly increasing their use of AI. Here, we unpack agencies’ AI use cases and top considerations for AI implementation in government.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 reasons to upgrade Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-reasons-to-upgrade-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-reasons-to-upgrade-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fear of missing out, or fear of missing logs?,
Let’s start with assurances that we’re not here to heap anxiety on anyone’s fear of missing out. That being said, we do want to make sure you’re aware of all the goodness that is available in Elastic Security, especially if you’re on an older version. It can be hard to find time to dig into every new release, to see what new features might be available, or check on ways to stretch your budget in order to pick up all the logs you might be missing.

Elastic® releases new versions fairly quickly, driven by new features, user submitted enhancement requests, and of course, the occasional bug fix. It can be challenging to schedule upgrades for every new release, particularly when we’re talking about a SIEM platform that needs to be running 24/7/365,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dain Perkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US federal agencies and AI: The race is on]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-federal-agencies-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/us-federal-agencies-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI revolution in federal agencies has begun,
Federal agencies are ramping up their use of artificial intelligence significantly, according to a US Government Accountability Office (GAO) audit. The report noted that there were 228 different AI use cases in operation, with over 500 more in planning and approximately another 500 in research or exploration phases. These numbers are likely conservative, considering the rapid advancement in AI since the report compiled its data for Fiscal Year 2022. 

Agencies are employing AI for diverse purposes to enhance their agency’s mission — from analyzing surveillance data for border activities to interpreting drone images to detecting cybersecurity threats and processing large data sets. Notably, NASA and the Department of Commerce are leading in A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Love Songs]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2870/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2870/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/love_songs.png" title="The Piña Colada song carves a trajectory across the chart over the course of the song." alt="The Piña Colada song carves a trajectory across the chart over the course of the song." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VideoPoet: A large language model for zero-shot video generation]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/videopoet-large-language-model-for-zero.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/videopoet-large-language-model-for-zero.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T21:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dan Kondratyuk and David Ross, Software Engineers, Google Research




A recent wave of video generation models has burst onto the scene, in many cases showcasing stunning picturesque quality. One of the current bottlenecks in video generation is in the ability to produce coherent large motions. In many cases, even the current leading models either generate small motion or, when producing larger motions, exhibit noticeable artifacts.
 

To explore the application of language models in video generation, we introduce VideoPoet, a large language model (LLM) that is capable of a wide variety of video generation tasks, including text-to-video, image-to-video, video stylization, video inpainting and outpainting, and video-to-audio. One notable observation is that the leading video gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS India customers can now save card information for monthly AWS billing]]></title>
        <id>1cd93eb93a4a6344bc1ea2d4e334af63f84faf21</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-india-customers-can-now-save-card-information-for-monthly-aws-billing/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T20:11:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, AWS India customers can now securely save their credit or debit cards in their AWS accounts according to the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) guidelines. Customers can use their saved cards to make payments for their AWS invoices. Previously, customers needed to manually enter their card information in the payments console for each payment. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the Private Preview of Our New Tool for Your ML Experiments!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=421433</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/12/join-the-private-preview-of-our-new-tool-for-your-ml-experiments/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T18:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to the rapid growth of the data science market, we’re enhancing support for data science libraries, ML models, and MLOps, including by collaborating with ML vendors. We’re starting with a private preview of our brand-new tool for ML experiments. It lets you set up and launch an experiment from local code on a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we organize and get things done with SERVICEOWNERS]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-19-how-we-organize-and-get-things-done-with-serviceowners/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-19-how-we-organize-and-get-things-done-with-serviceowners/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T18:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Take CODEOWNERS and GitHub teams to the next level. Learn about how GitHub engineering solves the age old problem of who owns what.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-19-how-we-organize-and-get-things-done-with-serviceowners/">How we organize and get things done with SERVICEOWNERS</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From migration tools to updates to Enterprise Managed Users, what’s new in GitHub Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-19-from-migration-tools-to-updates-to-enterprise-managed-users-whats-new-in-github-enterprise/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-19-from-migration-tools-to-updates-to-enterprise-managed-users-whats-new-in-github-enterprise/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T17:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Read a round-up of the exciting, new innovation coming from GitHub Enterprise.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-19-from-migration-tools-to-updates-to-enterprise-managed-users-whats-new-in-github-enterprise/">From migration tools to updates to Enterprise Managed Users, what’s new in GitHub Enterprise</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp 2023 year in review: Product innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2023-year-in-review-product-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2023-year-in-review-product-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking back on a busy year, we’re proud of so many technical accomplishments. We’re even more excited about the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in TeamCity: Remote Parameters and Updated HashiCorp Vault Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=421366</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/12/updated-hashicorp-vault-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T16:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When configuring a CI/CD pipeline, you may need to obtain secrets from a third party. This could be necessary to connect with an external service crucial for your pipeline or to secure the deployment of your application with the required confidential information. You can store all of these secrets as secure parameters in TeamCity. However, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simulations illuminate the path to post-event traffic flow]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/simulations-illuminate-path-to-post.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/simulations-illuminate-path-to-post.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yechen Li and Neha Arora, Software Engineers, Google Research




Fifteen minutes. That’s how long it took to empty the Colosseum, an engineering marvel that’s still standing as the largest amphitheater in the world. Two thousand years later, this design continues to work well to move enormous crowds out of sporting and entertainment venues.





But of course, exiting the arena is only the first step. Next, people must navigate the traffic that builds up in the surrounding streets. This is an age-old problem that remains unsolved to this day. In Rome, they addressed the issue by prohibiting private traffic on the street that passes directly by the Colosseum. This policy worked there, but what if you’re not in Rome? What if you’re at the Superbowl? Or at a Taylor Swift concert?

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · End of 2023 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-19-release-radar-dec-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-19-release-radar-dec-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T16:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hacktoberfest has wrapped up, GitHub Universe has come to a close, and our community has been super hard at work. All the while people enjoyed turkey over Thanksgiving in the United States and Canada and expressed gratitude for those around them. In this edition, we&#8217;d like to thank the open source community for all the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-19-release-radar-dec-2023/">Release Radar · End of 2023 Edition</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The problems with flat out]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46339</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/852206225/0/sethsblog~The-problems-with-flat-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The desire for 11 is proof that we often want to go all the way to ten. While 11 is silly, there is a lot of pressure to give our all. But there are problems. The first is that if you try to sprint an entire marathon, you’ll hurt yourself. Systems can be stressed for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy’s Course Catalog: A Hub for Learning Technical Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=420216</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/12/19/jetbrains-academy-s-course-catalog-a-hub-for-learning-technical-skills/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T09:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At JetBrains Academy, we aim to go beyond programming courses. That’s why we offer a 360-degree computer science learning experience. Over a million of our students study using our project-based approach, proving its effectiveness when it comes to learning technical skills. What’s more, we incorporate JetBrains IDEs – the daily tools of professional developers – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A ClangFormat Story and the Third CLion Nova Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=421133</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/12/a-clangformat-story-and-the-third-clion-nova-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T02:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion Nova is a free preview of CLion equipped with the ReSharper C++/Rider C++ language engine. It comes with all of the newest enhancements from the CLion Classic 2023.3 release, with the exception of AI Assistant. This means you can use CLion Nova if it works best for your use case without missing out on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 19th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/19/this-week-in-spring-december-19th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/19/this-week-in-spring-december-19th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 1.2.1, 1.1.4 and 0.4.5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/19/spring-authorization-server-1-2-1-1-1-4-and-0-4-5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/19/spring-authorization-server-1-2-1-1-1-4-and-0-4-5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Grandja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring AMQP 3.1.1 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/19/spring-amqp-3-1-1-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/19/spring-amqp-3-1-1-available"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Bilan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.8.9, 6.1.6, and 6.2.1 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/19/spring-security-5-8-9-6-1-6-and-6-2-1-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/19/spring-security-5-8-9-6-1-6-and-6-2-1-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Cummings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Kafka 3.1.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/19/spring-for-apache-kafka-3-1-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/19/spring-for-apache-kafka-3-1-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soby Chacko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M-21-31 logging compliance: Overcoming the 3 top challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/m-21-31-logging-compliance-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/m-21-31-logging-compliance-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US federal agencies have made progress in adhering to M-21-31’s cyber threat response requirements but lag in advanced event logging requirements. Learn how Elastic can help agencies overcome three major challenges slowing M-21-31 logging compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link,Richard Im</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU AI Act: What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/eu-ai-act</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/eu-ai-act"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EU’s AI Act, which sets regulations for artificial intelligence, is the first of its kind — but it likely will not be the last. Here’s what it means for global organizations and what you can do to prepare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do customers choose Elastic for logs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-do-customers-choose-elastic-for-logs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-do-customers-choose-elastic-for-logs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic helped define centralized logging; now we’re redefining the value modern logging tools can bring. We discuss how ES|QL, ML, AI, and OTel enable customers to transform logging from a reactive debugging tool to a proactive observability signal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ty Bekiares</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M-21-31 logging compliance: Overcoming the 3 top challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/m-21-31-logging-compliance-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/m-21-31-logging-compliance-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Recently, the US Government Accountability Office (GAO) released a study tracking US federal agencies’ progress on meeting the requirements set out in OMB M-21-31. Released in 2021, the Office of Management and Budget (OMB)’s M-21-31 memorandum provided guidance and requirements for federal agencies in order to improve centralized visibility into logging data before, during, and after cybersecurity incidents. The memo outlined a logging maturity model with four tiers (E0-3) to guide agencies in their compliance process.

In the new study, GAO found that agencies “have made progress in preparing for and responding to cyber threats.” At the same time, however, the study noted that 20 of the 23 agencies did not meet M-21-31’s tier 3 advanced event logging (“advanced EL3”) August deadline for tracking, storing, and managing event logs.

The study highlighted three challenges agencies are facing as they work to meet M-21-31 event logging requirements: 


Lack of staff

Event logging technical challenges

Limitations in cyber event information sharing


In this post, we’ll walk through these challenges and share how we’ve seen federal customers address them using Elasticsearch®.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link,Richard Im</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU AI Act: What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/eu-ai-act</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/eu-ai-act"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
On December 8, 2023, the European Union made a significant step in digital governance by introducing the first set of comprehensive artificial intelligence (AI) regulations. This legislation, poised for a European Parliament vote by early 2024, is first out of the gate in regulating AI. As organizations look to comply with this act (and the additional regulations likely to come on its heels), one thing is for sure: The ability to have access and insight into all data will be essential. And the stakes have never been higher.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.

In this blog post, we may have used or referred to third party generative AI tools, which are owned and operated by their respective owners. Elastic does not have any control over the third party tools and we have no responsibility or liability for their content, operation or use, nor for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of such tools. Please exercise caution when using AI tools with personal, sensitive or confidential information. Any data you submit may be used for AI training or other purposes. There is no guarantee that information you provide will be kept secure or confidential. You should familiarize yourself with the privacy practices and terms of use of any generative AI tools prior to use.

Elastic, Elasticsearch, ESRE, Elasticsearch Relevance Engine and associated marks are trademarks, logos or registered trademarks of Elasticsearch N.V. in the United States and other countries. All other company and product names are trademarks, logos or registered trademarks of their respective owners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do customers choose Elastic for logs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-do-customers-choose-elastic-for-logs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-do-customers-choose-elastic-for-logs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In the absence of other observability signals, generally everything in your infrastructure (hardware, software, and services) emits log lines. Logs, however, are often structured at a developer’s whim and, first and foremost, serve the developer’s needs (e.g., debugging). Once in production, these same log lines are inherently promoted to a first-class means of observing your applications and infrastructure, regardless of their original intent. This makes logs a notoriously noisy observability signal whose rate can swing wildly with errors and scale.

The simplicity of the log line as an observability signal (fundamentally, it’s just text!) makes it deceivingly simple to observe. On the other hand, its noisy, unstructured nature and unpredictable rate make it among the most difficult of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ty Bekiares</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.29: Decoupling taint-manager from node-lifecycle-controller]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/19/kubernetes-1-29-taint-eviction-controller/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/19/kubernetes-1-29-taint-eviction-controller/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Yuan Chen (Apple), Andrea Tosatto (Apple)
This blog discusses a new feature in Kubernetes 1.29 to improve the handling of taint-based pod eviction.
Background
In Kubernetes 1.29, an improvement has been introduced to enhance the taint-based pod eviction handling on nodes.
This blog discusses the changes made to node-lifecycle-controller
to separate its responsibilities and improve overall code maintainability.
Summary of changes
node-lifecycle-controller previously combined two independent functions:
Adding a pre-defined set of NoExecute taints to Node based on Node's condition.
Performing pod eviction on NoExecute taint.
With the Kubernetes 1.29 release, the taint-based eviction implementation has been
moved out of node-lifecycle-controller into a separate and independent compone…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.29: PodReadyToStartContainers Condition Moves to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/19/pod-ready-to-start-containers-condition-now-in-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/19/pod-ready-to-start-containers-condition-now-in-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Zefeng Chen (independent), Kevin Hannon (Red Hat)
With the recent release of Kubernetes 1.29, the PodReadyToStartContainers
condition is
available by default.
The kubelet manages the value for that condition throughout a Pod's lifecycle,
in the status field of a Pod. The kubelet will use the PodReadyToStartContainers
condition to accurately surface the initialization state of a Pod,
from the perspective of Pod sandbox creation and network configuration by a container runtime.
What's the motivation for this feature?
Cluster administrators did not have a clear and easily accessible way to view the completion of Pod's sandbox creation
and initialization. As of 1.28, the Initialized condition in Pods tracks the execution of init containers.
However, it has limitations in accurately re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — AWS Lambda, AWS Amplify, Amazon OpenSearch Service, Amazon Rekognition, and more — December 18, 2023]]></title>
        <id>2dacccda6aac8e12d9d28e3e086b8d65dbbd17b8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-lambda-aws-amplify-amazon-opensearch-service-amazon-rekognition-and-more-december-18-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T17:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My memories of Amazon Web Services (AWS) re:Invent 2023 are still fresh even when I’m currently wrapping up my activities in Jakarta after participating in AWS Community Day Indonesia. It was a great experience, from delivering chalk talks and having thoughtful discussions with AWS service teams, to meeting with AWS Heroes, AWS Community Builders, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Go This Week: A Language Built for Simplicity and Efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=419935</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/12/18/learn-go-community-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T10:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready to release your inner gopher. We’re thrilled to announce the addition of the popular Tour of Go course to JetBrains Marketplace. Originally developed by the Go community as a concise introduction to the language, this course is a perfect way to expand your programming repertoire with all of the benefits of in-IDE learning […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clara Maine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Focusing attention is a skill]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46337</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/852074222/0/sethsblog~Focusing-attention-is-a-skill/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T09:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where we choose to direct our gaze determines not only what we learn or believe, but how we choose to see the world. Typing is a skill. Juggling is a skill. So is project management. It’s easy to overlook the fact that we can get better at what we think about, create and consume. If […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Pulsar 1.0.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/18/spring-for-apache-pulsar-1-0-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/12/18/spring-for-apache-pulsar-1-0-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bono</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The benefits of using a Verified MSP for your Elastic deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/verified-msp-elastic-deployments-benefits</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/verified-msp-elastic-deployments-benefits"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the benefits of a managed service provider and learn about Elastic’s new MSP designation, Verified. Explore eight considerations for choosing the right MSP for your business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabelle Li,David Kosman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The benefits of using a Verified MSP for your Elastic deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/verified-msp-elastic-deployments-benefits</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/verified-msp-elastic-deployments-benefits"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why choose a Managed Service Provider (MSP)? ,
Using an MSP allows you to focus on your core business instead of your IT infrastructure. The right MSP not only provides deep technical expertise and 24/7 monitoring and management of your infrastructure, but it can also improve core operational and procedural challenges over time to help you reduce costs and streamline operations, so your IT team can focus on projects that accelerate your business.
Ready to engage with an Elastic Verified MSP?,
Whether you want to leverage Elastic within your data center or via the cloud, here are eight areas to consider when selecting a MSP:

Support: Ensure that your preferred MSP offers 24/7 support and security operation center(s) across time zones.

Pricing: Review pricing models to make sure it fits within your resources.

Breadth of services: Consider your needs today, but also what you might need in one, three, or five years. Choose an MSP with a wide range of services so you’re able to grow together and build a lasting partnership. 

Cloud or hybrid posture: What is your current environment? Make sure your MSP supports your model.

Service offerings: Inquire about additional offerings, like consulting or migration services.

References: Ask to see validated customer references and testimonials.

Certifications and clearances: If your industry is regulated, ensure that your MSP has the right certifications and clearances. 

Verified: Consider choosing an MSP who is Elastic Verified. This ensures the MSP has the correct architecture design, proof of 24/7 support, Elastic-certified engineers, successful customer deployments, and more.

Our current list of our Verified MSP partners includes:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabelle Li,David Kosman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Puzzles]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2869/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2869/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/puzzles.png" title="Why couldn't the amulet have been hidden by Aunt Alice, who understands modern key exchange algorithms?" alt="Why couldn't the amulet have been hidden by Aunt Alice, who understands modern key exchange algorithms?" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.29: New (alpha) Feature, Load Balancer IP Mode for Services]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/18/kubernetes-1-29-feature-loadbalancer-ip-mode-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/18/kubernetes-1-29-feature-loadbalancer-ip-mode-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aohan Yang
This blog introduces a new alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.29.
It provides a configurable approach to define how Service implementations,
exemplified in this blog by kube-proxy,
handle traffic from pods to the Service, within the cluster.
Background
In older Kubernetes releases, the kube-proxy would intercept traffic that was destined for the IP
address associated with a Service of type: LoadBalancer. This happened whatever mode you used
for kube-proxy.
The interception implemented the expected behavior (traffic eventually reaching the expected
endpoints behind the Service). The mechanism to make that work depended on the mode for kube-proxy;
on Linux, kube-proxy in iptables mode would redirecting packets directly to the endpoint; in ipvs mode,
kube-proxy would configure t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.29: Single Pod Access Mode for PersistentVolumes Graduates to Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/18/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/18/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chris Henzie (Google)
With the release of Kubernetes v1.29, the ReadWriteOncePod volume access mode
has graduated to general availability: it's part of Kubernetes' stable API. In
this blog post, I'll take a closer look at this access mode and what it does.
What is ReadWriteOncePod?
ReadWriteOncePod is an access mode for
PersistentVolumes (PVs)
and PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs)
introduced in Kubernetes v1.22. This access mode enables you to restrict volume
access to a single pod in the cluster, ensuring that only one pod can write to
the volume at a time. This can be particularly useful for stateful workloads
that require single-writer access to storage.
For more context on access modes and how ReadWriteOncePod works read
What are access modes and why are they important?
in the Intr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personal process notation]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48066</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/851910074/0/sethsblog~Personal-process-notation/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T09:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I’ll remember it later.” I’ll confess, I rarely do. It turns out, it’s easier to remember questions than answers. And tools like Google Docs and photos in the cloud give us a chance to build our own personal search engine. It takes 14 steps to construct the pages in one of my InDesign projects. Inevitably, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The friendly professional]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48064</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/851816768/0/sethsblog~The-friendly-professional/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T09:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friendly doesn’t mean saying ‘yes’ all the time, or changing every policy, or giving up our principles. Friendly is how it feels, not what it does.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advancements in machine learning for machine learning]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/advancements-in-machine-learning-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/advancements-in-machine-learning-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Phitchaya Mangpo Phothilimthana, Staff Research Scientist, Google DeepMind, and Bryan Perozzi, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Research





With the recent and accelerated advances in machine learning (ML), machines can understand natural language, engage in conversations, draw images, create videos and more. Modern ML models are programmed and trained using ML programming frameworks, such as TensorFlow, JAX, PyTorch, among many others. These libraries provide high-level instructions to ML practitioners, such as linear algebra operations (e.g., matrix multiplication, convolution, etc.) and neural network layers (e.g., 2D convolution layers, transformer layers). Importantly, practitioners need not worry about how to make their models run efficiently on hardware because an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[StyleDrop: Text-to-image generation in any style]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/styledrop-text-to-image-generation-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/styledrop-text-to-image-generation-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kihyuk Sohn and Dilip Krishnan, Research Scientists, Google Research




Text-to-image models trained on large volumes of image-text pairs have enabled the creation of rich and diverse images encompassing many genres and themes. Moreover, popular styles such as “anime” or “steampunk”, when added to the input text prompt, may translate to specific visual outputs. While many efforts have been put into prompt engineering, a wide range of styles are simply hard to describe in text form due to the nuances of color schemes, illumination, and other characteristics. As an example, “watercolor painting” may refer to various styles, and using a text prompt that simply says “watercolor painting style” may either result in one specific style or an unpredictable mix of several.
 




When we …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2023.11.1 Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=420077</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/12/teamcity-2023-11-1-is-here/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T14:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first bug-fix update for TeamCity On-Premises 2023.11 is out and available for download. Version 2023.11.1 addresses multiple issues (including limited LDAP synchronization and artifact domain isolation problems) and includes a few security and performance updates. Please refer to our release notes for the complete change list. As with other minor updates, TeamCity 2023.11.1 shares […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitrii Korovin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Portrait of the Average Data Scientist of 2023 in 3 Facts]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=418835</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2023/12/15/a-portrait-of-the-average-data-scientist-of-2023-in-3-facts/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider the average data scientist of 2023: They spend a significant chunk of their time visualizing data, with line and bar plots as their go-to tools. They’ve mastered their craft through independent study and use Jupyter notebooks for in-depth data analysis. Version control is not their strong suit, and when presenting findings, they tend to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signal and noise]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46030</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/851619875/0/sethsblog~Signal-and-noise/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T09:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the signal is very weak and the noise is large, it’s easy to imagine that there’s no signal at all. AI and computers can be used as lenses now, which means we can strip away the noise and see things that we certainly didn’t expect. Dina Katabi at MIT can point a radio antenna […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decemberfest is here! How we celebrate the holidays at Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-decemberfest-elastic-holiday-celebration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-decemberfest-elastic-holiday-celebration"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a peek at how Elasticians around the world are celebrating the holiday season during Decemberfest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decemberfest is here! How we celebrate the holidays at Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-decemberfest-elastic-holiday-celebration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-decemberfest-elastic-holiday-celebration"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
December is here and that means holiday celebrations. At Elastic, we call the season’s celebration Decemberfest. It’s a time for all Elasticians to connect — either at an in-person event or from home. 
We’ve always been distributed by design. To uphold that ethos and to allow everyone to join the festivities, we have many ways for our Elasticians to celebrate the season. 

Decemberfest started in 2020 when the world had to be 100% virtual and has evolved into our flagship holiday celebration running from the end of November to mid-December.
This year, Elasticians have multiple opportunities to join in on the fun. 
In-person events are organized in 48 cities around the world. Our workplace experience team has events planned in cities with Elastic offices. For those who don’t live near an …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Label the States]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2868/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2868/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/label_the_states.png" title="Even with a blank map, a lot of people can only name 45-50 of the 64 states." alt="Even with a blank map, a lot of people can only name 45-50 of the 64 states." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.29: CSI Storage Resizing Authenticated and Generally Available in v1.29]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/csi-node-expand-secret-support-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/csi-node-expand-secret-support-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Humble Chirammal (Vmware), Louis Koo (deeproute.ai)
Kubernetes version v1.29 brings generally available support for authentication
during CSI (Container Storage Interface) storage resize operations.
Let's embark on the evolution of this feature, initially introduced in alpha in
Kubernetes v1.25, and unravel the changes accompanying its transition to GA.
Authenticated CSI storage resizing unveiled
Kubernetes harnesses the capabilities of CSI to seamlessly integrate with third-party
storage systems, empowering your cluster to seamlessly expand storage volumes
managed by the CSI driver. The recent elevation of authentication secret support
for resizes from Beta to GA ushers in new horizons, enabling volume expansion in
scenarios where the underlying storage operation demands credenti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.29: VolumeAttributesClass for Volume Modification]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/kubernetes-1-29-volume-attributes-class/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/15/kubernetes-1-29-volume-attributes-class/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sunny Song (Google)
The v1.29 release of Kubernetes introduced an alpha feature to support modifying a volume
by changing the volumeAttributesClassName that was specified for a PersistentVolumeClaim (PVC).
With the feature enabled, Kubernetes can handle updates of volume attributes other than capacity.
Allowing volume attributes to be changed without managing it through different
provider's APIs directly simplifies the current flow.
You can read about VolumeAttributesClass usage details in the Kubernetes documentation
or you can read on to learn about why the Kubernetes project is supporting this feature.
VolumeAttributesClass
The new storage.k8s.io/v1alpha1 API group provides two new types:
VolumeAttributesClass
Represents a specification of mutable volume attributes defined by th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitchell reflects as he departs HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mitchell-reflects-as-he-departs-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mitchell-reflects-as-he-departs-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After more than 11 years, HashiCorp Co-Founder Mitchell Hashimoto pens a heartfelt goodbye letter to the company he helped create.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.29: Cloud Provider Integrations Are Now Separate Components]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/14/cloud-provider-integration-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/14/cloud-provider-integration-changes/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Michael McCune (Red Hat), Andrew Sy Kim (Google)
For Kubernetes v1.29, you need to use additional components to integrate your
Kubernetes cluster with a cloud infrastructure provider. By default, Kubernetes
v1.29 components abort if you try to specify integration with any cloud provider using
one of the legacy compiled-in cloud provider integrations. If you want to use a legacy
integration, you have to opt back in - and a future release will remove even that option.
In 2018, the Kubernetes community agreed to form the Cloud Provider Special
Interest Group (SIG), with a mission to externalize all cloud provider
integrations and remove all the existing in-tree cloud provider integrations.
In January 2019, the Kubernetes community approved the initial draft of
KEP-2395: Removing In-T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to Azure DevOps Demo Generator and Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67966</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/updates-to-azure-devops-demo-generator-and-labs/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that we have published new content to the Azure DevOps Demo Generator and Azure DevOps Labs!
The Azure DevOps Labs is a great tool to help you learn about the integrated features offered in Azure DevOps.
The post Updates to Azure DevOps Demo Generator and Labs appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our First Netflix Data Engineering Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f326b0589102</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/our-first-netflix-data-engineering-summit-f326b0589102?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holden Karau Elizabeth Stone Pedro Duarte Chris Stephens Pallavi Phadnis Lee Woodridge Mark Cho Guil Pires Sujay Jain Tristan Reid…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds on-demand policy evaluation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-on-demand-policy-evaluation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-on-demand-policy-evaluation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-demand policy evaluation improves visibility and control by letting users evaluate the effects of policy changes in Terraform Cloud before they are enforced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling vulnerability management across thousands of services and more than 150 million findings]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-14-scaling-vulnerability-management-across-thousands-of-services-and-more-than-150-million-findings/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-14-scaling-vulnerability-management-across-thousands-of-services-and-more-than-150-million-findings/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn about how we run a scalable vulnerability management program built on top of GitHub. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-14-scaling-vulnerability-management-across-thousands-of-services-and-more-than-150-million-findings/">Scaling vulnerability management across thousands of services and more than 150 million findings</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight marketing maxims]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48022</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/851485229/0/sethsblog~Eight-marketing-maxims/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trust is worth more than attention. Helping people get to where they seek to go is more effective than hustling people to persuade them to go where you’re going. Choose your customers, choose…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: November 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-13-github-availability-report-november-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-github-availability-report-november-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T20:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In November, we experienced one incident that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-github-availability-report-november-2023/">GitHub Availability Report: November 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing our home labs: Frigate code review]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-13-securing-our-home-labs-frigate-code-review/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-securing-our-home-labs-frigate-code-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This blog post describes two linked vulnerabilities found in Frigate, an AI-powered security camera manager, that could have enabled an attacker to silently gain remote code execution.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-securing-our-home-labs-frigate-code-review/">Securing our home labs: Frigate code review</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PKI certificate issuance flexibility with Vault CIEPS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pki-certificate-issuance-flexibility-with-vault-cieps</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pki-certificate-issuance-flexibility-with-vault-cieps"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault Enterprise 1.15 adds an external policy service for issuing PKI certificates. Learn about its benefits and how it compares to existing policies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Default setup now includes scheduled scans and supports all languages covered by CodeQL]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-13-default-setup-now-includes-scheduled-scans-and-supports-all-languages-covered-by-codeql/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-default-setup-now-includes-scheduled-scans-and-supports-all-languages-covered-by-codeql/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T16:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We’ve added new improvements to default setup, including automatically scheduling scans on repositories and support for all CodeQL covered languages.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-13-default-setup-now-includes-scheduled-scans-and-supports-all-languages-covered-by-codeql/">Default setup now includes scheduled scans and supports all languages covered by CodeQL</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering AWS with amazon.aws 7.0: A Dive into New Modules for Enhanced Security and Seamless Migrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/mastering-aws-with-amazon.aws-7.0-a-dive-into-new-modules-for-enhanced-security-and-seamless-migrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/mastering-aws-with-amazon.aws-7.0-a-dive-into-new-modules-for-enhanced-security-and-seamless-migrations"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the technology landscape continues to evolve, the latest release of the Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for amazon.aws introduces a suite of powerful modules that redefine the boundaries of automation within Amazon Web Services (AWS) while redefining how organizations approach security deployments and seamless migrations within the AWS ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第243話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755564103990</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755564103990"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valuable contributions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48015</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/850872368/0/sethsblog~Valuable-contributions/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T09:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We actually don’t really know. Netflix just released their first-ever detailed analysis of how many hours of engagement the top 15,000+ most watched shows on the network received over a six month period. Here’s the file. Who won? That question is actually the lesson here. The fact is, most organizations are pretty clueless about where […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DateTime]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2867/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2867/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/datetime.png" title="It's not just time zones and leap seconds. SI seconds on Earth are slower because of relativity, so there are time standards for space stuff (TCB, TGC) that use faster SI seconds than UTC/Unix time. T2 - T1 = [God doesn't know and the Devil isn't telling.]" alt="It's not just time zones and leap seconds. SI seconds on Earth are slower because of relativity, so there are time standards for space stuff (TCB, TGC) that use faster SI seconds than UTC/Unix time. T2 - T1 = [God doesn't know and the Devil isn't telling.]" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.29: Mandala]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/13/kubernetes-v1-29-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/12/13/kubernetes-v1-29-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes v1.29 Release Team
Editors: Carol Valencia, Kristin Martin, Abigail McCarthy, James Quigley
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.29: Mandala (The Universe), the last release of 2023!
Similar to previous releases, the release of Kubernetes v1.29 introduces new stable, beta, and alpha features. The consistent delivery of top-notch releases underscores the strength of our development cycle and the vibrant support from our community.
This release consists of 49 enhancements. Of those enhancements, 11 have graduated to Stable, 19 are entering Beta and 19 have graduated to Alpha.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes v1.29: Mandala (The Universe) ✨🌌
Join us on a cosmic journey with Kubernetes v1.29!
This release is inspired by the beautiful art form that is Mandala—a symbol o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68208</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/december-patches-for-azure-devops-server-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T19:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 Patch 1
The post December patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for AWS Amplify – Query MySQL and PostgreSQL database for AWS CDK]]></title>
        <id>32014208559319f447ba9286e5c9d009e392d2ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-aws-amplify-query-mysql-and-postgresql-database-for-aws-cdk/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T18:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the general availability to connect and query your existing MySQL and PostgreSQL databases with support for AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK), a new feature to create a real-time, secure GraphQL API for your relational database within or outside Amazon Web Services (AWS). You can now generate the entire API for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Cloud Automation with amazon.aws 7.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-7.0.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-7.0.0"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to Amazon Web Services (AWS) infrastructure automation, the latest release of the certified amazon.aws Ansible Content Collection for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform brings a number of enhancements to improve the overall user experience and speed up the process from development to production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital stocking stuffers (and the other kind)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47970</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/850431992/0/sethsblog~Digital-stocking-stuffers-and-the-other-kind/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since O. Henry wrote about the Magi, it’s been pretty clear that gifts aren’t about the stuff as much as they are the intent. Holidays where gifts are expected undermine this, because it’s hard to tell where obligation begins and intent fades away. One lightweight and quick alternative to traditional items are digital ones. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That's a wrap! Looking back on the Elastic and AWS collaboration in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-elastic-aws-partnership-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-elastic-aws-partnership-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens in Vegas stays in Vegas, except when it’s Elastic recapping AWS re:Invent 2023! As a Diamond sponsor, we enjoyed supporting our partner AWS at this flagship event. We’ve also compiled an Elastic + AWS 2023 year in review.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm,Austin Jones,Jennifer Jarrad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-3-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.16 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-16-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-16-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Buttner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That's a wrap! Looking back on the Elastic and AWS collaboration in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-elastic-aws-partnership-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/looking-back-elastic-aws-partnership-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
What a fantastic week at Amazon Web Services (AWS) re:Invent 2023! As a Diamond sponsor, we thoroughly enjoyed supporting our partner AWS at this flagship event and conversing with so many individuals from around the world who are interested in Elastic®.

On the heels of the event and with the holiday season upon us, we thought now would be a great time to share a blog post covering our highlights at AWS re:Invent and our extensive collaboration with AWS over the past year.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltbfd79ed3edce8588/657877cec7b407f848ad7f04/blog-elastic-aws-reinvent-jam.png,blog-elastic-aws-reinvent-jam.pngPresenting innovations at breakout sessions,
We held two Breakout Sessions covering pioneering technologies.

Elastic Distinguished Architect Micha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm,Austin Jones,Jennifer Jarrad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.11.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-11-3-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 8.11.3 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.11.3 over 8.11.2 and 8.10.x releases.
The 8.11.3 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security advisory for more details.

For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.

The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.16 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-16-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-16-released"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 7.17.16 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.16 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
The 7.17.16 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security advisory for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Buttner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Podman and HashiCorp Nomad integration matures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/red-hat-podman-and-hashicorp-nomad-integration-matures</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/red-hat-podman-and-hashicorp-nomad-integration-matures"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improvements in the integration of Red Hat Podman and HashiCorp Nomad make it suitable for high-value applications and workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at NeurIPS 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/google-at-neurips-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/google-at-neurips-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T14:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Catherine Armato, Program Manager, Google




This week the 37th annual Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS 2023), the biggest machine learning conference of the year, kicks off in New Orleans, LA. Google is proud to be a Diamond Level sponsor of NeurIPS this year and will have a strong presence with >170 accepted papers, two keynote talks, and additional contributions to the broader research community through organizational support and involvement in >20 workshops and tutorials. Google is also proud to be a Platinum Sponsor for both the Women in Machine Learning and LatinX in AI workshops. We look forward to sharing some of our extensive ML research and expanding our partnership with the broader ML research community.



Attending for NeurIPS 2023 in per…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sparsity-preserving differentially private training]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/sparsity-preserving-differentially.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/sparsity-preserving-differentially.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yangsibo Huang, Research Intern, Google Research; Chiyuan Zhang, Research Scientist, Google Research





Large embedding models have emerged as a fundamental tool for various applications in recommendation systems [1, 2] and natural language processing [3, 4, 5]. Such models enable the integration of non-numerical data into deep learning models by mapping categorical or string-valued input attributes with large vocabularies to fixed-length representation vectors using embedding layers. These models are widely deployed in personalized recommendation systems and achieve state-of-the-art performance in language tasks, such as  language modeling, sentiment analysis, and question answering. In many such scenarios, privacy is an equally important feature when deploying those models. A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrading GitHub.com to MySQL 8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-07-upgrading-github-com-to-mysql-8-0/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-upgrading-github-com-to-mysql-8-0/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub uses MySQL to store vast amounts of relational data. This is the story of how we seamlessly upgraded our production fleet to MySQL 8.0.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-upgrading-github-com-to-mysql-8-0/">Upgrading GitHub.com to MySQL 8.0</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From macOS runners to secure deployments, what’s new from GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-07-from-macos-runners-to-secure-deployments-whats-new-from-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-from-macos-runners-to-secure-deployments-whats-new-from-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Read a roundup of the exciting, new innovation coming from GitHub Actions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-from-macos-runners-to-secure-deployments-whats-new-from-github-actions/">From macOS runners to secure deployments, what’s new from GitHub Actions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.7 improves Vault and Consul integrations, adds NUMA support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.7 — now generally available — introduces improved workload identity, improved Vault and Consul integrations, NUMA support, Nomad actions, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[While you sleep, Automate resolving Dynatrace problem alerts and report them to ServiceNow!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/while-you-sleep-automate-resolving-dynatrace-problem-alerts-and-report-them-to-servicenow</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/while-you-sleep-automate-resolving-dynatrace-problem-alerts-and-report-them-to-servicenow"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating observability tools with automation is paramount in the realm of modern IT operations, as it fosters a symbiotic relationship between visibility and efficiency. Observability tools provide deep insights into the performance, health, and behavior of complex systems, enabling organizations to proactively identify and rectify issues before they escalate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bforrest@redhat.com (Ben Forrester)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VALID: A perceptually validated virtual avatar library for inclusion and diversity]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/valid-perceptually-validated-virtual.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/valid-perceptually-validated-virtual.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mar Gonzalez-Franco, Research Scientist, Google AR & VR


In the last decade, interdisciplinary scientists have dedicated a significant amount of effort to better understand the use of avatars, and have made many interesting observations, including the capacity of the users to embody their avatar (i.e., the illusion that the avatar body is their own) and the self-avatar follower effect, which creates a binding between the actions of the avatar and the user strong enough that the avatar can actually affect user behavior. 



The use of avatars in experiments isn’t just about how users will interact and behave in VR spaces, but also about discovering the limits of human perception and neuroscience. In fact, some VR social experiments often rely on recreating scenarios that can’t be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Innovation Graph Q2 2023 Data Release]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-12-07-github-innovation-graph-q2-2023-data-release/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-github-innovation-graph-q2-2023-data-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T16:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover the latest trends and insights on public software development activity on GitHub with the release of Q2 2023 data for the Innovation Graph.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2023-12-07-github-innovation-graph-q2-2023-data-release/">GitHub Innovation Graph Q2 2023 Data Release</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women in Tech podcast: Transforming tech education]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/women-in-tech-podcast-transforming-tech-education</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/women-in-tech-podcast-transforming-tech-education"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Episode 2 of the HashiCast: Women in Tech podcast features Deborah Carter, a catalyst for change working to reshape technology education while advocating for diversity and inclusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at EMNLP 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/google-at-emnlp-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/google-at-emnlp-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T01:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Malaya Jules, Program Manager, Google





Google is proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of Empirical Methods in Natural Language Processing (EMNLP 2023), a premier annual conference, which is being held this week in Sentosa, Singapore. Google has a strong presence at this year’s conference with over 65 accepted papers and active involvement in 11 workshops and tutorials. Google is also happy to be a Major Sponsor for the Widening NLP workshop (WiNLP), which aims to highlight global representations of people, perspectives, and cultures in AI and ML. We look forward to sharing some of our extensive NLP research and expanding our partnership with the broader research community.



We hope you’ll visit the Google booth to chat with researchers who are actively pursuing the latest innovati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new quantum algorithm for classical mechanics with an exponential speedup]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/a-new-quantum-algorithm-for-classical.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/a-new-quantum-algorithm-for-classical.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T22:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Robin Kothari and Rolando Somma, Research Scientists, Google Research, Quantum AI Team




Quantum computers promise to solve some problems exponentially faster than classical computers, but there are only a handful of examples with such a dramatic speedup, such as Shor’s factoring algorithm and quantum simulation. Of those few examples, the majority of them involve simulating physical systems that are inherently quantum mechanical — a natural application for quantum computers. But what about simulating systems that are not inherently quantum? Can quantum computers offer an exponential advantage for this?

 

In “Exponential quantum speedup in simulating coupled classical oscillators”, published in Physical Review X (PRX) and presented at the Symposium on Foundations of Computer …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary report optimization in the Privacy Sandbox Attribution Reporting API]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/summary-report-optimization-in-privacy.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/summary-report-optimization-in-privacy.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hidayet Aksu, Software Engineer, and Adam Sealfon, Research Scientist, Google





In recent years, the Privacy Sandbox initiative was launched to explore responsible ways for advertisers to measure the effectiveness of their campaigns, by aiming to deprecate third-party cookies (subject to resolving any competition concerns with the UK’s Competition and Markets Authority). Cookies are small pieces of data containing user preferences that websites store on a user’s device; they can be used to provide a better browsing experience (e.g., allowing users to automatically sign in) and to serve relevant content or ads. The Privacy Sandbox attempts to address concerns around the use of cookies for tracking browsing data across the web by providing a privacy-preserving alternative.



Ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp wins the Palo Alto Networks 2023 Global Technology Partner of the Year award]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-the-palo-alto-networks-2023-global-technology-partner-of-the-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-the-palo-alto-networks-2023-global-technology-partner-of-the-year"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp and Palo Alto Networks celebrate our ongoing partnership protecting customers with infrastructure security automation for the second year in a row.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsupervised speech-to-speech translation from monolingual data]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/12/unsupervised-speech-to-speech.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/12/unsupervised-speech-to-speech.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eliya Nachmani, Research Scientist, and Michelle Tadmor Ramanovich, Software Engineer, Google Research






Speech-to-speech translation (S2ST) is a type of machine translation that converts spoken language from one language to another. This technology has the potential to break down language barriers and facilitate communication between people from different cultures and backgrounds. 




Previously, we introduced Translatotron 1 and Translatotron 2, the first ever models that were able to directly translate speech between two languages. However they were trained in supervised settings with parallel speech data. The scarcity of parallel speech data is a major challenge in this field, so much that most public datasets are semi- or fully-synthesized from text. This adds additiona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Work Items in Visual Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68130</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/work-items-in-visual-studio/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T14:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several years ago, with the introduction of Visual Studio 2019, we launched a completely revamped work item experience. This updated view operates entirely on REST, replacing the deprecated SOAP APIs utilized in the legacy version. Although Visual Studio 2022 still includes the option to revert to the legacy view,
The post Work Items in Visual Studio appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use AWS Fault Injection Service to demonstrate multi-region and multi-AZ application resilience]]></title>
        <id>b5f470ba74c346ed6f525a2a5e92522dc46cd4d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-aws-fault-injection-service-to-demonstrate-multi-region-and-multi-az-application-resilience/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Fault Injection Service (FIS) helps you to put chaos engineering into practice at scale. Today we are launching new scenarios that will let you demonstrate that your applications perform as intended if an AWS Availability Zone experiences a full power interruption or connectivity from one AWS region to another is lost. You can use […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zonal autoshift – Automatically shift your traffic away from Availability Zones when we detect potential issues]]></title>
        <id>f677c6705f71814fd999f39b325af14c6e9289e9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/zonal-autoshift-automatically-shift-your-traffic-away-from-availability-zones-when-we-detect-potential-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re launching zonal autoshift, a new capability of Amazon Route 53 Application Recovery Controller that you can enable to automatically and safely shift your workload’s traffic away from an Availability Zone when AWS identifies a potential failure affecting that Availability Zone and shift it back once the failure is resolved. When deploying resilient applications, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IDE extension for AWS Application Composer enhances visual modern applications development with AI-generated IaC]]></title>
        <id>66dd6400ac1e7d9ba598572e5cd829f82e8b6c05</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/ide-extension-for-aws-application-composer-enhances-visual-modern-applications-development-with-ai-generated-iac/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to share the integrated development environment (IDE) extension for AWS Application Composer. Now you can use AWS Application Composer directly in your IDE to visually build modern applications and iteratively develop your infrastructure as code templates with Amazon CodeWhisperer. Announced as preview at AWS re:Invent 2022 and generally available in March 2023, Application Composer is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Studio adds web-based interface, Code Editor, flexible workspaces, and streamlines user onboarding]]></title>
        <id>8202e0701d0edec7189fd74a2684035983c2a23f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-studio-adds-web-based-interface-code-editor-flexible-workspaces-and-streamlines-user-onboarding/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing an improved Amazon SageMaker Studio experience! The new SageMaker Studio web-based interface loads faster and provides consistent access to your preferred integrated development environment (IDE) and SageMaker resources and tooling, irrespective of your IDE choice. In addition to JupyterLab and RStudio, SageMaker Studio now includes a fully managed Code Editor based […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three new capabilities for Amazon Inspector broaden the realm of vulnerability scanning for workloads]]></title>
        <id>dbd84d0e15dc49a513d11dc8814a2ace24c64aef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/three-new-capabilities-for-amazon-inspector-broaden-the-realm-of-vulnerability-scanning-for-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon Inspector adds three new capabilities to increase the realm of possibilities when scanning your workloads for software vulnerabilities: Amazon Inspector introduces a new set of open source plugins and an API allowing you to assess your container images for software vulnerabilities at build time directly from your continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudWatch Application Signals for automatic instrumentation of your applications (preview)]]></title>
        <id>1d6092ef569153d497e5ee163eee98821d30bf12</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-cloudwatch-application-signals-for-automatic-instrumentation-of-your-applications-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the challenges with distributed systems is that they are made up of many interdependent services, which add a degree of complexity when you are trying to monitor their performance. Determining which services and APIs are experiencing high latencies or degraded availability requires manually putting together telemetry signals. This can result in time and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New myApplications in the AWS Management Console simplifies managing your application resources]]></title>
        <id>ec4fc257d1c6efc31dbdad1cfa3fa78ebe223b5a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-myapplications-in-the-aws-management-console-simplifies-managing-your-application-resources/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the general availability of myApplications supporting application operations, a new set of capabilities that help you get started with your applications on AWS, operate them with less effort, and move faster at scale. With myApplications in the AWS Management Console, you can more easily manage and monitor the cost, health, security […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily deploy SaaS products with new Quick Launch in AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>165f32cc180f9fa0cf1f36aff4e46a246fa890b6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/easily-deploy-saas-products-with-new-quick-launch-in-aws-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are excited to announce the general availability of SaaS Quick Launch, a new feature in AWS Marketplace that makes it easy and secure to deploy SaaS products. Before SaaS Quick Launch, configuring and launching third-party SaaS products could be time-consuming and costly, especially in certain categories like security and monitoring. Some products require […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All of Netflix’s HDR video streaming is now dynamically optimized]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e9e0cb15f2ba</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/all-of-netflixs-hdr-video-streaming-is-now-dynamically-optimized-e9e0cb15f2ba?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by  Aditya Mavlankar, Zhi Li, Lukáš Krasula and Christos Bampis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Package and deploy models faster with new tools and guided workflows in Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>9dfa4013fdeb3ce3b8c9cd5ded8657c6f07139cc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/package-and-deploy-models-faster-with-new-tools-and-guided-workflows-in-amazon-sagemaker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that Amazon SageMaker now comes with an improved model deployment experience to help you deploy traditional machine learning (ML) models and foundation models (FMs) faster. As a data scientist or ML practitioner, you can now use the new ModelBuilder class in the SageMaker Python SDK to package models, perform local inference […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use natural language to explore and prepare data with a new capability of Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>52022c89be15e7efe7a0e5d886a1b76e6bb36028</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-natural-language-to-explore-and-prepare-data-with-a-new-capability-of-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to introduce the ability to use natural language instructions in Amazon SageMaker Canvas to explore, visualize, and transform data for machine learning (ML). SageMaker Canvas now supports using foundation model-(FM) powered natural language instructions to complement its comprehensive data preparation capabilities for data exploration, analysis, visualization, and transformation. Using natural language instructions, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker adds new inference capabilities to help reduce foundation model deployment costs and latency]]></title>
        <id>070abf1c19c0afcc710d7953b53d84a40e4e4b82</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-adds-new-inference-capabilities-to-help-reduce-foundation-model-deployment-costs-and-latency/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing new Amazon SageMaker inference capabilities that can help you optimize deployment costs and reduce latency. With the new inference capabilities, you can deploy one or more foundation models (FMs) on the same SageMaker endpoint and control how many accelerators and how much memory is reserved for each FM. This helps to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage foundation models for business analysis at scale with Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>286f7dd53aa2b49a2bbca8dcddcd42842c920920</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/leverage-foundation-models-for-business-analysis-at-scale-with-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m excited to introduce a new capability in Amazon SageMaker Canvas to use foundation models (FMs) from Amazon Bedrock and Amazon SageMaker Jumpstart through a no-code experience. This new capability makes it easier for you to evaluate and generate responses from FMs for your specific use case with high accuracy. Every business has its […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing highly durable Amazon OpenSearch Service clusters with 30% price/performance improvement]]></title>
        <id>9254592bff3a8ff942fbbd9434437e0a80455403</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-highly-durable-amazon-opensearch-service-clusters-with-30-price-performance-improvement/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the new OR1 instances to create Amazon OpenSearch Service clusters that use Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) for primary storage. You can ingest, store, index, and access just about any imaginable amount of data, while also enjoying a 30% price/performance improvement over existing instance types, eleven nines of data durability, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Clarify makes it easier to evaluate and select foundation models (preview)]]></title>
        <id>8eb45aec03e2c9174185648ea2e15d148920732c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-clarify-makes-it-easier-to-evaluate-and-select-foundation-models-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to share that Amazon SageMaker Clarify now supports foundation model (FM) evaluation (preview). As a data scientist or machine learning (ML) engineer, you can now use SageMaker Clarify to evaluate, compare, and select FMs in minutes based on metrics such as accuracy, robustness, creativity, factual knowledge, bias, and toxicity. This new capability adds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your Terraform development with Amazon CodeWhisperer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerate-your-terraform-development-with-amazon-codewhisperer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerate-your-terraform-development-with-amazon-codewhisperer"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improve the developer experience writing Terraform code with the help of generative AI powered by Amazon CodeWhisperer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第242話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755511181824</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755511181824"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform delivers launch-day support for Amazon S3 Express]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-delivers-launch-day-support-for-amazon-s3-express</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-delivers-launch-day-support-for-amazon-s3-express"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s Terraform provider for AWS now enables users to manage their S3 Express buckets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updated: Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68117</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-1-rtw-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[12/5 Update: There is a known issue where the Agent version does not update after upgrading to Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 and using Update Agent in Agent Pool configuration. We are currently working on a patch to resolve this issue and will share updates in the Developer Community as we make progress.
The post Updated: Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: New Experimental Features in Gateway API v1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/28/gateway-api-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/28/gateway-api-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Candace Holman (Red Hat), Dave Protasowski (VMware), Gaurav K Ghildiyal (Google), John Howard (Google), Simone Rodigari (IBM)
Recently, the Gateway API announced its v1.0 GA release, marking a huge milestone for the project.
Along with stabilizing some of the core functionality in the API, a number of exciting new experimental features have been added.
Backend TLS Policy
BackendTLSPolicy is a new Gateway API type used for specifying the TLS configuration of the connection from the Gateway to backend Pods via the Service API object.
It is specified as a Direct PolicyAttachment without defaults or overrides, applied to a Service that accesses a backend, where the BackendTLSPolicy resides in the same namespace as the Service to which it is applied.
All Gateway API Routes that point t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform extension for VS Code adds Terraform Cloud view]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-extension-for-vs-code-adds-terraform-cloud-view</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-extension-for-vs-code-adds-terraform-cloud-view"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new view in the HashiCorp Terraform extension for Visual Studio Code shows your Terraform Cloud workspaces and runs, reducing context-switching.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at re:Invent 2023: A year of collaboration with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-re-invent-2023-a-year-of-collaboration-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-re-invent-2023-a-year-of-collaboration-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recap of HashiCorp infrastructure and security news and developments on AWS from the past year, from self-service provisioning to fighting secrets sprawl and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault benchmark testing tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-benchmark-testing-tool</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-benchmark-testing-tool"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault benchmark is an open source tool that tests the performance of HashiCorp Vault auth methods and secrets engines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Original Research: MIT CODE 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9340b879176a</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/netflix-original-research-mit-code-2023-9340b879176a?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix was thrilled to be the premier sponsor for the 2nd year in a row at the 2023 Conference on Digital Experimentation (CODE@MIT).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gain operator confidence with HCP Consul Central observability features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/gain-operator-confidence-with-hcp-consul-central-observability-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/gain-operator-confidence-with-hcp-consul-central-observability-features"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul Central’s new observability features were recently used by a customer to help troubleshoot an issue with assistance from HashiCorp engineers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform stacks, explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-stacks-explained</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-stacks-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform stacks simplify provisioning and managing resources at scale, reducing the time and overhead of managing infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing resources with the Terraform AWS Cloud Control provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Cloud Control provider — built around the AWS Cloud Control API — is designed to bring new services to HashiCorp Terraform faster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Causal Machine Learning for Creative Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4b0ce22a8a96</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/causal-machine-learning-for-creative-insights-4b0ce22a8a96?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T01:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A framework to identify the causal impact of successful visual components.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/24/sig-testing-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/24/sig-testing-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sandipan Panda
Welcome to another edition of the SIG spotlight blog series, where we
highlight the incredible work being done by various Special Interest
Groups (SIGs) within the Kubernetes project. In this edition, we turn
our attention to SIG Testing,
a group interested in effective testing of Kubernetes and automating
away project toil. SIG Testing focus on creating and running tools and
infrastructure that make it easier for the community to write and run
tests, and to contribute, analyze and act upon test results.
To gain some insights into SIG Testing, Sandipan
Panda spoke with Michelle Shepardson,
a senior software engineer at Google and a chair of SIG Testing, and
Patrick Ohly, a software engineer and architect at
Intel and a SIG Testing Tech Lead.
Meet the contributors
San…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closing the skills and talent divide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/closing-the-skills-and-talent-divide</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/closing-the-skills-and-talent-divide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the HashiCast: Navigating the Cloud for C-Suites podcast addresses how to close the skills gap. Guest James Footman, Head of Talent for EMEA at HashiCorp, highlights the key takeaways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving simulations of clouds and their effects on climate]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/improving-simulations-of-clouds-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/improving-simulations-of-clouds-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tapio Schneider, Visiting Researcher, and Yi-fan Chen, Engineering Lead, Google Research




Today’s climate models successfully capture broad global warming trends. However, because of uncertainties about processes that are small in scale yet globally important, such as clouds and ocean turbulence, these models’ predictions of upcoming climate changes are not very accurate in detail. For example, predictions of the time by which the global mean surface temperature of Earth will have warmed 2℃, relative to preindustrial times, vary by 40–50 years (a full human generation) among today’s models. As a result, we do not have the accurate and geographically granular predictions we need to plan resilient infrastructure, adapt supply chains to climate disruption, and assess the risks of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>