<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-07-14T02:08:38.909Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-14T02:08:38.909Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Wins Microsoft Azure OSS US Partner of the Year for 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-microsoft-azure-oss-us-partner-of-the-year-for-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-microsoft-azure-oss-us-partner-of-the-year-for-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp has been chosen as the 2022 Microsoft US (MSUS) Partner Award winner OSS on Azure and a 2022 Microsoft OSS on Azure Partner of the Year Award finalist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rewriting Image Captions for Visual Question Answering Data Creation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/rewriting-image-captions-for-visual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/rewriting-image-captions-for-visual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T19:24:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Soravit Beer Changpinyo and Doron Kukliansky‎, Senior Software Engineers, Google Research 
Visual Question Answering (VQA) is a useful machine learning (ML) task that requires a model to answer a visual question about an image. What makes it challenging is its multi-task and open-ended nature; it involves solving multiple technical research questions in computer vision and natural language understanding simultaneously. Yet, progress on this task would enable a wide range of applications, from assisting the blind and the visually-impaired or communicating with robots to enhancing the user’s visual experience with external knowledge. 
Effective and robust VQA systems cannot exist without high-quality, semantically and stylistically diverse large-scale training data of image-questio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When localhost isn't what it seems in Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/when-localhost-isnt-what-it-seems-in-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/when-localhost-isnt-what-it-seems-in-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2  and the advent of automation execution environments, some behaviors are now different for. This blog explains the use case around using localhost and options for sharing data and persistent data storage, for VM-based Ansible Automation Platform 2  deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2022.04.2 is out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=264189</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2022/07/teamcity-2022-04-2-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T12:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re releasing the TeamCity 2022.04.2 update, which focuses on improving performance. TeamCity 2022.04.2 fixes about 50 issues, and here are the most significant improvements that you’ll find in this update: The bundled IntelliJ IDEA has been updated to address the reported Apache software vulnerabilities.  We’ve added fixes to the recently released features, such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Alexandrova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Gruner + Jahr Chose Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58130</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/why-gruner-jahr-chose-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new blog series, we explore the reasons why customers are migrating to Camunda 8. For our first installment of Camunda 8 Early Adopters, we talked to Gruner + Jahr, one of the largest premium magazine publishers in Europe. G+J includes such established (German) print and digital brands as STERN, GEO, BRIGITTE, ESSEN & TRINKEN, and SCHÖNER WOHNEN, as well as younger brands such as CHEFKOCH, BARBARA, BEEF, 11FREUNDE. In addition to the numerous print and digital media offerings, G+J offers products and licenses such as the SCHÖNER WOHNEN collection. The digital business contributes more than half of revenues and is exhibiting continued strong growth. Indeed, the company’s digital products lead the rankings in all publishing segments, from news...
The post Why Gruner + Jahr Chose Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Schroth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intentional design (and complicated systems)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42752</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/702628287/0/sethsblog~Intentional-design-and-complicated-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T08:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intentional design is the most productive kind. It begins with “who’s it for?” and “what’s it for?” as foundational questions. Along the way, complicated systems muddy design because there are so many “who”s to answer to. Take this simple product found at a Hilton hotel, designed and sold by a division of Sysco, the giant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Native 0.12.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/13/spring-native-0-12-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/13/spring-native-0-12-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Native 0.12.1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release.

This release includes 15 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades to Spring Boot 2.7.1 and Native Build Tools 0.9.13. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 information and operational technology trends making waves in manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-information-and-operational-technology-trends-in-manufacturing</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-information-and-operational-technology-trends-in-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Find out what's top of mind for manufacturing companies as they actively drive IT and OT convergence for increased productivity, faster innovation, and a more trustworthy customer experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search and replicate data between your Elastic Cloud and on-prem deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-and-replicate-data-between-your-elastic-cloud-and-on-prem-deployments</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-and-replicate-data-between-your-elastic-cloud-and-on-prem-deployments"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers can now replicate data from on-prem to cloud (and vice versa) and search data across their cloud and on-prem clusters, all from a single search interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 information and operational technology trends making waves in manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-information-and-operational-technology-trends-in-manufacturing</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-information-and-operational-technology-trends-in-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The convergence of information technologies (IT) and operational technologies (OT) sits at the core of the Industry 4.0 vision (industrial Internet of Things). This gradual convergence began more than a decade ago, and according to a recent McKinsey study, investments in industrialization paid rich dividends to the early adopters of Industry 4.0.*

But this process changed dramatically with the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic, which created a massive, multiyear ripple effect on worldwide economies, forcing manufacturers to reevaluate their priorities.

How are manufacturers adapting to today’s industrial world? Here are their top three priorities as they accelerate IT/OT convergence for increased productivity, faster innovation, and a more trustworthy customer experience.

[Related articl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search and replicate data between your Elastic Cloud and on-prem deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-and-replicate-data-between-your-elastic-cloud-and-on-prem-deployments</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-and-replicate-data-between-your-elastic-cloud-and-on-prem-deployments"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are pleased to announce the general availability of cross-cluster search (CCS) and cross-cluster replication (CCR) for your Elasticsearch clusters across any deployment environment. Starting today, you can easily search and replicate data between Elasticsearch clusters, even when they reside in different environments, such as on-premises, public cloud, as well as hybrid and multi-cloud.

In this blog, we’ll review some of the fundamentals regarding CCS and CCR. We’ll also take a look at how to apply this functionality to your Elasticsearch, Observability, and Security use cases.

[Related article: Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud 8.3: Search & replicate across any cluster]

Cross-cluster search
With this new release, CCS empowers you with a single view of your data — across all yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Camera]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2645/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2645/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/the_best_camera.png" title="The best camera is the one at L2." alt="The best camera is the one at L2." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Content archived for Azure DevOps previous versions]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64684</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/content-archived-for-azure-devops-previous-versions/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T21:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​In April of this year, we completed a major project to archive older versions of our content. 
The post Content archived for Azure DevOps previous versions appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[July patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64626</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/july-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T18:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
In Test Runs APIs, the continuation token being returned was greater than the “maxLastUpdatedDate” value that was specified.
The post July patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisiting Mask Transformer from a Clustering Perspective]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/revisiting-mask-transformer-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/revisiting-mask-transformer-from.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Qihang Yu, Student Researcher, and Liang-Chieh Chen, Research Scientist, Google Research 
Panoptic segmentation is a computer vision problem that serves as a core task for many real-world applications. Due to its complexity, previous work often divides panoptic segmentation into semantic segmentation (assigning semantic labels, such as “person” and “sky”, to every pixel in an image) and instance segmentation (identifying and segmenting only countable objects, such as “pedestrians” and “cars”, in an image), and further divides it into several sub-tasks. Each sub-task is processed individually, and extra modules are applied to merge the results from each sub-task stage. This process is not only complex, but it also introduces many hand-designed priors when processing sub-tasks and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Detect and Resolve Issues Quickly with Log Anomaly Detection and Recommendations from Amazon DevOps Guru]]></title>
        <id>f8f3e67b2d22e5494e1d6a32842aa2c9ac55f021</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-detect-and-resolve-issues-quickly-with-log-anomaly-detection-and-recommendations-from-amazon-devops-guru/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T15:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing a new feature, Log Anomaly Detection and Recommendations for Amazon DevOps Guru. With this feature, you can find anomalies throughout relevant logs within your app, and get targeted recommendations to resolve issues. Here’s a quick look at this feature: AWS launched DevOps Guru, a fully managed AIOps platform service, in December […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift Serverless – Now Generally Available with New Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>ab73365aa62a13a08dcff00f5a2037ca5ae573ee</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-redshift-serverless-now-generally-available-with-new-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T15:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year at re:Invent, we introduced the preview of Amazon Redshift Serverless, a serverless option of Amazon Redshift that lets you analyze data at any scale without having to manage data warehouse infrastructure. You just need to load and query your data, and you pay only for what you use. This allows more companies to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Cloud WAN : A Managed WAN Service]]></title>
        <id>e70e25bfbed198650cc3b5bd252108ee9fcb14b5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-cloud-wan-a-managed-wan-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T14:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update July 13, 2022 – we have added a list of blog posts and technical resources provided by our partners, in order to provide readers with additional information on this service. I am pleased to announce the availability of AWS Cloud WAN, a new network service that makes it easy to build and operate wide […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 12th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/12/this-week-in-spring-july-12th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/12/this-week-in-spring-july-12th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you? This week I’m writing you from sunny Seattle, Washington, where we’re having our next installment of the SpringOne Tour series. It’s been a ton of fun seeing all these fun and friendly faces again and getting to see people, many of whom I haven’t seen since before the pandemic! I’ve also had a lot of fun seeing some friends from some of the big cloud companies here, Microsoft and AWS. It’s always interesting to learn how people are using the latest and greatest from Spring to build amazing systems and software targeting these cloud platforms.

We’ve got a lot to cover this week so let’s dive right into it!


  
In last week’s podcast, I talked to Kubernetes contributor and fellow Tanzu Developer Advocate Leigh Capili

  
Distributed Tracing With OpenTelemetry, Spring Cloud Sleuth, Kafka, and Jaeger

  
Ingress vs. Load Balancer in Kubernetes

  
Instantiating Multiple Beans of the Same Class with Spring Annotations

  
Curious about when and why to use Java 14 Records vs. Lombok? Check out this article

  
I put together this little example , thanks to Reactor lead Simon Baslé, showing how to handle pagination with the expand operator in Project Reactor: Pagination in a Reactive Application. It looks at how to eleganrly expand the contents of a reactive stream as new data (in a data pagination scenario) becomes available.

  
Spring Shell 2.1.0-RC1 is now available

  
Pushing a Docker Image to a Self-Hosted Registry

  
Spring for Apache Kafka 2.9 Release Candidate Available

  
This Apache Maven Survival Guide is quite interesting, to me at least!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easier when you know]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43236</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/702523322/0/sethsblog~Its-easier-when-you-know/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone is going to ask you. They probably already have. A co-worker, a boss, a politician, a kid… they’ll ask you about sustainability, the climate, investments, choices to be made about the future. This is the Cliff’s Notes and guidebook for that moment. We make choices every day. Choices about what to buy, whether to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.2 EAP 4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=264198</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/07/12/datagrip-2022-2-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T09:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! Here’s what we improved in build #4 of this DataGrip 2022.2 EAP: DBE-15830: Columns can be hidden and unhidden in the Columns List without any issues. DBE-15790: [Apache Spark] Identifiers that begin with an underscore are now recognized correctly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58431</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-platform-8-1-0-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3. If you’d like to get started with Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3 right away, you can sign up for a free trial now. Create Process Instance Starting at User-Defined Elements An often requested feature is now available as a preview with Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3: create a process instance starting at user-defined elements. When creating a process instance through the CreateProcessInstance RPC, the process instance is started at the default none start event. For testing purposes, you may want to start at one (or multiple) of the other elements. This feature is now available through both the CreateProcessInstance RPC and the CreateProcessInstanceWithResult RPC. It is available for use in the Zeebe Java client...
The post Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58439</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-preview1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1. Camunda Optimize provides business activity monitoring for workflows, supporting continuous process improvement by providing transparency into your automated workflows and decisions. Business-friendly reports, dashboards, and alerts make it possible to identify process bottlenecks, improve end-to-end processes, and evaluate the success of your process automation initiative. If you’re a user of Camunda 7 – Enterprise Edition, you can download the Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 release right away with your customer credentials. If not, start your free 30-day trial of Camunda Platform 8, which includes Optimize. What’s New? Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 makes the process overview more readable, introduces one-click collection and dashboard creation, and provides an advanced look at a feature that lets you...
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58401</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-desktop-modeler-5-1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce the release of Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.1. This release focuses on providing a smooth and intuitive modeling experience through several minor and major enhancements, such as the new multi-select context pad.
The post Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Modeler Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58296</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-automation-platform-7-18-0-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.18. 
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building resilience for applications and services with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-resilience-for-applications-and-services-with-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-resilience-for-applications-and-services-with-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recently concluded third-party survey managed and analyzed by Socratic Technologies, over 1,400 Elastic customers shared their observability experiences. Take a look at the key takeaways from the survey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building resilience for applications and services with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-resilience-for-applications-and-services-with-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-resilience-for-applications-and-services-with-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Correlating data across multiple silos and applications to derive meaningful and actionable insights is an ongoing struggle. These challenges are only set to increase as high-speed connectivity becomes more ubiquitous and enables  data-heavy, digital experiences. 

In a recent third-party survey managed and analyzed by Socratic Technologies, over 1,400 Elastic customers shared their observability experiences, revealing quantifiable benefits that directly contributed to business outcomes. Elastic Observability is the world’s most widely deployed observability platform, built on the proven Elastic Stack — to break down silos and enable near real-time actionable insights. 

[Download the complete report for Elastic Observability.]

66% improved MTTx metrics brought by unified visibility
Cus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – July 11, 2022]]></title>
        <id>29f6affb960d165cfdeb50c0f58bea5e4ec5c744</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-july-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T18:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! In France, we know summer has started when you see the Tour de France bike race on TV or in a city nearby. This year, the tour stopped in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keyboard navigation mode in dotTrace 2022.1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=258032</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/07/11/keyboard-navigation-mode-in-dottrace-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T14:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With each dotTrace release, we primarily add features related to profiling, like support for new frameworks, improvements in data collection or analysis, and others. In this release, it’s not about profiling, but about the way you communicate with desktop applications.  There are a lot of Vim fans among software developers who prefer to use the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexey Totin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraforming clouds with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/terraforming-clouds-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/terraforming-clouds-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations use Terraform for quick infrastructure provisioning every day, but if we combine it with the power of Ansible, we can see that it builds into an efficient workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2 Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=263435</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/07/phpstorm-2022-2-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T10:34:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2 Beta is now available. Below is a roundup of the most notable updates included in the upcoming 2022.2 release. The links will take you to the EAP posts published over the last few months, which contain detailed descriptions of each feature: New features Mockery support Rector support Highlighting failed test assertions Create enums […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Knock, knock”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43340</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/702380374/0/sethsblog~Knock-knock/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T08:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The purpose of most communication isn’t to completely explain yourself. Too often, we get stuck relieving tension, making our case and closing the door on the discussion. The purpose is to open the door to interaction, learning and action. “Who’s there?” is a fine response to hope for. Communication is a process, not an event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[July 1 TeamCity Cloud Outage Postmortem]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=263841</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2022/07/july-1-teamcity-cloud-outage-postmortem/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T08:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 1, 2022 TeamCity Cloud experienced an outage that prevented our customers from running builds on build agents hosted by JetBrains. Here is the summary of the incident and the remediation actions. Affected subsystems: Hosted agents Billing system (credits calculation, new server assignments) Timeline (CEST): 3:05 PM – An incident was detected on Production […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yegor Naumov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 ways to optimize your Elastic Cloud costs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-ways-to-optimize-your-elastic-cloud-costs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-ways-to-optimize-your-elastic-cloud-costs"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud comes with many benefits, including the ability to lower your total cost of ownership. Learn the top five ways you can optimize your cloud cost while maintaining performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanda Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 ways to optimize your Elastic Cloud costs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-ways-to-optimize-your-elastic-cloud-costs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-ways-to-optimize-your-elastic-cloud-costs"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Cloud is the best and most cost effective way to consume Elastic. If you’re already using or are considering Elastic Cloud, here are some recommendations on optimizing costs.

Elastic Cloud uses resource-based pricing, where you pay for the infrastructure resources consumed to run the Elastic Stack capabilities for your use case. Therefore, the best way to optimize Elastic Cloud costs is to streamline resource consumption. 

You can reduce your resource consumption by leveraging our global presence and several cost-saving capabilities. Here are the top five recommendations: 

[Related article: How does Elastic Cloud pricing work?]

1) Use searchable snapshots and data tiers to optimize storage costs
You can optimize storage, search performance, and depth of insight from the data …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanda Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fMRI Billboard]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2644/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2644/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/fmri_billboard.png" title="[other side] If the first word of an instruction you're given starts with the same letter as your crush's name, for that step imagine the experimenter is your crush." alt="[other side] If the first word of an instruction you're given starts with the same letter as your crush's name, for that step imagine the experimenter is your crush." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best [insert] ever]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43223</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/702257770/0/sethsblog~Best-insert-ever/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a trap worth avoiding. When we examine our life experiences, the ones that stand out are usually about change. Either we were changed or we helped someone else get to where they sought to go. And change is fleeting. And change changes us. We can’t step in the same river twice, because the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With/for/to]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42285</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/702153130/0/sethsblog~Withforto/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T08:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of our interactions fall into one of these categories. Our strategy for the game involves doing something to the other team. Many service businesses are aligned around the idea of doing things for their patients or customers. And long-term mutually beneficial relationships are built around with. Trouble happens when one party expects a different […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​Deep Hierarchical Planning from Pixels]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/deep-hierarchical-planning-from-pixels.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/deep-hierarchical-planning-from-pixels.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T18:25:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Danijar Hafner, Student Researcher, Google Research 
Research into how artificial agents can make decisions has evolved rapidly through advances in deep reinforcement learning. Compared to generative ML models like GPT-3 and Imagen, artificial agents can directly influence their environment through actions, such as moving a robot arm based on camera inputs or clicking a button in a web browser. While artificial agents have the potential to be increasingly helpful to people, current methods are held back by the need to receive detailed feedback in the form of frequently provided rewards to learn successful strategies. For example, despite large computational budgets, even powerful programs such as AlphaGo are limited to a few hundred moves until receiving their next reward. 
In co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 Beta Is Here With Remote Development Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=261792</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/07/webstorm-2022-2-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T16:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 has reached the Beta milestone! You can upgrade to the latest build using the Toolbox App or from our website. To catch up on what has already been implemented, check out our previous EAP blog posts. DOWNLOAD WEBSTORM 2022.2 Beta We’d like to thank everyone who has tried the EAP builds and shared […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Office gossip]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42319</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/702055316/0/sethsblog~Office-gossip/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T08:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans gossipped before we figured out fire, housing or farming. It’s built into our culture and possibly our DNA. Gossip informs culture and can influence connection and hierarchies. And in many communities, it’s destructive. If office gossip is benefitting you and the people you work with, good for you. But if office gossip is leading […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get visibility into AWS Lambda serverless functions with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of Elastic Observability’s new capabilities around monitoring AWS Lambda functions in your cloud-native environment. Get detailed insights into your distributed, microservices architecture and applications through our APM capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akhilesh Pokhariyal,Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You have more ways to bake this cake: Bring your own Enterprise Search connector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bring-your-own-enterprise-search-connector</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bring-your-own-enterprise-search-connector"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Enterprise Search Connectors framework was created to help users bring their own connectors, or customize the ones that already exist. Read on to learn how to implement this framework, using GitLab as an example.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryna Cherniavska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get visibility into AWS Lambda serverless functions with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Adoption of AWS Lambda functions in cloud-native applications has increased exponentially over the past few years. Serverless functions, such as the AWS Lambda service, provide a high level of abstraction from the underlying infrastructure and orchestration, given these tasks are managed by the cloud provider. Software development teams can then focus on the implementation of business and application logic. 
Some additional benefits include billing for serverless functions based on the actual compute and memory resources consumed, along with automatic on-demand scaling. One difficulty in using serverless functions, however, is making them observable in the wider end-to-end microservices architecture context. 
,Elastic APM for AWS Lambda: The architecture
In a previous blog post, we showe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akhilesh Pokhariyal,Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You have more ways to bake this cake: Bring your own Enterprise Search connector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bring-your-own-enterprise-search-connector</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bring-your-own-enterprise-search-connector"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The Elastic Enterprise Search team is working on an exciting new project: Elastic Enterprise Search Connectors framework. It appeared in version 8.2 as a Technical Preview, and it has been significantly expanded in 8.3.

Elastic Enterprise Search, and specifically Workplace Search, is a solution that helps harness the power of Elasticsearch to search over company documents. The documents may come from a variety of sources, and the primary means of ingesting data into Workplace Search are connectors, which are easy-to-use, no-code, GUI-driven features that makes ingesting data a breeze. 

Before we dive into the details, here’s an important vocabulary to be familiar with:

Content source - data indexed into Elastic Enterprise Search and backed by a third-party service like GitHub, GoogleD…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryna Cherniavska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmologist Gift]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2643/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2643/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/cosmologist_gift.png" title="These neutrinos were freshly produced by a local source just 8 minutes ago" alt="These neutrinos were freshly produced by a local source just 8 minutes ago" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M1 Mac Instances]]></title>
        <id>d02cbfaaaed8a473decb31bee87fb99c5ce2448d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-m1-mac-instances/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T20:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, during the re:Invent 2021 conference, I wrote a blog post to announce the preview of EC2 M1 Mac instances. I know many of you requested access to the preview, and we did our best but could not satisfy everybody. However, the wait is over. I have the pleasure of announcing the general availability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Kubernetes contributor and fellow Tanzu Developer Advocate Leigh Capili]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-contributor-and-fellow-tanzu-developer-advocate-leigh-capili</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-contributor-and-fellow-tanzu-developer-advocate-leigh-capili"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow teammate and Kubernetes ecosystem legend Leigh Capili (@capileigh) about Gitops, Kubernetes, Puppet/Chef, continuous delivery, how zoom scales if you deploy on-prem, being a developer advocate, Flux, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling Creative Expression with Concept Activation Vectors]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/enabling-creative-expression-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/enabling-creative-expression-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T18:31:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Been Kim, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team, and Alison Lentz, Senior Staff Strategist, Google Research, Mural Team  
Advances in computer vision and natural language processing continue to unlock new ways of exploring billions of images available on public and searchable websites. Today’s visual search tools make it possible to search with your camera, voice, text, images, or multiple modalities at the same time. However, it remains difficult to input subjective concepts, such as visual tones or moods, into current systems. For this reason, we have been working collaboratively with artists, photographers, and image researchers to explore how machine learning (ML) might enable people to use expressive queries as a way of visually exploring datasets. 
Today, we are i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top tips for creating a healthy and sustainable open source community]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-07-healthy-and-sustainable-communities/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-07-healthy-and-sustainable-communities/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T18:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the six key themes, and tips for each, that ensure sustainable and healthy open source communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools Plugin 2022.6 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=262578</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/07/07/edutools-plugin-2022-6-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T17:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2022.6 of EduTools is out! With this release, we’ve added the Next button for edu tasks to navigate to the next task more easily, and we’ve improved plugin quality by fixing bugs. If you’ve been learning JavaScript with our CheckIO integration, please note that we disabled JavaScript support because the CheckiO platform switched over […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Kafka 2.9 Release Candidate Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/spring-for-apache-kafka-2-9-release-candidate-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/spring-for-apache-kafka-2-9-release-candidate-available"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T16:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that the release candidate Spring for Apache Kafka 2.9.0 is now available (2.9.0-RC1) in the Spring Milestone Repo.



This version is not provided by Spring Boot dependency management, but it can be used with Boot 2.7, as long as you override the Kafka dependencies as described in this appendix, especially if you are using the embedded Kafka broker.



Notable Changes




This version uses the 3.2.0 kafka-clients version



Non-blocking retry bootstrapping is now more robust



New Error Handler Mode





By default, after an error, the DefaultErrorHandler performs seeks on the remaining records from the last poll and re-fetches them from the broker on the next poll.
With high error rates and large max.poll.records, this can cause unnecessary strain on the network.
For this reason, the error handler has a new property seekAfterError, when set to false, instead of seeking the records, the remaining records are retained in memory and the consumer paused for the next poll (or multiple polls if the error handler is configured to use the ContainerPausingBackOffHandler).





Pausing Containers





By default, when you pause() a container, it actually pauses when all the records from the previous poll have been processed.
This version adds the pauseImmediate container property, which, when true, causes the container to pause after the current record is processed.



For information about all changes in this release, see What’s New.



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.2 EAP7: Toolchain Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=263347</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/07/clion-2022-2-eap7-toolchain-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T15:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new CLion 2022.2 EAP7 build, 222.3345.16, is available from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package for Ubuntu. If you are on macOS, there is a separate build for Apple Silicon (M1 chip). Those who are already using EAP6 can apply a patch to update to EAP7. DOWNLOAD CLION EAP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 Goes Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=261193</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/07/intellij-idea-2022-2-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T15:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 Beta is now available with the key improvements and changes that are expected in the upcoming major release.  You can download the latest build from our website, from the free Toolbox App, or by using snaps for Ubuntu.  In the blog posts tagged with IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2, you can read the details […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.2 Goes Beta!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=261773</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/07/07/goland-2022-2-goes-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T15:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.2 has reached the Beta milestone! During the next couple of weeks, we will be fixing bugs and getting GoLand ready for the major release at the end of July. This is the last build in our EAP cycle that doesn’t require a license.  You can get the build via the Toolbox App, download […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Procedural macros under the hood: Part II]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rust&amp;p=259927</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rust/2022/07/07/procedural-macros-under-the-hood-part-ii/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T13:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our previous blog post, we discussed the essence of Rust’s procedural macros. Now we invite you to dive deeper into how they are processed by the compiler and the IDE. Compilation of procedural macros To start, let’s see how we might write a ‘Hello, world’ program using a separate crate inside a procedural macro: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Deployments in Space]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=261733</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2022/07/07/introducing-deployments-in-space/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T12:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’ve reached an important milestone in Space Automation development. We’re releasing support for deployments, another piece of the puzzle in making Space a truly all-in-one solution.  A deployment is a Space entity that represents the delivery of source code changes to a deployment environment (a deployment target). For example, delivering a web app to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexey Totin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The practice effect]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42312</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701919978/0/sethsblog~The-practice-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T08:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two kinds of skills, resources and tools: Ones that get used up as you use them. And ones that get better when you do. Nobody wants there to be a crowd at the ski area on a bluebird powder day–too many people use up the new snow. On the other hand, it’s no […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.0-RC1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/spring-shell-2-1-0-rc1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/spring-shell-2-1-0-rc1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T08:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.0-RC1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe 2022 Recap: From Drift Detection to Our New Developer Site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-2022-recap-from-drift-detection-to-our-new-developer-site</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-2022-recap-from-drift-detection-to-our-new-developer-site"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe took place once again in Amsterdam this year. Watch our complete sessions playlist, read a recap of the big keynote announcements, and take a look back at the sights and sounds of our annual European community conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.3.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.3.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.3.2 over the previous patch versions in 8.3.x.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
8.3.2 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Version 8.3.2 fixes a Kibana issue where Alerting rules that were created or edited in 8.2 will stop running on upgrade to 8.3.0 to 8.3.1. Alerting users who have upgraded to 8.3.0 or 8.3.1 will need to follow the resolution steps to manually fix the alerting rules that have stopped running.
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Kobel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does Elastic Cloud pricing work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-does-elastic-cloud-pricing-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-does-elastic-cloud-pricing-work"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you leverage Elastic Cloud, you can apply search-powered solutions to any kind of data. Get a better understanding of how Elastic Cloud pricing works and the benefits provided.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanda Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onboarding at Elastic: What to Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/onboarding-at-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/onboarding-at-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a distributed company, we’re experts in remote onboarding. Learn how we onboard new hires at Elastic, and dive into X-School, our new hire orientation experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.3.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Kobel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does Elastic Cloud pricing work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-does-elastic-cloud-pricing-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-does-elastic-cloud-pricing-work"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The magic of Elastic lies in the ability to use our search-powered platform across a wide range of solutions and use cases: 

Enterprise Search: e-commerce, site search, customer support, and other search applications
Observability: unifying logs, metrics, and application traces, paired with anomaly detection and powerful root cause analysis
Security: threat hunting and incident response, malware detection, security analytics, cloud security, endpoint protection, monitoring, and more


In defining pricing for Elastic Cloud, we wanted to preserve that magic to empower our customers to use Elastic across these solutions and use cases.

Key benefits of Elastic Cloud pricing are:

You pay only for the resources you use
You can scale while balancing performance and cost
You pay for the platfo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanda Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onboarding at Elastic: What to Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/onboarding-at-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/onboarding-at-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic is a fully distributed organization by design, so when you start working with us, you’re in good and experienced hands. 

In fact, we bring you into the team as soon as you accept our job offer. You put in your equipment requests, complete your documents and paperwork, and get your swag ordered (we’re humble, but we do have great swag). 

On your first day, a team-wide email is sent introducing you and your new role. That way, people can introduce themselves and you’re immediately welcomed into the fold.

Your first week will likely include some meetings with your managers and team and X-School Essentials, a welcome call with other new hires in your region run by the local HR team. But, you dictate the bulk of your first week. Shelby Khan, Brand Strategy Director at Elastic, who …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLGO: A Machine Learning Framework for Compiler Optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/mlgo-machine-learning-framework-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/mlgo-machine-learning-framework-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yundi Qian, Software Engineer, Google Research and Mircea Trofin, Software Engineer, Google Core 
The question of how to compile faster and smaller code arose together with the birth of modem computers. Better code optimization can significantly reduce the operational cost of large datacenter applications. The size of compiled code matters the most to mobile and embedded systems or software deployed on secure boot partitions, where the compiled binary must fit in tight code size budgets. With advances in the field, the headroom has been heavily squeezed with increasingly complicated heuristics, impeding maintenance and further improvements.  
 Recent research has shown that machine learning (ML) can unlock more opportunities in compiler optimization by replacing complicated heuri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: June 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-06-github-availability-report-june-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-06-github-availability-report-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June, we experienced four incidents resulting in significant impact to multiple GitHub.com services. This report also sheds light into an incident that impacted several GitHub.com services in May.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many shards should I have in my Elasticsearch cluster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch is a very versatile platform that supports a variety of use cases and provides great flexibility around data organisation and replication strategies. This flexibility can, however, sometimes make it hard to determine up-front how to best organize your data into indices and shards, especially if you are new to the Elastic Stack. While suboptimal choices will not necessarily cause problems when first starting out, they have the potential to cause performance problems as data volumes grow over time. The more data the cluster holds, the more difficult it also becomes to correct the problem, as reindexing of large amounts of data can sometimes be required.
When we come across users that are experiencing performance problems, it is not uncommon that this can be traced back to issue…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Dahlqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many shards should I have in my Elasticsearch cluster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Dahlqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第212話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270375685329258711</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270375685329258711"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking Automation to the Next Level: Using Ansible + GitOps to Manage the Lifecycle of a Containerized Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/taking-automation-to-the-next-level-using-ansible-gitops-to-manage-the-lifecycle-of-a-containerized-application</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/taking-automation-to-the-next-level-using-ansible-gitops-to-manage-the-lifecycle-of-a-containerized-application"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the great advantages of combining GitOps with Ansible is that you get to streamline the automation delivery and the lifecycle of a containerized application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Do you have a plan?”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41304</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701795856/0/sethsblog~Do-you-have-a-plan/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First, let’s agree that there’s a problem. It may be that I think we’re facing something serious, something costly, something urgent–and you don’t. We can have an honest conversation about the problem without worrying about whether there’s an easy or certain solution. We can also have a conversation about whether it’s a problem (problems have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing a game dev community with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-06-managing-a-game-dev-community/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-06-managing-a-game-dev-community/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T08:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Little Game Called Mario is an open source, collectively developed hell project. Anyone and everyone is welcome to contribute their unique talents to make both the player and developer experience more enjoyable. Find out how the collective leverages GitHub Actions to manage this wonderful little community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta-Alternating Current]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2642/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2642/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/meta_alternating_current.png" title="It's always bothered me that you can't cancel out an inverter by putting a second inverter after it." alt="It's always bothered me that you can't cancel out an inverter by putting a second inverter after it." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 5th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/05/this-week-in-spring-july-5th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/05/this-week-in-spring-july-5th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! This week’s all sorts of weird for me. It’s Tuesday! But here in the US we just celebrated the 4th of July, and I, like many Americans, took a long weekend. Took some time with the family to do a little road trip up north to visit Mt. Shasta, Crater Lake, Lassen National Park, etc. It was a ton of fun, and a lot of driving! Anyway, it all kinda blurs together and felt like just one weekend, and today feels like Monday. I only just realized it was Tuesday! And you know what that means? It’s time for our weekly dive into the wild and wonderful world of Springdom! 


  
The last of my eight part series on building GraphQL applications with Spring for GraphQL is up! Check that page out and find links to all eight videos, each of which introduces one interesting dimension of the powerful and novel new Spring for GraphQL project.

  
In last week’s installment of A Bootiful Podcast, I talk to Spring Developer Advocate Dan Vega

  
Processing the Response Body in Spring Cloud Gateway

  
Spring Cloud 2020.0.6 is available

  
UUID as Entity ID in MongoDB

  
I liked this post over on Dzone: Are All Kubernetes Ingresses the Same?

  
Want to learn more about how to build GraalVM native images for Spring Boot 2.x-generation applications? Check out this article I wrote for InfoQ on Spring Native and GraalVM

  
The good folks over at Vaadin have put together a nice tutorial on building full-stack Spring Boot applications using their Java web framework called Hilla - check it out!

  
our friends over at Sivalabs have put together an interesting looking tutorial on how to use Spring Boot and Kubernetes together

  
Spring Boot team member Stéphane Nicoll did a French-language presentation for DevFest Lille recently introducing Spring AOT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Significant hurdles]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42308</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701675576/0/sethsblog~Significant-hurdles/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T08:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your plan, your idea or your art doesn’t involve any significant hurdles in moving forward, it’s probably not worth that much. If it were easy, everyone would do it. The tactic is to seek a path where you see and understand the significant hurdles that kept others away. And then dance with them. They’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving quantified success with Elastic Enterprise Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-enterprise-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-enterprise-search"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recently ran a customer Results that Matter survey managed and analyzed by Socratic Technologies. With 98% of customers saying that they will continue to use Elastic as much or more in the next year, the results were compelling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving quantified success with Elastic Enterprise Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-enterprise-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-enterprise-search"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Locating information and content is a universal problem that extends across industries, geographies, and use cases. This challenge is only getting more complex as data volumes grow and organizations experience tool sprawl.

Elasticsearch was created over a decade ago to solve this issue. Since then, millions of people have chosen Elasticsearch to implement robust, modern search experiences. 

This year, Elastic ran a customer study through a survey managed and analyzed by Socratic Technologies. Its purpose was to take a closer look at the problems customers are solving with Enterprise Search. Our findings not only inform the future of Elastic Enterprise Search, but they also serve as an example of how customers can best leverage the tool to be most successful in their search endeavors.

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – July 4, 2022]]></title>
        <id>7ed012657b91a09f4a4432a1cd0a97f3cc7ca3d4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-july-04-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T18:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Summer has arrived in Finland, and these last few days have been hotter than in the Canary Islands! Today in the US it is Independence Day. I hope that if […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demand responsibility]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42316</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701569946/0/sethsblog~Demand-responsibility/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T08:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plenty of people insist on freedom and independence. More rare and far more effective is to claim responsibility instead. “I’ve got this,” can go a long way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extend your dependency information in the GitHub Dependency Graph with new GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-01-extend-your-dependency-information-in-the-github-dependency-graph-with-new-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-01-extend-your-dependency-information-in-the-github-dependency-graph-with-new-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T17:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Actions from Anchore, NowSecure, SBT, and Trivy are now available to create a more comprehensive GitHub Dependency Graph.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the GitHub Security Team uses projects and GitHub Actions for planning, tracking, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-01-how-the-github-security-team-uses-projects-and-github-actions-for-planning-tracking-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-01-how-the-github-security-team-uses-projects-and-github-actions-for-planning-tracking-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T15:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can projects and GitHub Actions be used by your non-developer teams? They absolutely can. Check out how our Security Team uses GitHub to run the department effortlessly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying Disfluencies in Natural Speech]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/identifying-disfluencies-in-natural.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/identifying-disfluencies-in-natural.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T20:09:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dan Walker and Dan Liebling, Software Engineers, Google Research 
People don’t write in the same way that they speak. Written language is controlled and deliberate, whereas transcripts of spontaneous speech (like interviews) are hard to read because speech is disorganized and less fluent. One aspect that makes speech transcripts particularly difficult to read is disfluency, which includes self-corrections, repetitions, and filled pauses (e.g., words like “umm”, and “you know”). Following is an example of a spoken sentence with disfluencies from the LDC CALLHOME corpus: 
But that's it's not, it's not, it's, uh, it's a word play on what you just said.
It takes some time to understand this sentence — the listener must filter out the extraneous words and resolve all of the nots. Remo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Developer Advocate Dan Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-developer-advocate-dan-vega</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-developer-advocate-dan-vega"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow Spring Developer Advocate Dan Vega (@therealdanvega)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Better Commits, Build Better Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-30-write-better-commits-build-better-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-30-write-better-commits-build-better-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T19:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High-quality Git commits are the key to a maintainable and collaborative open- or closed-source project. Learn strategies to improve and use commits to streamline your development process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minerva: Solving Quantitative Reasoning Problems with Language Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/minerva-solving-quantitative-reasoning.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/minerva-solving-quantitative-reasoning.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T16:34:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ethan Dyer and Guy Gur-Ari, Research Scientists, Google Research, Blueshift Team 
Language models have demonstrated remarkable performance on a variety of natural language tasks — indeed, a general lesson from many works, including BERT, GPT-3, Gopher, and PaLM, has been that neural networks trained on diverse data at large scale in an unsupervised way can perform well on a variety of tasks. 
Quantitative reasoning is one area in which language models still fall far short of human-level performance. Solving mathematical and scientific questions requires a combination of skills, including correctly parsing a question with natural language and mathematical notation, recalling relevant formulas and constants, and generating step-by-step solutions involving numerical calculations and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.9 Adds New Runner Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-9-adds-new-runner-commands</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-9-adds-new-runner-commands"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint 0.9 introduces on-demand runner introspection, a runner install command, and support for HCP Waypoint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to do when your open source project becomes a community?]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-30-what-to-do-when-your-open-source-project-becomes-a-community/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-30-what-to-do-when-your-open-source-project-becomes-a-community/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T15:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintainers answer your questions about how to manage an open source project that grows into a community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the summer 2022 MLH Fellowship GitHub Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-30-announcing-the-summer-2022-mlh-fellowship-github-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-30-announcing-the-summer-2022-mlh-fellowship-github-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T15:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the 2022 MLH Fellowship cohort! This 12-week internship alternative is for aspiring software engineers, and powered by GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2020.0.6 is available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/spring-cloud-2020-0-6-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/spring-cloud-2020-0-6-is-available"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce the Spring Cloud 2020.0.6 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2020.0.6 release notes for more information. Please consider upgrading to the latest 2021.0.x release train since the 2020.0.x release train has reached the end of OSS support.
Notable Changes in the 2020.0.6 Release

This is primarily a bugfix and dependency upgrade release, including backports of various issues over from 2021.0.x releases. Some enhancements have also been backported. 

See the project page for all issues included in the release.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Backported bug fixes from 2021.0.x

  
Backported passing on request data to LoadBalancerLifecycle beans for the blocking Spring Cloud Load…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Chromium super (inline cache) type confusion]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-29-the-chromium-super-inline-cache-type-confusion/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-29-the-chromium-super-inline-cache-type-confusion/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T18:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post I'll exploit CVE-2022-1134, a type confusion in Chrome that I reported in March 2022, which allows remote code execution (RCE) in the renderer sandbox of Chrome by a single visit to a malicious site. I'll also look at some past vulnerabilities of this type and some implementation details of inline cache in V8, the JavaScript engine of Chrome.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Git monorepo performance with a file system monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-29-improve-git-monorepo-performance-with-a-file-system-monitor/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-29-improve-git-monorepo-performance-with-a-file-system-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monorepo performance can suffer due to the sheer number of files in your working directory. Git’s new builtin file system monitor makes it easy to speed up monorepo performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflections on Juneteenth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/reflections-on-juneteenth</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/reflections-on-juneteenth"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight members of the HashiCorp Blacksmiths’ employee resource group share how they spent Juneteenth this year, and reflect on what they learned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault Logging and Alerting on Day 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-logging-and-alerting-on-day-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-logging-and-alerting-on-day-1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a step-by-step guide to building a free solution for Day 1 Vault logging and alerting on AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Achieve Geo-redundancy with Zeebe]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57477</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/how-to-achieve-geo-redundancy-with-zeebe/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations can use Camunda Platform 8 to build resilient systems that can withstand disasters in the form of complete data center outages.
The post How to Achieve Geo-redundancy with Zeebe appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today is the last day to submit to the SpringOne 2022 Call For Papers!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/28/today-is-the-last-day-to-submit-to-the-springone-2022-call-for-papers</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/28/today-is-the-last-day-to-submit-to-the-springone-2022-call-for-papers"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! This year, SpringOne is back in person, and being held in my hometown of San Francisco, California, December 6th-8th. (Have you registered?) and today (June 28th, 2022) is the last day to submit to the Call For Papers! If you have a good idea or story you want to share, submit today!

Either way, I hope to see you in December in San Francisco, a city so famous for its foggy nightscapes that I think it’s fair to say we are the original cloud natives!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 28th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/28/this-week-in-spring-june-28th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/28/this-week-in-spring-june-28th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’m writing this from the Big Apple, New York City! I’m here for the SpringOne Tour 2022 NYC event. This is my first time back in New York City since before the pandemic and it has been so much fun. I’ve been catching up with people I’ve not seen in years. I even accidentally bumped into people I had no idea was going to also be in town at the same time as I was. New York City is like a magnet for fun, and for fun people. Anyway, we’ve got a lot of stuff to get to this roundup, so let’s dive right into it. 

Also: if you’re just reading this, today - the 28th of June - is the last day to submit to SpringOne 2022, being held in my hometown of San Francisco, California, in December of this year! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: JVM and .NET legend Ted Neward on… just about everything

  
JavaScript Function Call with Thymeleaf

  
Spring Boot 2.6.9 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.7.1 available now

  
Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (the last two episodes: parts 7 and 8)

  
Unique Field in MongoDB Document in Spring Data

  
Build 27 of Java 19, early access, is now available

  
On that note, Build 2 of Java 20 - yes, Java 20! - is also available now!

  
The Apache Software Foundation has also released Apache Tomcat 8.5.81 

  
This is an interesting review of the first principles of Spring and static code

  
I liked this article, exhaustive JUnit 5 testing with combinations, permutations, and products]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – June 27, 2022]]></title>
        <id>56fd8c2cc8a76ab65b87b44700ad43152791e34f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-27-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T21:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! It’s the beginning of a new week, and I’d like to start with a recap of the most significant AWS news from the previous 7 days. Last week was special […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new: network automation with ansible.netcommon 3.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-network-automation-with-ansible.netcommon-3.0.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-network-automation-with-ansible.netcommon-3.0.0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the recent release of the ansible.netcommon Collection version 3.0.0, we have promoted two features as standard: libssh transport and import_modules. These features provide increased performance and resiliency for your network automation. These two features, which have been available since July 2020 (libssh) and March 2021 (import_modules), are now turned on by default for playbooks running the latest version of the netcommon Collection, so let's take a look at what makes these changes so exciting!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Case</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (the last two episodes: parts 7 and 8)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-the-last-two-episodes-parts-7-and-8</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-the-last-two-episodes-parts-7-and-8"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In thi^^^ these installments, we continue our series introducing the Spring for GraphQL project. This series features Spring for GraphQL lead Rossen Stoyanchev (@rstoya05) - whose work you may know from basically everything in the wide and wonderful world of Springdom having to do with the web (HTTP, RSocket, WebSockets, GraphQL, JSF, MVC, etc) - and GraphQL Java engine founder and lead Andi Marek (@andimarek) and of course yours truly, Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long (@starbuxman). It provides an in-depth look at all things Spring for GraphQL.

This week I’m publishing two new installments. 

The first episode this week is part seven of eight, focusing on how to secure a Spring for GraphQL application with Spring Security. 


The last episode this week is part eig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: JVM and .NET legend Ted Neward on... just about everything]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/a-bootiful-podcast-jvm-and-net-legend-ted-neward-on-just-about-everything</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/a-bootiful-podcast-jvm-and-net-legend-ted-neward-on-just-about-everything"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, I (@starbuxman) talk to my old friend, world-famous polyglot and code curmudgeon, software philosopher, industry veteran, and legend of ecosystems aplenty, Ted Neward (@tedneward)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth Now Supports Synthetic Data Generation]]></title>
        <id>e413b62195858c26995a1f34b009da37b2b848a4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-sagemaker-ground-truth-now-supports-synthetic-data-generation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T16:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am happy to announce that you can now use Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth to generate labeled synthetic image data. Building machine learning (ML) models is an iterative process that, at a high level, starts with data collection and preparation, followed by model training and model deployment. And especially the first step, collecting large, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now in Preview – Amazon CodeWhisperer- ML-Powered Coding Companion]]></title>
        <id>43dc07fa1c6f9a27c44cdcc33417d7d205f91116</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-in-preview-amazon-codewhisperer-ml-powered-coding-companion/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T16:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I was getting ready to write this post I spent some time thinking about some of the coding tools that I have used over the course of my career. This includes the line-oriented editor that was an intrinsic part of the BASIC interpreter that I used in junior high school, the IBM keypunch that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul on Amazon ECS 0.5 Supports AWS IAM and Mesh Gateways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-5-supports-aws-iam-and-mesh-gateways</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-5-supports-aws-iam-and-mesh-gateways"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest version of HashiCorp Consul on Amazon ECS adds support for AWS IAM authentication and mesh gateways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New on HCP: Boundary, Waypoint, Drift Detection, and Azure Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-on-hcp-boundary-waypoint-and-drift-detection</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-on-hcp-boundary-waypoint-and-drift-detection"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Cloud Platform has added several new capabilities, including managed services for HashiCorp Boundary and Waypoint, and Drift Detection for Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-boot-2-7-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-boot-2-7-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T12:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.1 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 66 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.9 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-boot-2-6-9-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-boot-2-6-9-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T11:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.9 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 44 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Advantage in Learning from Experiments]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/quantum-advantage-in-learning-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/quantum-advantage-in-learning-from.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T18:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jarrod McClean, Staff Research Scientist, Google Quantum AI, and Hsin-Yuan Huang, Graduate Student, Caltech 
In efforts to learn about the quantum world, scientists face a big obstacle: their classical experience of the world. Whenever a quantum system is measured, the act of this measurement destroys the “quantumness” of the state. For example, if the quantum state is in a superposition of two locations, where it can seem to be in two places at the same time, once it is measured, it will randomly appear either ”here” or “there”, but not both. We only ever see the classical shadows cast by this strange quantum world. 
A growing number of experiments are implementing machine learning (ML) algorithms to aid in analyzing data, but these have the same limitations as the people they a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Urban Trees Across North America with the Auto Arborist Dataset]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/mapping-urban-trees-across-north.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/mapping-urban-trees-across-north.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T18:04:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Beery, Student Researcher, and Jonathan Huang, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception Team 
Over four billion people live in cities around the globe, and while most people interact daily with others — at the grocery store, on public transit, at work — they may take for granted their frequent interactions with the diverse plants and animals that comprise fragile urban ecosystems. Trees in cities, called urban forests, provide critical benefits for public health and wellbeing and will prove integral to urban climate adaptation. They filter air and water, capture stormwater runoff, sequester atmospheric carbon dioxide, and limit erosion and drought. Shade from urban trees reduces energy-expensive cooling costs and mitigates urban heat islands. In the US alone, urban fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modeling a Bill’s Journey through the U.S. House of Representatives]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57197</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/modeling-a-bills-journey-through-the-u-s-house-of-representatives/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bill's journey through the U.S. House of Representatives is modeled in Camunda Platform 8 and BPMN. Along the way, see how forms incorporate human tasks throughout the process and how DMN helps minimize errors.
The post Modeling a Bill’s Journey through the U.S. House of Representatives appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第211話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270296674428450886</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270296674428450886"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digitally signing Ansible Content Collections using private automation hub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/digitally-signing-ansible-content-collections-using-private-automation-hub</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/digitally-signing-ansible-content-collections-using-private-automation-hub"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform can manage and execute automation made from many different origins, coming from Red Hat product teams, ISV partners, community and private contributors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.11 Adds Kubernetes Secrets Engine, PKI Updates, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-11</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-11"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.11 focuses on improving Vault’s core workflows and making key features production-ready.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Launch and Free Public Beta of HCP Boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-and-free-public-beta-of-hcp-boundary</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-and-free-public-beta-of-hcp-boundary"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary is now available as a managed service on the HashiCorp Cloud Platform in  free public beta to standardize secure remote access to critical infrastructure regardless of where it resides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.3 Introduces HA Logical Gateways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-3-introduces-ha-logical-gateways</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-3-introduces-ha-logical-gateways"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest release of the HashiCorp Consul API Gateway allows users to generate multiple instances of a logical gateway — avoiding single points of failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.13 Tech Preview: Cluster Peering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-tech-preview-cluster-peering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-tech-preview-cluster-peering"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cluster peering in Consul 1.13 offers a whole new model of how Consul handles cross-cluster federation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Azure to go GA, Plus More Consul News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure-to-go-ga-plus-more-consul-news</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure-to-go-ga-plus-more-consul-news"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul is becoming generally available on Azure, Consul API Gateway version 0.3 is going GA, and Consul 1.13 is due later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IoT ExpressLink Now Generally Available – Quickly Develop Devices That Connect Securely to AWS Cloud]]></title>
        <id>487d07cf76d37f913a79c647cc30be56978e730d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-iot-expresslink-now-generally-available-quickly-develop-devices-that-connect-securely-to-aws-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T14:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced AWS IoT ExpressLink, software for partner-manufactured connectivity modules that makes it easier and faster for original equipment manufacturers to connect any type of product to the cloud, such as industrial sensors, small and large home appliances, irrigation systems, and medical devices. Today we announce the general availability of AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at CVPR 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/google-at-cvpr-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/google-at-cvpr-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T14:09:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shaina Mehta and Kristen Borg, Program Managers 
This week marks the beginning of the premier annual Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition conference (CVPR 2022), held both in-person in New Orleans, LA and virtually. As a leader in computer vision research and a Platinum Sponsor, Google will have a strong presence across CVPR 2022 with over 80 papers being presented at the main conference and active involvement in a number of conference workshops and tutorials. 
If you are attending CVPR this year, please stop by our booth and chat with our researchers who are actively exploring the latest machine learning techniques for application to various areas of machine perception. Our researchers will also be available to talk about and demo several recent efforts, including on-device M…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 21st, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/21/this-week-in-spring-june-21st-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/21/this-week-in-spring-june-21st-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you? It’s been a hot minute since we last chatted. I was in Germany this time last week. Now, I’m back in beautiful San Francisco. Today the weather will climb to a monumental 84 F! That’s very unusual, for any time of the year, here in San Francisco. Most places here in San Francisco don’t have air conditioning. Some have heating. I bought a brand new condo in 2014 and it didn’t have air conditioning. You just open the window. I am privileged enough that I have air conditioning today, of course. I mention all this to say that it’s hot here! I worry for the elderly! When it gets this hot, the YMCA and other organizations typically invite elderly people to come in and get some cool air and water. It’s dangerous. Some days it gets even hotter. Very rare, but it does happen. I hope you’re all doing well. Take care of yourselves and each other, my friends. 

And, speaking of being hot, let’s look at this week’s roundup of the latest-and-greatest that’s hot off the press! 


  
Bootiful Podcast: Spring Framework contributor Sébastien Deleuze on GraalVM, AOT, project Leyden, and WebAssembly

  
CVE report published for Spring Cloud Function

  
Debugging Collections, Streams and Watch Renderers

  
Difference Between Flux.create and Flux.generate

  
Handle Spring Security Exceptions With @ExceptionHandler

  
MongoDB Composite Key With Spring Data

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.3.1 available now

  
Monitoring Spring Boot applications using Spring Boot Admin

  
Spring Data 2021.2.1 and 2021.1.5 released

  
Spring Data JPA – Run an App Without a Database

  
Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression Injection Vulnerability (CVE-2022-22980)

  
Spring Framework 5.3.21 available now

  
Spring Security 5.7.2 and 5.6.6 available now

  
Spring Tools 4.15.0 released

  
Spring Tools 4.15.1 released

  
What are the Spring Boot Default Memory Settings?

  
A Guide to Docker Private Registry

  
Is There a Destructor in Java?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HashiCorp Developer Site is Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hashicorp-developer-site-is-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hashicorp-developer-site-is-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our new documentation platform makes it easy to learn from dozens of interactive lab environments, hundreds of tutorials, and thousands of reference docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Adds Drift Detection for Infrastructure Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-drift-detection-for-infrastructure-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-drift-detection-for-infrastructure-management"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drift Detection for Terraform Cloud continuously checks infrastructure state to detect and notify operators of any changes, minimizing risk, downtime, and costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the HCP Waypoint Private Beta Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcp-waypoint-private-beta-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcp-waypoint-private-beta-program"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HCP Waypoint Private Beta Program allows select early adopters to onboard applications and try out HCP Waypoint to develop a proof of concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.2 and 5.6.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-security-5-7-2-and-5-6-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-security-5-7-2-and-5-6-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.7.2 and 5.6.6 are available now.



You can find more details about the respective releases here and
 here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – High Volume Outbound Communication with Amazon Connect Outbound Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>a20b9048be0b3be3a34bbd843c36e4433e02d727</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-high-volume-outbound-communication-with-amazon-connect-outbound-campaigns/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T19:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new high volume outbound communication capability in Amazon Connect which was announced at Enterprise Connect last year, is now generally available to all. It is named Amazon Connect outbound campaigns. If you haven’t heard about Amazon Connect, it is an easy-to-use cloud contact center service that helps companies of any size deliver superior customer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo – UX/Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64531</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-ux-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T18:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I took the road less traveled, and that has made all the difference.
The post DevOps Dojo – UX/Accessibility appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – June 20, 2022]]></title>
        <id>a332bdf7b28369cb096731e12bebdd69553bacc1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-20-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T17:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Last Week’s Launches It’s been a quiet week on the AWS News Blog, however a glance at What’s New page shows the various service teams have been busy as usual. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Phases of Infrastructure Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-3-phases-of-infrastructure-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-3-phases-of-infrastructure-automation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From adoption to standardization to operating and optimizing at scale, the evolution of infrastructure automation is critical to modern hybrid and multi-cloud environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.3.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-authorization-server-0-3-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-authorization-server-0-3-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.3.1.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.3.1'




See the release notes for complete details.



This release includes downgrading to JDK 1.8 baseline along with some minor enhancements and bug fixes.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Automation Controller for API Driven Workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/scaling-automation-controller-for-api-driven-workloads</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/scaling-automation-controller-for-api-driven-workloads"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When scaling automation controller in an enterprise organization, administrators are faced with more clients automating their interactions with its REST API. As with any web application, automation controller has a finite capacity to serve web requests, and  web clients can experience degraded service if that capacity is met or superseded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elijah Delee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.2.1 and 2021.1.5 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-2021-2-1-and-2021-1-5-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-2021-2-1-and-2021-1-5-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T12:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce Spring Data service releases 2021.2.1 and 2021.1.5.
Both releases ship with a fix for mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot 2.7.1 respective 2.6.9 are going to pick up these releases in the upcoming days.

In addition, these releases include fixes for one vulnerability:


  
CVE-2022-22980
 “Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression Injection Vulnerability”
 SpEL injection attack in MongoDB applications through repository query methods annotated with @Query or @Aggregation using parametrized SpEL statements with non-sanitized input.
 Severity: High


These new versions are recommended upgrades for all Spring Data production scenarios.

To round things off, here are the links to the individual modules, chan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression Injection Vulnerability (CVE-2022-22980)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-mongodb-spel-expression-injection-vulnerability-cve-2022-22980</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-mongodb-spel-expression-injection-vulnerability-cve-2022-22980"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T12:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates 


  
[06-20] CVE-2022-22980 is published

  
[06-20] Spring Data MongoDB 3.4.1 and 3.3.5 are available


Table of Contents


  
Overview

  
Vulnerability

  
Am I Impacted

  
Status

  
Suggested Workarounds


Overview

We would like to announce that we have released Spring Data MongoDB 3.4.1 and 3.3.5 to address the following CVE report:


  
CVE-2022-22980: Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression injection vulnerability through annotated repository query methods


This vulnerability was responsibly reported by Zewei Zhang from NSFOCUS TIANJI Lab on Monday, June 13 2022. The full report will be published to MITRE and as security advisory under tanzu.vmware.com/security in the upcoming days.
Vulnerability

The vulnerability affects Spring Data MongoDB applications u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.15.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/18/spring-tools-4-15-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/18/spring-tools-4-15-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.15.1 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: VScode incorrectly suggests removing @Autowired annotation from methods (#787)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: VScode quick fix should not suggest removing @Autowired annotation from JUnit tests (#786)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Not able to extract the new version of spring-tool-suite-4-4.15.0.RELEASE-e4.24.0-win32.win32.x86_64.self-extracting.jar on windows 11 (#788)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Cannot open Spring Boot Language Server Java Editor settings menu (#789)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-06-17-4151-release-incl-language-servers-version-1360

Spring Tools 4.15.2 is scheduled to be released in early August 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stores from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 17.06.2022]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64512</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stores-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-17-06-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T10:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last weekend was the Scottish Summit, while this event is local to the UK, people flew in globally to speak and attend one of the best Azure events around! There were so many great sessions from technical folks in the community and an amazing keynote from Dona Sarkar about accessibility.
The post Top Stores from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 17.06.2022 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Service Mesh Support for AWS Lambda Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul support for AWS Lambda is now available in public beta enabling services in the mesh to invoke AWS Lambda functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​HashiCorp Recognized as a Best Workplace in the Bay Area]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-recognized-as-a-best-workplace-in-the-bay-area</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-recognized-as-a-best-workplace-in-the-bay-area"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp was ranked 28 on the 2022 Great Place to Work and Fortune magazine Best Workplaces in the Bay Area list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Can’t I Delete a Process Definition in Camunda Platform 8?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57095</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/why-cant-i-delete-a-process-definition-in-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deleting process definitions in Camunda Platform 8 requires complex behavior across multiple components in the system.
The post Why Can’t I Delete a Process Definition in Camunda Platform 8? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​Terraform Cloud Run Tasks with Styra DAS Provides OPA Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-with-styra-das-provides-opa-validation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-with-styra-das-provides-opa-validation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration of HashiCorp Terraform with OPA-founder Styra allows users to validate Terraform infrastructure as code with Open Policy Agent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Netflix Content Engineering makes a federated graph searchable (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/49348511c06c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/how-netflix-content-engineering-makes-a-federated-graph-searchable-part-2-49348511c06c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Alex Hutter, Falguni Jhaveri, and Senthil Sayeebaba]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure - Network Access - blog #2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you to Hicham Mourad and Scott Harwell for co-authoring this blog.
 
Introduction
 
In this blog series, we will continue discussing the deployment of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Harwell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe Is Back: Join Us in Amsterdam or Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years as a fully digital event, HashiConf Europe will once again return to Amsterdam on 20-22 June 2022. Here’s what you can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scanned Objects by Google Research: A Dataset of 3D-Scanned Common Household Items]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/scanned-objects-by-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/scanned-objects-by-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:06:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Laura Downs and Anthony Francis, Software Engineers, Robotics at Google  
Many recent advances in computer vision and robotics rely on deep learning, but training deep learning models requires a wide variety of data to generalize to new scenarios. Historically, deep learning for computer vision has relied on datasets with millions of items that were gathered by web scraping, examples of which include ImageNet, Open Images, YouTube-8M, and COCO. However, the process of creating these datasets can be labor-intensive, and can still exhibit labeling errors that can distort the perception of progress. Furthermore, this strategy does not readily generalize to arbitrary three-dimensional shapes or real-world robotic data.  
 

Real-world robotic data collection is very useful, but diffi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>