<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-07T00:15:33.599Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-07T00:15:33.599Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Indicates Success for Your Camunda POC?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=102164</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/03/what-indicates-success-camunda-poc/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T20:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you measure and demonstrate success? Learn how to determine success for your Camunda proof of concept.
The post What Indicates Success for Your Camunda POC? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon RDS now supports io2 Block Express volumes for mission-critical database workloads]]></title>
        <id>e1f154044ec7ddbc580e087aadbcf76d2131d2a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-rds-now-supports-io2-block-express-volumes-for-mission-critical-database-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am pleased to announce the availability of Provisioned IOPS (PIOPS) io2 Block Express storage volumes for all database engines in Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS). Amazon RDS provides you the flexibility to choose between different storage types depending on the performance requirements of your database workload. io2 Block Express volumes are designed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the newest Heroes of the year – March 2024]]></title>
        <id>1c28a1aa7d172c4f3ef6f586d0d873794d1f054c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-newest-heroes-of-the-year-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Heroes are inspirational thought leaders who go above and beyond to knowledge share in a variety of ways. You can find them speaking at local meetups, AWS Community Days, or even at re:Invent. And these technical experts are never done learning—they’re passionate about solving problems and creating content to enable the community to build […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Croissant: a metadata format for ML-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/croissant-metadata-format-for-ml-ready.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/croissant-metadata-format-for-ml-ready.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Omar Benjelloun, Software Engineer, Google Research, and Peter Mattson, Software Engineer, Google Core ML and President, MLCommons Association






Machine learning (ML) practitioners looking to reuse existing datasets to train an ML model often spend a lot of time understanding the data, making sense of its organization, or figuring out what subset to use as features. So much time, in fact, that progress in the field of ML is hampered by a fundamental obstacle: the wide variety of data representations. 





ML datasets cover a broad range of content types, from text and structured data to images, audio, and video. Even within datasets that cover the same types of content, every dataset has a unique ad hoc arrangement of files and data formats. This challenge reduces productivi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.18 GA improves enterprise reliability with Long-Term Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-18-ga-improves-enterprise-reliability-with-long-term-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-18-ga-improves-enterprise-reliability-with-long-term-support"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.18 improves enterprise reliability with Long-Term Support, fault-injection capabilities, and expanded Amazon ECS support for multi-runtime deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Enterprise Long-Term Support (LTS) improves operational efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-enterprise-long-term-support-lts-improves-operational-efficiency</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-enterprise-long-term-support-lts-improves-operational-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul Enterprise adds Long-Term Support (LTS) releases, reducing operational overhead and risk with extended maintenance and upgrade compatibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging trends in observability: GAI, AIOps, tools consolidation, and OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T17:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of the observability industry through the eyes of over 500 IT decision makers. Find out what’s top of mind for observability in 2024, from AIOps to GAI, tool consolidation and more from yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging trends in observability: GAI, AIOps, tools consolidation, and OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-gai-aiops-tools-consolidation-opentelemetry"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T17:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As technology evolution continues at its rapid pace, so does observability. Observability is becoming critical to driving positive business outcomes, and we wanted to understand how users are evaluating trends and their impact over the coming years. And while every organization approaches observability around its own unique needs, there are usually specific trends and shifts that the broader industry undergoes. 

Elastic® recently surveyed over 500 observability decision-makers around key topics in modern observability. Respondents were asked about the progress and benefits they are seeing in their observability initiatives, and the impact of generative AI and OpenTelemetry on observability. The survey, completed with Dimensional Research in January 2024, delivered some surprising results …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here's how merge queue transformed the way GitHub deploys changes to production at scale, so you can do the same for your organization.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/">How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-06-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>With this version, customers can choose how to best scale their security strategy, gain more control over deployments, and so much more.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-now-generally-available/">GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 is now generally available</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrich your Elasticsearch documents with Logstash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using a jdbc static filter connected to Elasticsearch might speed up your Logstash enrichment pipeline....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Pilato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrich your Elasticsearch documents with Logstash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/enrich-your-elasticsearch-documents-with-logstash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[input {
  # Read all documents from Elasticsearch
  elasticsearch {
    hosts => ["${ELASTICSEARCH_URL}"]
    user => "elastic"
    password => "${ELASTIC_PASSWORD}"
    index => "kibana_sample_data_logs"
    docinfo => true
    ecs_compatibility => "disabled"
  }
}
filter {
  # Enrich every document with Elasticsearch
  elasticsearch {
    hosts => ["${ELASTICSEARCH_URL}"]
    user => "elastic"
    password => "${ELASTIC_PASSWORD}"
    index => "vip"
    query => "ip:%{[clientip]}"
    sort => "ip:desc"
    fields => {
      "[name]" => "[name]"
      "[vip]" => "[vip]"
    }
  }
  mutate { 
    remove_field => ["@version", "@timestamp"] 
  }
}
output {
  if [name] {
    # Write all modified documents to Elasticsearch
    elasticsearch {
      manage_template => false
      hosts => ["${E…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Pilato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic continues to innovate and grow through AWS Generative AI Competency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-aws-generative-ai-competency</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-aws-generative-ai-competency"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T15:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic has achieved AWS Generative AI Partner Competency by working closely with AWS. This recognition highlights Elastic’s deep technical expertise with generative AI in AWS and proven customer succ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy (Uday),Greg Johnson,Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic continues to innovate and grow through AWS Generative AI Competency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-aws-generative-ai-competency</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-aws-generative-ai-competency"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T15:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic® is excited to share the achievement of the AWS Generative AI Competency status, a testament to our unwavering commitment to equip our valued customers with cutting-edge search technologies. This prestigious accolade underscores our dedication to helping you deliver exceptional search experiences that meet your end users' expectations, all while safeguarding your proprietary data from undue exposure to large language models (LLMs).
The AWS Generative AI Competency is a mark of distinction reserved for AWS partners who have consistently exhibited deep technical expertise and a track record of customer satisfaction in deploying generative AI-driven solutions. Elastic's attainment of this credential required an extensive evaluation of our technical capabilities and a thorough examinat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy (Uday),Greg Johnson,Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regressing to the mean all by yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44896</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873133262/0/sethsblog~Regressing-to-the-mean-all-by-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The mean” is the average. Another word for “mediocre.” When an organization gets big enough, by definition, it’s the average. When you have enough customers, they represent the population as a whole. If you find yourself seeking to serve the largest possible number of people, you’ve signed up to be average. Without a doubt, you’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bending pause times to your will with Generational ZGC]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/256629c9386b</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/bending-pause-times-to-your-will-with-generational-zgc-256629c9386b?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T01:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The surprising and not so surprising benefits of generations in the Z Garbage Collector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Function Calling in Java and Spring AI using the latest Mistral AI API]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/06/function-calling-in-java-and-spring-ai-using-the-latest-mistral-ai-api</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/06/function-calling-in-java-and-spring-ai-using-the-latest-mistral-ai-api"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Tzolov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: the Spring Authorization Server: durability of data]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/06/spring-tips-the-spring-authorization-server-durability-of-data</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/06/spring-tips-the-spring-authorization-server-durability-of-data"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earth/Venus Venn Diagram]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2903/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2903/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/earth_venus_venn_diagram.png" title="Actually, the fact that Mars is still orbiting safely over here means that it was technically an *Euler* apocalypse, not a Venn one." alt="Actually, the fact that Mars is still orbiting safely over here means that it was technically an *Euler* apocalypse, not a Venn one." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make a chatbot: Dos and don'ts for developers in an AI-driven world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-make-a-chatbot</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-make-a-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T19:22:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to develop a chatbot effectively with this guide, covering do’s and don'ts for chatbot developers and other useful tips....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make a chatbot: Dos and don'ts for developers in an AI-driven world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-make-a-chatbot</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-make-a-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T19:22:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every day the world is becoming increasingly powered by artificial intelligence. In fact, you’d struggle to find tech companies that have not announced AI integrations into their tech stack in one way or another. Cynics might say this is a passing phase, but the reason AI is so popular is that it’s a versatile set of capabilities that can help solve a lot of problems.
The most direct way AI can be utilized is in the form of a chatbot: a conversational interface that mimics human interaction, generating contextual responses based on what the user inputs. Sometimes these are text-based, such as the customer service bots you often see on websites or apps. And sometimes they’re voice-enabled, like Siri, Google Assistant, and Alexa. These specific examples only just scratch the surface of what …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insights and Timeline: Our Approach to Addressing the Recently Discovered Vulnerabilities in TeamCity On-Premises]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=453253</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2024/03/our-approach-addressing-recently-discovered-vulnerabilities-in-teamcity-on-premises/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T15:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a follow-up to the vulnerability announcement we published on March 4, 2024. It’s important that we properly communicate the timeline for fixing the CVE-2024-27198 and CVE-2024-27199 vulnerabilities from JetBrains’ side. All times below are expressed in CET. February 19 6:54 pm – Rapid7 reached out to us, saying they had discovered significant security […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Gallo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free data transfer out to internet when moving out of AWS]]></title>
        <id>75d716af79fb6ef0c02f33b4b7ca18cfd5dd4743</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/free-data-transfer-out-to-internet-when-moving-out-of-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You told us one of the primary reasons to adopt Amazon Web Services (AWS) is the broad choice of services we offer, enabling you to innovate, build, deploy, and monitor your workloads. AWS has continuously expanded its services to support virtually any cloud workload. It now offers over 200 fully featured services for compute, storage, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Dev Teams Surviving or Thriving in 2024? Insights from JetBrains and GitKraken’s State of Git Collaboration Report]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=team&amp;p=451765</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/team/2024/03/05/are-dev-teams-surviving-or-thriving-in-2024-insights-from-jetbrains-and-gitkraken-s-state-of-git-collaboration-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T13:42:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A development team’s cohesion and efficiency can make or break a project. With that in mind, how can we distinguish a good team from a great one? JetBrains, in collaboration with GitKraken, explored this question, analyzing data from over 150,000 developers to bring you the 2024 State of Git Collaboration Report. This study provides an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastassiya Sichkarenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTrack Adds More Flexibility for Helpdesk Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=youtrack&amp;p=441751</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/youtrack/2024/03/youtrack-adds-more-flexibility-for-helpdesk-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T13:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the new YouTrack version 2024.1, we’ve improved the experience of support teams working with YouTrack Helpdesk based on the most popular feature requests from our customers. Support teams working with several helpdesk projects for multiple customers or products can now restrict any helpdesk project for predefined groups of reporters and manage their tickets privately. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Pishkova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2024.1 EAP Digest #3: Full Line Code Completion, Language Services Widget, React Quick-Fixes, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=451733</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2024/03/webstorm-2024-1-eap3/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T13:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for our last EAP digest that will walk you through the new features and improvements in WebStorm 2024.1! For more information, check out our previous blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. You can also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vladislav Minaev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The positive auction]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48726</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873056405/0/sethsblog~The-positive-auction/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T12:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Sorry, I hit publish prematurely. I’ll be updating this and correcting the errors as we go.] In 2023, I developed a new idea that transforms an old way of doing commerce. In traditional auctions, there are rounds of bidding and the high bidder pays to get the prize. The last bid is the amount paid, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Django Apps in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=442983</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2024/03/deploying-django-apps-in-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T10:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an open-source container orchestration platform that automates deployment, scaling, and load balancing, Kubernetes offers unparalleled resilience and flexibility in the management of your Django applications. Whether you’re launching a small-scale project or managing a complex application, Kubernetes provides a robust environment to enhance your Django application, ensuring it’s ready to meet the demands of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mukul Mantosh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy: New Learning Content in March]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=452607</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2024/03/05/jetbrains-academy-new-learning-content-in-march/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T10:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re learning Go and you’re interested in adding a new project to your developer portfolio, we’ve got you covered! We’re also introducing 53 new topics across programming languages, machine learning, computer science fundamentals, and more – all of which will allow you to further expand your programming knowledge. Let’s take a closer look at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Regina Muradova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On building a cathedral]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48713</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873050204/0/sethsblog~On-building-a-cathedral/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T09:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re in need of a gathering place, a dry, functional, centrally located facility for your folks to meet, a cathedral is probably way more than you need. It’s far more expensive to build and maintain and not optimal in delivering what’s required. But what if this building needs to fill other functions as well? […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – March 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=452418</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/03/java-annotated-monthly-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T08:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month’s Java Annotated Monthly is packed with the latest Java news ahead of Java 22’s release in March. It’s also full of Kotlin updates, tutorials for Spring and Hibernate, and more. If all that wasn’t enough, there’s also a podcast featuring AI-generated music!  Simply put, it’s full of cool stuff for anyone interested in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Mariasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State of Spring Survey Is Back!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/05/the-state-of-spring-survey-is-back</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/05/the-state-of-spring-survey-is-back"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Minella</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - March 5th, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/05/this-week-in-spring-march-5th-2024</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/05/this-week-in-spring-march-5th-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping repository maintainer information accurate]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T21:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover how keeping repository maintainer information accurate through CODEOWNERS files and automating maintenance with tools like cleanowners fosters efficient collaboration and sustainable software projects.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/">Keeping repository maintainer information accurate</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolving from Rule-based Classifier: Machine Learning Powered Auto Remediation in Netflix Data…]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/039d5efd115b</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/evolving-from-rule-based-classifier-machine-learning-powered-auto-remediation-in-netflix-data-039d5efd115b?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Learning Pathway: Accelerate your business with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-04-github-copilot-learning-pathway-accelerate-your-business-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-github-copilot-learning-pathway-accelerate-your-business-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn what GitHub Copilot can help your business achieve in this expert-guided GitHub Learning Pathway, featuring insights from tech leaders at top organizations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-github-copilot-learning-pathway-accelerate-your-business-with-ai/">GitHub Copilot Learning Pathway: Accelerate your business with AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.13: GA of AI Assistant support for AWS Bedrock and enhancements for AI Assistant and SLO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-13-0"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability announces connectivity to AWS Bedrock for AI Assistant. Other enhancements include contextual awareness of the entry point into the AI Assistant and tech preview of editing and v...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Grabowski,Drew Post</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.13: GA of AI Assistant support for AWS Bedrock and enhancements for AI Assistant and SLO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-13-0"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic® Observability 8.13 announces general availability (GA) for AWS Bedrock support in Elastic AI Assistant, along with enhancements for the AI Assistant and SLOs.
AI Assistant enhancements 

Elastic AI Assistant support for AWS Bedrock

Contextual awareness of the entry point into AI Assistant

Performance improvements

Tech preview of editing and visualizing ES|QL queries from the AI Assistant

SLO enhancements

Ability to group your SLOs by tag, SLI indicator type, or status

Ability to triage burn rate alerts

Elastic Observability 8.13 is available now on Elastic Cloud — the only hosted Elasticsearch® offering to include all of the new features in this latest release. You can also download the Elastic Stack and our cloud orchestration products, Elastic Cloud Enterprise and Elastic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Grabowski,Drew Post</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — New models for Amazon Bedrock, CloudFront embedded POPs, and more — March 4, 2024]]></title>
        <id>f440c1bc8007c2c450a5b97f3269e968ed59221b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-models-for-amazon-bedrock-cloudfront-embedded-pops-and-more-march-4-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T16:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This has been a busy week – we introduced a new kind of Amazon CloudFront infrastructure, more efficient ways to analyze data stored on Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3), and new generative AI capabilities. Last week’s launches Here’s what got my attention: Amazon Bedrock – Mistral AI’s Mixtral 8x7B and Mistral 7B foundation models […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s Claude 3 Sonnet foundation model is now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>afa44e98fb3dea486d0fe36887411e429dd8794c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/anthropics-claude-3-sonnet-foundation-model-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T16:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September 2023, we announced a strategic collaboration with Anthropic that brought together their respective technology and expertise in safer generative artificial intelligence (AI), to accelerate the development of Anthropic’s Claude foundation models (FMs) and make them widely accessible to AWS customers. You can get early access to unique features of Anthropic’s Claude model in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering businesses with Airtel Managed Security Services and Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/airtel-managed-security-services-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/airtel-managed-security-services-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we'll unravel the key features, benefits, and unparalleled security solutions that Airtel brings to its B2B customers and explore the cutting-edge Airtel Managed Security Services, forti...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arvind Bhat,Neeraj Gupta,Puneet Duggal,Ravindra Ramnani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering businesses with Airtel Managed Security Services and Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/airtel-managed-security-services-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/airtel-managed-security-services-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of digital business, security is paramount. As businesses navigate the complexities of today's interconnected world, ensuring the safety of sensitive data and maintaining the integrity of operations becomes a top priority. Partner with Airtel, a trusted leader in telecommunications, and explore the cutting-edge Airtel Managed Security Services, fortified by the robust Elastic Security stack. In this blog, we'll unravel the key features, benefits, and unparalleled security solutions that Airtel brings to its B2B customers.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltda51aa555328c548/65e5fb31aca171625da00bc4/1-airtel-mdr-services.png,1-airtel-mdr-services.pngThe Elastic Security stack: A pillar of strength
Airtel's choice of the Elastic Secur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arvind Bhat,Neeraj Gupta,Puneet Duggal,Ravindra Ramnani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at APS 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/03/google-at-aps-2024.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/03/google-at-aps-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kate Weber and Shannon Leon, Google Research, Quantum AI Team




Today the 2024 March Meeting of the American Physical Society (APS) kicks off in Minneapolis, MN. A premier conference on topics ranging across physics and related fields, APS 2024 brings together researchers, students, and industry professionals to share their discoveries and build partnerships with the goal of realizing fundamental advances in physics-related sciences and technology. 



This year, Google has a strong presence at APS with a booth hosted by the Google Quantum AI team, 50+ talks throughout the conference, and participation in conference organizing activities, special sessions and events. Attending APS 2024 in person? Come visit Google’s Quantum AI booth to learn more about the exciting work we’re d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Additional Critical Security Issues Affecting TeamCity On-Premises (CVE-2024-27198 and CVE-2024-27199) – Update to 2023.11.4 Now]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=449146</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2024/03/additional-critical-security-issues-affecting-teamcity-on-premises-cve-2024-27198-and-cve-2024-27199-update-to-2023-11-4-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T14:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 update: Please also see this follow-up blog post that describes our insights and timeline for addressing these vulnerabilities. Summary Details Two new critical security vulnerabilities have been discovered in TeamCity On-Premises. If abused, the flaws may enable an unauthenticated attacker with HTTP(S) access to a TeamCity server to bypass the authentication checks […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Gallo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2023.11.4 Is Out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=445812</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2024/03/teamcity-2023-11-4-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T14:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new bug-fix release for TeamCity On-Premises is now available. In addition to important security fixes, version 2023.11.4 addresses several regular issues, including decreased TeamCity performance when the server cannot reach the jetbrains.com domain, a broken build log when publishing caches is aborted due to an error, inability to process cross-node events in a multi-node […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitrii Korovin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best PyCharm Plugins 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=438003</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2024/03/best-pycharm-plugins/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm is designed to be used straight out of the box, but you can customize it further by installing the right plugins.  In this article, we’ll be highlighting the top PyCharm plugins that can bring great value to you. They are not available out of the box, but if you’re looking for something to further […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maha Taqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headwinds]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46873</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872990861/0/sethsblog~Headwinds/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T09:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it’s tough going and it feels fraught, it’s easy to imagine that the headwinds will never end. And yet, when all is going well and the wind is at our back, it’s tempting to imagine that this is the way it’s going to stay. Neither is true. The reason we see them as headwinds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Releases for February 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/04/spring-releases-for-february-2024</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/04/spring-releases-for-february-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Konicki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ice Core]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2902/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2902/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/ice_core.png" title="If you find an ash deposition layer from a year in which an eruption destroyed an island that had Camellia sinensis growing on it, you can make a Gone Island Ice_τ." alt="If you find an ash deposition layer from a year in which an eruption destroyed an island that had Camellia sinensis growing on it, you can make a Gone Island Ice_τ." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Becoming intentional about virtual meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45471</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872940299/0/sethsblog~Becoming-intentional-about-virtual-meetings/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A manual I recently read listed the “cons” of having a meeting virtually: To be accurate, every one of these points should have “so far” added. The videogame market is far bigger than the box office of Hollywood films. The people who play video games at home for hours at a time have no problem […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The weird math of halfway]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48706</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872889836/0/sethsblog~The-weird-math-of-halfway/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[6 times 1/2 doesn’t equal 3. It equals zero. We’re tempted to do a little less than we need to. Perhaps we’re busy, with too many options. Perhaps it’s resistance, pushing us to hold a little bit back. Whatever the reason, when we show up just a little, we get zero credit. The smallest viable […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI models now available on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>89d81f50ad915d63aec01b16bf9f82dd3a8cf534</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/mistral-ai-models-now-available-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T21:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, we announced that Mistral AI models are coming to Amazon Bedrock. In that post, we elaborated on a few reasons why Mistral AI models may be a good fit for you. Mistral AI offers a balance of cost and performance, fast inference speed, transparency and trust, and is accessible to a wide range […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2024.1 EAP 7: C# Updates, New Product Icons, Bundled Kubernetes Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=451417</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/03/01/rider-2024-1-eap-7/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T19:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Early Access Program for Rider 2024.1 is in full swing!  Before you download Rider 2024.1 EAP 7, let’s take a look at what’s new. C# support You will get suggestions to convert more code constructions in your source code to collection expressions from C# 12, such as an empty array or the ImmutableArray declaration […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Kurakin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2024.1 EAP 7: Updates to C# and C++ Support]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=451376</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/03/01/resharper-2024-1-eap-7/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T19:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ReSharper 2024.1 EAP 7 build has just been released and is ready for you to download!  This build contains several improvements to C# and C++ support. Let’s take a look! C# support You will get suggestions to convert more code constructions in your source code to collection expressions from C# 12, such as an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Kurakin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The question book]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46857</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872825138/0/sethsblog~The-question-book/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the old days, companies had a suggestion box. It was immortalized in cartoons, but the idea that an employee could anonymously submit a suggestion to make things better is a first step in engagement. Some companies took this much further and paid employees for suggestions that generated profits. Digital communication and more open workplaces […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Support timeline announcement for Spring Framework 6.0.x and 5.3.x]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/01/support-timeline-announcement-for-spring-framework-6-0-x-and-5-3-x</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/01/support-timeline-announcement-for-spring-framework-6-0-x-and-5-3-x"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juergen Hoeller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Functions Catalog 5.0.0‐M1 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/01/spring-functions-catalog-5-0-0-m1-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/03/01/spring-functions-catalog-5-0-0-m1-available"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Bilan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Women of Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have employee resource groups aligned with a variety of shared identities that allow Elasticians to build a sense of community and belonging at work. Here, we meet Women of Elastic....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Women of Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Employee resource groups, or as we like to call them, Elastician resource groups, have been an informal part of Elastic’s culture since 2016. They started as Slack channels that any Elastician could join.
These ERGs were formalized in 2021 to ensure that the members would have structure, budget, and ultimately, a voice based on any dimension of diversity, allyship, and advocacy. This was an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion journey.
Our ERGs are aligned to shared identities, interests, affinities, or allyships. The goal is to create a community of people with something in common and to encourage sharing, learning, and networking. Each has visions and goals they are working towards besides building a sense of community and belonging.
Our Core ERGs
We have seven f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geographic Qualifiers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2901/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2901/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/geographic_qualifiers.png" title="'Thank you for the loveliest evening I've ever had...' [normal] '...east of the Mississippi.' [instant intrigue!]" alt="'Thank you for the loveliest evening I've ever had...' [normal] '...east of the Mississippi.' [instant intrigue!]" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on SIG Cloud Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/01/sig-cloud-provider-spotlight-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/01/sig-cloud-provider-spotlight-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Arujjwal Negi
One of the most popular ways developers use Kubernetes-related services is via cloud providers, but
have you ever wondered how cloud providers can do that? How does this whole process of integration
of Kubernetes to various cloud providers happen? To answer that, let's put the spotlight on SIG
Cloud Provider.
SIG Cloud Provider works to create seamless integrations between Kubernetes and various cloud
providers. Their mission? Keeping the Kubernetes ecosystem fair and open for all. By setting clear
standards and requirements, they ensure every cloud provider plays nicely with Kubernetes. It is
their responsibility to configure cluster components to enable cloud provider integrations.
In this blog of the SIG Spotlight series, Arujjwal Negi interviews
Michael McCune (Re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create a search engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-create-a-search-engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-create-a-search-engine"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T20:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify the process of building a search engine with Elastic and start exploring its endless possibilities....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create a search engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-create-a-search-engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-create-a-search-engine"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T20:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Search engines are one of those things in life we take for granted. Whenever we’re looking for something, we throw a word or phrase into a search engine and, like magic, it gives us a list of matching results. It might not feel as magical nowadays because it’s something we do every day. But anyone who remembers the days of Alta Vista should understand how well we have it now.
When I say “search engine,” it’s easy to picture popular web search engines like Google and — to a lesser extent — Bing. But the application of search engines goes far beyond just searching the web. Popular apps like Uber and Tinder include powerful search engines that match users to drivers and dates using geo-location and other characteristics exclusively from their platform. This is the same for streaming apps, aca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · February 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-29-game-bytes-february-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-game-bytes-february-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T19:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on! 🕹️</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-game-bytes-february-2024/">Game Bytes · February 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Kayla: A college student and open source ambassador]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-29-meet-kayla-a-college-student-and-open-source-ambassador/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-meet-kayla-a-college-student-and-open-source-ambassador/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From learner to mentor, Kayla, an All In for Students ambassador, has become an open source leader on her campus.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-meet-kayla-a-college-student-and-open-source-ambassador/">Meet Kayla: A college student and open source ambassador</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A game of nations — How nation-states prepare for cyber threats with Locked Shields (part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/nation-states-cyber-threats-locked-shields</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/nation-states-cyber-threats-locked-shields"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is part 2 of a series on Locked Shields, the world's largest cybersecurity exercise. Learn how Elastic is typically set up during Locked Shields and gain insights into the top incidents that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marvin Ngoma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A game of nations — How nation-states prepare for cyber threats with Locked Shields (part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/nation-states-cyber-threats-locked-shields</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/nation-states-cyber-threats-locked-shields"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is part 2 of a previous blog, which introduced Locked Shields. It gives a brief overview of how Elastic® is typically set up during Locked Shields. There is also a focus on the meticulously executed comprehensive series of attack simulations on systems housing critical infrastructure in the fictitious country of Berylia. 

Within the controlled Locked Shields environment, Elastic SIEM and Endpoint Security demonstrated their capabilities by successfully detecting and preventing a myriad of attack tactics and techniques. The blog encapsulates a brief summary of the top incidents that emerged during these simulations, offering valuable insights into the efficacy of Elastic Security as a unified cybersecurity solution. 

While the blog does not go into the specifics, high-level thre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marvin Ngoma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping secrets out of public repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-29-keeping-secrets-out-of-public-repositories/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-keeping-secrets-out-of-public-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>With push protection now enabled by default, GitHub helps open source developers safeguard their secrets, and their reputations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-29-keeping-secrets-out-of-public-repositories/">Keeping secrets out of public repositories</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppFabric support expands how HashiCorp Terraform Cloud integrates with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/appfabric-support-expands-how-hashicorp-terraform-cloud-integrates-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/appfabric-support-expands-how-hashicorp-terraform-cloud-integrates-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud now offers even more ways to connect, secure and provision infrastructure with AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Business Process and Why Should You Care]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101992</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/what-is-a-business-process-why-important/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are business processes, and why are they important? Learn how they work, types of business processes, & why well-orchestrated processes are critical.
The post What is a Business Process and Why Should You Care appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The leap]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48611</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872750507/0/sethsblog~The-leap/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T09:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In action movies, there’s a lot of leaping. Brave shifts in which the hero gets from here to there, all at once. It’s easy to imagine that sudden leaps are how we make our impact. This is blog post #9000 (give or take). When did the leap happen? It wasn’t an external leap. The first […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Roni Dover on Digma AI]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/29/a-bootiful-podcast-roni-dover-on-digma-ai</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/29/a-bootiful-podcast-roni-dover-on-digma-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customizing and fine-tuning LLMs: What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-28-customizing-and-fine-tuning-llms-what-you-need-to-know/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-28-customizing-and-fine-tuning-llms-what-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T18:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how your organization can customize its LLM-based solution through retrieval augmented generation and fine-tuning.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-28-customizing-and-fine-tuning-llms-what-you-need-to-know/">Customizing and fine-tuning LLMs: What you need to know</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we’re using GitHub Projects to standardize our workflows and stay aligned]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-28-how-were-using-github-projects-to-standardize-our-workflows-and-stay-aligned/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-28-how-were-using-github-projects-to-standardize-our-workflows-and-stay-aligned/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T17:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how we’re managing feature releases and establishing best practices within and across teams at GitHub using GitHub Projects.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-28-how-were-using-github-projects-to-standardize-our-workflows-and-stay-aligned/">How we’re using GitHub Projects to standardize our workflows and stay aligned</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fraud in financial services: Leaning on generative AI to protect a rapidly expanding attack surface]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-fraud-generative-ai-attack-surface</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-fraud-generative-ai-attack-surface"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T14:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI technologies, particularly machine learning and advanced analytics, have emerged as powerful tools in the fight against fraud in financial services. Combined with Elastic, FSIs can better combat th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Towle,Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fraud in financial services: Leaning on generative AI to protect a rapidly expanding attack surface]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-fraud-generative-ai-attack-surface</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-fraud-generative-ai-attack-surface"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T14:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The financial ecosystem is experiencing an exciting evolution in global payment systems, driven by a digital first approach. The pandemic changed both consumer and business behavior toward adopting new and emerging forms of digital channels. The increased use of digital wallets, real-time payments, embedded payments (such as ApplePay and GooglePay), peer to peer payment systems, and other emerging vehicles ramped up. In fact, according to statista.com, digital payments are projected to reach $11.55 trillion in transaction value within 2024 — all while cash as a form of payment continues to decrease globally.
While this revolution has greatly improved efficiency and reduced friction for customers, banks, and merchants, it has also resulted in an exponential growth in fraud in financial serv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Towle,Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By association]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48693</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872593313/0/sethsblog~By-association/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T10:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re busy, we’re confused and we’re always seeking a shortcut. If a company is hiring, the person who worked at Google or Apple or Disney gets more of the benefit of the doubt. Even if all they did was bring coffee to someone. But, if that person was one of the hundreds laid off yesterday […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: the Spring Authorization Server: securing SPAs and messaging flows]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/28/spring-tips-the-spring-authorization-server-securing-spas-and-messaging</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/28/spring-tips-the-spring-authorization-server-securing-spas-and-messaging"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 3.1.9 and 3.2.2 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/28/spring-shell-3-1-9-and-3-2-2-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/02/28/spring-shell-3-1-9-and-3-2-2-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call My Cell]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2900/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2900/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/call_my_cell.png" title="'Hey, can you call my cell?' '...I'm trying, but it says this number is blocked?' 'Ok, thanks, just checking.'" alt="'Hey, can you call my cell?' '...I'm trying, but it says this number is blocked?' 'Ok, thanks, just checking.'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X.509 certificate management with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/certificate-management-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/certificate-management-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll look at practical public key certificate management in HashiCorp Vault using dynamic secrets rotation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(Free) subscription drive]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48667</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872308334/0/sethsblog~Free-subscription-drive/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every four years, give or take, I make a big but cheap ask: Consider subscribing to this blog. If you’re already a subscriber, please ask five colleagues or friends to subscribe. It’s free. You can subscribe by email by putting your email address in the little box. Click below if you’re reading this in an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Delivered 408% ROI According to New Study]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101985</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/camunda-delivered-408-roi-new-study/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T16:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Study demonstrates significant benefits to adopting Camunda and provides a powerful customizable tool to help you understand the impact it can have on your organization.
The post Camunda Delivered 408% ROI According to New Study appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Enterprise is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-27-github-copilot-enterprise-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-27-github-copilot-enterprise-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T15:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our most advanced AI offering to date is customized to your organization’s knowledge and codebase, infusing GitHub Copilot throughout the software development lifecycle.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-27-github-copilot-enterprise-is-now-generally-available/">GitHub Copilot Enterprise is now generally available</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — .Net Runtime for AWS Lambda, PartyRock Hackathon, and more — February 26, 2024]]></title>
        <id>557c364821cd44b128215dafdb19f284275de1ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-net-runtime-for-aws-lambda-partyrock-hackathon-and-more-february-26-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Community AWS re:invent 2023 re:caps continue! Recently, I was invited to participate in one of these events hosted by the AWS User Group Kenya, and was able to learn and spend time with this amazing community. AWS User Group Kenya Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention during the previous […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp and Google Cloud announce GKE Autopilot support for Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-and-google-cloud-announce-gke-autopilot-support-for-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-and-google-cloud-announce-gke-autopilot-support-for-consul"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul is now supported in Google Cloud’s GKE Autopilot partner program, enabling deployment of Consul to GKE Autopilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing bpftop: Streamlining eBPF performance optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6a727c1ae2e5</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/announcing-bpftop-streamlining-ebpf-performance-optimization-6a727c1ae2e5?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T16:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Region in Mexico is in the works]]></title>
        <id>1c1efeb64d8a5864b3db0f67a64b46b33d53cb69</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-region-in-mexico-is-in-the-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T14:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am happy to announce that we are working on an AWS Region in Mexico. This AWS Mexico (Central) Region will be the second Region in Latin America joining the AWS South America (São Paulo) Region and will give AWS customers the ability to run workloads and store data that must remain in-country. Mexico […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Insights to Action: Harnessing Camunda Optimize for Effective Development]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101840</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/insights-to-action-camunda-optimize-effective-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Samantha, as a developer and a new Camunda user, explored Camunda Optimize to enhance their development process.
The post From Insights to Action: Harnessing Camunda Optimize for Effective Development appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samantha Holstine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picking the Perfect Process for Your Camunda POC]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101958</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/picking-perfect-process-camunda-proof-of-concept/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picking the right process to use for your proof-of-concept is critical. In the next post in our series on creating a Camunda POC, learn how to choose the right one.
The post Picking the Perfect Process for Your Camunda POC appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI models coming soon to Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>308fb7192ffb87eae22e5e1a861fa7efc2aa36a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/mistral-ai-models-coming-soon-to-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI, an AI company based in France, is on a mission to elevate publicly available models to state-of-the-art performance. They specialize in creating fast and secure large language models (LLMs) that can be used for various tasks, from chatbots to code generation. We’re pleased to announce that two high-performing Mistral AI models, Mistral 7B […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VideoPrism: A foundational visual encoder for video understanding]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/videoprism-foundational-visual-encoder.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/videoprism-foundational-visual-encoder.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Long Zhao, Senior Research Scientist, and Ting Liu, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research




An astounding number of videos are available on the Web, covering a variety of content from everyday moments people share to historical moments to scientific observations, each of which contains a unique record of the world. The right tools could help researchers analyze these videos, transforming how we understand the world around us.

 

Videos offer dynamic visual content far more rich than static images, capturing movement, changes, and dynamic relationships between entities. Analyzing this complexity, along with the immense diversity of publicly available video data, demands models that go beyond traditional image understanding. Consequently, many of the approaches that be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Workflow Orchestration? Guide with Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101616</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/what-is-workflow-orchestration-guide-use-cases/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what workflow orchestration is, how it works, its benefits, and how you can get started using it today.
The post What is Workflow Orchestration? Guide with Use Cases appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A look into the Kubernetes Book Club]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/02/22/k8s-book-club/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/02/22/k8s-book-club/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
Learning Kubernetes and the entire ecosystem of technologies around it is not without its
challenges. In this interview, we will talk with Carlos Santana
(AWS) to learn a bit more about how he created the
Kubernetes Book Club, how it works, and
how anyone can join in to take advantage of a community-based learning experience.

Frederico Muñoz (FSM): Hello Carlos, thank you so much for your availability. To start with,
could you tell us a bit about yourself?
Carlos Santana (CS): Of course. My experience in deploying Kubernetes in production six
years ago opened the door for me to join Knative and then contribute to
Kubernetes through the Release Team. Working on upstream Kubernetes has been one of the best
experiences I've had in open-source. Over the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advances in private training for production on-device language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/advances-in-private-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/advances-in-private-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zheng Xu, Research Scientist, and Yanxiang Zhang, Software Engineer, Google




Language models (LMs) trained to predict the next word given input text are the key technology for many applications [1, 2]. In Gboard, LMs are used to improve users’ typing experience by supporting features like next word prediction (NWP), Smart Compose, smart completion and suggestion, slide to type, and proofread. Deploying models on users’ devices rather than enterprise servers has advantages like lower latency and better privacy for model usage. While training on-device models directly from user data effectively improves the utility performance for applications such as NWP and smart text selection, protecting the privacy of user data for model training is important. 









Gboard features powe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第247話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:2550668106003104547</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/2550668106003104547"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I use Boundary to build automation for live streams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-i-use-boundary-to-build-automation-for-live-streams</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-i-use-boundary-to-build-automation-for-live-streams"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how HashiCorp Developer Advocate Rosemary Wang uses HashiCorp Boundary on live streams to automate access to servers and record commands to build into future automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — AWS Control Tower new API, TLS 1.3 with API Gateway, Private Marketplace Catalogs, and more — February 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>b59bdf9a07666673edfdba0242f35b6312ab73cb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-control-tower-new-api-tls-1-3-with-api-gateway-private-marketplace-catalogs-and-more-february-19-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T18:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past week, our service teams have continued to innovate on your behalf, and a lot has happened in the Amazon Web Services (AWS) universe that I want to tell you about. I’ll also share about all the AWS Community events and initiatives that are happening around the world. Let’s dive in! Last week’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Pipelines deprecated tasks retirement schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68388</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-pipelines-deprecated-tasks-retirement-schedule/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T15:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Pipelines includes around 150 build & release tasks as well as many more task extensions. Various included tasks have multiple (major) versions bringing the total to over included 200 tasks.
The post Azure Pipelines deprecated tasks retirement schedule appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How NatWest Built a Center of Excellence to Improve Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101178</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/learn-how-natwest-built-a-center-of-excellence-to-improve-process-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how NatWest accelerated their process automation and orchestration, even as their usage grew, with a CoE using Camunda.
The post Learn How NatWest Built a Center of Excellence to Improve Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Modeling Faster with the New Simplified Modeling Canvas]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101261</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/model-faster-simplified-modeling-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T21:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out our cleaner and more intuitive modeling UI, coming later this month.
The post Start Modeling Faster with the New Simplified Modeling Canvas appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of SSH-RSA support for Azure Repos]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68534</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/ssh-rsa-deprecation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T17:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Repos provides two methods for users to access a git repository in Azure Repos – HTTPS and SSH. To use SSH, you need to create a key pair using one of the supported encryption methods. In the past we’ve been supporting only SSH-RSA and we’ve asked users to enable the SSH-RSA here.
The post End of SSH-RSA support for Azure Repos appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bohdan Janousek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform integrations with Wiz, Cisco, Palo Alto Networks, Couchbase, VMware, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-wiz-cisco-palo-alto-networks-couchbase-vmware</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-wiz-cisco-palo-alto-networks-couchbase-vmware"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[17 new Terraform integrations from 14 partners provide more options to automate and secure cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUnit Attachments Support for Publish Test Results]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67933</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/junit-attachments-support-for-publish-test-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T16:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve recently made some improvements to the Publish Test Results task in Azure Pipelines. This task now supports file attachments when publishing test results from a JUnit report.
The post JUnit Attachments Support for Publish Test Results appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Paquette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning the importance of training data under concept drift]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/learning-importance-of-training-data.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/learning-importance-of-training-data.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T18:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nishant Jain, Pre-doctoral Researcher, and Pradeep Shenoy, Research Scientist, Google Research




The constantly changing nature of the world around us poses a significant challenge for the development of AI models. Often, models are trained on longitudinal data with the hope that the training data used will accurately represent inputs the model may receive in the future. More generally, the default assumption that all training data are equally relevant often breaks in practice. For example, the figure below shows images from the CLEAR nonstationary learning benchmark, and it illustrates how visual features of objects evolve significantly over a 10 year span (a phenomenon we refer to as slow concept drift), posing a challenge for object categorization models. 








Sample ima…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault integrations with New Relic, Cloudbees, Coder, and more continue to strengthen customer security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-new-relic-cloudbees-coder-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-new-relic-cloudbees-coder-and-more"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight new HashiCorp Vault ecosystem integrations extend security use cases for customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DP-Auditorium: A flexible library for auditing differential privacy]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/dp-auditorium-flexible-library-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/dp-auditorium-flexible-library-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T22:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mónica Ribero Díaz, Research Scientist, Google Research





Differential privacy (DP) is a property of randomized mechanisms that limit the influence of any individual user’s information while processing and analyzing data. DP offers a robust solution to address growing concerns about data protection, enabling technologies across industries and government applications (e.g., the US census) without compromising individual user identities.  As its adoption increases, it’s important to identify the potential risks of developing mechanisms with faulty implementations. Researchers have recently found errors in the mathematical proofs of private mechanisms, and their implementations. For example, researchers compared six sparse vector technique (SVT) variations and found that only two…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[February patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68473</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/february-patches-for-azure-devops-server-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T21:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 Patch 2
The post February patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequential A/B Testing Keeps the World Streaming Netflix
Part 1: Continuous Data]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/cba6c7ed49df</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/sequential-a-b-testing-keeps-the-world-streaming-netflix-part-1-continuous-data-cba6c7ed49df?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T19:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Alpha Release February 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101141</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/camunda-alpha-release-february-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to announce the February 2024 alpha release of Camunda. Check out what's new.
The post Camunda Alpha Release February 2024 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing SafeTest: A Novel Approach to Front End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/37f9f88c152d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/introducing-safetest-a-novel-approach-to-front-end-testing-37f9f88c152d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T16:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workload identity federation for Azure deployments is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68479</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/workload-identity-federation-for-azure-deployments-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T07:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September, we announced the ability to configure Azure service connections that do not need a secret. Azure service connections that use workload identity federation are easier to manage and more secure. Many customers have adopted this feature and we’re excited to announce it is now generally available!
The post Workload identity federation for Azure deployments is now generally available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planning Your Camunda Proof of Concept]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=101054</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2024/02/planning-your-camunda-proof-of-concept/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T22:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over half of software projects fail. A well-planned and executed POC makes a difference, and this post will help show you how to plan yours.
The post Planning Your Camunda Proof of Concept appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock now supports Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL and Cohere embedding models]]></title>
        <id>88d3cbd7b505e228dadab86f0501d5938c543301</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/knowledge-bases-for-amazon-bedrock-now-supports-amazon-aurora-postgresql-and-cohere-embedding-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T21:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During AWS re:Invent 2023, we announced the general availability of Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock. With a knowledge base, you can securely connect foundation models (FMs) in Amazon Bedrock to your company data for Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG). In my previous post, I described how Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock manages the end-to-end RAG workflow […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Happy Lunar New Year, IaC generator, NFL’s digital athlete, AWS Cloud Clubs, and more — February 12, 2024]]></title>
        <id>568484dcfa30bc001b0bf56c13972382e5ce2537</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-happy-lunar-new-year-iac-generator-nfls-digital-athlete-aws-cloud-clubs-and-more-february-12-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T20:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Lunar New Year! Wishing you a year filled with joy, success, and endless opportunities! May the Year of the Dragon bring uninterrupted connections and limitless growth 🐉 ☁️ In case you missed it, here’s outstanding news you need to know as you plan your year in early 2024. AWS was named as a Leader […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform gains upgrades for module tests, explorer, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-gains-upgrades-for-module-tests-explorer-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-gains-upgrades-for-module-tests-explorer-and-more"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest Terraform Cloud and Enterprise enhancements help users leverage high-quality modules, monitor their workspace health, minimize management overhead, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing HashiCorp tools in Alpine Linux containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/installing-hashicorp-tools-in-alpine-linux-containers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/installing-hashicorp-tools-in-alpine-linux-containers"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the installation and verification workflow for any Linux distribution that does not include HashiCorp software in its package repository.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault chaos engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-chaos-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-chaos-engineering"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to make your Vault clusters more resilient with Gremlin chaos engineering tests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第246話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:11341664176591995253</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/11341664176591995253"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graph neural networks in TensorFlow]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/02/graph-neural-networks-in-tensorflow.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/02/graph-neural-networks-in-tensorflow.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T19:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dustin Zelle, Software Engineer, Google Research, and Arno Eigenwillig, Software Engineer, CoreML




Objects and their relationships are ubiquitous in the world around us, and relationships can be as important to understanding an object as its own attributes viewed in isolation — take for example transportation networks, production networks, knowledge graphs, or social networks. Discrete mathematics and computer science have a long history of formalizing such networks as graphs, consisting of nodes connected by edges in various irregular ways. Yet most machine learning (ML) algorithms allow only for regular and uniform relations between input objects, such as a grid of pixels, a sequence of words, or no relation at all. 




Graph neural networks, or GNNs for short, have emerged…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>