<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-07-25T02:02:06.731Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-25T02:02:06.731Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependable]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42367</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/703633290/0/sethsblog~Dependable/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T06:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a distinct skill. Something can be dependable without being extraordinary, rare or even a good value. It’s also one of the easiest skills to acquire, and often quite valuable if you stick with it. While sticking with dependable is sort of redundant, it’s also required.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bestseller energy]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43424</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/703572016/0/sethsblog~Bestseller-energy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T11:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Something magical happens when people are in alignment and an idea becomes a bestseller. When there’s a line out the door. When there’s a buzz in the room. When people are talking about the work you’re doing. At least some of the people. A restaurant is more fun. A course seems more important. A project […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2022.2 Release Candidate Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=266854</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/07/2022-2-rc/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T10:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can get the new build from our website, via the free Toolbox App, or by using snaps for Ubuntu.  To familiarize yourself with the most notable updates in v2022.2, browse the PyCharm 2022.2 EAP section of our blog. This release candidate also delivers some updates we haven’t previously covered, so read on for the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I believe things that aren’t true]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42363</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/703468120/0/sethsblog~I-believe-things-that-arent-true/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T08:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us do. The interesting challenge is that our brain doesn’t often make beliefs and tested reality feel like different things. It’s almost as if ‘true’ and ‘belief’ only became separate categories in our recent past. As our actions continue to bump against reality, and our culture has dramatically more interactions between and among […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physics Cost-Saving Tips]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2649/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2649/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/physics_cost_saving_tips.png" title="I got banned from the county fair for handing out Helium-2 balloons. Apparently the instant massive plasma explosions violated some local ordinance or something." alt="I got banned from the county fair for handing out Helium-2 balloons. Apparently the instant massive plasma explosions violated some local ordinance or something." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Training Generalist Agents with Multi-Game Decision Transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/training-generalist-agents-with-multi.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/training-generalist-agents-with-multi.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T22:17:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Winnie Xu, Student Researcher and Kuang-Huei Lee, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
Current deep reinforcement learning (RL) methods can train specialist artificial agents that excel at decision-making on various individual tasks in specific environments, such as Go or StarCraft. However, little progress has been made to extend these results to generalist agents that would not only be capable of performing many different tasks, but also upon a variety of environments with potentially distinct embodiments. 
Looking across recent progress in the fields of natural language processing, vision, and generative models (such as PaLM, Imagen, and Flamingo), we see that breakthroughs in making general-purpose models are often achieved by scaling up Transformer-based models an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formulating ‘Out of Memory Kill’ Prediction on the Netflix App as a Machine Learning Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/989599029109</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/formulating-out-of-memory-kill-prediction-on-the-netflix-app-as-a-machine-learning-problem-989599029109?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T21:16:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Aryan Mehra,  with Farnaz Karimdady Sharifabad, Prasanna Vijayanathan, Chaïna Wade, Vishal Sharma and Mike Schassberger]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Sent an AWS Snowcone into Orbit]]></title>
        <id>d05b293512d0481393cd06a097706cb42601bfa4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-we-sent-an-aws-snowcone-into-orbit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T18:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been a fan of space travel and the US space program since I was 4 or 5 years old. I remember reading about the Mercury and Gemini programs, and watched with excitement as Lunar Module Eagle landed on the Moon. Today, with the cost to reach Low Earth Orbit (LEO) seemingly declining with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 Release Candidate Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=265601</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/07/webstorm-2022-2-rc/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release date just around the corner, we’re happy to present the release candidate for WebStorm 2022.2. Unlike our previous EAP builds, you must have an active WebStorm license to use it. Otherwise, you’ll need to sign up for a 30-day free trial to install and run this build. DOWNLOAD WEBSTORM 2022.2 RC Let’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips &#038; tricks for using GitHub Projects for personal productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-21-tips-tricks-for-using-github-projects-for-personal-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-21-tips-tricks-for-using-github-projects-for-personal-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues is a core component of how developers get things done and, as we built more project planning capabilities into GitHub, we’ve found some fun and unique ways to use the new projects experience for personal productivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand’s Hidden Gems]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=266798</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/07/21/hidden-gems-in-goland/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all know how tricky it is to unlock the full power of an IDE. There will always be more features you haven’t fully explored yet. But we’ve all been in at least one situation where we discovered a tiny feature or action by accident and it pleasantly surprised us or saved us a ton […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Zharova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.2: The option to import multiple CSV files, New Modify UI, Playground and Script resolve modes, and more!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=264767</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/07/21/datagrip-2022-2-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, We’ve just released the second major update of 2022. Here’s a list of all the improvements introduced in 2022.2. For detailed descriptions of all new features and enhancements, please visit our What’s new page. The option to import multiple CSV files You can now select several CSV files and import them at once! Playground […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.1.4 Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=265641</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/07/phpstorm-2022-1-4-is-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T14:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released PhpStorm 2022.1.4, the fourth minor update for PhpStorm 2022.1. You can update by using the Toolbox App or from right inside the IDE. You can also download PhpStorm 2022.1.4 from our website. These are the most notable changes and bug fixes: Fixed: External diff tools settings being lost after IDE restart (IDEA-296696)  […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode 2022.2 Goes Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=266697</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/07/appcode-2022-2-goes-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T14:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, The Beta version of AppCode 2022.2 (build 222.3345.83) is available for download now. You can get it from our website, via the Toolbox App, or update from the 2022.2 EAP6 build via patch. This build addresses performance regressions related to project loading in AppCode. We’ve managed to improve the times for both initial and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.2 Release Candidate]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=266486</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/07/clion-2022-2-release-candidate/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.2 Release Candidate is now available for download! To install CLion 2022.2 RC (build 222.3345.93), download it from the website, update from our Toolbox App, or use this snap package (for Ubuntu). You can also update from CLion 2022.2 Beta via a patch. You need to have an active subscription or start a free […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2022.1.4 is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=266647</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/07/pycharm-2022-1-4-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharrm 2022.1.4, the fourth bug-fix update for PyCharm 2022.1, is now available! You can get the latest version from our website, via the Toolbox App, from inside the IDE, or by using snaps if you’re a Ubuntu user. Here are the most notable fixes: Fixed the issue causing text flickers in the Commit details pane […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Process Orchestration Needs Advanced Workflow Patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58811</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/why-process-orchestration-needs-advanced-workflow-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life is seldom a straight line, and the same is true for processes. Therefore, you must be able to accurately express all the things happening in your business processes for proper end-to-end process orchestration. This requires workflow patterns that go beyond basic control flow patterns (like sequence or condition). If your orchestration tool does not provide those advanced workflow patterns, you will experience confusion amongst developers, you will need to implement time-consuming workarounds, and you will end up with confusing models. Let’s explore this by examining an example of why these advanced workflow patterns matter in today’s blog post. Initial process example Let’s assume you’re processing incoming orders of hand-crafted goods to be shipped individually. Each order consists of many...
The post Why Process Orchestration Needs Advanced Workflow Patterns appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-M4 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-3-0-0-m4-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-3-0-0-m4-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T11:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-M4 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 161 enhancements, documentation improvements, dependency upgrades, and bug fixes. Notable new features include:


  
Support for Elasticsearch’s new Java client

  
Support for Flyway 9

  
Support for Hibernate 6.1


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 Release Candidate Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=265760</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/07/intellij-idea-2022-2-release-candidate/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T11:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 Release Candidate is now available!  Download the latest build from our website, via the Toolbox App, upgrade to it from inside the IDE, or use snaps for Ubuntu. The major release for v2022.2 is almost here, meaning that the Early Access Program is coming to a close. We’d like to thank […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-2-7-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-2-7-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T10:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.2 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 40 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud and Spring Cloud Kubernetes contributor Ryan Baxter]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-and-spring-cloud-kubernetes-contributor-ryan-baxter</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-and-spring-cloud-kubernetes-contributor-ryan-baxter"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to a person who knows more than most about the awesome implications of both the words “Spring” and “Cloud,” Spring Cloud Kubernetes lead Ryan Baxter (@ryanjbaxter).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.10 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-2-6-10-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-2-6-10-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T08:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.10 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 30 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting stuck on the title]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42359</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/703384024/0/sethsblog~Getting-stuck-on-the-title/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The brand name, the first name, the label… Is To Kill a Mockingbird a good title? By most measures of most committees, definitely not. And yet, it clearly and most definitely worked. Starbucks has nothing to do with Moby Dick. Nike is easy to mispronounce. The title is simply the thing you say when you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a Managed Detection and Response Service with Elastic XDR and Corelight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-a-managed-detection-and-response-service-with-elastic-xdr-and-corelight</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-a-managed-detection-and-response-service-with-elastic-xdr-and-corelight"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we discuss using the Elastic eXtended Detection and Response platform with the power of Corelight Network Detection and Response to build a mature Managed Detection and Response Service and bring its capabilities to users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdelwahhab Satta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observability can be the secret to enabling the board room]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-can-be-the-secret-to-enabling-the-board-room</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-can-be-the-secret-to-enabling-the-board-room"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The big questions can’t wait for quarterly reviews anymore — live insights can help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Weston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a Managed Detection and Response Service with Elastic XDR and Corelight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-a-managed-detection-and-response-service-with-elastic-xdr-and-corelight</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-a-managed-detection-and-response-service-with-elastic-xdr-and-corelight"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Managed Detection and Response Services (MDRS) extend well beyond the capacities of the traditional Managed Security Service Provider (MSSP) model. They strive for deeper infrastructure monitoring, response to detected threats, and a full SOC-grade portfolio of proactive capabilities such as threat hunting, forensics, and advanced analytics and reporting.

Elastic, which has historically been used as a powerful threat hunting platform, now provides a unified security solution that encapsulates security information and event management (SIEM) and endpoint security capabilities in the industry’s first free and open Limitless XDR platform.

The solution unifies prevention, detection, investigation, and response in one platform that can be the foundation of a massive scale MDRS. 

Below, I’l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdelwahhab Satta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observability can be the secret to enabling the board room]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-can-be-the-secret-to-enabling-the-board-room</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-can-be-the-secret-to-enabling-the-board-room"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For a long time, the best many organizations could do was to look at trailing business and operational data to understand enterprise performance or make proactive business decisions. But today, with the right technology, data streams in real-time — IT leaders can instantly elevate risks and opportunities to their boards.

This is where observability kicks in with answers. Observability enables organizations to collect metrics, logs, and traces with high dimensionality to detect root causes faster and answer the unknown unknowns. With Application Performance Monitoring (APM) for log, infrastructure, and digital experience monitoring, decision-making becomes less about having a crystal ball and more about having a live view of the state of the enterprise. Observability is key to enabling d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Weston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The likable brand (or person)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43402</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/703342366/0/sethsblog~The-likable-brand-or-person/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Likability is a weird quality. Plenty of people are fans of Aretha Franklin or Bob Dylan, but it’s not because either of them spent a lot of time mailing out Christmas cards or being particularly warm to their fans. Google doesn’t do tech support and plenty of popular high-end restaurants got that way by being […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.0-M4 available now!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-batch-5-0-0-m4-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-batch-5-0-0-m4-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T19:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M4 is now available from our milestone repository.

This fourth milestone introduces several improvements for Java Records support. It also comes with a number of enhancements, bug fixes, dependency upgrades, and documentation updates. For more details about all the changes, see the release notes.
Java Records Support Improvement

The support for Java records as items in a chunk-oriented step was initially introduced in v4.3, but that support was limited, due to the fact that v4 has Java 8 as a baseline. In Java 8, records were not even in preview yet. That initial support was based on reflection tricks to create Java records and populate them with data, without having access to the j…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1.4 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=265572</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/07/webstorm-2022-1-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T18:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1.4, the fourth bug-fix update for WebStorm 2022.1, is now available! You can update to v2022.1.4 by using the Toolbox App, installing it right from the IDE, or downloading it from our website. Here are the most notable fixes available in v2022.1.4: WebStorm no longer crashes on macOS High Sierra (IDEA-296489). Fixed the Run […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-for-graphql-1-0-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-for-graphql-1-0-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of everyone involved, I’m pleased to announce the first maintenance release of Spring for GraphQL, it is now available from Maven Central. This version will be shipped with Spring Boot 2.7.2.

This release includes 10 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-graphql tag.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Annotated – July 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=266438</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/07/php-annotated-july-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings everyone! Welcome to the July installment of PHP Annotated, where we’ll catch up on the most interesting things that have happened in the PHP world over the last month, including curated news, articles, tools, and videos. News PHP 8.2.0 Alpha 2 and PHP 8.2.0 Alpha 3 have been released The third and final alpha […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cribl, MongoDB, and Thales Highlight New HCP and Enterprise Vault Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cribl-mongodb-thales-highlight-new-hcp-enterprise-vault-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cribl-mongodb-thales-highlight-new-hcp-enterprise-vault-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Vault ecosystem continues to show strong growth with 12 new HCP, Enterprise, and OSS integrations added this quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how academic research is shaping GitHub Discussions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-20-heres-how-academic-research-is-shaping-github-discussions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-20-heres-how-academic-research-is-shaping-github-discussions/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We strive to understand how developers collaborate and work on GitHub, and we sometimes partner with academics to better understand how we can improve our products. Here's how we did that to build and evolve GitHub Discussions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第213話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270375685361384268</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270375685361384268"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: I Can’t Believe It’s Not Real Data! An Introduction to Synthetic Data]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=266234</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/07/webinar-i-can-t-believe-it-s-not-real-data-an-introduction-to-synthetic-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T13:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easy access to relevant, safe data is a major bottleneck hindering developers and data scientists. But what if you could generate your own accurate, privacy-protected, shareable data?  Synthetic data can provide an inexpensive alternative to real sets of data that can’t be used due to its sensitivity or regulations. Such data is used for training […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Cloud Automation with amazon.aws 4.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-4.0.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-4.0.0"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post goes through what has changed and highlights what’s new in the 4.0.0 release of this Content Collection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detachment and commitment]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41536</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/703296784/0/sethsblog~Detachment-and-commitment/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working professionals develop emotional detachment. It’s the only way to thrive in the work. Emotional detachment helps us remember that we are not our work, and that feedback is useful, not an attack. Commitment permits us to keep going (especially when we’re asked to provide more effort than we planned). It’s easy to confuse the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Kubernetes Native Java (Redux, 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-tips-kubernetes-native-java-redux-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-tips-kubernetes-native-java-redux-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) looks at some of the amazing opportunities for building Spring Boot applications intended for production in Kubernetes in mid 2022. 

The code, as usual, is available on the spring-tips Github organization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chemicals]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2648/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2648/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/chemicals.png" title="It's hard to believe, but lots of kids these days ONLY know how to buy prepackaged molecules." alt="It's hard to believe, but lots of kids these days ONLY know how to buy prepackaged molecules." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 R6a Instances Powered by 3rd Gen AMD EPYC Processors for Memory-Intensive Workloads]]></title>
        <id>644f029ceb1ef3d47149b3db6e5a0d485f62f874</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-r6a-instances-powered-by-3rd-gen-amd-epyc-processors-for-memory-intensive-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T22:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched the general-purpose Amazon EC2 M6a instances at AWS re:Invent 2021 and compute-intensive C6a instances in February of this year. These instances are powered by the 3rd Gen AMD EPYC processors running at frequencies up to 3.6 GHz to offer up to 35 percent better price performance versus the previous generation instances. Today, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplified Transfer Learning for Chest Radiography Model Development]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/simplified-transfer-learning-for-chest.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/simplified-transfer-learning-for-chest.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Akib Uddin, Product Manager and Andrew Sellergren, Software Engineer, Google Health 
Every year, nearly a billion chest X-ray (CXR) images are taken globally to aid in the detection and management of health conditions ranging from collapsed lungs to infectious diseases. Generally, CXRs are cheaper and more accessible than other forms of medical imaging. However, existing challenges continue to impede the optimal use of CXRs. For example, in some areas, trained radiologists that can accurately interpret CXR images are in short supply. In addition, interpretation variability between experts, workflow differences between institutions, and the presence of rare conditions familiar only to subspecialists all contribute to making high-quality CXR interpretation a challenge. 
 Recent res…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 strategic ways to level up your CI/CD pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-19-6-strategic-ways-to-level-up-your-ci-cd-pipeline/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-19-6-strategic-ways-to-level-up-your-ci-cd-pipeline/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From incorporating accessibility testing to implementing blue-green deployment models, here are six practical and strategic ways to improve your CI/CD pipeline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring Azure Application Gateway with Consul-Terraform-Sync]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/configuring-azure-application-gateway-with-consul-terraform-sync</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/configuring-azure-application-gateway-with-consul-terraform-sync"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synchronize HCP Consul services as backend address pools for Microsoft Azure Application Gateway using Consul-Terraform-Sync (CTS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 19th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/19/this-week-in-spring-july-19th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/19/this-week-in-spring-july-19th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! This week I’m trying to wind down some threads and take some vacation with my family. It’s going to be an amazing time, indeed! But that doesn’t stop the deluge of novelties and news in the wide world of Springdom, so we’ve got a lot to cover this week. Let’s get to it!

Before I go, though, I have a new “Spring Tips” episode dropping Wednesday morning, at midnight, so be on the look out :) 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Nate Schutta: The Thinking Person’s Architect, My Friend, and Teammate

  
Blog: Kubernetes Gateway API Graduates to Beta

  
JWT Authentication with OAuth2 Resource Server and an external Authorization Server

  
Kotlin & Spring Boot: Building a Rest API

  
Release v1.5.1 · toedter/spring-hateoas-jsonapi

  
Spring Boot – Keycloak Integration Testing with Testcontainers

  
Spring Boot – Testing Redis With Testcontainers

  
Spring Data 2022.0.0-M5 2021.2.2 and 2021.1.6 released

  
Spring Data Rest – Serializing the Entity ID

  
Spring Framework 6.0.0-M5 and 5.3.22 available now

  
Spring Native 0.12.1 available now

  
Spring Security 5.8.0-M1 and 6.0.0-M6 are released

  
Spring Tips: Kubernetes Native Java (Redux, 2022)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you an autodidact?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43044</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/703217714/0/sethsblog~Are-you-an-autodidact/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T08:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s far easier now than it’s ever been before. (You can look it up.) [Bonus PS: highlighting some climate-related art and artists who helped with the Almanac: Von Wong (launching a new piece this week), Justin Brice Guariglia and Shepard Fairey.] [Bonus PS2: A major addendum to the Almanac just went live today. It’s free […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Eleni Syrmou on why working at Elastic means Greek ocean views and a focus on family]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-someone-like-me-eleni-syrmou-focus-on-family</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-someone-like-me-eleni-syrmou-focus-on-family"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea of Home, Dinner is to empower Elasticians with the flexibility they need to find a balance of work and personal lives. For Eleni, that’s walking to the beach every morning and being able to have lunch with her family.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFOs and CIOs have a trillion reasons to team up to win the race to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-trillion-dollar-reason-cfos-and-cios-should-work-together-to-drive-the-move-to-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-trillion-dollar-reason-cfos-and-cios-should-work-together-to-drive-the-move-to-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Procurement and finance teams have already decided that systems are moving to cloud, often ahead of IT or Security teams that want to maintain on-prem servers. ITDMs need to enable these business requirements for their leadership teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trish Sammer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Eleni Syrmou on why working at Elastic means Greek ocean views and a focus on family]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-someone-like-me-eleni-syrmou-focus-on-family</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-someone-like-me-eleni-syrmou-focus-on-family"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Eleni Syrmou spent the majority of her working life living a plane ride away from the rest of her family. She lived in London, UK for 15 years before moving back to Southern Europe—a tiny house in Sicily to be exact. But her former employer wanted her back in the office, and back in London. 

After their reluctance to let her continue to work remotely, Eleni decided it was time to find a company that celebrated working remotely. She joined Elastic in May 2021 as Lead Recruiter, Southern Europe. 

Now, she works from a converted stone farmhouse that is a two minute walk from the beach and surrounded by orchards, potato farms, and olive groves.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt853162c57fef5219/62d584d40d8ac2360dc72971/IMG_20220424_090942.jpg,IMG_20220424_09094…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFOs and CIOs have a trillion reasons to team up to win the race to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-trillion-dollar-reason-cfos-and-cios-should-work-together-to-drive-the-move-to-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-trillion-dollar-reason-cfos-and-cios-should-work-together-to-drive-the-move-to-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
What’s the potential business value of moving to the cloud? According to McKinsey, it’s a cool $1 trillion that’s up for grabs.

It’s such a huge number that it may seem like pie in the sky. But companies are already positioning themselves to grab a piece of that pie for themselves. The most recent example is FedEx, which made headlines earlier this month when it announced that it plans to move entirely to cloud-native structures within two years. The shipping giant estimates that it will save about $400 million annually. 

CFOs may be excited about the cost-benefit analysis, but IT teams have a lot to gain, too. From operational efficiencies to innovation, CFOs and CIOs should be building this plan together. 
Why early adopters win big — and how you can be one of them
Remember that whop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trish Sammer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ICML 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/google-at-icml-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/google-at-icml-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:54:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cat Armato, Program Manager, University Relations 
Google is a leader in machine learning (ML) research with groups innovating across virtually all aspects of the field, from theory to application. We build machine learning systems to solve deep scientific and engineering challenges in areas of language, music, visual processing, algorithm development, and more. Core to our approach is to actively engage with the broader research community by open-sourcing datasets and models, publishing our discoveries, and actively participating in leading conferences. 
Google is proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of the thirty-ninth International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML 2022), a premier annual conference, which is being held this week in Baltimore, Maryland. Google has a strong presenc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.8.0-M1 and 6.0.0-M6 are released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/18/spring-security-5-8-0-m1-and-6-0-0-m6-are-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/18/spring-security-5-8-0-m1-and-6-0-0-m6-are-released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.8.0-M1 and 6.0.0-M6 are available now.



This release includes dependency upgrades, bug fixes, and enhancements. Here are a few noteworthy changes:





Deferred SecurityContext lookup



SecurityContextHolderStrategy Bean lookup



AuthorizationManager support



SHA-256 RememberMe support



Release automation improvements





See the 5.8.0-M1 and 6.0.0-M6 release notes for more details.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recruiting for Early Careers at HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/recruiting-for-early-careers-at-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/recruiting-for-early-careers-at-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second year of HashiCorp’s Early Career Program includes some 70 interns. The Early Career recruiting team shares details and offers tips for prospective candidates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – July 18, 2022]]></title>
        <id>0d85312f4833bb666f3613acb995ab332f610620</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-july-18-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, AWS Summit New York was held in person at the Javits Center with thousands of attendees and over 100 sponsors and partners. During the keynote, Martin Beeby, AWS Principal Developer Advocate, talked about how innovations in cloud infrastructure enable customers to adapt to challenges and seize new opportunities. It included Liz Fong-Jones‘s great […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Monthly: July 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-18-open-source-monthly-july-2022-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-18-open-source-monthly-july-2022-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July's Open Source Monthly features Zag.js, which leverages state machines to make framework agnostic components.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where do jobs come from?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42351</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/703134812/0/sethsblog~Where-do-jobs-come-from/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It must be more than a coincidence that there are almost enough jobs for everyone–a billion more jobs on Earth than there were a generation ago. Unemployment is debilitating and a real problem, but even high unemployment in many countries still means that most people have a job. Many times, it’s a job that didn’t […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capri Suns]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2647/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2647/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/capri_suns.png" title="[As security is dragging me away] &quot;Come on, at least I didn't make the mistake in the other direction!&quot;" alt="[As security is dragging me away] &quot;Come on, at least I didn't make the mistake in the other direction!&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little billboards]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43263</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/703058416/0/sethsblog~Little-billboards/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the West Side Highway in Manhattan, there’s currently a billboard for some sort of placebo supplement. In the corner is a QR code for more information. Unless the person in the passenger seat has a telephoto lens on their phone, there’s no way in the world that this is going to work. My late […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The crossroads]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=31800</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/702974886/0/sethsblog~The-crossroads/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which way to head? We live in a world characterized by mistrust, ill health, economic uncertainty, inflicted racial trauma, generational shift and the existential crisis caused by carbon. Not to mention the stress and dissolution of traditional pillars like organized education, office space and live gatherings. And we live in a world with breathtaking medical […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2022.0.0-M5 2021.2.2 and 2021.1.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/15/spring-data-2022-0-0-m5-2021-2-2-and-2021-1-6-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/15/spring-data-2022-0-0-m5-2021-2-2-and-2021-1-6-released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the 5th Milestone of Spring Data 2022.0.0 as well as service releases 2021.2.2 and 2021.1.6. The service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades. One notable upgrade in 2022.0.0-M5 is the move to Hibernate 6.

For your convenience, the next Spring Boot releases are going to pick up 2021.2.2 and 2021.1.6 in the upcoming days. To round things off, here are the links to the individual modules, changelogs, and documentation:
2022.0.0-M5


  
Spring Data Commons 3.0 M5 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 3.0 M5 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data MongoDB 4.0 M5 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data KeyValue 3.0 M5 - Artifacts - Java…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minkowski Space]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2646/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2646/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/minkowski_space.png" title="My liege, we were able to follow the ship into Minkowski space, but now they've jumped to Hilbert space and they could honestly be anywhere." alt="My liege, we were able to follow the ship into Minkowski space, but now they've jumped to Hilbert space and they could honestly be anywhere." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Boards Summer Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64636</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-boards-summer-update-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over these last few months, our team has been working hard at delivering new value in Azure Boards. We would like to take a moment to highlight some of the most recently released features. Be sure to check out the Features Timeline for updates and our product roadmap.
The post Azure Boards Summer Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards Reliability in Deep Learning Systems]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/towards-reliability-in-deep-learning.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/towards-reliability-in-deep-learning.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T17:07:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dustin Tran and Balaji Lakshminarayanan, Research Scientists, Google Research 
Deep learning models have made impressive progress in vision, language, and other modalities, particularly with the rise of large-scale pre-training. Such models are most accurate when applied to test data drawn from the same distribution as their training set. However, in practice, the data confronting models in real-world settings rarely match the training distribution. In addition, the models may not be well-suited for applications where predictive performance is only part of the equation. For models to be reliable in deployment, they must be able to accommodate shifts in data distribution and make useful decisions in a broad array of scenarios.  
In “Plex: Towards Reliability Using Pre-trained Larg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research: How GitHub Copilot helps improve developer productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-14-research-how-github-copilot-helps-improve-developer-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-14-research-how-github-copilot-helps-improve-developer-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We surveyed more than 2,000 developers about whether GitHub Copilot helped them be more productive and improved their coding. Then, we matched this qualitative feedback and subjective perception with quantitative data around objective usage measurements and productivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Azure Stack Hub Provider 1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-azure-stack-hub-provider-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-azure-stack-hub-provider-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new HashiCorp Terraform Azure Stack provider 1.0 includes several provider behavior improvements, 19 new resources, and supports a new service for Key Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Nate Schutta: The Thinking Person's Architect, My Friend, and Teammate]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/14/a-bootiful-podcast-nate-schutta-the-thinking-person-s-architect-my-friend-and-teammate</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/14/a-bootiful-podcast-nate-schutta-the-thinking-person-s-architect-my-friend-and-teammate"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to his friend, teammate, and architect extraordinaire, Nate Schutta (@ntschutta)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.0-M5 and 5.3.22 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/14/spring-framework-6-0-0-m5-and-5-3-22-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/14/spring-framework-6-0-0-m5-and-5-3-22-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T09:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.0-M5 and 5.3.22 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.22 includes 45 fixes and improvements and is a recommended upgrade for all Spring production scenarios.

Spring Framework 6.0.0-M5 includes 85 additional fixes and improvements specific to the 6.0 branch.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Wins Microsoft Azure OSS US Partner of the Year for 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-microsoft-azure-oss-us-partner-of-the-year-for-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-microsoft-azure-oss-us-partner-of-the-year-for-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp has been chosen as the 2022 Microsoft US (MSUS) Partner Award winner OSS on Azure and a 2022 Microsoft OSS on Azure Partner of the Year Award finalist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rewriting Image Captions for Visual Question Answering Data Creation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/rewriting-image-captions-for-visual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/rewriting-image-captions-for-visual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T19:24:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Soravit Beer Changpinyo and Doron Kukliansky‎, Senior Software Engineers, Google Research 
Visual Question Answering (VQA) is a useful machine learning (ML) task that requires a model to answer a visual question about an image. What makes it challenging is its multi-task and open-ended nature; it involves solving multiple technical research questions in computer vision and natural language understanding simultaneously. Yet, progress on this task would enable a wide range of applications, from assisting the blind and the visually-impaired or communicating with robots to enhancing the user’s visual experience with external knowledge. 
Effective and robust VQA systems cannot exist without high-quality, semantically and stylistically diverse large-scale training data of image-questio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When localhost isn't what it seems in Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/when-localhost-isnt-what-it-seems-in-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/when-localhost-isnt-what-it-seems-in-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2  and the advent of automation execution environments, some behaviors are now different for. This blog explains the use case around using localhost and options for sharing data and persistent data storage, for VM-based Ansible Automation Platform 2  deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Gruner + Jahr Chose Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58130</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/why-gruner-jahr-chose-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new blog series, we explore the reasons why customers are migrating to Camunda 8. For our first installment of Why Camunda 8, we talked to Gruner + Jahr, one of the largest premium magazine publishers in Europe. G+J includes such established (German) print and digital brands as STERN, GEO, BRIGITTE, ESSEN & TRINKEN, and SCHÖNER WOHNEN, as well as younger brands such as CHEFKOCH, BARBARA, BEEF, 11FREUNDE. In addition to the numerous print and digital media offerings, G+J offers products and licenses such as the SCHÖNER WOHNEN collection. The digital business contributes more than half of revenues and is exhibiting continued strong growth. Indeed, the company’s digital products lead the rankings in all publishing segments, from news through...
The post Why Gruner + Jahr Chose Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Schroth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Native 0.12.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/13/spring-native-0-12-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/13/spring-native-0-12-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Native 0.12.1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release.

This release includes 15 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades to Spring Boot 2.7.1 and Native Build Tools 0.9.13. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 information and operational technology trends making waves in manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-information-and-operational-technology-trends-in-manufacturing</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-information-and-operational-technology-trends-in-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Find out what's top of mind for manufacturing companies as they actively drive IT and OT convergence for increased productivity, faster innovation, and a more trustworthy customer experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search and replicate data between your Elastic Cloud and on-prem deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-and-replicate-data-between-your-elastic-cloud-and-on-prem-deployments</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-and-replicate-data-between-your-elastic-cloud-and-on-prem-deployments"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers can now replicate data from on-prem to cloud (and vice versa) and search data across their cloud and on-prem clusters, all from a single search interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 information and operational technology trends making waves in manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-information-and-operational-technology-trends-in-manufacturing</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-information-and-operational-technology-trends-in-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The convergence of information technologies (IT) and operational technologies (OT) sits at the core of the Industry 4.0 vision (industrial Internet of Things). This gradual convergence began more than a decade ago, and according to a recent McKinsey study, investments in industrialization paid rich dividends to the early adopters of Industry 4.0.*

But this process changed dramatically with the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic, which created a massive, multiyear ripple effect on worldwide economies, forcing manufacturers to reevaluate their priorities.

How are manufacturers adapting to today’s industrial world? Here are their top three priorities as they accelerate IT/OT convergence for increased productivity, faster innovation, and a more trustworthy customer experience.

[Related articl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search and replicate data between your Elastic Cloud and on-prem deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-and-replicate-data-between-your-elastic-cloud-and-on-prem-deployments</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/search-and-replicate-data-between-your-elastic-cloud-and-on-prem-deployments"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are pleased to announce the general availability of cross-cluster search (CCS) and cross-cluster replication (CCR) for your Elasticsearch clusters across any deployment environment. Starting today, you can easily search and replicate data between Elasticsearch clusters, even when they reside in different environments, such as on-premises, public cloud, as well as hybrid and multi-cloud.

In this blog, we’ll review some of the fundamentals regarding CCS and CCR. We’ll also take a look at how to apply this functionality to your Elasticsearch, Observability, and Security use cases.

[Related article: Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud 8.3: Search & replicate across any cluster]

Cross-cluster search
With this new release, CCS empowers you with a single view of your data — across all yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Content archived for Azure DevOps previous versions]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64684</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/content-archived-for-azure-devops-previous-versions/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T21:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​In April of this year, we completed a major project to archive older versions of our content. 
The post Content archived for Azure DevOps previous versions appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[July patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64626</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/july-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T18:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
In Test Runs APIs, the continuation token being returned was greater than the “maxLastUpdatedDate” value that was specified.
The post July patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisiting Mask Transformer from a Clustering Perspective]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/revisiting-mask-transformer-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/revisiting-mask-transformer-from.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Qihang Yu, Student Researcher, and Liang-Chieh Chen, Research Scientist, Google Research 
Panoptic segmentation is a computer vision problem that serves as a core task for many real-world applications. Due to its complexity, previous work often divides panoptic segmentation into semantic segmentation (assigning semantic labels, such as “person” and “sky”, to every pixel in an image) and instance segmentation (identifying and segmenting only countable objects, such as “pedestrians” and “cars”, in an image), and further divides it into several sub-tasks. Each sub-task is processed individually, and extra modules are applied to merge the results from each sub-task stage. This process is not only complex, but it also introduces many hand-designed priors when processing sub-tasks and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Detect and Resolve Issues Quickly with Log Anomaly Detection and Recommendations from Amazon DevOps Guru]]></title>
        <id>f8f3e67b2d22e5494e1d6a32842aa2c9ac55f021</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-detect-and-resolve-issues-quickly-with-log-anomaly-detection-and-recommendations-from-amazon-devops-guru/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T15:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing a new feature, Log Anomaly Detection and Recommendations for Amazon DevOps Guru. With this feature, you can find anomalies throughout relevant logs within your app, and get targeted recommendations to resolve issues. Here’s a quick look at this feature: AWS launched DevOps Guru, a fully managed AIOps platform service, in December […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift Serverless – Now Generally Available with New Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>ab73365aa62a13a08dcff00f5a2037ca5ae573ee</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-redshift-serverless-now-generally-available-with-new-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T15:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year at re:Invent, we introduced the preview of Amazon Redshift Serverless, a serverless option of Amazon Redshift that lets you analyze data at any scale without having to manage data warehouse infrastructure. You just need to load and query your data, and you pay only for what you use. This allows more companies to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Cloud WAN : A Managed WAN Service]]></title>
        <id>e70e25bfbed198650cc3b5bd252108ee9fcb14b5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-cloud-wan-a-managed-wan-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T14:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update July 13, 2022 – we have added a list of blog posts and technical resources provided by our partners, in order to provide readers with additional information on this service. I am pleased to announce the availability of AWS Cloud WAN, a new network service that makes it easy to build and operate wide […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 12th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/12/this-week-in-spring-july-12th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/12/this-week-in-spring-july-12th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you? This week I’m writing you from sunny Seattle, Washington, where we’re having our next installment of the SpringOne Tour series. It’s been a ton of fun seeing all these fun and friendly faces again and getting to see people, many of whom I haven’t seen since before the pandemic! I’ve also had a lot of fun seeing some friends from some of the big cloud companies here, Microsoft and AWS. It’s always interesting to learn how people are using the latest and greatest from Spring to build amazing systems and software targeting these cloud platforms.

We’ve got a lot to cover this week so let’s dive right into it!


  
In last week’s podcast, I talked to Kubernetes contributor and fellow Tanzu Developer Advocate Leigh Capili

  
Distributed Tracing With OpenTelemetry, Spring Cloud Sleuth, Kafka, and Jaeger

  
Ingress vs. Load Balancer in Kubernetes

  
Instantiating Multiple Beans of the Same Class with Spring Annotations

  
Curious about when and why to use Java 14 Records vs. Lombok? Check out this article

  
I put together this little example , thanks to Reactor lead Simon Baslé, showing how to handle pagination with the expand operator in Project Reactor: Pagination in a Reactive Application. It looks at how to eleganrly expand the contents of a reactive stream as new data (in a data pagination scenario) becomes available.

  
Spring Shell 2.1.0-RC1 is now available

  
Pushing a Docker Image to a Self-Hosted Registry

  
Spring for Apache Kafka 2.9 Release Candidate Available

  
This Apache Maven Survival Guide is quite interesting, to me at least!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58431</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-platform-8-1-0-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3. If you’d like to get started with Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3 right away, you can sign up for a free trial now. Create Process Instance Starting at User-Defined Elements An often requested feature is now available as a preview with Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3: create a process instance starting at user-defined elements. When creating a process instance through the CreateProcessInstance RPC, the process instance is started at the default none start event. For testing purposes, you may want to start at one (or multiple) of the other elements. This feature is now available through both the CreateProcessInstance RPC and the CreateProcessInstanceWithResult RPC. It is available for use in the Zeebe Java client...
The post Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58439</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-preview1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1. Camunda Optimize provides business activity monitoring for workflows, supporting continuous process improvement by providing transparency into your automated workflows and decisions. Business-friendly reports, dashboards, and alerts make it possible to identify process bottlenecks, improve end-to-end processes, and evaluate the success of your process automation initiative. If you’re a user of Camunda 7 – Enterprise Edition, you can download the Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 release right away with your customer credentials. If not, start your free 30-day trial of Camunda Platform 8, which includes Optimize. What’s New? Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 makes the process overview more readable, introduces one-click collection and dashboard creation, and provides an advanced look at a feature that lets you...
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58401</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-desktop-modeler-5-1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce the release of Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.1. This release focuses on providing a smooth and intuitive modeling experience through several minor and major enhancements, such as the new multi-select context pad.
The post Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Modeler Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58296</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-automation-platform-7-18-0-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.18. 
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building resilience for applications and services with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-resilience-for-applications-and-services-with-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-resilience-for-applications-and-services-with-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recently concluded third-party survey managed and analyzed by Socratic Technologies, over 1,400 Elastic customers shared their observability experiences. Take a look at the key takeaways from the survey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building resilience for applications and services with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-resilience-for-applications-and-services-with-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-resilience-for-applications-and-services-with-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Correlating data across multiple silos and applications to derive meaningful and actionable insights is an ongoing struggle. These challenges are only set to increase as high-speed connectivity becomes more ubiquitous and enables  data-heavy, digital experiences. 

In a recent third-party survey managed and analyzed by Socratic Technologies, over 1,400 Elastic customers shared their observability experiences, revealing quantifiable benefits that directly contributed to business outcomes. Elastic Observability is the world’s most widely deployed observability platform, built on the proven Elastic Stack — to break down silos and enable near real-time actionable insights. 

[Download the complete report for Elastic Observability.]

66% improved MTTx metrics brought by unified visibility
Cus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – July 11, 2022]]></title>
        <id>29f6affb960d165cfdeb50c0f58bea5e4ec5c744</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-july-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T18:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! In France, we know summer has started when you see the Tour de France bike race on TV or in a city nearby. This year, the tour stopped in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraforming clouds with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/terraforming-clouds-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/terraforming-clouds-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations use Terraform for quick infrastructure provisioning every day, but if we combine it with the power of Ansible, we can see that it builds into an efficient workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 ways to optimize your Elastic Cloud costs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-ways-to-optimize-your-elastic-cloud-costs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-ways-to-optimize-your-elastic-cloud-costs"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud comes with many benefits, including the ability to lower your total cost of ownership. Learn the top five ways you can optimize your cloud cost while maintaining performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanda Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 ways to optimize your Elastic Cloud costs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-ways-to-optimize-your-elastic-cloud-costs</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/top-5-ways-to-optimize-your-elastic-cloud-costs"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Cloud is the best and most cost effective way to consume Elastic. If you’re already using or are considering Elastic Cloud, here are some recommendations on optimizing costs.

Elastic Cloud uses resource-based pricing, where you pay for the infrastructure resources consumed to run the Elastic Stack capabilities for your use case. Therefore, the best way to optimize Elastic Cloud costs is to streamline resource consumption. 

You can reduce your resource consumption by leveraging our global presence and several cost-saving capabilities. Here are the top five recommendations: 

[Related article: How does Elastic Cloud pricing work?]

1) Use searchable snapshots and data tiers to optimize storage costs
You can optimize storage, search performance, and depth of insight from the data …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanda Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​Deep Hierarchical Planning from Pixels]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/deep-hierarchical-planning-from-pixels.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/deep-hierarchical-planning-from-pixels.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T18:25:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Danijar Hafner, Student Researcher, Google Research 
Research into how artificial agents can make decisions has evolved rapidly through advances in deep reinforcement learning. Compared to generative ML models like GPT-3 and Imagen, artificial agents can directly influence their environment through actions, such as moving a robot arm based on camera inputs or clicking a button in a web browser. While artificial agents have the potential to be increasingly helpful to people, current methods are held back by the need to receive detailed feedback in the form of frequently provided rewards to learn successful strategies. For example, despite large computational budgets, even powerful programs such as AlphaGo are limited to a few hundred moves until receiving their next reward. 
In co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get visibility into AWS Lambda serverless functions with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of Elastic Observability’s new capabilities around monitoring AWS Lambda functions in your cloud-native environment. Get detailed insights into your distributed, microservices architecture and applications through our APM capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akhilesh Pokhariyal,Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You have more ways to bake this cake: Bring your own Enterprise Search connector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bring-your-own-enterprise-search-connector</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bring-your-own-enterprise-search-connector"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Enterprise Search Connectors framework was created to help users bring their own connectors, or customize the ones that already exist. Read on to learn how to implement this framework, using GitLab as an example.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryna Cherniavska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get visibility into AWS Lambda serverless functions with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Adoption of AWS Lambda functions in cloud-native applications has increased exponentially over the past few years. Serverless functions, such as the AWS Lambda service, provide a high level of abstraction from the underlying infrastructure and orchestration, given these tasks are managed by the cloud provider. Software development teams can then focus on the implementation of business and application logic. 
Some additional benefits include billing for serverless functions based on the actual compute and memory resources consumed, along with automatic on-demand scaling. One difficulty in using serverless functions, however, is making them observable in the wider end-to-end microservices architecture context. 
,Elastic APM for AWS Lambda: The architecture
In a previous blog post, we showe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akhilesh Pokhariyal,Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You have more ways to bake this cake: Bring your own Enterprise Search connector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bring-your-own-enterprise-search-connector</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bring-your-own-enterprise-search-connector"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The Elastic Enterprise Search team is working on an exciting new project: Elastic Enterprise Search Connectors framework. It appeared in version 8.2 as a Technical Preview, and it has been significantly expanded in 8.3.

Elastic Enterprise Search, and specifically Workplace Search, is a solution that helps harness the power of Elasticsearch to search over company documents. The documents may come from a variety of sources, and the primary means of ingesting data into Workplace Search are connectors, which are easy-to-use, no-code, GUI-driven features that makes ingesting data a breeze. 

Before we dive into the details, here’s an important vocabulary to be familiar with:

Content source - data indexed into Elastic Enterprise Search and backed by a third-party service like GitHub, GoogleD…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maryna Cherniavska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M1 Mac Instances]]></title>
        <id>d02cbfaaaed8a473decb31bee87fb99c5ce2448d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-m1-mac-instances/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T20:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, during the re:Invent 2021 conference, I wrote a blog post to announce the preview of EC2 M1 Mac instances. I know many of you requested access to the preview, and we did our best but could not satisfy everybody. However, the wait is over. I have the pleasure of announcing the general availability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Kubernetes contributor and fellow Tanzu Developer Advocate Leigh Capili]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-contributor-and-fellow-tanzu-developer-advocate-leigh-capili</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-contributor-and-fellow-tanzu-developer-advocate-leigh-capili"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow teammate and Kubernetes ecosystem legend Leigh Capili (@capileigh) about Gitops, Kubernetes, Puppet/Chef, continuous delivery, how zoom scales if you deploy on-prem, being a developer advocate, Flux, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling Creative Expression with Concept Activation Vectors]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/enabling-creative-expression-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/enabling-creative-expression-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T18:31:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Been Kim, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team, and Alison Lentz, Senior Staff Strategist, Google Research, Mural Team  
Advances in computer vision and natural language processing continue to unlock new ways of exploring billions of images available on public and searchable websites. Today’s visual search tools make it possible to search with your camera, voice, text, images, or multiple modalities at the same time. However, it remains difficult to input subjective concepts, such as visual tones or moods, into current systems. For this reason, we have been working collaboratively with artists, photographers, and image researchers to explore how machine learning (ML) might enable people to use expressive queries as a way of visually exploring datasets. 
Today, we are i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top tips for creating a healthy and sustainable open source community]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-07-healthy-and-sustainable-communities/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-07-healthy-and-sustainable-communities/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T18:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the six key themes, and tips for each, that ensure sustainable and healthy open source communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Kafka 2.9 Release Candidate Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/spring-for-apache-kafka-2-9-release-candidate-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/spring-for-apache-kafka-2-9-release-candidate-available"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that the release candidate Spring for Apache Kafka 2.9.0 is now available (2.9.0-RC1) in the Spring Milestone Repo.



This version is not provided by Spring Boot dependency management, but it can be used with Boot 2.7 (or 2.6), as long as you override the Kafka dependencies as described in this appendix, especially if you are using the embedded Kafka broker.



Notable Changes




This version uses the 3.2.0 kafka-clients version



Non-blocking retry bootstrapping is now more robust



New Error Handler Mode





By default, after an error, the DefaultErrorHandler performs seeks on the remaining records from the last poll and re-fetches them from the broker on the next poll.
With high error rates and large max.poll.records, this can cause unnecessary strain on the network.
For this reason, the error handler has a new property seekAfterError, when set to false, instead of seeking the records, the remaining records are retained in memory and the consumer paused for the next poll (or multiple polls if the error handler is configured to use the ContainerPausingBackOffHandler).





Pausing Containers





By default, when you pause() a container, it actually pauses when all the records from the previous poll have been processed.
This version adds the pauseImmediate container property, which, when true, causes the container to pause after the current record is processed.



For information about all changes in this release, see What’s New.



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.0-RC1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/spring-shell-2-1-0-rc1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/07/spring-shell-2-1-0-rc1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T08:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.0-RC1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe 2022 Recap: From Drift Detection to Our New Developer Site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-2022-recap-from-drift-detection-to-our-new-developer-site</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-2022-recap-from-drift-detection-to-our-new-developer-site"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe took place once again in Amsterdam this year. Watch our complete sessions playlist, read a recap of the big keynote announcements, and take a look back at the sights and sounds of our annual European community conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLGO: A Machine Learning Framework for Compiler Optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/mlgo-machine-learning-framework-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/mlgo-machine-learning-framework-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yundi Qian, Software Engineer, Google Research and Mircea Trofin, Software Engineer, Google Core 
The question of how to compile faster and smaller code arose together with the birth of modem computers. Better code optimization can significantly reduce the operational cost of large datacenter applications. The size of compiled code matters the most to mobile and embedded systems or software deployed on secure boot partitions, where the compiled binary must fit in tight code size budgets. With advances in the field, the headroom has been heavily squeezed with increasingly complicated heuristics, impeding maintenance and further improvements.  
 Recent research has shown that machine learning (ML) can unlock more opportunities in compiler optimization by replacing complicated heuri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: June 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-06-github-availability-report-june-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-06-github-availability-report-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June, we experienced four incidents resulting in significant impact to multiple GitHub.com services. This report also sheds light into an incident that impacted several GitHub.com services in May.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many shards should I have in my Elasticsearch cluster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch is a very versatile platform that supports a variety of use cases and provides great flexibility around data organisation and replication strategies. This flexibility can, however, sometimes make it hard to determine up-front how to best organize your data into indices and shards, especially if you are new to the Elastic Stack. While suboptimal choices will not necessarily cause problems when first starting out, they have the potential to cause performance problems as data volumes grow over time. The more data the cluster holds, the more difficult it also becomes to correct the problem, as reindexing of large amounts of data can sometimes be required.
When we come across users that are experiencing performance problems, it is not uncommon that this can be traced back to issue…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Dahlqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many shards should I have in my Elasticsearch cluster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Dahlqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第212話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270375685329258711</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270375685329258711"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking Automation to the Next Level: Using Ansible + GitOps to Manage the Lifecycle of a Containerized Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/taking-automation-to-the-next-level-using-ansible-gitops-to-manage-the-lifecycle-of-a-containerized-application</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/taking-automation-to-the-next-level-using-ansible-gitops-to-manage-the-lifecycle-of-a-containerized-application"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the great advantages of combining GitOps with Ansible is that you get to streamline the automation delivery and the lifecycle of a containerized application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing a game dev community with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-06-managing-a-game-dev-community/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-06-managing-a-game-dev-community/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T08:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Little Game Called Mario is an open source, collectively developed hell project. Anyone and everyone is welcome to contribute their unique talents to make both the player and developer experience more enjoyable. Find out how the collective leverages GitHub Actions to manage this wonderful little community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 5th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/05/this-week-in-spring-july-5th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/05/this-week-in-spring-july-5th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! This week’s all sorts of weird for me. It’s Tuesday! But here in the US we just celebrated the 4th of July, and I, like many Americans, took a long weekend. Took some time with the family to do a little road trip up north to visit Mt. Shasta, Crater Lake, Lassen National Park, etc. It was a ton of fun, and a lot of driving! Anyway, it all kinda blurs together and felt like just one weekend, and today feels like Monday. I only just realized it was Tuesday! And you know what that means? It’s time for our weekly dive into the wild and wonderful world of Springdom! 


  
The last of my eight part series on building GraphQL applications with Spring for GraphQL is up! Check that page out and find links to all eight videos, each of which introduces one interesting dimension of the powerful and novel new Spring for GraphQL project.

  
In last week’s installment of A Bootiful Podcast, I talk to Spring Developer Advocate Dan Vega

  
Processing the Response Body in Spring Cloud Gateway

  
Spring Cloud 2020.0.6 is available

  
UUID as Entity ID in MongoDB

  
I liked this post over on Dzone: Are All Kubernetes Ingresses the Same?

  
Want to learn more about how to build GraalVM native images for Spring Boot 2.x-generation applications? Check out this article I wrote for InfoQ on Spring Native and GraalVM

  
The good folks over at Vaadin have put together a nice tutorial on building full-stack Spring Boot applications using their Java web framework called Hilla - check it out!

  
our friends over at Sivalabs have put together an interesting looking tutorial on how to use Spring Boot and Kubernetes together

  
Spring Boot team member Stéphane Nicoll did a French-language presentation for DevFest Lille recently introducing Spring AOT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – July 4, 2022]]></title>
        <id>7ed012657b91a09f4a4432a1cd0a97f3cc7ca3d4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-july-04-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T18:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Summer has arrived in Finland, and these last few days have been hotter than in the Canary Islands! Today in the US it is Independence Day. I hope that if […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extend your dependency information in the GitHub Dependency Graph with new GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-01-extend-your-dependency-information-in-the-github-dependency-graph-with-new-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-01-extend-your-dependency-information-in-the-github-dependency-graph-with-new-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T17:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Actions from Anchore, NowSecure, SBT, and Trivy are now available to create a more comprehensive GitHub Dependency Graph.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the GitHub Security Team uses projects and GitHub Actions for planning, tracking, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-01-how-the-github-security-team-uses-projects-and-github-actions-for-planning-tracking-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-01-how-the-github-security-team-uses-projects-and-github-actions-for-planning-tracking-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T15:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can projects and GitHub Actions be used by your non-developer teams? They absolutely can. Check out how our Security Team uses GitHub to run the department effortlessly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying Disfluencies in Natural Speech]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/identifying-disfluencies-in-natural.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/identifying-disfluencies-in-natural.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T20:09:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dan Walker and Dan Liebling, Software Engineers, Google Research 
People don’t write in the same way that they speak. Written language is controlled and deliberate, whereas transcripts of spontaneous speech (like interviews) are hard to read because speech is disorganized and less fluent. One aspect that makes speech transcripts particularly difficult to read is disfluency, which includes self-corrections, repetitions, and filled pauses (e.g., words like “umm”, and “you know”). Following is an example of a spoken sentence with disfluencies from the LDC CALLHOME corpus: 
But that's it's not, it's not, it's, uh, it's a word play on what you just said.
It takes some time to understand this sentence — the listener must filter out the extraneous words and resolve all of the nots. Remo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Developer Advocate Dan Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-developer-advocate-dan-vega</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-developer-advocate-dan-vega"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow Spring Developer Advocate Dan Vega (@therealdanvega)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minerva: Solving Quantitative Reasoning Problems with Language Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/minerva-solving-quantitative-reasoning.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/minerva-solving-quantitative-reasoning.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T16:34:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ethan Dyer and Guy Gur-Ari, Research Scientists, Google Research, Blueshift Team 
Language models have demonstrated remarkable performance on a variety of natural language tasks — indeed, a general lesson from many works, including BERT, GPT-3, Gopher, and PaLM, has been that neural networks trained on diverse data at large scale in an unsupervised way can perform well on a variety of tasks. 
Quantitative reasoning is one area in which language models still fall far short of human-level performance. Solving mathematical and scientific questions requires a combination of skills, including correctly parsing a question with natural language and mathematical notation, recalling relevant formulas and constants, and generating step-by-step solutions involving numerical calculations and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.9 Adds New Runner Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-9-adds-new-runner-commands</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-9-adds-new-runner-commands"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint 0.9 introduces on-demand runner introspection, a runner install command, and support for HCP Waypoint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2020.0.6 is available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/spring-cloud-2020-0-6-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/spring-cloud-2020-0-6-is-available"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce the Spring Cloud 2020.0.6 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2020.0.6 release notes for more information. Please consider upgrading to the latest 2021.0.x release train since the 2020.0.x release train has reached the end of OSS support.
Notable Changes in the 2020.0.6 Release

This is primarily a bugfix and dependency upgrade release, including backports of various issues over from 2021.0.x releases. Some enhancements have also been backported. 

See the project page for all issues included in the release.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Backported bug fixes from 2021.0.x

  
Backported passing on request data to LoadBalancerLifecycle beans for the blocking Spring Cloud Load…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflections on Juneteenth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/reflections-on-juneteenth</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/reflections-on-juneteenth"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight members of the HashiCorp Blacksmiths’ employee resource group share how they spent Juneteenth this year, and reflect on what they learned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault Logging and Alerting on Day 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-logging-and-alerting-on-day-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-logging-and-alerting-on-day-1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a step-by-step guide to building a free solution for Day 1 Vault logging and alerting on AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Achieve Geo-redundancy with Zeebe]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57477</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/how-to-achieve-geo-redundancy-with-zeebe/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations can use Camunda Platform 8 to build resilient systems that can withstand disasters in the form of complete data center outages.
The post How to Achieve Geo-redundancy with Zeebe appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – June 27, 2022]]></title>
        <id>56fd8c2cc8a76ab65b87b44700ad43152791e34f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-27-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T21:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! It’s the beginning of a new week, and I’d like to start with a recap of the most significant AWS news from the previous 7 days. Last week was special […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new: network automation with ansible.netcommon 3.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-network-automation-with-ansible.netcommon-3.0.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-network-automation-with-ansible.netcommon-3.0.0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the recent release of the ansible.netcommon Collection version 3.0.0, we have promoted two features as standard: libssh transport and import_modules. These features provide increased performance and resiliency for your network automation. These two features, which have been available since July 2020 (libssh) and March 2021 (import_modules), are now turned on by default for playbooks running the latest version of the netcommon Collection, so let's take a look at what makes these changes so exciting!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Case</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>