<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-29T00:49:47.112Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-29T00:49:47.112Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.9.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.05.28]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61777</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-05-28/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T17:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Friday, DevOps Friends!  Hope you had a great Microsoft Build, I know I did.  I really enjoyed a lot of the great sessions, Ask The Experts, and of course keynotes that were broadcast throughout the week.  One of my favorite sessions was Ask the Experts: Infra as Code –
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.05.28 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How diverse perspectives create a better workplace — and product]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-diverse-perspectives-create-a-better-workplace-and-product</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-diverse-perspectives-create-a-better-workplace-and-product"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a quality assurance engineer on the Kibana team at Elastic, Bhavya Raju Mandya makes an effort to see things from a different perspective. 

“My job is to break things,” says Bhavya. “I like impersonating a cat, being curious, seeing what happens if I knock something off, or moving something or changing the order to figure out what gives. The end goal is to protect and defend the quality of Kibana and that makes me happy.”

The value Bhavya places on curiosity and diverse perspectives is a direct result of her experiences. Bhavya grew up in the South of India, in a province called Karnataka. She studied software engineering and worked in Bangalore before moving to Montreal with her partner. 
“India is vast and diverse, with many different skin tones and features,” she says. “In South In…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Process Automation in Government: Challenges, Benefits, Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=21613</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/process-automation-in-government-challenges-benefits-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T10:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we make government tech work better for our citizens and our stakeholders? 
The post Process Automation in Government: Challenges, Benefits, Best Practices appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift ML Is Now Generally Available – Use SQL to Create Machine Learning Models and Make Predictions from Your Data]]></title>
        <id>e2c09f3554087f29b1181cd21535e08f33a1a37d</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/vsIBQ-WoQ8I/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T20:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Amazon Redshift, you can use SQL to query and combine exabytes of structured and semi-structured data across your data warehouse, operational databases, and data lake. Now that AQUA (Advanced Query Accelerator) is generally available, you can improve the performance of your queries by up to 10 times with no additional costs and no code […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing CDK for Terraform 0.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-cdk-for-terraform-0-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-cdk-for-terraform-0-4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cloud Development Kit for Terraform 0.4 introduces experimental Go language support, asset construct, and Terraform Cloud integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Amazon ECS Anywhere – Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>b0c9138fd7857802566b82e31a93ec008da273b7</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/68ocNDKQLfs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T17:13:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) was launched in 2014, AWS has released other options for running Amazon ECS tasks outside of an AWS Region such as AWS Wavelength, an offering for mobile edge devices or AWS Outposts, a service that extends to customers’ environments using hardware owned and fully managed by AWS. But […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics Studio – Quickly Interact with Streaming Data Using SQL, Python, or Scala]]></title>
        <id>5183c1f235442ea38ac6eeec50996b3abd39e531</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/1k3SgVOc2Ag/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T16:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best way to get timely insights and react quickly to new information you receive from your business and your applications is to analyze streaming data. This is data that must usually be processed sequentially and incrementally on a record-by-record basis or over sliding time windows, and can be used for a variety of analytics […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Elasticsearch is an indispensable component of the Adyen stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-elasticsearch-is-an-indispensable-component-of-the-adyen-stack</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-elasticsearch-is-an-indispensable-component-of-the-adyen-stack"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Adyen, we use Elasticsearch to power various parts of our payments platform. This includes payment search, monitoring, and log search. Let’s take a look at how we use Elastic for these different use cases and see how we capitalize on the power of Elasticsearch. 

We recently did a talk about some of our Elasticsearch adventures at an Elastic meetup. You can find a recording here.

Before we look into our different use cases, it helps to get a high-level understanding of Adyen’s architecture.

At Adyen, we do many things, but the core of what we do is payment processing. Our payment platform is built for any business and every customer journey. We process payments across all sales channels. 

Let’s say you want to buy a beer at the local pub (a merchant) and you want to pay with your cre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adyen Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Exploration with a New Python Library with Doris Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10991</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/27/data-exploration-with-a-new-python-library-with-doris-lee/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-exploration-with-a-new-python-library-with-doris-lee"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data exploration uses visual exploration to understand what is in a dataset and the characteristics of the data. Data scientists explore data to understand things like customer behavior and resource utilization. Some common programming languages used for data exploration are Python, R, and Matlab.  Doris Jung-Lin Lee is currently a Graduate Research Assistant at the
The post Data Exploration with a New Python Library with Doris Lee appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Micrometer-lead Tommy Ludwig]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/27/a-bootiful-podcast-micrometer-lead-tommy-ludwig</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/27/a-bootiful-podcast-micrometer-lead-tommy-ludwig"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Micrometer-lead and observability guru Tommy Ludwig (@tommyludwig) about Tokyo, Japan; metrics; tracing; and so much more. 


  
the Micrometer project]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Management Systems and Artificial Intelligence with Arun Kumar]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10990</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/26/data-management-systems-and-artificial-intelligence-with-arun-kumar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-management-systems-and-artificial-intelligence-with-arun-kumar"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T02:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arun Kumar is an Assistant Professor in the Department of Computer Science and Engineering and the Halicioglu Data Science Institute at the University of California, San Diego. His primary research interests are in data management and systems for machine learning/artificial intelligence-based data analytics.  Systems and ideas based on his research have been released as part
The post Data Management Systems and Artificial Intelligence with Arun Kumar appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Tech Preview of Consul Service Mesh for Amazon ECS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-consul-service-mesh-for-amazon-ecs</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-consul-service-mesh-for-amazon-ecs"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS users may now select Consul as their service mesh for ECS deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run a Successful Hacktoberfest Campaign with No Prior Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=21453</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/how-to-run-a-successful-hacktoberfest-campaign-with-no-prior-experience/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T17:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did we see such a great increase in engagement during our busiest season, despite not participating in Hacktoberfest before?
The post How to Run a Successful Hacktoberfest Campaign with No Prior Experience appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[King & Wood Mallesons CISO relies on Elastic to “spot and identify” security threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/king-wood-mallesons-ciso-relies-on-elastic-to-spot-and-identify-security-threats</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/king-wood-mallesons-ciso-relies-on-elastic-to-spot-and-identify-security-threats"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[King & Wood Mallesons (KWM) is among the world’s most innovative law firms and is represented by 2,400 lawyers in 28 locations across the globe. The international law firm, based in Australia, helps clients flourish in Asian markets by helping them understand and navigate local challenges and by delivering solutions that provide clients with a competitive advantage.

The firm believes in taking a partnership approach with clients and in pushing boundaries to connect Asia to the world and the world to Asia. 

To succeed in that mission, John Reeman, the Chief Information Security Officer for KWM, says the firm began leveraging Elastic about two years ago for security operations. The move has provided the firm with fresh insights to quickly pinpoint security events across the enterprise.

“W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiConf Europe Highlights You Don’t Want to Miss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-hashiconf-europe-highlights-you-don-t-want-to-miss</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-hashiconf-europe-highlights-you-don-t-want-to-miss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe 2021 is coming June 8-11. Here are some of the highlights that you don’t want to miss, from customer stories to product deep-dives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Works – AWS Region in the United Arab Emirates (UAE)]]></title>
        <id>06a103b32d7540917020406954100ea849bffe76</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/cPBIIiAjODI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T04:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are currently building AWS regions in Australia, Indonesia, Spain, India, and Switzerland. UAE in the Works I am happy to announce that the AWS Middle East (UAE) Region is in the works and will open in the first half of 2022. The new region is an extension of our existing investment, which already includes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inheritance]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2468/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2468/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/inheritance.png" title="People ask me whether I feel any moral qualms about the source of the points, but if he hadn't introduced factory farming to Agricola, someone else would have." alt="People ask me whether I feel any moral qualms about the source of the points, but if he hadn't introduced factory farming to Agricola, someone else would have." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 7.13.0 released: Search and store more data on Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key enhancements include cost-effective search across more data with searchable snapshots and the frozen tier, analyst-driven data enhancements on the fly with runtime fields, and expanded Microsoft integrations
We are pleased to announce the general availability (GA) of Elastic 7.13. This release brings a broad set of new capabilities to our Elastic Enterprise Search, Observability, and Security solutions, which are built into the Elastic Stack — Elasticsearch and Kibana. This release enables customers to search petabytes of data in minutes cost-effectively by leveraging searchable snapshots and the new frozen tier. Analysts can now enhance data on the fly using runtime fields, our implementation of schema on read, in Kibana Lens and Discover. 

And we are building upon our Microsoft part…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kearns,Angelos Kottas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Cloud for 7.13: Microsoft Azure portal integration, Azure Private Link in private beta, and frozen tier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-cloud-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-cloud-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest updates to Elastic Cloud make it easier to deploy and manage Elasticsearch on Microsoft Azure, secure data in motion with Azure Private Link, and cost-effectively store and search more data across all cloud service providers with the frozen tier and searchable snapshots. Keep reading to learn more.
 
Easily find, deploy, and manage Elastic directly within Microsoft Azure

We’re excited to announce the latest development in our ongoing partnership with Microsoft, the public preview of our Azure portal integration, which allows you to find, deploy, and manage Elasticsearch directly within the Azure portal. You can also take advantage of simplified ingestion for Azure platform, resource, and virtual machine logs, accelerating time to value for observability. By adding Workplace Sea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 7.13 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce Elasticsearch 7.13.0, based on Apache Lucene 8.8.2. 

Version 7.13 is the latest stable release of Elasticsearch and is now available for deployment via Elasticsearch Service on Elastic Cloud or via download for use in your own environment(s).

Ready to roll up your sleeves and get started? We have the links you need:

Start Elasticsearch on Elastic Cloud
Download Elasticsearch
Elasticsearch 7.13.0 release notes
Elasticsearch 7.13.0 breaking changes
Search petabytes of data in minutes using low-cost object storage with the frozen tier
We believe that data is a differentiator for businesses and operations. But with exponential data growth, it becomes economically unfeasible to store and search it all.

The frozen tier, now generally available in 7.13, gives the abi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Kibana 7.13: With great power comes great data exploration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-kibana-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-kibana-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kibana 7.13 is now available, bringing new capabilities that give you more flexibility in ad hoc analysis and faster speed in workflows, so you can focus on exploring your data and acting on insights. Highlights include:

Creating, editing, and removing runtime fields in Discover, Kibana Lens, and index patterns via the Kibana runtime fields editor
The general availability of Elastic Maps Server and supervised machine learning
Starting with Kibana Lens as the recommended visualization for ad hoc analysis
See how far you can go in your data exploration with the power of these features (and more) by signing up for a free trial of Elasticsearch Service on Elastic Cloud. You can also download the latest versions of Kibana and the Elastic Stack. 

For a quick list of the new 7.13 features, take…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeline Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Elastic Observability 7.13: Native Azure console integration, Fleet Server, and enhanced APM workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the release of Elastic Observability 7.13. An expanded partnership with Microsoft allows seamless integration between Elastic Observability and your Azure workloads, directly from the Azure console, the new Fleet Server paves the way for better scalability and flexibility, new workflows in APM help speed up root-cause analysis, and more. Let's dive in! 
 Expanded Microsoft partnership enables seamless onboarding to Elastic Cloud via a native Azure console integration
 Through our strategic partnership with Microsoft, we are excited to announce that Elastic Cloud is now available as a native, first-class service, available directly from the Azure console. Now, users can easily discover, procure, and create Elastic deployments directly from the Azure console, just …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Security 7.13: Equip analysts with vital context]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to share Elastic Security 7.13, which connects analysts to the information they need to make smart decisions. The release is a major step forward in our support for osquery, streamlining access to host data from across your environment. Threat intelligence is surfaced in new ways and new detection content spots concerning events. Last but not least, the release shares some developments in the endpoint area and support for new data sources.

Osquery for everybody
Elastic Security 7.13 substantially broadens our support for osquery, the open source host instrumentation framework. Osquery is the not-so-secret weapon of many sophisticated security teams, augmenting numerous security, compliance, and operations use cases, such as:

Unexpected changes in disk free space or memory …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Enterprise Search 7.13: Broader Dropbox integration and enhanced APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re thrilled to announce the latest release of Elastic Enterprise Search. In our 7.13 release you’ll find exciting enhancements you can use in your workplace, website, and mobile app search experiences. Included are new additions to the already broad content source integrations for Elastic Workplace Search, so you can index and synchronize even more content than ever. Also included are new APIs — and improvements to existing APIs — to give developers and admins powerful new tools for fine-tuning search results and indexing content. Let’s dive into some more detail.
 
Deeper Dropbox integration

Elastic Workplace Search offers unified search across all the content spanning all your productivity and storage apps. If your organization uses Dropbox to house all that content — and to collabor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Meiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Logstash 7.13.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-logstash-7-13-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-logstash-7-13-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the general availability of the Logstash 7.13.0 release. This is the latest stable release and is now available for download! Please refer to the release notes for the complete list of features and bug fixes. 
 
Elasticsearch data streams support
 
The Elastic Stack is commonly used to analyze time series data like logs and metrics. In Elasticsearch 7.9.0, the data streams feature was introduced, offering a cleaner experience for ingesting, searching, and managing time series datasets. With Logstash 7.13.0, we are happy to announce our new data streams integration in the Elasticsearch output plugin. 
 This integration extends the Elasticsearch output plugin with new settings for enabling and configuring the ability to write to data streams. We align with the Elasti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experience Elasticsearch from the Microsoft Azure portal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/experience-elasticsearch-microsoft-azure-portal</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/experience-elasticsearch-microsoft-azure-portal"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to share the latest development in our ongoing partnership with Microsoft. Available in public preview, you can now find, deploy, and manage Elasticsearch from within the Azure portal. Bring powerful enterprise search, observability, and security capabilities to your Azure environment with a user interface and tools that are already familiar to you. 
 
Deploy Elasticsearch and send data in minutes

Azure portal integration makes it faster and easier for you to experience the value of Elastic in your Azure environment, allowing you to: 

Purchase an Elastic Cloud plan and consolidate billing through the Azure marketplace. 
Provision your Elasticsearch deployment in a supported Azure region.  
Ingest Azure platform, resource, and virtual machine logs with just a few clicks. 
V…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uri Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy and manage Elastic on Microsoft Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-with-the-azure-integration-enhancement</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-with-the-azure-integration-enhancement"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently announced that users can find, deploy, and manage Elasticsearch from within the Azure portal. This new integration provides a simplified onboarding experience, all with the Azure portal and tooling you already know, so you can easily deploy Elastic without having to sign up for an external service or configure billing information.
In this blog post, you’ll learn how to create and manage an Elasticsearch resource on Azure as well as how to automate the ingestion of Azure logs and metrics into Elastic. See our documentation for even more details.
 
Getting started from the Azure console

First log in to the Azure portal. We’ll walk through the steps required to create an Elasticsearch resource on Azure. Behind the scenes, this process will provision a marketplace subscription wit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Osman Ishaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 6.8.16 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-6-8-16-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-6-8-16-released"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 6.8.16 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
The 6.8.16 patch contains fixes and small enhancements for the stack. 
For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
6.8.16 Release Notes
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ioana Tagirta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes – Containers and Kubernetes with @brendandburns]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61690</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-containers-and-kubernetes-with-brendandburns/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes – Containers and Kubernetes with @brendandburns appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2020.1 RTW]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61768</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/now-available-azure-devops-server-2020-1-rtw/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T17:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we released Azure DevOps Server 2020.1 RTW. This is our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2020.1. You can upgrade from Azure DevOps Server 2020.1 RC or previous versions of TFS and Azure DevOps. You can find the full details in our release notes.
The post Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2020.1 RTW appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AzureAD Provider Now Supports Microsoft Graph]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-azuread-provider-now-supports-microsoft-graph</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-azuread-provider-now-supports-microsoft-graph"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 1.5.0 of the Terraform AzureAD provider lets you manage your Azure Active Directory resources using the Microsoft Graph API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firebolt: Data Warehouses with Eldad Farkash]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10969</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/25/firebolt-data-warehouses-with-eldad-farkash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=firebolt-data-warehouses-with-eldad-farkash"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud data warehouses are databases hosted in cloud environments. They provide typical benefits of the cloud like flexible data access, scalability, and performance.  The company Firebolt provides a cloud data warehouse built for modern data environments. It decouples storage and compute to operate on top of existing data lakes like S3. It computes orders of
The post Firebolt: Data Warehouses with Eldad Farkash appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 25th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/24/this-week-in-spring-may-25th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/24/this-week-in-spring-may-25th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How’re you doing? I’m still fresh off my little vacation last week, feeling fantastic. I’ve spent the last several days working with Spring Boot and Spring Native and I have to tell you, they’re epic. 

It’s gotten to the point where I sometimes spend time working on enabling Spring Native integrations for other projects - it really makes some third party abstractions come alive! It’s hard to know what the right comparison is. There’s not much you can do in this life that results in such an instantaneous, night-and-day difference in performance and memory profile with so few (user-visibile) changes. Imagine snapping your fingers and having your luxury hypercar (Spring Boot in this metaphor) transform into an equally c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copy Dashboard – Public Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61759</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/copy-dashboard-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T17:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure Reporting and Analytics team is excited to announce the public preview of Copy Dashboard!
The post Copy Dashboard – Public Preview appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Waypoint Runners To Enable GitOps Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-waypoint-runners-to-enable-gitops-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-waypoint-runners-to-enable-gitops-workflows"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint runners perform builds, deployments, poll for Git repository changes, and allow deployments for any platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda Extensions Are Now Generally Available – Get Started with Your Favorite Operations Tools Today]]></title>
        <id>00cf76fbba9108f99f97d0a829f5da99bca9989e</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/Ojzzq6mN-AU/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T16:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In October 2020, we announced the preview of AWS Lambda extensions, which you can use to easily integrate Lambda functions with your favorite tools for monitoring, observability, security, and governance. Today, I’m happy to announce the general availability of AWS Lambda Extensions which comes with new performance improvements and an expanded set of partners. As […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Portainer: Container Management with Neil Cresswell]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10978</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/24/portainer-container-management-with-neil-cresswell/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=portainer-container-management-with-neil-cresswell"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T09:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running applications in containerized environments involves regularly organizing, adding and replacing containers. This complex job may involve managing clusters of containers in different geographic locations with different configuration requirements. Platforms like Kubernetes are great for managing this complexity, but include steep learning curves to efficiently get anything off the ground. The company Portainer provides a
The post Portainer: Container Management with Neil Cresswell appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wikipedia Caltrops]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2467/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2467/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/wikipedia_caltrops.png" title="Oh no, they set up a roadblock which is just a sign with the entire 'Czech hedgehog' article printed on it." alt="Oh no, they set up a roadblock which is just a sign with the entire 'Czech hedgehog' article printed on it." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.05.21]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61737</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-05-21/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T16:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Friday everyone! I can’t believe it’s already the end of May. This year is flying by! The area of Texas I live in has been getting some much-needed rain, and I’ve enjoyed checking out what the community has been up to during these torrential storms.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.05.21 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary Deptawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drafting Your Camunda Cloud Architecture – Part 2: Service Integration Patterns With BPMN And Camunda Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=20841</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/drafting-your-camunda-cloud-architecture-part-2-service-integration-patterns-with-bpmn-and-camunda-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When automating processes you typically integrate systems and services, or in other words you orchestrate various APIs. In order to achieve this you not only have different technical possibilities, but also can choose between various modeling possibilities in BPMN. This post will give you an overview and advice on how to decide between alternatives.
The post Drafting Your Camunda Cloud Architecture – Part 2: Service Integration Patterns With BPMN And Camunda Cloud appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5 is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-5-is-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-5-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T00:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update 2021-05-25: The release contains fixes for Spring Framework CVE-2021-22118.

On behalf of the Spring Boot team and everyone that has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.0 has been released and is available from Maven Central. 

This release adds a significant number of new features and improvements. For full upgrade instructions and new and noteworthy features please see the release notes.
What’s new in 2.5


  
Support for Java 16

  
Support for Gradle 7

  
Enhanced Docker image building

  
New mechanism for Datasource initialization


Additionally, the HTML documentation published by the project has an updated look-and-feel and some new features. There is also support for dark mode! 
Dependency upgrades

Spring Boot 2.5 moves to new versions of several Spring projects:


  
Spring Data 2021.0

  
Spring HATEOAS 1.3

  
Spring Integration 5.5

  
Spring Kafka 2.7

  
Spring Retry 1.3

  
Spring Security 5.5

  
Spring Session 2021.0


We’ve also upgraded to the latest stable releases of other third-party libraries wherever possible. Please see the release notes for details.
Other changes

There’s a whole host of other changes and improvements that are documented in the release notes. You can also find a list of deprecated classes and methods that we plan to remove in the next version.
Thank you

We want to take this opportunity to again thank all our users and contributors.

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask at stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.4.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-4-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-4-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T00:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update 2021-05-25: This release contains fixes for Spring Framework CVE-2021-22118.

On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.4.6 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 84 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Your Classroom]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2466/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2466/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/in_your_classroom.png" title="Ontology is way off to the left and geography is way off to the right." alt="Ontology is way off to the left and geography is way off to the right." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: James Ward]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/a-bootiful-podcast-james-ward</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/a-bootiful-podcast-james-ward"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Google Cloud Developer Advocate (and mentor, and friend!) James Ward (@_JamesWard) about his podcast Happy Path Programming (@HappyPathProg), programming, software, Spring Native, and his work at various organizations like Adobe, Heroku, Lightbend, SalesForce, and now Google Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration for AWS 2.5 goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-integration-for-aws-2-5-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-integration-for-aws-2-5-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring (and AWS) Community,



Today it’s my pleasure to announce a release of Spring Integration for Amazon Web Services extension version 2.5.



It is available from Maven Central:




compile "org.springframework.integration:spring-integration-aws:2.5.0"




Mostly this version is a major move from Spring Cloud for AWS project hosted on Spring Cloud side to its own organization.
Plus it includes upgrades to the latest dependencies, including recently released Spring Integration 5.5.



Many thanks to everyone from the Community for all the feedback and contribution to this project.



Spring Integration for AWS resources:



Project Page | Contributing | Help | Chat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.3.11 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-3-11-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-boot-2-3-11-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.3.11 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 52 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Secure Access Management with Boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/learn-secure-access-management-boundary</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/learn-secure-access-management-boundary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Boundary provides secure access to hosts and services based on user identity with new tutorials on HashiCorp Learn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud Zeebe K8s Operator]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=20493</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/camunda-cloud-zeebe-k8s-operator/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with Cloud Native applications on top of Kubernetes, you might need to make some tough decisions about where to run the services and infrastructure that your applications need, which will directly impact your maintenance costs.
The post Camunda Cloud Zeebe K8s Operator appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mauricio Salatino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preset: Visualizing Big Data with Srini Kadamati]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10968</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/20/preset-visualizing-big-data-with-srini-kadamati/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=preset-visualizing-big-data-with-srini-kadamati"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T09:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Superset is an open-source, fast, lightweight and modern data exploration and visualization platform. It can connect to any SQL based data source through SQLAlchemy at petabyte scale. Its architecture is highly scalable and it ships with a wide array of visualizations. The company Preset provides a powerful, easy to use data exploration and visualization
The post Preset: Visualizing Big Data with Srini Kadamati appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Web Services 3.1.1 is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-web-services-3-1-1-is-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/20/spring-web-services-3-1-1-is-out"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings Spring community,



The Spring Web Services team has released 3.1.1. This is the first major release under the new versioning schema. Releases will no longer have .RELEASE and snapshots will only be -SNAPSHOT, to better comply with community approaches.



While we strive to maintain alignment with Spring Framework and Spring Security, we also test against Java 8, Java 11, and Java LATEST (JDK 16 as of today).



For more details, read the following release notes for each version:



Release Notes - Spring Web Services - Version 3.1.1.





#1198 - Test against JDK 16 on CI.



#1197 - Upgrade to Spring Framework 5.3.7.



#1187 - Upgrade to Spring Security 5.5.0.



#1199 - Don’t skip main build targets during releases.





Links: Project Page | GitHub | Issues



The artifacts are located on Maven Central. Get it while it’s hot!





SpringOne 2021 is coming



The hottest Spring conference is right around the corner. Spring developers from around the globe will sign in. It’s still not too late to register.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why accessibility matters to someone like me]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-why-accessibility-matters-to-someone-like-me</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-why-accessibility-matters-to-someone-like-me"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all want to work for a company where we fit in. That’s why Elastic built a Source Code that encourages all to come as they are. In the Someone Like Me blog series, we highlight Elasticians who have a unique story — one, perhaps, just as unique as yours.

In this edition we revisit Bill McConaghy, senior manager of software engineering on Kibana, to talk about his experience with Elastic’s Accessibility Working Group, an employee resource and equity-seeking team that works to create and develop a disability inclusive workplace at Elastic.

Last year we talked to you about the recently formed Accessibility Working Group, and the work they were planning to make Elastic more accessible. What has the group been able to accomplish?

I’m proudest of the work we’ve accomplished with the recruit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BaseTen: Creating Machine Learning APIs with Tuhin Srivastava and Amir Haghighat]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10963</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/19/baseten-creating-machine-learning-apis-with-tuhin-srivastava-and-amir-haghighat/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=baseten-creating-machine-learning-apis-with-tuhin-srivastava-and-amir-haghighat"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T04:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application Programming Interfaces (APIs) are interfaces that enable multiple software applications to send and retrieve data from one another. They are commonly used for retrieving, saving, editing, or deleting data from databases, transmitting data between apps, and embedding third-party services into apps. The company BaseTen helps companies build and deploy machine learning APIs and applications.
The post BaseTen: Creating Machine Learning APIs with Tuhin Srivastava and Amir Haghighat appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Support for Predictive Scaling Policy in the Terraform AWS Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-support-for-predictive-scaling-policy-in-the-terraform-aws-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-support-for-predictive-scaling-policy-in-the-terraform-aws-provider"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform AWS provider now supports predictive scaling policy, a machine learning based scaling mechanism of Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 4.2.7 and 4.3.3 are out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/19/spring-batch-4-2-7-and-4-3-3-are-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/19/spring-batch-4-2-7-and-4-3-3-are-out"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T21:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 4.2.7 and 4.3.3 have been released and are available now from Maven Central repository. These patch releases come with a number of bug fixes, improvements and dependency updates. You can find the complete change logs here: 4.2.7 and 4.3.3.

I would like to thank all contributors who had a role in these releases!

Spring Batch Home | Source on GitHub | Reference Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Common Schema: The journey so far]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-common-schema-the-journey-so-far</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-common-schema-the-journey-so-far"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been just over two years since we introduced the Elastic Common Schema (ECS), and what a journey it’s been. From categorization fields to request for comments to Threat Intelligence fields, ECS has evolved rapidly over the course of the last two years. In this blog post, I would like to reflect on the ECS journey so far, and look towards the future of ECS. 
 You may by now be well experienced with ECS as a specification that provides a consistent and customizable way to structure your data in Elasticsearch, facilitating the analysis of data from diverse sources. With ECS, analytics content such as dashboards and machine learning jobs can be applied more broadly, searches can be crafted more narrowly, and field names are easier to remember. 
 Back in 2019, ECS 1.0 started out with 27…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Hynds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration 5.5 goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/19/spring-integration-5-5-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/19/spring-integration-5-5-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring community,



On behalf of the team and all the contributors, it’s my pleasure to announce a General Availability for Spring Integration 5.5, plus Spring Integration 5.4.7 patch release.



Both versions can be obtained from Maven Central and it is recommended to upgrade your projects or just pull them transitively from respective latest Spring Boot patch versions!




compile 'org.springframework.integration:spring-integration-core:5.5.0'




Spring Integration 5.4.7 version contains mostly critical bug fixes and here is a highlight of notable changes made to Spring Integration 5.5, which, in general, is based on the community feedback to make the framework useful for end-user use-cases:





A support for Spring Native compatibility - a lot of bean definiti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fun with private Automation Hub - Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/fun-with-private-automation-hub-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/fun-with-private-automation-hub-part-1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the introduction of Ansible Automation Platform 1.2 at AnsibleFest 2020, Ansible released private Automation Hub. This enables a means to deliver, manage and curate Ansible Automation Platform Certified Content via a central on-premises, self-hosted solution for use by internal automation communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Leroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What You Should Know About Using Camunda Platform Run in Production]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=20487</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/what-you-should-know-about-using-camunda-platform-run-in-production/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Run, or Camunda Run for short, is a lightweight distribution of Camunda Platform that works straight out-of-the-box and comes pre-configured for production environments. Camunda Run is an excellent option if you’re just getting started with Camunda, or if you’re ready to use Camunda Platform in production. You can download the open-source Community Edition for free, and easily upgrade to the Enterprise Edition to access more features and support options. After you download and extract Camunda Run, you’ll find a configuration folder that contains a file called production.yml. The properties defined in this file are important for production environments and are derived from our guide to securing your Camunda Platform installation. To start Camunda Run with the production.yml configuration,...
The post What You Should Know About Using Camunda Platform Run in Production appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda BPM Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 18th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/18/this-week-in-spring-may-18th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/18/this-week-in-spring-may-18th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T00:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We’ve got a ton of great stuff to get to, and I’m otherwise on vacation (though you can still expect a new episode of A Bootiful Podcast (@BootifulPodcast), as usual) for this week, so let’s get to it!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Axon Framework Founder Allard Buijze on CQRS, Sagas, and more

  
A cool video demonstrating Spring Native

  
Automate Spring Boot application deployments to Azure!

  
Blog: Using Finalizers to Control Deletion

  
Check out the latest version of the HAL explorer

  
Check out the recording of my talk with Julien Dubois, and Rory Preddy

  
Live Webinar - From MVC to Reactive - Registration

  
Modern Web Development - DZone Trend Report

  
Move out workshops generation · Issue #249 · spring-cloud-samples/spring-cloud-contract-samples · GitHub

  
Spring AMQP 2.2.17.RELEAE & 2.3.7 available

  
Spring Data 2021.0.1 and 2020.0.9 released

  
Spring Framework 5.3.7 and 5.2.15 available now

  
Spring HATEOAS 1.2.6 and 1.3.1 released

  
Spring LDAP 2.3.4 released

  
Spring Security 5.5 goes GA

  
Spring for Apache Kafka 2.5.13.RELEASE, 2.6.8 & 2.7.1 available

  
SpringOne Tour: Booternetes II - May 12, 2021. Join me - Josh Long, Mark Heckler, Mario Gray, David Turanski, Tiffany Jernigan, Chris Sterling, Nate Schutta, and special guest star Joe Beda, co-founder of Kubernetes, for this epic introduction to the ways

  
The team I work on is hiring (in the US only, sadly)! Join me and the rest of the epic team and let’s change the world together!

  
Automate Spring Boot app deployments to Azure. Use Blue-Green to reduce downtime and risk. Automate end-to-end! Create a pipeline using Azure Pipelines

  
Want to learn more about Java on Microsoft Azure? Join the “Ask the #Java Experts” live session at #MSBuild with: Asir Selvasingh, Bruno Borges, and many others

  
Check out this talk on the Microsoft build of OpenJDK and other useful Java things on VS Code and Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dimensional Chess]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2465/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2465/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/dimensional_chess.png" title="In Dimensional Chess, every move is annotated '?!'." alt="In Dimensional Chess, every move is annotated '?!'." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS App Runner: From Code to a Scalable, Secure Web Application in Minutes]]></title>
        <id>2eb32615b0311b807948f09e866da9700a4494e7</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/95poDWZrIXg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T23:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers have become the default way that I package my web applications. Although I love the speed, productivity, and consistency that containers provide, there is one aspect of the container development workflow that I do not like: the lengthy routine I go through when I deploy a container image for the first time. You might […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Beeby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skynet Labs: Decentralized Internet with Matthew Sevey]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10933</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/18/skynet-labs-decentralized-internet-with-matthew-sevey/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=skynet-labs-decentralized-internet-with-matthew-sevey"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T18:20:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company Skynet Labs provides an open protocol for hosting data and web applications on the decentralized web. Skynet allows for decentralized, censorship-resistant, highly redundant storage and applications that are available around the globe. Developers don’t pay for their application’s storage, can launch apps with access to a user’s data right away, are free from
The post Skynet Labs: Decentralized Internet with Matthew Sevey appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes – Demystifying Helm with @DonovanBrown]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61686</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-demystifying-helm-with-donovanbrown/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T18:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes – Demystifying Helm with @DonovanBrown appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ProblemChild: Detecting living-off-the-land attacks using the Elastic Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/problemchild-detecting-living-off-the-land-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/problemchild-detecting-living-off-the-land-attacks"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to malware attacks, one of the more common techniques is “living off the land” (LOtL). Utilizing standard tools or features that already exist in the target environment allows these attacks to blend into the environment and avoid detection. While these techniques can appear normal in isolation, they start looking suspicious when observed in the parent-child context. This is where the ProblemChild framework can help. 

In this blog, we will talk about how you can use Elastic machine learning to create your own ProblemChild framework to detect LOtL activity in Windows process event data (we will be referring to Windows process events as just “events” throughout this blog). We will talk in detail about the following:

Extracting features from event metadata
Training a supervised…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Apoorva Joshi,Disha Dasgupta,Craig Chamberlain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Launch Day Support for AWS App Runner in the Terraform AWS Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-day-support-for-aws-app-runner-in-the-terraform-aws-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-day-support-for-aws-app-runner-in-the-terraform-aws-provider"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform AWS provider now supports AWS AppRunner, a purpose-built container application service that enables customers to build and run containerized web applications in just a few clicks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of HashiCorp Nomad 1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-general-availability-of-hashicorp-nomad-1-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-general-availability-of-hashicorp-nomad-1-1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.1 is now generally available. This release delivers more than 10 new features to enable more flexible scheduling and a simplified operator experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.5 goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/18/spring-security-5-5-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/18/spring-security-5-5-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Security 5.5. This release is the result of the work that went into 5.5.0-M1, 5.5.0-M2, 5.5.0-M3, 5.5.0-RC1, 5.5.0-RC2 and 5.5.0. In combination, they close 250+ tickets.



You can find the highlights of 5.5 in the What’s new section of the Spring Security reference.



As always, we look forward to hearing your feedback!



Project Site |
Reference
| Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Kafka 2.5.13.RELEASE, 2.6.8 & 2.7.1 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/17/spring-for-apache-kafka-2-5-13-release-2-6-8-2-7-1-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/17/spring-for-apache-kafka-2-5-13-release-2-6-8-2-7-1-available"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring for Apache Kafka 2.5.13.RELEASE, 2.6.8 and 2.7.1 are available now.

All versions have some number of bug fixes and minor improvements, especially additions to recently introduced Topic Delayed Non-Blocking Retry.
Big thanks to Tomaz Fernandes for amazing contributions in this area!

See their release notes for more information:

https://github.com/spring-projects/spring-kafka/releases/tag/v2.5.13.RELEASE
https://github.com/spring-projects/spring-kafka/releases/tag/v2.6.8
https://github.com/spring-projects/spring-kafka/releases/tag/v2.7.1

Stay tuned for follow-up Spring Boot releases later this week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ClickHouse: Data Warehousing with Robert Hodges]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10932</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/17/clickhouse-data-warehousing-with-robert-hodges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=clickhouse-data-warehousing-with-robert-hodges"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Columnar databases store and retrieve columns of data rather than rows of data. Each block of data in a columnar database stores up to 3 times as many records as row-based storage. This means you can read data with a third of the power needed in row-based data, among other advantages. The company Altinity is
The post ClickHouse: Data Warehousing with Robert Hodges appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the New AWS Application Migration Service for Lift-and-Shift Migrations]]></title>
        <id>8b2c4cd789faee0e06adea3f067ac1241363e50a</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/6CDf9qduI2I/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since AWS acquired CloudEndure in 2019, our new colleagues have offered CloudEndure Migration and CloudEndure Disaster Recovery. CloudEndure Migration can move applications from any physical, virtual, or cloud-based infrastructure to AWS at no charge. This complements AWS Server Migration Service (AWS SMS), which is an agentless service for migrating on-premises workloads to AWS. CloudEndure Disaster […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring AMQP 2.2.17.RELEAE & 2.3.7 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/17/spring-amqp-2-2-17-releae-2-3-7-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/17/spring-amqp-2-2-17-releae-2-3-7-available"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring AMQP 2.3.7 and 2.2.17.RELEASE are available now.

Both versions have some number of bug fixes and minor improvements together with upgrades to the latest minor dependencies.
See their release notes for more information:

https://github.com/spring-projects/spring-amqp/releases/tag/v2.2.17.RELEASE
https://github.com/spring-projects/spring-amqp/releases/tag/v2.3.7

Stay tuned for follow-up Spring Boot releases later this week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You’re Struggling with Your BPM Suite]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=20482</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/why-youre-struggling-with-your-bpm-suite/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you using a business process management (BPM) suite such as IBM Business Process Manager, Pega, Appian, jBPM, or Bonitasoft? If so, do any of these problems sound familiar? The software was hard to install, and we need specialized knowledge to maintain it We haven’t been able to fully integrate the software with other parts of our tech stack It’s hard to find developers who know how to make the software do what we need it to do Our developers have to work around the software’s technical or functional limitations These problems stem from the fact that many BPM suites are built on a closed architecture and take a proprietary approach to application development and process automation. That’s not just...
The post Why You’re Struggling with Your BPM Suite appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpringOne Tour: Booternetes - May 12th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/14/springone-tour-booternetes-may-12th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/14/springone-tour-booternetes-may-12th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T03:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! We wrapped up the epic SpringOne Tour installment for May a couple of days ago. Here’s the Day 1 recording - Booternetes II: The YAML Strikes Back - featuring yours truly, Mark Heckler, Mario Gray, David Turanski, Tiffany Jernigan, Chris Sterling, and special guest star, Kubernetes cofounder, Joe Beda. 

This edition pulls together a lot of different Spring ecosystem technologies, showing projects that you might use to more fully exploit the power of Kubernetes. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Mechanics: Data Engineering with Jean-Yves Stephan]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10928</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/14/data-mechanics-data-engineering-with-jean-yves-stephan/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-mechanics-data-engineering-with-jean-yves-stephan"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T23:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Spark is a popular open source analytics engine for large-scale data processing. Applications can be written in Java, Scala, Python, R, and SQL. These applications have flexible options to run on like Kubernetes or in the cloud.  The company Data Mechanics is a cloud-native Spark platform for data engineers. It runs continuously optimized Apache
The post Data Mechanics: Data Engineering with Jean-Yves Stephan appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring LDAP 2.3.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/14/spring-ldap-2-3-4-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/14/spring-ldap-2-3-4-released"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T22:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring LDAP 2.3.4!  This release fixes including a fix where Spring LDAP breaks on JDK9+.



You can find the complete details in the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.0.1 and 2020.0.9 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/14/spring-data-2021-0-1-and-2020-0-9-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/14/spring-data-2021-0-1-and-2020-0-9-released"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T17:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data service releases 2021.0.1 and 2020.0.9.

Both releases are built on top of Spring Framework 5.3.7. For your convenience, these releases can be consumed through Spring Boot 2.5.0 respective 2.4.6.

The service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.

To round things off, here are the links to the artifacts, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.0.1


  
Spring Data Commons 2.5.1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.2.1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.5.1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data for Apache Geode 2.5.1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Modules on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-modules-on-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-modules-on-aws"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use best practices-based modules to build production-grade Terraform deployments on AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.05.14]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61704</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-05-14/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T15:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Friday everyone! I can’t believe we’re already nearly to the middle of May, where has this month gone? This was another week full of great posts and content from the community. We love when folks share their experiences – it helps us all grow,
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.05.14 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary Deptawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Axon Framework Founder Allard Buijze on CQRS, Sagas, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/13/a-bootiful-podcast-axon-framework-founder-allard-buijze-on-cqrs-sagas-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/13/a-bootiful-podcast-axon-framework-founder-allard-buijze-on-cqrs-sagas-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman)  talks to Axon founder Allard Buijze (@allardbz) about AxonIQ (@axoniq), the Axon framework, architecture patterns like CQRS and Sagas, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Spring Boot application deployments to Azure!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/13/automate-spring-boot-application-deployments-to-azure</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/13/automate-spring-boot-application-deployments-to-azure"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to announce the availability of the Azure Pipeline Task for deploying Spring Boot applications to Azure Spring Cloud. You can get started by building your pipelines using the Azure Spring Cloud task to automate Spring Boot application deployments to any number of environments and Azure Regions.

Over the past 18 months, we worked with many enterprise customers to learn about their scenarios including thoughts on automating end-to-end from idea to provisioning Azure resources to building Spring Boot applications to deploying those applications to production. Many of these customers have thousands of Spring Boot applications running in on-premises data centers. As they migrate these applications to the cloud, they need everything automated end-to-end to ensure repeatabi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Swimlane partner to deliver an extensible framework for the modern SOC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-swimlane-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-swimlane-partnership"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T22:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I’m happy to share more about our partnership with Swimlane, which further reinforces our commitment to empowering security teams everywhere. Today’s security teams rely on the power of Elastic’s high-speed, cloud-scale analytics to solve their most complex and pressing security issues. Swimlane’s security automation platform provides a way for these same teams to accelerate and optimize their workflows for max efficiency and to solve SOAR use cases.  
  
Through joint development of key integrations to support SIEM, continuous monitoring, threat detection and prevention, threat hunting, incident response, and more, SOC teams are now able to combine the benefits of high-fidelity detection and alerting delivered by Elastic Security with Swimlane’s robust automation and scalable orches…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Fick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Prem To the Cloud: Let’s Rub Some DevOps On It! (Ep 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61679</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/on-prem-to-the-cloud-lets-rub-some-devops-on-it-ep-3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T18:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In episode 2 of this series, Jay helped Abel migrate the Mercury Health application environment into Azure. So we’re in the cloud! But what about future changes? How do we get them out to customers? The answer is DevOps.
Rubbing Some DevOps on a “Legacy”
The post On Prem To the Cloud: Let’s Rub Some DevOps On It! (Ep 3) appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Brady</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Azure Resources with TypeScript Using the CDK for Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-azure-resources-with-typescript-using-the-cdk-for-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-azure-resources-with-typescript-using-the-cdk-for-terraform"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn a quick method for getting started with the Cloud Development Kit (CDK) for Terraform using TypeScript as infrastructure code and provisioning on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owning his voice, no matter the accent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-owning-his-voice-no-matter-the-accent</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-owning-his-voice-no-matter-the-accent"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An accent made Nikko Jocson’s mom stand out. An immigrant from the Philippines to the US, she spoke differently than his friends’ parents. Now a senior IT support technician, Nikko has learned that her voice helped to define his story.
“Sometimes people teased her about her accent, but she was always so proud. She didn’t care. Her accent was her own. I have always looked for places that allow me to have my own accent as well. It hasn’t always been easy,” said Nikko.
He began his career in IT when he got a job in retail at an Apple store to support himself while pursuing a degree in child and adolescent development. Eventually, he was promoted to an internal corporate tech support role. As his mom taught him, he kept focusing on how his experiences could help him stand out and achieve more.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming data challenges for state and local government and education with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/overcoming-data-challenges-for-state-and-local-government-and-education-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/overcoming-data-challenges-for-state-and-local-government-and-education-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the surge of endpoints and growing demands for access to data, public sector organizations have seen an increase in security threats since the onset of the pandemic.  Against this backdrop, Elastic gathered industry leaders to learn how to manage these challenges and demands and build a path toward the future. The recent State and Local Government & Education ElasticON Public Sector event showcased the tech solutions that are delivering for constituents, faster. What should organizations keep top of mind to achieve these goals? Presenters focused on these takeaways:

Regardless of the size or purpose of your organization, the volume of data at your disposal will increase. Having the tools to analyze that increased data load and to adapt processes at speed and scale will be critical fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Mara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Route Maps Resource Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-route-maps-resource-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-route-maps-resource-modules"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Engine v2.9 introduced the first set of Resource Modules that make network automation easier and more consistent, especially in multi-vendor environments. These network resource specific and opinionated Ansible modules help us avoid creating overly complex Jinja2 templates to render and push network configurations, thereby easing the adoption of network automation both in green and brownfield environments. The resource modules, along with the tools provided in ansible.utils, are highly focused on allowing the end user to manipulate network configuration as “structured data” and not have to worry about network platform specific details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nilashish Chakraborty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud: Podcast Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=20432</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/camunda-cloud-podcast-edition/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Camunda Nation podcast is live. Hear all about Camunda Cloud going GA with the release of Camunda Cloud 1.0.
The post Camunda Cloud: Podcast Edition appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Hudi: Large Scale Data Systems with Vinoth Chandar]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10920</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/13/apache-hudi-large-scale-data-systems-with-vinoth-chandar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=apache-hudi-large-scale-data-systems-with-vinoth-chandar"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T09:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Hudi is an open-source data management framework used to simplify incremental data processing and data pipeline development. This framework more efficiently manages business requirements like data lifecycle and improves data quality. Some common use cases for Hudi is record-level insert, update, and delete, simplified file management and near real-time data access, and simplified CDC
The post Apache Hudi: Large Scale Data Systems with Vinoth Chandar appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring HATEOAS 1.2.6 and 1.3.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/12/spring-hateoas-1-2-6-and-1-3-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/12/spring-hateoas-1-2-6-and-1-3-1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T22:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the Spring community I’d like to announce the availability of Spring HATEOAS 1.2.6 and 1.3.1. The releases contain general bugfixes and are scheduled for inclusion in the upcoming Spring Boot service releases.



Find the detailed changelogs for 1.2.6 here and the one for 1.3.1 here.



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Akita: Application Programming Interfaces with Jean Yang]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10909</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/12/akita-application-programming-interfaces-with-jean-yang/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=akita-application-programming-interfaces-with-jean-yang"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An application programming interface, API for short, is the connector between 2 applications. For example, a user interface that needs user data will call an endpoint, like a special URL, with request parameters and receive the data back if the request is valid. Modern applications rely on APIs to send data back and forth to
The post Akita: Application Programming Interfaces with Jean Yang appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Default Tags in the Terraform AWS Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/default-tags-in-the-terraform-aws-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/default-tags-in-the-terraform-aws-provider"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform AWS Provider now offers users the ability to define default tags at the provider level, simplifying tag management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Create Microsoft SQL Server Instances of Amazon RDS on AWS Outposts]]></title>
        <id>ac7cf694748e381f3ecd13f45c5f0e00f775e991</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/olh38OAOylQ/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T19:32:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, we announced Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) on AWS Outposts, which allows you to deploy fully managed database instances in your on-premises environments. AWS Outposts is a fully managed service that extends AWS infrastructure, AWS services, APIs, and tools to virtually any datacenter, co-location space, or on-premises facility for a truly consistent […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes – Microsoft Identity with Christos Matskas!]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61625</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-microsoft-identity-with-christos-matskas/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific / 2 PM Eastern on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes – Microsoft Identity with Christos Matskas! appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61694</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/may-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Inconsistent Test Results data when using Microsoft.TeamFoundation.TestManagement.Client.
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.1 Patch 3
The post May patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explore HashiCorp Consul with Docker Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/explore-hashicorp-consul-with-docker-compose</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/explore-hashicorp-consul-with-docker-compose"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy, test, and explore various Consul use cases in record time with Docker Compose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Local Zones Are Now Open in Boston, Miami, and Houston]]></title>
        <id>59a17c201dc1612c584da4671571f6299a3cc1bc</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/AMAVyWivYOA/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Local Zones place select AWS services (compute, storage, database, and so forth) close to large population, industry, and IT centers. They support use cases such as real-time gaming, hybrid migrations, and media & entertainment content creation that need single-digit millisecond latency for end-users in a specific geographic area. Last December I told you about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Camunda Cloud – Industry-First Process Automation as a Service]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=20085</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/relentless-innovation-introducing-camunda-cloud-10/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Camunda, we have always pushed ourselves to innovate in the field of Process Automation. From our early days as a lightweight Java project, we’ve relentlessly innovated — engineering an end-to-end Process Automation tech stack that has helped organizations across the globe automate mission-critical processes. But innovation never stops and organizations continue to look for new ways to increase the velocity of business transformation. To address this need, more and more organizations are turning to the cloud, which is increasingly becoming a business transformation accelerator.  That being said, as enterprise applications are being built entirely in the cloud, organizations are struggling with automating processes across multiple systems, people, and devices in an end-to-end manner. These processes often include modern components...
The post Introducing Camunda Cloud – Industry-First Process Automation as a Service appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=20285</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/camunda-cloud-10-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Cloud 1.0. Camunda Cloud 1.0 is a significant milestone for the product as well as for Camunda. Read in more detail what Daniel Meyer, CTO of Camunda, has to say about this release. We have run an extensive beta program for Camunda Cloud including Zeebe 0.26 as well as an early-access program. We’ve improved the product over this time with input from customers and are now ready to take the next step and make Camunda Cloud generally available. If you’re interested in trying out Camunda Cloud – Sign up here for a free 30-day trial. The remainder of this blog post will focus on the highlights of Camunda Cloud 1.0.The release notes can be found on GitHub. Camunda...
The post Camunda Cloud 1.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.5.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=20162</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/05/camunda-optimize-3-5-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T07:11:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.5.0-alpha1. Camunda Optimize provides business activity monitoring for workflows, supporting continuous process improvement by providing transparency into your automated workflows and decisions. Business-friendly reports, dashboards and alerts make it possible to identify process bottlenecks and improve end-to-end processes. If you’d like to get started with Optimize 3.5.0-alpha1 right away, you can download the release here with your Camunda Enterprise Platform customer credentials. And if you’re not yet a Camunda customer, you can sign up here for a free 30-day trial of the Camunda Enterprise Platform, which includes Camunda Optimize. In the rest of this post, we’ll highlight some of the new capabilities introduced in Optimize 3.5.0-alpha1. Raw Data Report Improvements How to get it Raw Data Report...
The post Camunda Optimize 3.5.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Mueller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nextmv: Optimization in Fluid Work Environments with Carolyn Mooney]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10908</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/10/nextmv-optimization-in-fluid-work-environments-with-carolyn-mooney/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=nextmv-optimization-in-fluid-work-environments-with-carolyn-mooney"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T02:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The traveling salesman problem is a classic challenge of finding the shortest and most efficient route for a person to take given a list of destinations. This is one of many real-world optimization problems that companies encounter. How should they schedule product distribution, or promote product bundles, or define sales territories? The answers to these
The post Nextmv: Optimization in Fluid Work Environments with Carolyn Mooney appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resolve IT Incidents Faster with Incident Manager, a New Capability of AWS Systems Manager]]></title>
        <id>a782aff927c5ec2c0d1bc4c64000011ddc707801</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/JJ_9Uim_LcM/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T22:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT engineers pride themselves on the skill and care they put into building applications and infrastructure. However, as much as we all hate to admit it, there is no such thing as 100% uptime. Everything will fail at some point, often at the worst possible time, leading to many a ruined evening, birthday party, or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Network Resource Purge parameter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-network-resource-purge-parameter</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-network-resource-purge-parameter"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Network Automation continues to be a popular domain for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. We have continually developed additional resource modules to make automating network appliances easier, and more approachable, for novices and experts alike. These resource modules provide a consistent experience across multiple network vendors. There are seven main state parameters for resource modules: merged, replaced, overridden, deleted, gathered, rendered and parsed. The Ansible network team is adding one more parameter, purged, to this tool chest for resource modules. This blog will cover the purged parameter and show use-cases through a practical example.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temporal Product: Managing State with Ryland Goldstein]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10893</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/08/temporal-product-managing-state-with-ryland-goldstein/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=temporal-product-managing-state-with-ryland-goldstein"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T09:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microservice architecture has become very common over the past few years because of the availability of containers and container orchestrators like Kubernetes. While containers are overall positive for scaling apps and making them more available, they’ve also introduced hurdles like persisting data and state, and container restarts or pod failures. Development teams put significant work
The post Temporal Product: Managing State with Ryland Goldstein appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Botpress: Natural Language Processing with Sylvain Perron]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10892</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/07/botpress-natural-language-processing-with-sylvain-perron/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=botpress-natural-language-processing-with-sylvain-perron"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T22:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Natural Language Processing (NLP) is a branch of artificial intelligence concerned with giving computers the ability to understand text and spoken words. “Understanding” includes intent, sentiment, and what’s important in the message. NLP powers things like voice-operated software, digital assistants, customer service chat bots, and many other academic, consumer and enterprise tools. The company Botpress
The post Botpress: Natural Language Processing with Sylvain Perron appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Auto Scaling Strategy with HashiCorp Nomad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-auto-scaling-strategy-with-hashicorp-nomad</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-auto-scaling-strategy-with-hashicorp-nomad"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nomad Autoscaler has new plugins and capabilities to make it easier to achieve consistent autoscaling across cloud providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Relic: Telemetry and Intelligent Observability with Zain Asgar and Ishan Mukherjee]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10885</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/05/new-relic-telemetry-and-intelligent-observability-with-zain-asgar-and-ishan-mukherjee/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=new-relic-telemetry-and-intelligent-observability-with-zain-asgar-and-ishan-mukherjee"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T23:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In software engineering, telemetry is the data that is collected about your applications. Unlike logging, which is used in the development of apps to pinpoint errors and code flows, telemetry data includes all operational data including logs, metrics, events, traces, usage, and other analytical data. Companies usually visualize this information to troubleshoot problems and understand
The post New Relic: Telemetry and Intelligent Observability with Zain Asgar and Ishan Mukherjee appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNCF Technology Radar Highlights HashiCorp Vault’s Broad Multi-Cloud Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cncf-technology-radar-highlights-vault-broad-multi-cloud-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cncf-technology-radar-highlights-vault-broad-multi-cloud-adoption"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CNCF End User Technology Radar for secrets management reveals HashiCorp Vault has the broadest adoption across many companies and industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieve HashiCorp Vault Secrets with Kubernetes CSI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/retrieve-hashicorp-vault-secrets-with-kubernetes-csi</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/retrieve-hashicorp-vault-secrets-with-kubernetes-csi"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use CSI to expose secrets on a volume within a Kubernetes pod and retrieve them using our beta Vault Provider for the Kubernetes Secrets Store CSI Driver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring as code with Sensu + Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/monitoring-as-code-with-sensu-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/monitoring-as-code-with-sensu-ansible"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive infrastructure as code (IaC) initiative should include monitoring and observability. Incorporating the active monitoring of the infrastructure under management results in a symbiotic relationship in which failures are detected automatically, enabling event-driven code changes and new deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jef@sensu.io (Jef Spaleta)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Resources for Workloads with Nomad 1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-for-workloads-with-nomad-1-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-for-workloads-with-nomad-1-1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.1 introduces new resource control features to improve efficiency, including memory oversubscription, reserved CPU cores, and improved UI visibility into resource utilization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Controlled Remote State Access for Terraform Cloud and Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-controlled-remote-state-access-for-terraform-cloud-and-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-controlled-remote-state-access-for-terraform-cloud-and-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Controlled Remote State Access feature in Terraform Cloud and Terraform Enterprise adds a more granular way to control access to each workspace’s state file.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to HashiCorp at KubeCon Europe Virtual 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-guide-to-hashicorp-at-kubecon-europe-virtual-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-guide-to-hashicorp-at-kubecon-europe-virtual-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about our plans for this year’s KubeCon Europe virtual conference and get CNCF- and Kubernetes-related updates on our products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon FinSpace Simplifies Data Management and Analytics for Financial Services]]></title>
        <id>5d9d7901c0f2a705e6da6f3a3ee45368c37c33ff</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/TtNYudIv4iI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T22:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing data is the core of the Financial Services Industry (FSI). I worked for private banking and fund management companies and helped analysts to collect, aggregate, and analyze hundreds of petabytes of data from internal data sources, such as portfolio management, order management, and accounting systems, but also from external data sources, such as real-time […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CloudFront Functions – Run Your Code at the Edge with Low Latency at Any Scale]]></title>
        <id>6a19c82bf6ccb578a508a38136408971f389d9da</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/5mteSKBDr8Q/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T21:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Amazon CloudFront, you can securely deliver data, videos, applications, and APIs to your customers globally with low latency and high transfer speeds. To offer a customized experience and the lowest possible latency, many modern applications execute some form of logic at the edge. The use cases for applying logic at the edge can be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 10th Birthday – AWS Identity and Access Management]]></title>
        <id>5c30cc5211fd69350e157ce3a7d2124b4431379f</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/JisYEOZh878/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T16:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 turned 15 earlier this year, and Amazon EC2 will do the same in a couple of months. Today we are celebrating the tenth birthday of AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM). The First Decade Let’s take a walk through the last decade and revisit some of the most significant IAM launches: May 2011 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Nomad 1.1 Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-nomad-1-1-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-nomad-1-1-beta"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.1 delivers more than 10 new features to enable more flexible scheduling and a simplified operator experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handling OOB Network Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/handling-oob-network-changes</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/handling-oob-network-changes"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog I would like to showcase the power of Ansible Content Collections to build powerful abstractions. Collections are a distribution format for Ansible content that can include playbooks, roles, modules and plugins. For this blog post, let us address an Infrastructure as Code(IaC) use case for network configuration management of BGP. We will walk through examples for both Cisco IOS and Arista EOS devices. 
First, let us define a data-model that encapsulates the vendor-agnostic configuration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>achenamp@redhat.com (Ajay Chenampara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network MOP's as automated workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/network-mops-as-automated-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/network-mops-as-automated-workflows"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does successful network automation look like? What are the metrics that can measure the effectiveness of this practice and its business value?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Leiva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>