<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-29T00:19:41.874Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-29T00:19:41.874Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform delivers launch-day support for Amazon S3 Express]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-delivers-launch-day-support-for-amazon-s3-express</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-delivers-launch-day-support-for-amazon-s3-express"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s Terraform provider for AWS now enables users to manage their S3 Express buckets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68117</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-1-rtw-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we released Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW. This is our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2022.1. You can directly install Azure DevOps Server 2022 Update 1 or upgrade from any version of Azure DevOps or TFS, including Team Foundation Server 2015 and newer.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RTW now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New generative AI capabilities for Amazon DataZone to further simplify data cataloging and discovery (preview)]]></title>
        <id>131acee0101beb35548fe2e11d609915ea34389d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-generative-ai-capabilities-for-amazon-datazone-to-further-simplify-data-cataloging-and-discovery-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing a preview of an automation feature backed by generative artificial intelligence (AI) for Amazon DataZone that will dramatically decrease the amount of time needed to provide context for organizational data. The new feature can automate the traditionally labor-intensive process of data cataloging. Powered by the large language models (LLMs) of Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon DynamoDB zero-ETL integration with Amazon OpenSearch Service is now available]]></title>
        <id>d95b735e282792585eecc5e44adea24aeca9599b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-dynamodb-zero-etl-integration-with-amazon-opensearch-service-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the general availability of Amazon DynamoDB zero-ETL integration with Amazon OpenSearch Service, which lets you perform a search on your DynamoDB data by automatically replicating and transforming it without custom code or infrastructure. This zero-ETL integration reduces the operational burden and cost involved in writing code for a data pipeline architecture, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: New Experimental Features in Gateway API v1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/28/gateway-api-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/28/gateway-api-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Candace Holman (Red Hat), Dave Protasowski (VMware), Gaurav K Ghildiyal (Google), John Howard (Google), Simone Rodigari (IBM)
Recently, the Gateway API announced its v1.0 GA release, marking a huge milestone for the project.
Along with stabilizing some of the core functionality in the API, a number of exciting new experimental features have been added.
Backend TLS Policy
BackendTLSPolicy is a new Gateway API type used for specifying the TLS configuration of the connection from the Gateway to backend Pods via the Service API object.
It is specified as a Direct PolicyAttachment without defaults or overrides, applied to a Service that accesses a backend, where the BackendTLSPolicy resides in the same namespace as the Service to which it is applied.
All Gateway API Routes that point t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New generative AI features in Amazon Connect, including Amazon Q, facilitate improved contact center service]]></title>
        <id>afb7136138459d51bb0664355f9648404168db8f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-generative-ai-features-in-amazon-connect-including-amazon-q-facilitate-improved-contact-center-service/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:52:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you manage a contact center, then you know the critical role that agents play in helping your organization build customer trust and loyalty. Those of us who’ve reached out to a contact center know how important agents are with guiding through complex decisions and providing fast and accurate solutions where needed. This can take […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon Q in QuickSight uses generative AI assistance for quicker, easier data insights (preview)]]></title>
        <id>d3be7143ca89918a5f3104192e00d334ec1a512d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-q-in-quicksight-uses-generative-ai-assistance-for-quicker-easier-data-insights-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to share that Amazon Q in QuickSight is available for preview. Now you can experience the Generative BI capabilities in Amazon QuickSight announced on July 26, as well as two additional capabilities for business users. Turning insights into impact faster with Amazon Q in QuickSight With this announcement, business users can now […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon Q, a new generative AI-powered assistant (preview)]]></title>
        <id>09ba312e05a9eac030f2f774d18e964ac51f557d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-q-a-new-generative-ai-powered-assistant-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing Amazon Q, a new generative artificial intelligence- (AI)-powered assistant designed for work that can be tailored to your business. You can use Amazon Q to have conversations, solve problems, generate content, gain insights, and take action by connecting to your company’s information repositories, code, data, and enterprise systems. Amazon Q provides […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade your Java applications with Amazon Q Code Transformation (preview)]]></title>
        <id>902b2224f0e2419cfd5aa25d7472cec10dd3690f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/upgrade-your-java-applications-with-amazon-q-code-transformation-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As our applications age, it takes more and more effort just to keep them secure and running smoothly. Developers managing the upgrades must spend time relearning the intricacies and nuances of breaking changes and performance optimizations others have already discovered in past upgrades. As a result, it’s difficult to balance the focus between new features […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve developer productivity with generative-AI powered Amazon Q in Amazon CodeCatalyst (preview)]]></title>
        <id>0c6f4ee8100aaed5e833d37fc914fab6b7f48cab</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/improve-developer-productivity-with-generative-ai-powered-amazon-q-in-amazon-codecatalyst-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m excited to introduce the preview of new generative artificial intelligence (AI) capabilities within Amazon CodeCatalyst that accelerate software delivery using Amazon Q. Accelerate feature development – The feature development capability in Amazon Q can help you accelerate the implementation of software development tasks such as adding comments and READMEs, refining issue descriptions, generating […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q brings generative AI-powered assistance to IT pros and developers (preview)]]></title>
        <id>47565295a861451fa61e61c6317ff31204ba9868</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-q-brings-generative-ai-powered-assistance-to-it-pros-and-developers-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the preview of Amazon Q, a new type of generative artificial intelligence (AI) powered assistant that is specifically for work and can be tailored to a customer’s business. Amazon Q brings a set of capabilities to support developers and IT professionals. Now you can use Amazon Q to get started building […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock helps implement safeguards customized to your use cases and responsible AI policies (preview)]]></title>
        <id>01dfc0957429a71acf2fe3c03698f5805b96b532</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/guardrails-for-amazon-bedrock-helps-implement-safeguards-customized-to-your-use-cases-and-responsible-ai-policies-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:10:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of your responsible artificial intelligence (AI) strategy, you can now use Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock (preview) to promote safe interactions between users and your generative AI applications by implementing safeguards customized to your use cases and responsible AI policies. AWS is committed to developing generative AI in a responsible, people-centric way by focusing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agents for Amazon Bedrock is now available with improved control of orchestration and visibility into reasoning]]></title>
        <id>22482146630bd395af100df7eae6fb9b9e15d1a2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/agents-for-amazon-bedrock-is-now-available-with-improved-control-of-orchestration-and-visibility-into-reasoning/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in July, we introduced Agents for Amazon Bedrock in preview. Today, Agents for Amazon Bedrock is generally available. Agents for Amazon Bedrock helps you accelerate generative artificial intelligence (AI) application development by orchestrating multistep tasks. Agents uses the reasoning capability of foundation models (FMs) to break down user-requested tasks into multiple steps. They use […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customize models in Amazon Bedrock with your own data using fine-tuning and continued pre-training]]></title>
        <id>b4f213430b4dd94b7dbc29cff4c51fda104118ef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/customize-models-in-amazon-bedrock-with-your-own-data-using-fine-tuning-and-continued-pre-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m excited to share that you can now privately and securely customize foundation models (FMs) with your own data in Amazon Bedrock to build applications that are specific to your domain, organization, and use case. With custom models, you can create unique user experiences that reflect your company’s style, voice, and services. With fine-tuning, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knowledge Bases now delivers fully managed RAG experience in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>463df1540583c390177f7d54e51f7a6f5141eb2e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/knowledge-bases-now-delivers-fully-managed-rag-experience-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in September, we introduced Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock in preview. Starting today, Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock is generally available. With a knowledge base, you can securely connect foundation models (FMs) in Amazon Bedrock to your company data for Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG). Access to additional data helps the model generate more relevant, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform extension for VS Code adds Terraform Cloud view]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-extension-for-vs-code-adds-terraform-cloud-view</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-extension-for-vs-code-adds-terraform-cloud-view"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new view in the HashiCorp Terraform extension for Visual Studio Code shows your Terraform Cloud workspaces and runs, reducing context-switching.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at re:Invent 2023: A year of collaboration with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-re-invent-2023-a-year-of-collaboration-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-re-invent-2023-a-year-of-collaboration-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recap of HashiCorp infrastructure and security news and developments on AWS from the past year, from self-service provisioning to fighting secrets sprawl and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the preview for new memory-optimized, AWS Graviton4-powered Amazon EC2 instances (R8g)]]></title>
        <id>31e7604b1ba06c3b64436d8a66bb766f4db13f92</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/join-the-preview-for-new-memory-optimized-aws-graviton4-powered-amazon-ec2-instances-r8g/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T16:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are opening up a preview of the next generation of Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances. Equipped with brand-new Graviton4 processors, the new R8g instances will deliver better price performance than any existing memory-optimized instance. The R8g instances are suitable for your most demanding memory-intensive workloads: big data analytics, high-performance databases, in-memory caches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new Amazon S3 Express One Zone high performance storage class]]></title>
        <id>42404115b44fce7c428d3305cbda7ba553e29db2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-s3-express-one-zone-high-performance-storage-class/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T16:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Amazon S3 Express One Zone storage class is designed to deliver up to 10x better performance than the S3 Standard storage class while handling hundreds of thousands of requests per second with consistent single-digit millisecond latency, making it a great fit for your most frequently accessed data and your most demanding applications. Objects […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study groups]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47885</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/842651315/0/sethsblog~Study-groups/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T09:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I had to choose one metric that would determine how well someone would do in law school, it wouldn’t be the LSAT or another test. It would be whether or not they formed a study group, and who else was in it. Of course, the same is true for your project, or any sort […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reserve quantum computers, get guidance and cutting-edge capabilities with Amazon Braket Direct]]></title>
        <id>b0e9b2cf45d2adb13ae90131e01955354ce28a22</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/reserve-quantum-computers-get-expertise-and-cutting-edge-capabilities-with-amazon-braket-direct/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T05:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the availability of Braket Direct, a new Amazon Braket program that helps quantum researchers dive deeper into quantum computing. This program lets you get dedicated, private access to the full capacity of various quantum processing units (QPUs) without any queues or wait times, connect with quantum computing specialists to receive expert […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Step Functions Workflow Studio is now available in AWS Application Composer]]></title>
        <id>15d25564c3a156fd6349efd5e56463420e981896</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-step-functions-workflow-studio-is-now-available-in-aws-application-composer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T04:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re announcing that AWS Step Functions Workflow Studio is now available in AWS Application Composer. This new integration brings together the development of workflows and application resources into a unified visual infrastructure as code (IaC) builder. Now, you can have a seamless transition between authoring workflows with AWS Step Functions Workflow Studio and defining resources with AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeCatalyst introduces custom blueprints and a new enterprise tier]]></title>
        <id>8594bdd7b37a95454383ad4284a2a4caaeb0df3d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-codecatalyst-introduces-custom-blueprints-and-a-new-enterprise-tier/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T04:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m excited to introduce the new Amazon CodeCatalyst enterprise tier and custom blueprints. Amazon CodeCatalyst enterprise tier is a new pricing tier that offers features like custom blueprints and project lifecycle management. The enterprise tier is $20/user per month, and each enterprise tier space gets 1,500 compute minutes, 160 Dev Environment hours, and 64GB […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon ElastiCache Serverless for Redis and Memcached is now available]]></title>
        <id>3af5ba5bb42d52881e5884fb6552e29cae3d7a3c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-elasticache-serverless-for-redis-and-memcached-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T04:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the availability of Amazon ElastiCache Serverless, a new serverless option that allows customers to create a cache in under a minute and instantly scale capacity based on application traffic patterns. ElastiCache Serverless is compatible with two popular open-source caching solutions, Redis and Memcached. You can use ElastiCache Serverless to operate a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the preview of Amazon Aurora Limitless Database]]></title>
        <id>f35e535f65605d93c28bd3897c14a55409cacf8b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/join-the-preview-amazon-aurora-limitless-database/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T03:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the preview of Amazon Aurora Limitless Database, a new capability supporting automated horizontal scaling to process millions of write transactions per second and manage petabytes of data in a single Aurora database. Amazon Aurora read replicas allow you to increase the read capacity of your Aurora cluster beyond the limits of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - 28 November, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/this-week-in-spring-28-november-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/this-week-in-spring-28-november-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.15, 3.0.10, 3.1.6 and 3.2.0-RC1 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/spring-shell-2-1-15-3-0-10-3-1-6-and-3-2-0-rc1-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/28/spring-shell-2-1-15-3-0-10-3-1-6-and-3-2-0-rc1-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step guide to creating custom ES Rally tracks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ES Rally is a benchmarking tool for Elasticsearch, enabling performance testing and decision-making through custom data tracks and comparative analysis. This comprehensive guide will show you the steps to take to craft personalized ES Rally tracks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alejandro Sánchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step guide to creating custom ES Rally tracks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/creating-custom-es-rally-tracks-guide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is ES Rally, and what is it for?,
ES Rally is a tool for testing performance on Elasticsearch® that allows you to run and record comparative tests.

Decision-making can be difficult, especially when you don't have the information you need and only have guesses or experience from past changes that have been positive or negative.

If we add to this that the data world must be flexible, as it evolves rapidly and therefore our Elasticsearch must adapt to it, this tool will help us to be able to measure all the changes and evolutions that we make over time and evaluate their impact. And most importantly, we can then obtain the information needed to make the right decisions.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt1d9db82a7e208b53/6566052e3994175cc8b4981b/1-elastic-bl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alejandro Sánchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Original Research: MIT CODE 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9340b879176a</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/netflix-original-research-mit-code-2023-9340b879176a?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix was thrilled to be the premier sponsor for the 2nd year in a row at the 2023 Conference on Digital Experimentation (CODE@MIT).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with new Amazon RDS for Db2]]></title>
        <id>ed2da70e3caf72f4eca217f84994974c765662ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/getting-started-with-new-amazon-rds-for-db2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that IBM and AWS have come together to offer Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) for Db2, a fully managed Db2 database engine running on AWS infrastructure. IBM Db2 is an enterprise-grade relational database management system (RDBMS) developed by IBM. It offers a comprehensive set of features, including strong data […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gain operator confidence with HCP Consul Central observability features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/gain-operator-confidence-with-hcp-consul-central-observability-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/gain-operator-confidence-with-hcp-consul-central-observability-features"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul Central’s new observability features were recently used by a customer to help troubleshoot an issue with assistance from HashiCorp engineers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform stacks, explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-stacks-explained</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-stacks-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform stacks simplify provisioning and managing resources at scale, reducing the time and overhead of managing infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing resources with the Terraform AWS Cloud Control provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Cloud Control provider — built around the AWS Cloud Control API — is designed to bring new services to HashiCorp Terraform faster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tackle Advent of Code 2023 With Kotlin and Win Prizes!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=409489</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/11/advent-of-code-2023-with-kotlin/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unwrap the joy of coding challenges as we gear up for Advent of Code, which JetBrains is proud to be sponsoring for a third consecutive year! Starting December 1, the JetBrains community will be diving into 25 days of coding challenges at adventofcode.com, and we warmly invite you to participate using Kotlin. Advent of Code […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ksenia Shneyveys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet us at AWS re:Invent 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=409493</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/11/meet-us-at-aws-reinvent-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains is participating in AWS re:Invent 2023 in Las Vegas this week (November 27 – December 1), and the TeamCity team is part of the booth crew. We’re excited about the opportunity to connect with you at the event! We are happy to chat with you about the state of CI/CD in your company, answer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hard part first]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44586</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/842296271/0/sethsblog~The-hard-part-first/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T09:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re trying to reduce risk, do the hard part first. That way, if it fails, you’ll have minimized your time and effort. On the other hand, if you’re looking for buy-in and commitment so you can get through the hard part, do it last. People are terrible at ignoring sunk costs, and the early […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Django Web Framework?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=391226</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/11/what-is-the-django-web-framework/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T08:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll introduce you to web frameworks and explore what they are and why they’re vital if you want to develop apps rapidly without compromising on security. More importantly, we’ll explain exactly what the Django web framework is – an open-source web framework for building web applications using Python. Whether you’re a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mukul Mantosh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2023-34053, CVE-2023-34055: Spring Framework and Spring Boot vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/27/cve-2023-34053-cve-2023-34055-spring-framework-and-spring-boot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/27/cve-2023-34053-cve-2023-34055-spring-framework-and-spring-boot"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decay Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2860/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2860/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/decay_modes.png" title="Unlike an Iron Age collapse, a Bronze Age collapse releases energy, since copper and tin are past the iron peak on the curve of binding energy." alt="Unlike an Iron Age collapse, a Bronze Age collapse releases energy, since copper and tin are past the iron peak on the curve of binding energy." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The long-range forecast keeps shifting]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46175</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/841853183/0/sethsblog~The-longrange-forecast-keeps-shifting/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exactly. That’s why it’s a forecast, not an accurate account of what’s going to happen in the future. This seems axiomatic, but our desire for certainty keeps letting us down. The shifting of forecasts is evidence that they’re merely forecasts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After the meteorite]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43520</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/841468958/0/sethsblog~After-the-meteorite/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it slams into your house and destroys it, we’re likely to pursue one of two lines of thinking: –How did I cause this? What choices did I make, what mistakes did I permit, why did I deserve to have this damage, or who can I blame? –Well, that happened, now what should I do? […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Causal Machine Learning for Creative Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4b0ce22a8a96</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/causal-machine-learning-for-creative-insights-4b0ce22a8a96?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T01:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A framework to identify the causal impact of successful visual components.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion Nova: A New Update With Various Bug Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=409246</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/11/clion-nova-a-new-update-with-various-bug-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T19:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion Nova, a free preview of CLion with the ReSharper C++/Rider C++ language engine, was announced recently. We’re excited to see how well you liked the first build! There are about 3,700 users right now and the overall feedback is mostly positive, especially that which is related to performance and language engine accuracy. Today, we’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Webinar] Build Like Gearbox: Developing a CI/CD Pipeline With Helix Core and JetBrains TeamCity]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=409137</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/11/webinar-gearbox-perforce-teamcity/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T14:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of the gaming industry, staying at the forefront of technology is crucial for success. Gearbox, the renowned AAA game studio responsible for the famous Borderlands franchise, has been a trailblazer since its inception in 1999. Over the years, Gearbox has continually adapted its tech stack to meet the escalating demands of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[String Templates in Java – why should you care?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=408802</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/11/string-templates-in-java-why-should-you-care/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T12:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TLDR; The existing String concatenation options are difficult to work with and could be error prone. String Templates (a preview feature introduced in Java 21) greatly improves how we create strings in Java by merging constant strings with variable values. The name of this feature pretty much says it all – String Templates. Think of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mala Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The network scam]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47825</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/841229846/0/sethsblog~The-network-scam/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T09:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lana Swartz coined this term in her breakthrough paper on crypto. A scam always involves a transaction. In the traditional fraud, the scammer tells a lie and the buyer, either with or without diligence, believes it and loses everything. You buy the magic beans, but they don’t grow. But modern scams have a network component […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.1 GA and 1.0.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/24/spring-modulith-1-1-ga-and-1-0-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/24/spring-modulith-1-1-ga-and-1-0-3-released"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Vault 3.1 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/24/spring-vault-3-1-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/24/spring-vault-3-1-available"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oceanography Gift]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2859/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2859/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/oceanography_gift.png" title="Shipping times vary. Same-ocean delivery may only take a few years, but delivery from the Weddell Sea in Antarctica may take multiple decades, and molecules meant for inland seas like the Mediterranean may be returned as undeliverable by surface currents." alt="Shipping times vary. Same-ocean delivery may only take a few years, but delivery from the Weddell Sea in Antarctica may take multiple decades, and molecules meant for inland seas like the Mediterranean may be returned as undeliverable by surface currents." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/24/sig-testing-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/24/sig-testing-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sandipan Panda
Welcome to another edition of the SIG spotlight blog series, where we
highlight the incredible work being done by various Special Interest
Groups (SIGs) within the Kubernetes project. In this edition, we turn
our attention to SIG Testing,
a group interested in effective testing of Kubernetes and automating
away project toil. SIG Testing focus on creating and running tools and
infrastructure that make it easier for the community to write and run
tests, and to contribute, analyze and act upon test results.
To gain some insights into SIG Testing, Sandipan
Panda spoke with Michelle Shepardson,
a senior software engineer at Google and a chair of SIG Testing, and
Patrick Ohly, a software engineer and architect at
Intel and a SIG Testing Tech Lead.
Meet the contributors
San…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet 1.27 Is Here With Emmet Support in PHP, a Compare With Clipboard Action, the Global Status Bar, New WSL Networking Mode Support, and More.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=fleet&amp;p=407463</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/fleet/2023/11/fleet-1-27-is-here-with-emmet-support-in-php-a-i-compare-with-clipboard-i-action-the-global-status-bar-new-wsl-networking-mode-support-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T15:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet 1.27 has arrived! Check out our latest release, loaded with new features to make your development experience even better. Let’s take a closer look at the highlights of this update. New features Improvements Bug fixes These are the most important updates for Fleet 1.27. See the full release notes for the complete list of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Prokashev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Primary Constructors – Using C# 12 in Rider and ReSharper]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=407893</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/11/23/primary-constructors-using-csharp-12-in-rider-and-resharper/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T15:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to our series, where we take a closer look at the C# 12 language features and how ReSharper and Rider make it easy for you to adopt them in your codebase. If you haven’t yet, download the latest .NET 8 SDK and update your project files! In this series, we are looking at: This is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias Koch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 Beta 3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=406984</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/11/intellij-idea-2023-3-beta-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T10:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 Beta 3 is now available for download! You can get the latest build through our website, the free Toolbox App, from inside the IDE, or by using snaps for Ubuntu. Download IntelliJ IDEA Beta 3 This marks the last week before the release candidate is scheduled for delivery. It’s the final call […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generosity and gratitude]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47869</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/840924704/0/sethsblog~Generosity-and-gratitude/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A gift doesn’t diminish the giver. Sharing creates connection, possibility and energy. And the magic of gratitude is that it improves everything it touches, especially the person who offered it in the first place. So, what holds us back? Fear. Fear of connection, of change, of seeing what is possible. It might feel safer to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-2-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-2-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-1-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-1-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: iText Creator Bruno Lowagie]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/a-bootiful-podcast-itext-creator-bruno-lowagie</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/a-bootiful-podcast-itext-creator-bruno-lowagie"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.13 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-0-13-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-boot-3-0-13-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.1.1 Available Now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-framework-6-1-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/11/23/spring-framework-6-1-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stéphane Nicoll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closing the skills and talent divide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/closing-the-skills-and-talent-divide</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/closing-the-skills-and-talent-divide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the HashiCast: Navigating the Cloud for C-Suites podcast addresses how to close the skills gap. Guest James Footman, Head of Talent for EMEA at HashiCorp, highlights the key takeaways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.3 Beta 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=408473</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/11/phpstorm-2023-3-beta-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.3 Beta 2 is now available! You can upgrade to the latest build using the Toolbox App or from our website. This build includes: Fix: PHPUnit tests in Docker running in WSL without Docker Desktop don’t work with namespaced –filter because of non-escaped slashes [WI-73742] Fix: Files don’t get saved automatically when running PHP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tania Goral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving simulations of clouds and their effects on climate]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/improving-simulations-of-clouds-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/improving-simulations-of-clouds-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tapio Schneider, Visiting Researcher, and Yi-fan Chen, Engineering Lead, Google Research




Today’s climate models successfully capture broad global warming trends. However, because of uncertainties about processes that are small in scale yet globally important, such as clouds and ocean turbulence, these models’ predictions of upcoming climate changes are not very accurate in detail. For example, predictions of the time by which the global mean surface temperature of Earth will have warmed 2℃, relative to preindustrial times, vary by 40–50 years (a full human generation) among today’s models. As a result, we do not have the accurate and geographically granular predictions we need to plan resilient infrastructure, adapt supply chains to climate disruption, and assess the risks of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar Recording: Uploading a Plugin to JetBrains Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=408405</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2023/11/webinar-recording-uploading-a-plugin-to-jetbrains-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recording of the latest episode of the Busy Plugin Developers webinar is now available on JetBrains TV. In this webinar, Natalia Melnikova from the JetBrains Marketplace team provided valuable insights into the plugin upload process. As a seasoned member of the team, she shed some light on the approval process as well as common […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Livestream: Harnessing the Power of AI Assistant in IntelliJ IDEA]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=406588</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/11/new-livestream-harnessing-the-power-of-ai-assistant-in-intellij-idea/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for the new IntelliJ IDEA LiveStream episode with Anton Arhipov to learn about the capabilities of AI Assistant in IntelliJ IDEA. Date: December 7, 2023 Time: 3:00 pm – 4:00 pm UTC REGISTER FOR THE LIVESTREAM Session abstract AI Assistant provides AI-powered features for software development based on the JetBrains AI service. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Rovinskaia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long form AI]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47865</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/838258340/0/sethsblog~Long-form-AI/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new version of Claude can read a document of up to 400 pages in about three minutes. You can then ask it for criticism, summaries or other insights. I wouldn’t use it on a piece of literature, but if you’re reading for work (aren’t we all), it will dramatically increase how much you can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability monitors metrics for Google Cloud in just minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow this step-by-step process to enable Elastic Observability for Google Cloud Platform metrics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon,Eric Lowry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability monitors metrics for Google Cloud in just minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-monitors-metrics-google-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Developers and SREs choose to host their applications on Google Cloud Platform (GCP) for its reliability, speed, and ease of use. On Google Cloud, development teams are finding additional value in migrating to Kubernetes on GKE, leveraging the latest serverless options like Cloud Run, and improving traditional, tiered applications with managed services.
Elastic Observability offers 16 out-of-the-box integrations for Google Cloud services with more on the way. A full list of Google Cloud integrations can be found in our online documentation.
In addition to our native Google Cloud integrations, Elastic Observability aggregates not only logs but also metrics for Google Cloud services and the applications running on Google Cloud compute services (Compute Engine, Cloud Run, Cloud Functions, K…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Simon,Eric Lowry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanksgiving Arguments]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2858/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2858/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/thanksgiving_arguments.png" title="An occasional source of mild Thanksgiving tension in my family is that my mother is a die-hard fan of The Core (2003), and various family members sometimes have differing levels of enthusiasm for her annual tradition of watching it." alt="An occasional source of mild Thanksgiving tension in my family is that my mother is a die-hard fan of The Core (2003), and various family members sometimes have differing levels of enthusiasm for her annual tradition of watching it." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open sourcing Project Guideline: A platform for computer vision accessibility technology]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/open-sourcing-project-guideline.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/open-sourcing-project-guideline.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dave Hawkey, Software Engineer, Google Research




Two years ago we announced Project Guideline, a collaboration between Google Research and Guiding Eyes for the Blind that enabled people with visual impairments (e.g., blindness and low-vision) to walk, jog, and run independently. Using only a Google Pixel phone and headphones, Project Guideline leverages on-device machine learning (ML) to navigate users along outdoor paths marked with a painted line. The technology has been tested all over the world and even demonstrated during the opening ceremony at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games.



Since the original announcement, we set out to improve Project Guideline by embedding new features, such as obstacle detection and advanced path planning, to safely and reliably navigate users t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Good First Issue: Introducing a new way to contribute]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-21-for-good-first-issue-introducing-a-new-way-to-contribute/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-21-for-good-first-issue-introducing-a-new-way-to-contribute/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For Good First Issue is a curated list of open source projects that are also digital public goods and need the help of developers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-21-for-good-first-issue-introducing-a-new-way-to-contribute/">For Good First Issue: Introducing a new way to contribute</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at AWS re:Invent: Your blueprint for cloud success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-your-blueprint-for-cloud-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-your-blueprint-for-cloud-success"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re attending AWS re:Invent in Las Vegas, Nov. 27 - Dec. 1, visit us for breakout sessions, expert talks, and product demos to learn how to accelerate your adoption of a cloud operating model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Fall Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68016</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-fall-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T16:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have been following these posts, then you are more than familiar with our New Boards Hub initiative. We have been doing our best to keep our community informed of the new features and our rollout plans. Now is a good time to provide an update on where things are at with a couple of our new preview features,
The post New Boards Hub, Fall Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three sheet metaphors]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46154</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/836911259/0/sethsblog~Three-sheet-metaphors/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T11:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a large blue bedsheet, queen sized. If we’re going to pull it taut, it will take the coordinated effort of eight people, each pulling just the right amount, from each corner and edge. If we’re going to billow it up and down, like a parachute, we’re going to need those people to work in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Processing using Netflix Maestro and Apache Iceberg]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b8ba072ddeeb</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/incremental-processing-using-netflix-maestro-and-apache-iceberg-b8ba072ddeeb?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T05:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Jun He, Yingyi Zhang, and Pawan Dixit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josey Coles shares what skills translated from the military to the corporate world and her tips for other veterans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tips-for-veterans</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tips-for-veterans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josey Coles joined the US military in 2016 as a cyber operations specialist. She has since transitioned out of the military and shares her experience and advice for other veterans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C-suite insights on the transformative power of generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore insights from top IT leaders on leveraging generative AI for enhancing operational resilience, mitigating security risk, and creating exceptional customer experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Klinger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josey Coles shares what skills translated from the military to the corporate world and her tips for other veterans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tips-for-veterans</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tips-for-veterans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Josey Coles, Sr. Manager, Education Services at Elastic®, joined the US military in 2016 as a cyber operations specialist. As a math major, cybersecurity wasn’t her background or on her list of interests but the Army gave her a lot of experience, she says.
As a cyber operations specialist, Josey was part of the Cyber Protection Brigade. She responded to incidents and was required to be onsite within 48 hours of the call. Onsite, her team would listen to network traffic, determine if the line was compromised, and put a risk mitigation plan in place to prevent future intrusions. 

After four years, and a promotion to senior network analyst, Josey transitioned out of the military for medical reasons. 

“The most challenging part was the uncertainty,” she says. “The military has a way of tak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C-suite insights on the transformative power of generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/portfolio/c-suite-insights-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Generative AI is revolutionizing the way businesses operate, from improving operational resilience to mitigating security risks and enhancing customer experiences. In a recent roundup of c-suite insights from three IT leaders — Matt Minetola, CIO, Mandy Andress, CISO, and Rick Laner, chief customer officer — we gain a comprehensive understanding of how generative AI is being used to improve business outcomes across organizations.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt3135954a466f9c02/655d0750107d423a15b7b191/1-elastic-blog-matt-minetola.png,1-elastic-blog-matt-minetola.png,
Matt Minetola, CIO at Elastic, highlights the use of generative AI in improving operational resilience. He points out that organizations already possess a wealth of telemetry data, which is cr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Klinger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from Git 2.43]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-20-highlights-from-git-2-43/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-20-highlights-from-git-2-43/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T18:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The last Git release of 2023 is here! Take a look at some of our highlights on what's new in Git 2.43.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-20-highlights-from-git-2-43/">Highlights from Git 2.43</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault integrations with Intel, Pure Storage, Red Hat, and more continue to strengthen customer security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-intel-pure-storage-red-hat-and-more-continue-to-strengthe</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-integrations-with-intel-pure-storage-red-hat-and-more-continue-to-strengthe"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10 new HashiCorp Vault ecosystem integrations extend security use cases for customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nice bike]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47850</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/836338772/0/sethsblog~Nice-bike/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T09:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A well-designed bicycle is efficient, inexpensive and delightful. If you use your bike on the right paths, with appropriate goals, it can deliver exactly what you need, while also allowing you to go at your own pace, see what’s going on around you and feel grounded. Until, of course, you get jealous. If you start […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuttals]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2857/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2857/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/rebuttals.png" title="The mainstream dogma sparked a wave of dogmatic revisionism, and this revisionist mainstream dogmatism has now given way to a more rematic mainvisionist dogstream." alt="The mainstream dogma sparked a wave of dogmatic revisionism, and this revisionist mainstream dogmatism has now given way to a more rematic mainvisionist dogstream." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The perfect conditions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43630</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/836213015/0/sethsblog~The-perfect-conditions/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T09:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhere, there is the ideal soil for growing mangoes. Or the best possible wave for surfing. Or the most romantic sunset for a proposal. But it’s not right here and it’s not right now. Our success has a lot to do with how we dance with conditions that aren’t quite perfect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging practices for Society-Centered AI]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/emerging-practices-for-society-centered.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/emerging-practices-for-society-centered.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Anoop Sinha, Research Director, Technology & Society, and Yossi Matias, Vice President, Google Research




The first of Google’s AI Principles is to “Be socially beneficial.” As AI practitioners, we’re inspired by the transformative potential of AI technologies to benefit society and our shared environment at a scale and swiftness that wasn’t possible before. From helping address the climate crisis to helping transform healthcare, to making the digital world more accessible, our goal is to apply AI responsibly to be helpful to more people around the globe. Achieving global scale requires researchers and communities to think ahead — and act — collectively across the AI ecosystem.



We call this approach Society-Centered AI. It is both an extension and an expansion of Human-Cente…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting Kibana health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-kibana-health</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-kibana-health"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post provides a troubleshooting framework for Kibana’s health overall, focusing on its Task Manager and Alerting framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stef Nestor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting Kibana health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-kibana-health</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/troubleshooting-kibana-health"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
You can access the Elasticsearch® database through Elastic’s UI product: Kibana®. While most Elastic® services run from Elasticsearch, a handful of key features run from within Kibana’s servers: Telemetry, Rules (with associated Actions), Reporting, and Sessions. We’ll walk through troubleshooting overall Kibana health and its most popular plugins. This content is generally true for 7.x and 8.x, but it is tested directly against v8.7.1.
# undocumented, internal API
## ui
> GET KIBANA_URL/status
## api
> GET kbn:/api/status

# https://www.elastic.co/guide/en/kibana/current/task-manager-api-health.html
> GET kbn:api/task_manager/_health
,
Once you have these responses stored respectively as kibana_status.json and kibana_task_manager_health.json, then you have the two core APIs Support insp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stef Nestor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps’ First Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68002</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-first-consensus-assessment-initiative-questionnaire-caiq-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am thrilled to announce that we have now published, for the first time, a Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) specific to Azure DevOps. The Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) is a tool developed by the Cloud Security Alliance (CSA). It serves as a standard set of questions aimed at helping potential cloud customers evaluate the security capabilities of cloud service providers.
The post Azure DevOps’ First Consensus Assessment Initiative Questionnaire (CAIQ) Now Available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benibo Ajumogobia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Adversarial testing for generative AI safety]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research_16.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research_16.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kathy Meier-Hellstern, Building Responsible AI & Data Systems, Director, Google Research




The Responsible AI and Human-Centered Technology (RAI-HCT) team within Google Research is committed to advancing the theory and practice of responsible human-centered AI through a lens of culturally-aware research, to meet the needs of billions of users today, and blaze the path forward for a better AI future. The BRAIDS (Building Responsible AI Data and Solutions) team within RAI-HCT aims to simplify the adoption of RAI practices through the utilization of scalable tools, high-quality data, streamlined processes, and novel research with a current emphasis on addressing the unique challenges posed by generative AI (GenAI).





GenAI models have enabled unprecedented capabilities leading …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security best practices for authors of GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-16-security-best-practices-for-authors-of-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-16-security-best-practices-for-authors-of-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Improve your GitHub Action’s security posture by securing your source repository, protecting your maintainers, and making it easy to report security incidents. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-16-security-best-practices-for-authors-of-github-actions/">Security best practices for authors of GitHub Actions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and University of Canberra: A partnership for student success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-university-of-canberra-partnership-student-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-university-of-canberra-partnership-student-success"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, learn about the partnership between Elastic and the University of Canberra as well as the benefits and outcomes of the partnership for the students, the university, and the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vu Pham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching majors led Kathleen DeRusso to a career in search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-kathleen-derusso-search-software-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-kathleen-derusso-search-software-engineer"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kathleen DeRusso likes to solve problems, something she gets to do every day in her software engineering job. Read more about her career journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do Elasticsearch snapshots work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-do-incremental-snapshots-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-do-incremental-snapshots-work"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During our instructor-led “Elasticsearch Engineer” training, one of the most common questions we get while teaching about snapshots is “what is the incremental nature of snapshots?” This blog post will cover that topic in detail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lutf ur Rehman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Support Hub moves to semantic search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-support-hub-moves-to-semantic-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-support-hub-moves-to-semantic-search"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We transitioned our Support Hub to semantic search, a more advanced search method that understands user intent rather than relying on keywords. This transition helps provide customers with more relevant search results in Elastic's support content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blaisure</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Agent’s new output to Kafka: Endless possibilities for data collection and streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-output-kafka-data-collection-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-output-kafka-data-collection-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Elastic Agent's new feature: native output to Kafka. With this latest addition, Elastic's users can now effortlessly route their data to Kafka clusters, unlocking unparalleled scalability and flexibility in data streaming and processing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerio Arvizzigno,Geetha Anne,Jeremy Hogan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and University of Canberra: A partnership for student success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-university-of-canberra-partnership-student-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-university-of-canberra-partnership-student-success"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The IT sector is one of the most dynamic and innovative industries in the world. However, it also faces a serious challenge of finding and retaining qualified talent. The Australian Information Industry Association (AIIA) survey for 2023 revealed that skill shortages are the single biggest inhibitor to business growth in Australia. The survey also found that 49% of IT graduates in Australia needed further training to be effective employees. To address this issue, the University of Canberra (UC) is committed to delivering work-ready graduates who can meet the industry’s needs and expectations. One of the ways UC does this is by offering its final year students Capstone projects, which help them apply and improve their skills for their future careers.
Elastic®, a leading provider of softwa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vu Pham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching majors led Kathleen DeRusso to a career in search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-kathleen-derusso-search-software-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-kathleen-derusso-search-software-engineer"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
After completing a Java developer course during college, Kathleen DeRusso liked it enough to change her major from business to computer science. 

“I like to solve interesting and challenging problems,” Kathleen says.

Early in her career, she worked for a B2B product company in their search organization where she evolved their search to enable electronic parts to be searchable by number. 

“I stayed on search the entire time,” she says. “I started in a role that would probably be thought of as SRE today and then moved into search development. We had a home grown search engine over manufacturer catalogs based on Lucene, then another search product searching electronic part numbers backed by SOLR. I led the project to migrate from both homegrown and SOLR search engines to Elasticsearch®.”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do Elasticsearch snapshots work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-do-incremental-snapshots-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-do-incremental-snapshots-work"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic offers many instructor-led, in-person and virtual live trainings, as well as on-demand trainings. Our flagship courses are Elasticsearch Engineer, Data Analysis with Kibana, and Elastic Observability Engineer. All of these courses lead to certifications. 

We recently released the latest version of Elasticsearch Engineer training in response to increased demand and new features. This course is designed for both new Elasticsearch users and Elasticsearch professionals. It begins with the basics for getting started with the Elastic Stack, then quickly dives deep into topics ranging from optimizing search performance to building efficient clusters. View the detailed course outline to find out more about what you’ll learn. All lessons include hands-on labs.

During this instructor-led…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lutf ur Rehman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Support Hub moves to semantic search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-support-hub-moves-to-semantic-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-support-hub-moves-to-semantic-search"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re excited to share a recent enhancement made to the Elastic Support Hub: it’s now powered by semantic search!
But before we go into more detail on the changes we made to the Elastic® Support Hub and its impact on our customers, it's important that we take a moment to explain the concept of semantic search. At its core, semantic search is a method of search that uses AI to return more relevant search results. Take a look at this quick video explaining the concept:
,As shown in the video, semantic search matches the intent of what the user searches to the content available rather than the words. You can read more about the AI behind it on our blog, Introducing Elastic Learned Sparse Encoder: Elastic’s AI model for semantic search. The rest of this blog tells our story about moving the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blaisure</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Agent’s new output to Kafka: Endless possibilities for data collection and streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-output-kafka-data-collection-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-output-kafka-data-collection-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Introducing Elastic Agent's new feature: native output to Kafka. With this latest addition, Elastic®’s users can now effortlessly route their data to Kafka clusters, unlocking unparalleled scalability and flexibility in data streaming and processing. In this article, we'll delve into the benefits and use cases of this powerful integration.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt0c705feae2ac6bf7/65563b759984b862c15aadcd/1-elastic-blog-fleet.png,1-elastic-blog-fleet.png,
You will be able to set partitioning rules and multiple topics to send data to, depending on specific rules you define. This will allow sorting events and logs collected by the Elastic Agent to be routed and segregated to the right dedicated topic, if needed.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerio Arvizzigno,Geetha Anne,Jeremy Hogan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Removals, Deprecations, and Major Changes in Kubernetes 1.29]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/kubernetes-1-29-upcoming-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/kubernetes-1-29-upcoming-changes/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Carol Valencia, Kristin Martin, Abigail McCarthy, James Quigley, Hosam Kamel
As with every release, Kubernetes v1.29 will introduce feature deprecations and removals. Our continued ability to produce high-quality releases is a testament to our robust development cycle and healthy community. The following are some of the deprecations and removals coming in the Kubernetes 1.29 release.
The Kubernetes API removal and deprecation process
The Kubernetes project has a well-documented deprecation policy for features. This policy states that stable APIs may only be deprecated when a newer, stable version of that same API is available and that APIs have a minimum lifetime for each stability level. A deprecated API is one that has been marked for removal in a future Kubernetes release; it w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: The Case for Kubernetes Resource Limits: Predictability vs. Efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/the-case-for-kubernetes-resource-limits/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/16/the-case-for-kubernetes-resource-limits/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Milan Plžík (Grafana Labs)
There’s been quite a lot of posts suggesting that not using Kubernetes resource limits might be a fairly useful thing (for example, For the Love of God, Stop Using CPU Limits on Kubernetes or Kubernetes: Make your services faster by removing CPU limits ). The points made there are totally valid – it doesn’t make much sense to pay for compute power that will not be used due to limits, nor to artificially increase latency. This post strives to argue that limits have their legitimate use as well.
As a Site Reliability Engineer on the Grafana Labs platform team, which maintains and improves internal infrastructure and tooling used by the product teams, I primarily try to make Kubernetes upgrades as smooth as possible. But I also spend a lot of time going down…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Universe&#8217;s key takeaway: Innovate better with AI-powered workflows on a single, unified platform]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-15-universes-key-takeaway-innovate-better-with-ai-powered-workflows-on-a-single-unified-platform/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-15-universes-key-takeaway-innovate-better-with-ai-powered-workflows-on-a-single-unified-platform/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T21:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover new AI-powered features and tools to help developers stay in the flow and organizations innovate at scale.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-15-universes-key-takeaway-innovate-better-with-ai-powered-workflows-on-a-single-unified-platform/">Universe&#8217;s key takeaway: Innovate better with AI-powered workflows on a single, unified platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solutions to secret sprawl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/solutions-to-secret-sprawl</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/solutions-to-secret-sprawl"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret sprawl makes companies more vulnerable to data breaches. Learn how to locate and centralize secrets in a single location for greater security and simplified management and compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第241話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755451951724</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755451951724"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agentless configuration drift detection and remediation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/agentless-configuration-drift-detection-and-remediation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/agentless-configuration-drift-detection-and-remediation"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over time, application owners find themselves compelled to continuously refine their applications and the underlying infrastructure to enhance the products they deliver, whether to internal or external customers. These modifications inevitably lead to changes in the configuration of both applications and infrastructure. While some of these changes may be benign, others can unintentionally steer the systems away from their securely configured state, a phenomenon commonly referred to as "configuration drift." Left unaddressed, the extent of this drift can introduce substantial risks to the organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bforrest@redhat.com (Ben Forrester)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Psyberg: Automated end to end catch up]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/260fbe366fe2</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/3-psyberg-automated-end-to-end-catch-up-260fbe366fe2?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T03:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Abhinaya Shetty, Bharath Mummadisetty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving Deeper into Psyberg: Stateless vs Stateful Data Processing]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1d273b3aaefb</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/2-diving-deeper-into-psyberg-stateless-vs-stateful-data-processing-1d273b3aaefb?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T03:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Abhinaya Shetty, Bharath Mummadisetty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1. Streamlining Membership Data Engineering at Netflix with Psyberg]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f68830617dd1</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/1-streamlining-membership-data-engineering-at-netflix-with-psyberg-f68830617dd1?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T03:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Abhinaya Shetty, Bharath Mummadisetty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling multimodal understanding to long videos]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/scaling-multimodal-understanding-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/scaling-multimodal-understanding-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T20:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Isaac Noble, Software Engineer, Google Research, and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientist, Google DeepMind 





When building machine learning models for real-life applications, we need to consider inputs from multiple modalities in order to capture various aspects of the world around us. For example, audio, video, and text all provide varied and complementary information about a visual input. However, building multimodal models is challenging due to the heterogeneity of the modalities. Some of the modalities might be well synchronized in time (e.g., audio, video) but not aligned with text. Furthermore, the large volume of data in video and audio signals is much larger than that in text, so when combining them in multimodal models, video and audio often cannot be fully consumed a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[November patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67953</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/november-patches-for-azure-devops-server-and-team-foundation-server/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T18:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server, as well as Team Foundation Server 2018.3.2.
Note: If you have Azure DevOps Server 2022, you should first update to Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 and then install Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 Patch 5.
The post November patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Speech and Music in Audio Content]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/afd64e6a5bf8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/detecting-speech-and-music-in-audio-content-afd64e6a5bf8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T01:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iroro Orife, Chih-Wei Wu and Yun-Ning (Amy) Hung]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: October 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-13-github-availability-report-october-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-13-github-availability-report-october-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T20:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In October, we experienced two incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-13-github-availability-report-october-2023/">GitHub Availability Report: October 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform integrations with Dell, DNSimple, Fortinet, Palo Alto Networks, Juniper Networks, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-dell-dnsimple-fortinet-palo-alto-networks-juniper</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-with-dell-dnsimple-fortinet-palo-alto-networks-juniper"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[18 new Terraform integration partners provide more options to automate and secure cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling large-scale health studies for the research community]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/enabling-large-scale-health-studies-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/enabling-large-scale-health-studies-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Chintan Ghate, Software Engineer, and Diana Mincu, Research Engineer, Google Research




As consumer technologies like fitness trackers and mobile phones become more widely used for health-related data collection, so does the opportunity to leverage these data pathways to study and advance our understanding of medical conditions. We have previously touched upon how our work explores the use of this technology within the context of chronic diseases, in particular multiple sclerosis (MS). This effort leverages the FDA MyStudies platform, an open-source platform used to create clinical study apps, that makes it easier for anyone to run their own studies and collect good quality healthcare data, in a trusted and safe way.


 


Today, we describe the setup that we developed by expan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks 2024: 24-hours of virtual knowledge sharing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2024-24-hours-of-virtual-knowledge-sharing</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2024-24-hours-of-virtual-knowledge-sharing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks returns on February 15, 2024. Join our global community for 24 hours of knowledge sharing. The call for proposals is open through November 30, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating the GitHub Awards 2023 recipients 🎉]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-09-celebrating-the-github-awards-2023-recipients/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-09-celebrating-the-github-awards-2023-recipients/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T00:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The GitHub Awards recognizes and celebrates the outstanding contributions and achievements in the developer community, honoring individuals, projects, and organizations for their impactful work, innovation, thought leadership, and creating an outsized positive impact on the community.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-09-celebrating-the-github-awards-2023-recipients/">Celebrating the GitHub Awards 2023 recipients 🎉</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Context in AI Research (CAIR)]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T22:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Katherine Heller, Research Scientist, Google Research, on behalf of the CAIR Team




Artificial intelligence (AI) and related machine learning (ML) technologies are increasingly influential in the world around us, making it imperative that we consider the potential impacts on society and individuals in all aspects of the technology that we create. To these ends, the Context in AI Research (CAIR) team develops novel AI methods in the context of the entire AI pipeline: from data to end-user feedback. The pipeline for building an AI system typically starts with data collection, followed by designing a model to run on that data, deployment of the model in the real world, and lastly, compiling and incorporation of human feedback. Originating in the health space, and now expanded to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming leakage on error-corrected quantum processors]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/overcoming-leakage-on-error-corrected.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/overcoming-leakage-on-error-corrected.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:20:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kevin Miao and Matt McEwen, Research Scientists, Quantum AI Team




The qubits that make up Google quantum devices are delicate and noisy, so it’s necessary to incorporate error correction procedures that identify and account for qubit errors on the way to building a useful quantum computer. Two of the most prevalent error mechanisms are bit-flip errors (where the energy state of the qubit changes) and phase-flip errors (where the phase of the encoded quantum information changes). Quantum error correction (QEC) promises to address and mitigate these two prominent errors. However, there is an assortment of other error mechanisms that challenges the effectiveness of QEC.



While we want qubits to behave as ideal two-level systems with no loss mechanisms, this is not the case in r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Kubernetes ingress with HashiCorp Boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/secure-kubernetes-ingress-with-hashicorp-boundary</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/secure-kubernetes-ingress-with-hashicorp-boundary"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See a potential method for securing application content and components hosted within Kubernetes using Boundary as an alternative to ingress controllers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.17 GA adds locality-aware routing and multi-port support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-17-ga-adds-locality-aware-routing-and-multi-port-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-17-ga-adds-locality-aware-routing-and-multi-port-support"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.17 enhances unified workflow management, reliability, scale, and security for service networking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Step in Personalization: Dynamic Sizzles]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4dc4ce2011ef</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/the-next-step-in-personalization-dynamic-sizzles-4dc4ce2011ef?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T20:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors:Bruce Wobbe, Leticia Kwok]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest Terraform Enterprise features reduce operational burdens, save money]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/latest-terraform-enterprise-features-reduce-operational-burdens-save-money</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/latest-terraform-enterprise-features-reduce-operational-burdens-save-money"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent additions to Terraform Enterprise to enhance manageability and efficiency include flexible deployment options, ephemeral workspaces, and run data retention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Universe 2023: Copilot transforms GitHub into the AI-powered developer platform]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-08-universe-2023-copilot-transforms-github-into-the-ai-powered-developer-platform/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-08-universe-2023-copilot-transforms-github-into-the-ai-powered-developer-platform/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub is announcing general availability of GitHub Copilot Chat and previews of the new GitHub Copilot Enterprise offering, new AI-powered security features, and the GitHub Copilot Partner Program.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-08-universe-2023-copilot-transforms-github-into-the-ai-powered-developer-platform/">Universe 2023: Copilot transforms GitHub into the AI-powered developer platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Octoverse: The state of open source and rise of AI in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-08-the-state-of-open-source-and-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-08-the-state-of-open-source-and-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T17:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In this year’s Octoverse report, we study how open source activity around AI, the cloud, and Git are changing the developer experience. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-08-the-state-of-open-source-and-ai/">Octoverse: The state of open source and rise of AI in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AI-powered application security testing with GitHub Advanced Security]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-08-ai-powered-appsec/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-08-ai-powered-appsec/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T17:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn about how GitHub Advanced Security’s new AI-powered features can help you secure your code more efficiently than ever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-08-ai-powered-appsec/">Introducing AI-powered application security testing with GitHub Advanced Security</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternating updates for efficient transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/alternating-updates-for-efficient.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/alternating-updates-for-efficient.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T20:34:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xin Wang, Software Engineer, and Nishanth Dikkala, Research Scientist, Google Research




Contemporary deep learning models have been remarkably successful in many domains, ranging from natural language to computer vision. Transformer neural networks (transformers) are a popular deep learning architecture that today comprise the foundation for most tasks in natural language processing and also are starting to extend to applications in other domains, such as computer vision, robotics, and autonomous driving. Moreover, they form the backbone of all the current state-of-the-art language models.
 

Increasing scale in Transformer networks has led to improved performance and the emergence of behavior not present in smaller networks. However, this increase in scale often comes with pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud now supports dynamic provider credentials for Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-now-supports-dynamic-provider-credentials-for-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-now-supports-dynamic-provider-credentials-for-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud dynamic provider credentials now enable automated authentication for Kubernetes via EKS and GKE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Operator v2 for Kubernetes is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-operator-v2-for-kubernetes-is-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-operator-v2-for-kubernetes-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Operator v2 for Kubernetes is now generally available, enhancing resource management and scaling of Terraform Cloud agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 use cases for automating your infrastructure with Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/5-use-cases-for-automating-your-infrastructure-with-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/5-use-cases-for-automating-your-infrastructure-with-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure automation is an area where systems administrators and  IT operations teams can see some of the biggest benefits from automation, including time savings, reducing tedious manual work, and improving the overall health of their systems. In this blog, I've identified the top 5 infrastructure automation use cases for Ansible Automation Platform that you can deploy in your own environment, and I've incorporated new capabilities like Event-Driven Ansible to make managing your infrastructure even easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>trmcconn@redhat.com (Tricia McConnell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing SIG etcd]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/07/introducing-sig-etcd/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/07/introducing-sig-etcd/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Han Kang (Google), Marek Siarkowicz (Google), Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
Special Interest Groups (SIGs) are a fundamental part of the Kubernetes project, with a substantial share of the community activity happening within them. When the need arises, new SIGs can be created, and that was precisely what happened recently.
SIG etcd is the most recent addition to the list of Kubernetes SIGs. In this article we will get to know it a bit better, understand its origins, scope, and plans.
The critical role of etcd
If we look inside the control plane of a Kubernetes cluster, we will find etcd, a consistent and highly-available key value store used as Kubernetes' backing store for all cluster data -- this description alone highlights the critical role that etcd plays, and the importanc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building In-Video Search]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/936766f0017c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/building-in-video-search-936766f0017c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering video editors with multimodal machine learning to discover perfect moments across the entire Netflix catalog]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault adds 3 new observability integrations and HTTP streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-adds-3-new-observability-integrations-and-http-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-adds-3-new-observability-integrations-and-http-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault gains 3 new observability integrations with AWS Cloudwatch, Elasticsearch, and New Relic, as well as a generic HTTP endpoint for flexible metrics streaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streaming SQL in Data Mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/0d83f5a00d08</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/streaming-sql-in-data-mesh-0d83f5a00d08?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T21:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratizing Stream Processing @ Netflix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of both worlds: Achieving scalability and quality in text clustering]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/best-of-both-worlds-achieving.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/best-of-both-worlds-achieving.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T18:23:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Ahmadian and Mehran Kazemi, Research Scientists, Google Research




Clustering is a fundamental, ubiquitous problem in data mining and unsupervised machine learning, where the goal is to group together similar items. The standard forms of clustering are metric clustering and graph clustering. In metric clustering, a given metric space defines distances between data points, which are grouped together based on their separation. In graph clustering, a given graph connects similar data points through edges, and the clustering process groups data points together based on the connections between them. Both clustering forms are particularly useful for large corpora where class labels can’t be defined. Examples of such corpora are the ever-growing digital text collections of variou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate networking across Google Cloud runtimes with Consul and Apigee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/automate-networking-across-google-cloud-runtimes-with-consul-and-apigee</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/automate-networking-across-google-cloud-runtimes-with-consul-and-apigee"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to manage service-to-service communication across environments using Consul and the Apigee adapter for Envoy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Contributor Summit: Behind-the-scenes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/03/k8s-contributor-summit-behind-the-scenes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/03/k8s-contributor-summit-behind-the-scenes/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author : Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
Every year, just before the official start of KubeCon+CloudNativeCon, there's a special event that
has a very special place in the hearts of those organizing and participating in it: the Kubernetes
Contributor Summit. To find out why, and to provide a behind-the-scenes perspective, we interview
Noah Abrahams, whom amongst other roles was the co-lead for the Kubernetes Contributor Summit in
2023.
Frederico Muñoz (FSM): Hello Noah, and welcome. Could you start by introducing yourself and
telling us how you got involved in Kubernetes?
Noah Abrahams (NA): I’ve been in this space for quite a while.  I got started in IT in the mid
90's, and I’ve been working in the "Cloud" space for about 15 years.  It was, frankly, through a
combination of sheer luck (be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-shot adaptive prompting of large language models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/zero-shot-adaptive-prompting-of-large.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/zero-shot-adaptive-prompting-of-large.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T22:01:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xingchen Wan, Student Researcher, and Ruoxi Sun, Research Scientist, Cloud AI Team




Recent advances in large language models (LLMs) are very promising as reflected in their capability for general problem-solving in few-shot and zero-shot setups, even without explicit training on these tasks. This is impressive because in the few-shot setup, LLMs are presented with only a few question-answer demonstrations prior to being given a test question. Even more challenging is the zero-shot setup, where the LLM is directly prompted with the test question only. 




Even though the few-shot setup has dramatically reduced the amount of data required to adapt a model for a specific use-case, there are still cases where generating sample prompts can be challenging. For example, handcrafting…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging AI to empower all developers at GitHub Universe 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-11-02-leveraging-ai-to-empower-all-developers-at-github-universe-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-11-02-leveraging-ai-to-empower-all-developers-at-github-universe-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T16:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub Universe 2023 is just around the corner! Join us and learn how GitHub is leveraging AI to empower all developers, including developers with disabilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-11-02-leveraging-ai-to-empower-all-developers-at-github-universe-2023/">Leveraging AI to empower all developers at GitHub Universe 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fact-Gathering with Event-Driven Ansible for Microsoft Windows ITSM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/fact-gathering-with-event-driven-ansible-and-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/fact-gathering-with-event-driven-ansible-and-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The use of Event-Driven Ansible to enable fact gathering from events is considered a “Getting Started” type of use case, but it can be extremely powerful. This use case is simple and it is what we consider a “Read Only” type of action, meaning that we are not making any changes, but we are using the event to trigger a fact gathering process which we can later publish to the IT Service Management system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Architecture: Production Readiness]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/02/sig-architecture-production-readiness-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/11/02/sig-architecture-production-readiness-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS Institute)
This is the second interview of a SIG Architecture Spotlight series that will cover the different
subprojects. In this blog, we will cover the SIG Architecture: Production Readiness
subproject.
In this SIG Architecture spotlight, we talked with Wojciech Tyczynski
(Google), lead of the Production Readiness subproject.
About SIG Architecture and the Production Readiness subproject
Frederico (FSM): Hello Wojciech, could you tell us a bit about yourself, your role and how you
got involved in Kubernetes?
Wojciech Tyczynski (WT): I started contributing to Kubernetes in January 2015. At that time,
Google (where I was and still am working) decided to start a Kubernetes team in the Warsaw office
(in addition to already existing teams in California and Seattle…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.7 beta improves Vault and Consul integrations, adds NUMA support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-7-improves-vault-and-consul-integrations-adds-numa-support"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.7 — now in beta — introduces improved workload identity, improved Vault and Consul integrations, NUMA support, Nomad actions, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetNet-3: A state-of-the-art neural weather model available in Google products]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/11/metnet-3-state-of-art-neural-weather.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/11/metnet-3-state-of-art-neural-weather.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T17:30:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Samier Merchant, Google Research, and Nal Kalchbrenner, Google DeepMind






Forecasting weather variables such as precipitation, temperature, and wind is key to numerous aspects of society, from daily planning and transportation to energy production. As we continue to see more extreme weather events such as floods, droughts, and heat waves, accurate forecasts can be essential to preparing for and mitigating their effects. The first 24 hours into the future are especially important as they are both highly predictable and actionable, which can help people make informed decisions in a timely manner and stay safe. 
 

Today we present a new weather model called MetNet-3, developed by Google Research and Google DeepMind. Building on the earlier MetNet and MetNet-2 models, MetNet-3 p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Partial Clone Now Supported in Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67877</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/git-partial-clone-now-supported-in-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T17:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git Partial Clone
The post Git Partial Clone Now Supported in Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Carlson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第240話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755396392866</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755396392866"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC2 now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67838</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-1-rc2-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T18:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC2. This is our last planned prerelease before our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2022.1. A direct upgrade is supported from Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC1, any version of TFS, including Team Foundation Server 2015 and newer.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022.1 RC2 now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Gateway API v1.0: GA Release]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/31/gateway-api-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/10/31/gateway-api-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Shane Utt (Kong), Nick Young (Isovalent), Rob Scott (Google)
On behalf of Kubernetes SIG Network, we are pleased to announce the v1.0 release of Gateway
API! This release marks a huge milestone for
this project. Several key APIs are graduating to GA (generally available), while
other significant features have been added to the Experimental channel.
What's new
Graduation to v1
This release includes the graduation of
Gateway,
GatewayClass, and
HTTPRoute to v1, which
means they are now generally available (GA). This API version denotes a high
level of confidence in the API surface and provides guarantees of backwards
compatibility. Note that although, the version of these APIs included in the
Standard channel are now considered stable, that does not mean that they are
complete. These…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Boards + GitHub Integration Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67897</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-boards-github-integration-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T16:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The existing Azure Boards + GitHub integration has been in place for several years now. This integration was a great starting point, but it does not offer the level of traceability that our customers have grown accustomed to. Based on your feedback,
The post Azure Boards + GitHub Integration Improvements appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>