<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-23T01:06:17.366Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-23T01:06:17.366Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resolving Process Incidents and Exceptions with Operate]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=90999</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/resolving-process-incidents-exceptions-operate/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that you can keep your process instances moving with Operate? Learn how in this tutorial.
The post Resolving Process Incidents and Exceptions with Operate appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Contributor Summit, Durham 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-contributor-summit-durham-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-contributor-summit-durham-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Ansible Contributor Summit in Durham, as well as how to register and propose topics for the event. This is a full day working session especially for community contributors to interact with one another, as well as with Ansible development teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Ansible Community Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.3 Early Access Program Is Now Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=389335</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/09/webstorm-2023-3-eap1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T09:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re ready to kick off WebStorm 2023.3 with a new Early Access Program (EAP). If you’re unfamiliar with how our EAPs work, check out this blog post where we explain what it is and the benefits of participating. If you haven’t already seen what to expect in WebStorm 2023.3, have a look at our roadmap. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 EAP Is Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=387992</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/09/intellij-idea-2023-3-eap/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T09:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Early Access Program for IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3 kicks off today, offering you a sneak peek of the exciting new features and improvements we expect to include in the next major release. If you’re not familiar with how the EAP works, please read this blog post for an introduction to the program and an explanation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CLion 2023.3 Early Access Program Is Open]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=389505</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/09/the-clion-2023-3-early-access-program-is-open/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T07:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently shared our preliminary plans for v2023.3, which we plan to release at the end of November. We are now happy to announce that the CLion 2023.3 Early Access Program (EAP) starts today! Our EAP lets the community participate in discussions devoted to our products and influence the development plans from early on. EAP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting to no]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47289</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/794313518/0/sethsblog~Getting-to-no/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T07:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Yes” is magical. It brings possibility and forward motion. But it’s almost impossible without “no” and no can be just as frightening. First, there’s the no of “I can’t go for that.” The no of refusing to race to the bottom, the no of avoiding the selfish hustle, the no of walking away from instincts […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paketo Buildpacks Bionic End Of Support]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/22/paketo-buildpacks-bionic-end-of-support</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/22/paketo-buildpacks-bionic-end-of-support"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Frederick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplified Event Externalization with Spring Modulith]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/22/simplified-event-externalization-with-spring-modulith</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/22/simplified-event-externalization-with-spring-modulith"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic launches new Verified Designation for Managed Service Provider partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-verified-designation-managed-service-provider-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-verified-designation-managed-service-provider-partners"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic invests in new partner programs designed to empower Managed Service Provider partners to sell, support, and embed Elastic solutions as part of your global portfolio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kosman,Isabelle Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your Elastic Cloud deployment with AWS PrivateLink traffic filter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-elastic-cloud-deployment-aws-privatelink-traffic-filter</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-elastic-cloud-deployment-aws-privatelink-traffic-filter"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your Elastic Cloud deployment using Elasticsearch AWS PrivateLink traffic filter. It improves security by establishing private connectivity between customer AWS VPC and customer Elastic Cloud deployments in the respective AWS region.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemendra Singh Lodhi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic launches new Verified Designation for Managed Service Provider partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-verified-designation-managed-service-provider-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-verified-designation-managed-service-provider-partners"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic® understands the need for quality, reliability, innovation, and support to foster strong relationships and partnerships. As such, Elastic is committed to investing in new partner programs designed to empower you to sell, support, and embed Elastic solutions as part of your global portfolio. 

As part of our evolving partner strategy, we are focusing on helping our Managed Service Provider (MSP) partners better represent and differentiate themselves to new and prospective end customers. As such, we have designed a number of new program benefits, which include: Guided Support, Enablement, Service co-creation workshops, and go-to-market support. 

In addition, Elastic is happy to announce a new special designation available to all of our MSPs: the Verified Managed Services Provider (MSP) designation. By capitalizing on exclusive benefits for our Verified MSP partners, you can further strengthen your partnership with Elastic, engage with your customers, and distinguish yourself in the market.
How to get started,
If you are interested in becoming a Verified MSP, simply sign up to be evaluated. To fill out the form, you need these three items:


Two Elastic certified engineers

One existing reference architecture or design document 

A list of your third-party vendors 


For more information on the benefits of becoming Elastic Verified, visit our MSP partners page.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kosman,Isabelle Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your Elastic Cloud deployment with AWS PrivateLink traffic filter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-elastic-cloud-deployment-aws-privatelink-traffic-filter</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-elastic-cloud-deployment-aws-privatelink-traffic-filter"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
One of the security features available in Elasticsearch® Service (Elastic® Cloud) is traffic filtering. Traffic filtering enables network layer security by limiting access to the deployment from configured networks only. In addition to the security policies consisting of role based access control (RBAC) employing principle of least privilege, using traffic filtering in conjunction provides greater security.

Elasticsearch Service (Elastic Cloud) supports CIDR (Classless Inter-Domain Routing) or IP address based traffic filtering in the form of 199.226.244.0/24 or 82.102.25.74. It also integrates traffic from major cloud providers: Amazon Web Services (AWS) VPC over AWS PrivateLink, Azure Virtual Network (VNets), and Google Cloud (GCP) Private Service Connect, for their respective cloud p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemendra Singh Lodhi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Urban Planning Opinion Progression]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2832/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2832/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/urban_planning_opinion_progression.png" title="If they're going to make people ride bikes and scooters in traffic, then it should at LEAST be legal to do the Snow Crash thing where you use a hook-shot-style harpoon to catch free rides from cars." alt="If they're going to make people ride bikes and scooters in traffic, then it should at LEAST be legal to do the Snow Crash thing where you use a hook-shot-style harpoon to catch free rides from cars." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distilling step-by-step: Outperforming larger language models with less training data and smaller model sizes]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/distilling-step-by-step-outperforming.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/distilling-step-by-step-outperforming.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cheng-Yu Hsieh, Student Researcher, and Chen-Yu Lee, Research Scientist, Cloud AI Team





Large language models (LLMs) have enabled a new data-efficient learning paradigm wherein they can be used to solve unseen new tasks via zero-shot or few-shot prompting. However, LLMs are challenging to deploy for real-world applications due to their sheer size. For instance, serving a single 175 billion LLM requires at least 350GB of GPU memory using specialized infrastructure, not to mention that today's state-of-the-art LLMs are composed of over 500 billion parameters. Such computational requirements are inaccessible for many research teams, especially for applications that require low latency performance.




To circumvent these deployment challenges, practitioners often choose to deplo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 6 Benefits of Event-Driven Business Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=90875</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/top-benefits-event-driven-business-process-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T21:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-streaming technology has many advantages. Learn how your business processes can benefit from using it for process orchestration.
The post Top 6 Benefits of Event-Driven Business Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Security Lab’s journey to disclosing 500 CVEs in open source projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-21-the-github-security-labs-journey-to-disclosing-500-cves-in-open-source-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-21-the-github-security-labs-journey-to-disclosing-500-cves-in-open-source-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T20:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The GitHub Security Lab audits open source projects for security vulnerabilities and helps maintainers fix them. Recently, we passed the milestone of 500 CVEs disclosed. Let’s take a trip down memory lane with a review of some noteworthy CVEs!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-21-the-github-security-labs-journey-to-disclosing-500-cves-in-open-source-projects/">The GitHub Security Lab’s journey to disclosing 500 CVEs in open source projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Security Issue Affecting TeamCity On-Premises – Update to 2023.05.4 Now]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=390094</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/09/critical-security-issue-affecting-teamcity-on-premises-update-to-2023-05-4-now/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T16:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Details A critical security issue was recently identified in TeamCity On-Premises. If abused, the flaw may enable an unauthenticated attacker with HTTP(S) access to a TeamCity server to perform a remote code execution (RCE) attack and gain administrative control of the TeamCity server.  All versions of TeamCity On-Premises are affected by this critical security […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys are generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-21-passkeys-are-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-21-passkeys-are-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T16:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>All GitHub.com users can now register a passkey to sign in without a password.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-21-passkeys-are-generally-available/">Passkeys are generally available</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet HashiCorp’s boomerang interns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/meet-hashicorp-s-boomerang-interns</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/meet-hashicorp-s-boomerang-interns"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hear from four Hashi-interns who have spent more than one summer with the company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the GitHub Innovation Graph]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-21-announcing-the-github-innovation-graph/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-21-announcing-the-github-innovation-graph/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T15:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore a universe of data about how the world is building software together on GitHub.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-21-announcing-the-github-innovation-graph/">Announcing the GitHub Innovation Graph</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eager, Lazy and Explicit Loading with Entity Framework Core]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=388891</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/09/21/eager-lazy-and-explicit-loading-with-entity-framework-core/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T13:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entity Framework Core (EF Core) supports a number of ways to load related data. There’s eager loading, lazy loading, and explicit loading. Each of these approaches have their own advantages and drawbacks. In this post, let’s have a quick look at each of these ways to load data for navigational properties! Eager loading Eager loading […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maarten Balliauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity Cloud 2023.09 Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=386538</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/09/teamcity-cloud-202309/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T13:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In TeamCity Cloud 2023.09, we’re introducing the ability to stream files from agents to the log while the build is still running. TeamCity users will also be able to add parameter-based execution conditions thanks to the new ability to report the statuses of preceding build steps. We’ve also enhanced a number of TeamCity integrations, including […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: CI/CD Pipelines for .NET With TeamCity, October 3, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=389060</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/09/teamcity-clearmeasure-webinar-oct3-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T12:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the annual StackOverflow Developer Survey, almost 73% of respondents identified .NET as their favorite framework. And it’s no wonder – .NET offers multi-language support and allows developers to build many different types of applications. TeamCity, a CI/CD tool developed by JetBrains, supports all programming languages, integrates with all popular technologies, and comes with the built-in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A protest or a project?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47248</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/794169395/0/sethsblog~A-protest-or-a-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T08:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protests let off steam. They organize people who might not show up by creating a moment in time where there’s enough opportunity and social pressure that they participate. A protest sends a message. But almost every time, the very things that made a protest appealing mean that it fails to change much. That’s because protests […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.1 M1 and 1.0.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-modulith-1-1-m1-and-1-0-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-modulith-1-1-m1-and-1-0-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Java community legend Sharat Chander]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/a-bootiful-podcast-java-community-legend-sharat-chander</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/a-bootiful-podcast-java-community-legend-sharat-chander"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.0-M3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-boot-3-2-0-m3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-boot-3-2-0-m3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.4 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-boot-3-1-4-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-boot-3-1-4-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.11 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-boot-3-0-11-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-boot-3-0-11-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.16 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-boot-2-7-16-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-boot-2-7-16-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.11.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-11-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/21/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-11-0-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bono</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.10.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-10-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-10-2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.10.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version especially if you use Cross-cluster search (CCS). We recommend 8.10.2 over the previous patch versions in 8.10.x.
The 8.10.2 patch release contains a fix for an issue with Cross-cluster search. After upgrading to 8.10.0/8.10.1, Kibana was incorrectly displaying a “Received partial response” error in various apps (e.g. Discover, Security) when the underlying Cross-cluster search (CCS) requests are returning partial results (i.e. with is_partial: true in their responses).
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maha Alsayasneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.10.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-10-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-10-2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maha Alsayasneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Add Your Swift Packages to AWS CodeArtifact]]></title>
        <id>416cc344dd4464df6f6cae5418f4a7665bdcd4a2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-add-your-swift-packages-to-aws-codeartifact/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T22:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, Swift developers who write code for Apple platforms (iOS, iPadOS, macOS, tvOS, watchOS, or visionOS) or for Swift applications running on the server side can use AWS CodeArtifact to securely store and retrieve their package dependencies. CodeArtifact integrates with standard developer tools such as Xcode, xcodebuild, and the Swift Package Manager (the swift […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is ACME PKI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-is-acme-pki</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-is-acme-pki"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the ACME protocol for PKI, the common problems it solves, and why it should be part of your certificate management roadmap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observing Camunda Environments with IBM Instana Business Monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=90552</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/observing-camunda-environments-ibm-instana-business-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T19:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Combining a process orchestration solution like Camunda with an observability solution like Instana can break down silos and help teams better understand their systems.
The post Observing Camunda Environments with IBM Instana Business Monitoring appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cross Ganaway</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MPS 2023.2 RC is out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=mps&amp;p=383457</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/mps/2023/09/mps-2023-2-rc-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T17:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re releasing the Release Candidate for MPS 2023.2. We have finished implementing all the major changes and features, and now we need your help. Please test it out properly on your projects and let us know if you encounter any bugs so we can be sure to fix them before the final release. DOWNLOAD […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaclav Pech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Chat beta now available for all individuals]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-20-github-copilot-chat-beta-now-available-for-all-individuals/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-20-github-copilot-chat-beta-now-available-for-all-individuals/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T17:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>All GitHub Copilot for Individuals users now have access to GitHub Copilot Chat beta, bringing natural language-powered coding to every developer in all languages.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-20-github-copilot-chat-beta-now-available-for-all-individuals/">GitHub Copilot Chat beta now available for all individuals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Learning Paths on Global Campus]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-20-introducing-learning-paths-on-global-campus/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-20-introducing-learning-paths-on-global-campus/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T16:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Guiding student developers through skill building foundations, a building block in their learning journey with GitHub Education.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-20-introducing-learning-paths-on-global-campus/">Introducing Learning Paths on Global Campus</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise adds new flexible deployment options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-new-flexible-deployment-options</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-new-flexible-deployment-options"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise now supports more flexible deployment options for self-hosted environments, including cloud-managed Kubernetes services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Generally Available: GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps is ready for you to use]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67480</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/now-generally-available-github-advanced-security-for-azure-devops-is-ready-for-you-to-use/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T15:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps is now generally available and is ready for you to use in your own Azure DevOps repos! You can now enable code, secret, and dependency scanning within Azure Repos and take advantage of the new product updates.
The post Now Generally Available: GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps is ready for you to use appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing general availability of GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-20-announcing-general-availability-of-github-advanced-security-for-azure-devops/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-20-announcing-general-availability-of-github-advanced-security-for-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T15:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps is now generally available. Enable secret scanning, dependency scanning, and code scanning on your organization directly in Azure DevOps configuration settings. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-20-announcing-general-availability-of-github-advanced-security-for-azure-devops/">Announcing general availability of GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第237話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755225457808</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755225457808"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor Process Instance Progress on a BPMN diagram via the Operate API]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=90560</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/monitor-process-instance-progress-bpmn-diagram-operate-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to provide the status of running and completed instances in your own custom UIs.
The post Monitor Process Instance Progress on a BPMN diagram via the Operate API appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm Public Roadmap: What’s Coming in 2023.3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=388808</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/09/phpstorm-public-roadmap-whats-coming-in-2023-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T12:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After recently releasing PhpStorm 2023.2, we’re now ready to share our plans for the next version of PhpStorm.   This is not the complete list of all improvements, but an overview of the most important ones. Your opinions matter, and we’d love to hear your feedback so we can shape PhpStorm into an even more powerful […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tania Goral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT for you]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47243</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/793990886/0/sethsblog~ChatGPT-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T07:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is a mystery. To many, it’s a threat. It turns out that understanding a mystery not only makes it feel less like a threat, it gives us the confidence to make it into something better. I use ChatGPT4 just about every day, and I’m often surprised at how frequently it surprises me, good and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration 6.2.0 Milestone 3 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/20/spring-integration-6-2-0-milestone-3-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/09/20/spring-integration-6-2-0-milestone-3-available"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Bilan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security stops memory and kernel attacks in Round 5 of MITRE Engenuity Evaluations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-stops-memory-kernel-attacks-round-5-mitre-engenuity-evaluations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-stops-memory-kernel-attacks-round-5-mitre-engenuity-evaluations"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security successfully defended against memory and kernel level attacks in the MITRE Engenuity ATT&CK 2023 Turla Enterprise Evaluations. Our deep visibility and machine learning capabilities were key to detecting and preventing the attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamarian Del Conte,James Spiteri,Paul Ewing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data compliance in public sector: Making data secure <i>and</i> accessible isn’t mutually exclusive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-compliance-public-sector-secure-accessible</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-compliance-public-sector-secure-accessible"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For UK public sector organisations, operating in accordance with ICO is essential in serving the public with integrity and finding the balance between data transparency and privacy. Learn more about how Elastic and our partner Aiimi can help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security stops memory and kernel attacks in Round 5 of MITRE Engenuity Evaluations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-stops-memory-kernel-attacks-round-5-mitre-engenuity-evaluations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-stops-memory-kernel-attacks-round-5-mitre-engenuity-evaluations"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
MITRE Engenuity is a nonprofit organization that provides adversarial threat intelligence and evaluation services to the security community. The ATT&CK framework is a comprehensive knowledge base of adversary tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs). The MITRE Engenuity Evaluations: Enterprise are a series of rigorous, adversarial evaluations that assess the effectiveness of security products against real-world threats.
This year, MITRE Engenuity focused on the Turla malware family — a Russian advanced persistent threat (APT) group that has been active since the early 2000s and has seen heightened activity since 2015. Turla is known for its use of sophisticated TTPs, including fileless malware, living-off-the-land attacks, and custom implants.
Elastic® participated in the MITRE Engenui…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamarian Del Conte,James Spiteri,Paul Ewing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data compliance in public sector: Making data secure <i>and</i> accessible isn’t mutually exclusive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-compliance-public-sector-secure-accessible</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-compliance-public-sector-secure-accessible"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In the UK, the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) has the responsibility of upholding information rights in the public interest. The ICO work with businesses and public sector organisations to offer guidance and best practices for using data and information responsibly, as well as regulating and enforcing relevant laws. 
For public sector organisations especially, operating in accordance with the ICO is essential in serving the public with integrity and finding the balance between data transparency and privacy.
In their strategic plan ICO25, the ICO lays out their objectives for the next three years: 

Empowering people to confidently share their information to use the products and services that drive our economy and our society

Empowering organisations to use information responsibly and confidently to invest and innovate

Empowering people to hold government to account, driving transparency that helps us all better trust in the decisions taken by public bodies

In a free and open society, these are important principles for governing public bodies and their interaction with citizens. Adhering to these objectives, however, can place significant and additional burden on already stretched public sector resources and at a time when data control and access is so high profile and fraught with risk. What’s more, the ICO also has powers to apply monetary penalties for organisations  — 54 such incidents are listed on the ICO website for 2023 as of this writing.So how can private sector technology companies like Elastic® and our partners help you align with the ICO’s goals?
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xkcd Phone Flip]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2831/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2831/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/xkcd_phone_flip.png" title="Theranos partnership: Sorry, we know, but we signed the contract back before all the stuff and the lawyers say we can't back out, so just try to keep your finger away from the bottom of the phone." alt="Theranos partnership: Sorry, we know, but we signed the contract back before all the stuff and the lawyers say we can't back out, so just try to keep your finger away from the bottom of the phone." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M2 Pro Mac Instances Built on Apple Silicon M2 Pro Mac Mini Computers]]></title>
        <id>44c35de4f6bf0c5b6f008dc79b434a3de65444cd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-m2-pro-mac-instances-built-on-apple-silicon-m2-pro-mac-mini-computers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T20:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the general availability of Amazon EC2 M2 Pro Mac instances. These instances deliver up to 35 percent faster performance over the existing M1 Mac instances when building and testing applications for Apple platforms. New EC2 M2 Pro Mac instances are powered by Apple M2 Pro Mac Mini computers featuring 12 core […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Azure DevOps Server 2022 Update 1 RC1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67633</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-azure-devops-server-2022-update-1-rc1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T19:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re very excited to announce the first release candidate (RC1) of Azure DevOps Server 2022.1!
Last Accessed column on Delivery Plans page
There are many more features with this release,
The post Introducing Azure DevOps Server 2022 Update 1 RC1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – NVMe Reservations for Amazon Elastic Block Store io2 Volumes]]></title>
        <id>8a8dbf5c7083cca1519f0502d44702094c90f6a1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-nvme-reservations-for-amazon-elastic-block-store-io2-volumes/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T18:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) io2 and io2 Block Express volumes now support storage fencing using NVMe reservations. As I learned while writing this post, storage fencing is used to regulate access to storage for a compute or database cluster, ensuring that just one host in the cluster has permission to write to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the removal of bundled plugins in HashiCorp Packer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-removal-of-bundled-plugins-in-hashicorp-packer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-removal-of-bundled-plugins-in-hashicorp-packer"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the final step in moving towards external plugins, HashiCorp Packer will stop bundling official plugins within its binary releases. Here’s what that means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud now supports assigning agent pools at the organization level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-now-supports-assigning-agent-pools-at-the-organization-level</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-now-supports-assigning-agent-pools-at-the-organization-level"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assigning agents at the organization level provides a faster, more consistent, and scalable approach to agent pool configuration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.2.2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=388477</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/09/phpstorm-2023-2-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T13:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.2.2 is released and includes a host of bug fixes and quality-of-life improvements.  You can update by using the Toolbox App or from right inside the IDE. You can also download PhpStorm 2023.2.2 from our website. The full list of changes in PhpStorm 2023.2.2 is available in the release notes. You can download PhpStorm 2023.2.2 here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tania Goral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convenience and scams]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47240</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/793873340/0/sethsblog~Convenience-and-scams/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T08:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The scam era is upon us. Aided by AI, borderless currency and the internet of things, there are more people than ever before making a living hustling to steal, impersonate, defraud and otherwise violate our trust. When the world was inconvenient, this was difficult. The banker met with you in person, so did the charitable […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native OpenTelemetry support in Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/native-opentelemetry-support-in-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/native-opentelemetry-support-in-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic offers native support for OpenTelemetry by allowing for direct ingest of OpenTelemetry traces, metrics, and logs without conversion, and applying any Elastic feature against OTel data without degradation in capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transforming observability with AI Assistant, OTel standardization, continuous profiling, and enhanced log analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/transforming-observability-ai-assistant-otel-standardization-continuous-profiling-log-analytics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/transforming-observability-ai-assistant-otel-standardization-continuous-profiling-log-analytics"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability delivers interactive AI-powered insights with AI Assistant, provides a solution standardized on OpenTelemetry, expands to include profiling, and enhances log analytics, breaking down silos and accelerating problem resolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Context-aware insights using the Elastic AI Assistant for Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/context-aware-insights-elastic-ai-assistant-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/context-aware-insights-elastic-ai-assistant-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harness the power of generative AI to turn insights into actions. Powered by the Elasticsearch Relevance Engine™, Elastic’s AI Assistant transforms problem identification with an interactive assistant that delivers context-aware remediation for SREs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The power of effective log management in software development and operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-management-observability-operations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-management-observability-operations"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improve your development and operations processes with effective log management strategies. Our blog offers insights into the importance of log management, best practices, and tools for managing logs efficiently. From identifying errors to troubleshooting issues, learn how to leverage log management for enhanced performance and streamlined operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Wintergerst,David Hope,Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native OpenTelemetry support in Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/native-opentelemetry-support-in-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/native-opentelemetry-support-in-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
OpenTelemetry is more than just becoming the open ingestion standard for observability. As one of the major Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) projects, with as many commits as Kubernetes, it is gaining support from major ISVs and cloud providers delivering support for the framework. Many global companies from finance, insurance, tech, and other industries are starting to standardize on OpenTelemetry. With OpenTelemetry, DevOps teams have a consistent approach to collecting and ingesting telemetry data providing a de-facto standard for observability. 

Elastic® is strategically standardizing on OpenTelemetry for the main data collection architecture for observability and security. Additionally, Elastic is making a commitment to help OpenTelemetry become the best de facto data colle…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transforming observability with AI Assistant, OTel standardization, continuous profiling, and enhanced log analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/transforming-observability-ai-assistant-otel-standardization-continuous-profiling-log-analytics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/transforming-observability-ai-assistant-otel-standardization-continuous-profiling-log-analytics"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
A more modern era of observability is being ushered in with the emergence of AI and generative AI. As these AI technologies go mainstream, expect observability to advance from a manual, reactive process to a more proactive AI-driven approach with auto-diagnosis of issues followed by remediation.

Long gone are the days of monolithic applications running in data centers, where software updates were infrequent events. Operations teams relied on server, network, and storage tools to monitor their tech silos, manually analyzed data, and used an on-call conference bridge with others to identify, triage, and resolve issues. With the advent of cloud along with its complexity, abstraction of infrastructure, and faster development cycles, operations and SRE teams needed observability to help addr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Context-aware insights using the Elastic AI Assistant for Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/context-aware-insights-elastic-ai-assistant-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/context-aware-insights-elastic-ai-assistant-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic® is extending the Elastic AI Assistant — the open, generative AI Assistant powered by the Elasticsearch Relevance Engine™ (ESRE) — to enhance observability analysis and enable users of every skill level. Elastic’s AI Assistant (in technical preview for Observability) transforms problem identification and resolution and eliminates manual data chasing across silos with an interactive assistant that delivers context-aware information for SREs. 

The Elastic AI Assistant enhances the understanding of application errors, log message interpretation, alert analysis, and suggestions for optimal code efficiency. Additionally, Elastic AI Assistant’s interactive chat interface allows SREs to chat and visualize all relevant telemetry cohesively in one place, while also leveraging proprietary…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The power of effective log management in software development and operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-management-observability-operations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-management-observability-operations"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The rapid software development process that exists today requires an expanding and complex infrastructure and application components, and the job of operations and development teams is ever growing and multifaceted. Observability, which helps manage and analyze telemetry data, is the key to ensuring the performance and reliability of your applications and infrastructure. In particular, logs are the main default signal developers enable, providing a significant amount of detail for debugging, performance analysis, security, and compliance management. So how do you define a strategy to get the most out of your logs?

In this blog post, we'll explore:

The logging journey, which reviews the collection, processing and enrichment, and analysis and rationalization of logs
The difference betwee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Wintergerst,David Hope,Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: C7i Instances, Knowledge Base for Amazon Bedrock, and More (Sept. 18, 2023)]]></title>
        <id>d1bcf2bd9f720f4423af24b67cf619a2cbec257c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-c7i-instances-knowledge-base-for-amazon-bedrock-and-more-sept-18-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While daylight is getting shorter in the Northern hemisphere, we’ve got two new EC2 instance types optimized for compute and memory and many new capabilities for other services. Last week there was also the EMEA AWS Heroes Summit in Munich, an amazing day full of insights and passion. Here’s a nice picture of the participants! […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching from Bitbucket Server and Bamboo to GitHub just got easier]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-18-switching-from-bitbucket-server-and-bamboo-to-github-just-got-easier/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-18-switching-from-bitbucket-server-and-bamboo-to-github-just-got-easier/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T16:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Starting today, GitHub Enterprise Importer supports repository migrations from Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center, and GitHub Actions Importer offers CI/CD migrations from Bitbucket and Bamboo.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-18-switching-from-bitbucket-server-and-bamboo-to-github-just-got-easier/">Switching from Bitbucket Server and Bamboo to GitHub just got easier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a multi-cloud golden image pipeline with Terraform Cloud and HCP Packer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multicloud-golden-image-pipeline-terraform-cloud-hcp-packer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multicloud-golden-image-pipeline-terraform-cloud-hcp-packer"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how creating a golden image pipeline can help unify and streamline your imaging and provisioning workflows throughout your infrastructure estate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RustRover bug-fix update 2023.2 EAP 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rust&amp;p=388366</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rust/2023/09/18/rustrover-bug-fix-update-2023-2-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T15:53:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RustRover bug-fix update 2023.2 EAP 2 is now available! The fixes included in this bug-fix update are listed below. Download build 232.9921.62 from our website, through the Toolbox App. Further updates of standalone installation will be available from inside an IDE as well. This update’s main highlights include: You can read the full release […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatiana Parshutkina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2023.05.4 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=388319</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/09/teamcity-2023-05-4-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T15:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just shy of a month since our August bug-fix update, we’re rolling out the 2023.05.4 update for TeamCity On-Premises. This version features a minor enhancement that allows you to modify the format of timestamps in TeamCity build logs, security issue fixes, and a few quite significant performance updates. Please refer to our release notes for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitrii Korovin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just looking]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47237</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/793783739/0/sethsblog~Just-looking/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T08:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lots of people go to the beach but very few get in the water. 3,000 students go to the football game to watch 20 of their peers play. And we go to a conference to meet people and connect, and then spend most of our time hoping someone else will see us and care enough […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.10.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-10-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-10-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.10.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.10.1 over the previous patch versions in 8.10.x.
This release contains fixes for security issues. Please see our security announcements for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maha Alsayasneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.10.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-10-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-10-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maha Alsayasneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Haunted House]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2830/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2830/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/haunted_house.png" title="You can leave at any time through the door over there. It's a Louisville door, so you'll need to find a compatible knob. No, don't be silly, that one is a Lexington knob! Of course it won't fit." alt="You can leave at any time through the door over there. It's a Louisville door, so you'll need to find a compatible knob. No, don't be silly, that one is a Lexington knob! Of course it won't fit." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It goes without saying]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47222</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/793722857/0/sethsblog~It-goes-without-saying/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A phrase that’s been showing up recently is, “no pressure.” It usually comes in a pitch letter of some sort, written by someone who isn’t in a position to exert any pressure. So why say it? It’s a bit like, “while supplies last.” And “to be honest…” which is perhaps the most self-negating of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been doing it wrong all along]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47146</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/793657475/0/sethsblog~Ive-been-doing-it-wrong-all-along/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is one of the great benefits of learning. It’s also a common challenge. When we get better at something, it is preceded by a moment of incompetence. In that moment, we’re not exactly sure how to do it better, but we realize that the way we’d been doing it wasn’t nearly as useful. It […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MediaPipe FaceStylizer: On-device real-time few-shot face stylization]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/mediapipe-facestylizer-on-device-real.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/mediapipe-facestylizer-on-device-real.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T17:39:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Haolin Jia, Software Engineer, and Qifei Wang, Senior Software Engineer, Core ML



In recent years, we have witnessed rising interest across consumers and researchers in integrated augmented reality (AR) experiences using real-time face feature generation and editing functions in mobile applications, including short videos, virtual reality, and gaming. As a result, there is a growing demand for lightweight, yet high-quality face generation and editing models, which are often based on generative adversarial network (GAN) techniques. However, the majority of GAN models suffer from high computational complexity and the need for a large training dataset. In addition, it is also important to employ GAN models responsibly. 



In this post, we introduce MediaPipe FaceStylizer, an effi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating AI adoption on Azure with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerating-ai-adoption-on-azure-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/accelerating-ai-adoption-on-azure-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use Terraform to scale the adoption of artificial intelligence in a Microsoft Azure environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tricked (again)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46987</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/793561514/0/sethsblog~Tricked-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T08:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you knew then what you know now, would you have made the same decision? In the last fifty years, more than 25,000,000 Americans have died prematurely due to cigarette smoking. Worldwide, it’s significantly higher. That’s fifty times as many U.S. citizens as died in World War II. How did cigarette marketers manage to keep […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iceberg Efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2829/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2829/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/iceberg_efficiency.png" title="Our experimental aerogel iceberg with helium pockets manages true 100% efficiency, barely touching the water, and it can even lift off of the surface and fly to more efficiently pursue fleeing hubristic liners." alt="Our experimental aerogel iceberg with helium pockets manages true 100% efficiency, barely touching the water, and it can even lift off of the surface and fly to more efficiently pursue fleeing hubristic liners." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-device content distillation with graph neural networks]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/on-device-content-distillation-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/on-device-content-distillation-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:39:00.035Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Gabriel Barcik and Duc-Hieu Tran, Research Engineers, Google Research




In today's digital age, smartphones and desktop web browsers serve as the primary tools for accessing news and information. However, the proliferation of website clutter — encompassing complex layouts, navigation elements, and extraneous links — significantly impairs both the reading experience and article navigation. This issue is particularly acute for individuals with accessibility requirements.



To improve the user experience and make reading more accessible, Android and Chrome users may leverage the Reading Mode feature, which enhances accessibility by processing webpages to allow customizable contrast, adjustable text size, more legible fonts, and to enable text-to-speech utilities. Additionally, An…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing auto-triage rules for Dependabot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-14-introducing-auto-triage-rules-for-dependabot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-14-introducing-auto-triage-rules-for-dependabot/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Make quick work of alerts with preset and custom rules.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-14-introducing-auto-triage-rules-for-dependabot/">Introducing auto-triage rules for Dependabot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding the others]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=47199</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/793437320/0/sethsblog~Finding-the-others/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider purple.space a new community for professionals to connect without hustle. Peer-to-peer support, brainstorming, community workshops, coaching, dailies and more. Distributed work doesn’t have to be disconnected work. Freelancing, creating, and leading can feel solitary, even lonely, but they don’t need to be. And most of all, we can get better. Better together. Our best […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a Camunda Champion?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89980</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/are-you-a-camunda-champion/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T19:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to become a Camunda Champion? Join our community and get some great benefits.
The post Are you a Camunda Champion? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Alcantara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: August 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-13-github-availability-report-august-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-13-github-availability-report-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T19:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In August, we experienced two incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-13-github-availability-report-august-2023/">GitHub Availability Report: August 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apply now for GitHub Universe 2023 micro-mentoring]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-09-13-apply-now-for-github-universe-2023-micro-mentoring/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-09-13-apply-now-for-github-universe-2023-micro-mentoring/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T16:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As part of our ongoing commitment to accelerate human progress through Social Impact initiatives, we’re offering students 30-minute, 1:1 micro-mentoring sessions with GitHub employees ahead of Universe.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog/2023-09-13-apply-now-for-github-universe-2023-micro-mentoring/">Apply now for GitHub Universe 2023 micro-mentoring</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp extends security use cases with new Vault integrations including Oracle, Veeam, and Venafi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-extends-security-use-cases-with-new-vault-integrations-including-oracle</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-extends-security-use-cases-with-new-vault-integrations-including-oracle"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New HashiCorp Vault ecosystem integrations extend security use cases for customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview – Connect Foundation Models to Your Company Data Sources with Agents for Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>1364088e6dfe688a2aef712ce4bd05603087a126</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/preview-connect-foundation-models-to-your-company-data-sources-with-agents-for-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T14:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July, we announced the preview of agents for Amazon Bedrock, a new capability for developers to create generative AI applications that complete tasks. Today, I’m happy to introduce a new capability to securely connect foundation models (FMs) to your company data sources using agents. With a knowledge base, you can use agents to give […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The MVP and fear]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45502</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/793307705/0/sethsblog~The-MVP-and-fear/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T08:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The minimum viable product is a powerful way to find out if your solution is going to find a market. Bean-to-bar chocolate in the US didn’t happen because someone raised millions of dollars, built a factory and got shelf space at the A&P. It happened because John Scharffenberger made a small batch of chocolate by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: User Namespaces: Now Supports Running Stateful Pods in Alpha!]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/13/userns-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/13/userns-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Rodrigo Campos Catelin (Microsoft), Giuseppe Scrivano (Red Hat), Sascha Grunert (Red Hat)
Kubernetes v1.25 introduced support for user namespaces for only stateless
pods. Kubernetes 1.28 lifted that restriction, after some design changes were
done in 1.27.
The beauty of this feature is that:
it is trivial to adopt (you just need to set a bool in the pod spec)
doesn't need any changes for most applications
improves security by drastically enhancing the isolation of containers and
mitigating CVEs rated HIGH and CRITICAL.
This post explains the basics of user namespaces and also shows:
the changes that arrived in the recent Kubernetes v1.28 release
a demo of a vulnerability rated as HIGH that is not exploitable with user namespaces
the runtime requirements to use this feature
what yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World scale inverse reinforcement learning in Google Maps]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/world-scale-inverse-reinforcement.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/world-scale-inverse-reinforcement.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T21:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Matt Barnes, Software Engineer, Google Research




Routing in Google Maps remains one of our most helpful and frequently used features. Determining the best route from A to B requires making complex trade-offs between factors including the estimated time of arrival (ETA), tolls, directness, surface conditions (e.g., paved, unpaved roads), and user preferences, which vary across transportation mode and local geography. Often, the most natural visibility we have into travelers' preferences is by analyzing real-world travel patterns.



Learning preferences from observed sequential decision making behavior is a classic application of inverse reinforcement learning (IRL). Given a Markov decision process (MDP) — a formalization of the road network — and a set of demonstration traject…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[September patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67525</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/september-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T19:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.0.1
Team Foundation Server 2018.3.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 Patch 3
Note: If you have Azure DevOps Server 2022,
The post September patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Alpha Release September 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89947</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/camunda-alpha-release-september-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T16:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to announce the August 2023 alpha release of Camunda. Check out what's new.
The post Camunda Alpha Release September 2023 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Comparing Local Kubernetes Development Tools: Telepresence, Gefyra, and mirrord]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/12/local-k8s-development-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/09/12/local-k8s-development-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Eyal Bukchin (MetalBear)
The Kubernetes development cycle is an evolving landscape with a myriad of tools seeking to streamline the process. Each tool has its unique approach, and the choice often comes down to individual project requirements, the team's expertise, and the preferred workflow.
Among the various solutions, a category we dubbed “Local K8S Development tools” has emerged, which seeks to enhance the Kubernetes development experience by connecting locally running components to the Kubernetes cluster. This facilitates rapid testing of new code in cloud conditions, circumventing the traditional cycle of Dockerization, CI, and deployment.
In this post, we compare three solutions in this category: Telepresence, Gefyra, and our own contender, mirrord.
Telepresence
The oldest a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 R7a Instances Powered By 4th Gen AMD EPYC Processors for Memory Optimized Workloads]]></title>
        <id>64de4acd73459b1274a4808233a3fb07d4637598</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-r7a-instances-powered-by-4th-gen-amd-epyc-processors-for-memory-optimized-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T23:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched the memory optimized Amazon EC2 R6a instances in July 2022 powered by 3rd Gen AMD EPYC (Milan) processors, running at frequencies up to 3.6 GHz. Many customers who run workloads that are dependent on x86 instructions, such as SAP, are looking for ways to optimize their cloud utilization. They’re taking advantage of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: R7iz Instances, Amazon Connect, CloudWatch Logs, and Lots More (Sept. 11, 2023)]]></title>
        <id>e1de18a127682dd7c4d5fdc0b14ca2c6dd79e1b2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-r7iz-instances-amazon-connect-cloudwatch-logs-and-lots-more-sept-11-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T18:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like it is my turn once again to write the AWS Weekly Roundup. I wrote and published the first one on April 16, 2012 — just 4,165 short day ago! Last Week’s Launches Here are some of the launches that caught my eye last week: R7iz Instances – Optimized for high CPU performance and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp enters Gartner PAM MQ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-enters-gartner-pam-mq</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-enters-gartner-pam-mq"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Vault and Boundary, HashiCorp makes its debut in Gartner’s Magic Quadrant for privileged access management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the new Ansible Community Forum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/welcome-to-the-new-ansible-community-forum</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/welcome-to-the-new-ansible-community-forum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we're delighted to announce the launch of the new Ansible Community Forum - a single starting point for questions and help, development discussions, events, and much more. Everyone is invited, whether you are an Ansible user, contributor or developer, we are all community! Register here to join us!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Ansible Community Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public preview of Workload identity federation for Azure Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67467</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/public-preview-of-workload-identity-federation-for-azure-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T08:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to stop storing secrets and certificates in Azure service connections? Are you tired rotating these secrets whenever they expire? We are now announcing a public preview of workload identity federation for Azure service connections. Workload identity federation uses an industry-standard technology,
The post Public preview of Workload identity federation for Azure Pipelines appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differentially private median and more]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/differentially-private-median-and-more.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/differentially-private-median-and-more.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T22:59:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Edith Cohen and Uri Stemmer, Research Scientists, Google Research





Differential privacy (DP) is a rigorous mathematical definition of privacy. DP algorithms are randomized to protect user data by ensuring that the probability of any particular output is nearly unchanged when a data point is added or removed. Therefore, the output of a DP algorithm does not disclose the presence of any one data point. There has been significant progress in both foundational research and adoption of differential privacy with contributions such as the Privacy Sandbox and Google Open Source Library.


ML and data analytics algorithms can often be described as performing multiple basic computation steps on the same dataset. When each such step is differentially private, so is the output, but with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New version of ServiceNow Terraform Catalog enables resource updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-of-servicenow-terraform-catalog-enables-resource-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-of-servicenow-terraform-catalog-enables-resource-updates"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ServiceNow Service Catalog for Terraform now lets you update existing Terraform workspaces and reprovision resources with new variables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A novel computational fluid dynamics framework for turbulent flow research]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/a-novel-computational-fluid-dynamics.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/a-novel-computational-fluid-dynamics.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shantanu Shahane, Software Engineer, and Matthias Ihme, Research Scientist, Athena Team




Turbulence is ubiquitous in environmental and engineering fluid flows, and is encountered routinely in everyday life. A better understanding of these turbulent processes could provide valuable insights across a variety of research areas — improving the prediction of cloud formation by atmospheric transport and the spreading of wildfires by turbulent energy exchange, understanding sedimentation of deposits in rivers, and improving the efficiency of combustion in aircraft engines to reduce emissions, to name a few. However, despite its importance, our current understanding and our ability to reliably predict such flows remains limited. This is mainly attributed to the highly chaotic nature a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon EC2 R7iz Instances are Optimized for High CPU Performance, Memory-Intensive Workloads]]></title>
        <id>8ba74cddc223f444061c3b940056b7e5bf430c07</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-r7iz-instances-memory-optimized-for-high-cpu-performance-memory-intensive-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re announcing general availability of the Amazon EC2 R7iz instances. R7iz instances are the fastest 4th Generation Intel Xeon Scalable-based (Sapphire Rapids) instances in the cloud with 3.9 GHz sustained all-core turbo frequency. R7iz instances are suitable for workloads where there’s a requirement for more memory to process additional data, larger sizes of instances […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2 of the Packer Azure plugin is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/version-2-packer-azure-plugin-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/version-2-packer-azure-plugin-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Packer Azure plugin has migrated to the HashiCorp Go Azure SDK to address known Azure SDK deprecations and provide a consistent foundation for managing Azure infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TSMixer: An all-MLP architecture for time series forecasting]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/09/tsmixer-all-mlp-architecture-for-time.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/09/tsmixer-all-mlp-architecture-for-time.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:47:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Si-An Chen, Student Researcher, Cloud AI Team, and Chun-Liang Li, Research Scientist, Cloud AI Team



  
Update — 2023/09/12: This post has been updated as the work described is now published in Transactions on Machine Learning Research. 
Time series forecasting is critical to various real-world applications, from demand forecasting to pandemic spread prediction. In multivariate time series forecasting (forecasting multiple variants at the same time), one can split existing methods into two categories: univariate models and multivariate models. Univariate models focus on inter-series interactions or temporal patterns that encompass trends and seasonal patterns on a time series with a single variable. Examples of such trends and seasonal patterns might be the way mortgage rates i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The newest AWS Heroes are here – September 2023]]></title>
        <id>191318f95fbfcb42c00d05fc4648b0a473270294</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/the-newest-aws-heroes-are-here-september-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each quarter, the AWS Heroes program recognizes technical enthusiasts who lift up the greater AWS community through various approaches. While these inspirational individuals are driven to knowledge share, they sometimes discover novel and fun ways of using technology, such as leveraging LEDs to create a magical display of holiday lights. Many are also contributing heavily […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第236話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755178180638</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755178180638"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate OpenShift with Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automate-openshift-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automate-openshift-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy an application to OpenShift and configure it with Ansible Automation Platform using the Red Hat Certified Collection for OpenShift.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachna Dodia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS End User Computing Innovation Day 2023:  Architecting End User Computing for Change and Agility]]></title>
        <id>bbcc0023eaa53f35fd89db9349acde25fa3f6254</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-end-user-computing-innovation-day-2023-architecting-end-user-computing-for-change-and-agility/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on Wednesday, September 13, for a free-to-attend online event, AWS End User Computing Innovation Day 2023. AWS will stream the event simultaneously across multiple platforms, including LinkedIn Live, Twitter, YouTube, and Twitch. Adapting to a complex landscape shaped by return-to-oﬃce mandates, pressure to migrate out of self-operated data centers, escalating security concerns, scarcity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vercel Shipped Cron Jobs in 2 Months Using Amazon EventBridge Scheduler]]></title>
        <id>b17a63568d9769bf55a6e0e7bf657f0b4f373478</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-vercel-shipped-cron-jobs-in-2-months-using-amazon-eventbridge-scheduler/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vercel implemented Cron Jobs using Amazon EventBridge Scheduler, enabling their customers to create, manage, and run scheduled tasks at scale. The adoption of this feature was rapid, reaching over 7 million weekly cron invocations within a few months of release. This article shows how they did it and how they handle the massive scale they’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is REST API in Java? Guide with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89827</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/what-is-rest-api-in-java-guide-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the basics, learn the specifics, and get hands-on with examples of using REST API in Java. 
The post What is REST API in Java? Guide with Examples appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Doglio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Farewell EC2-Classic, EBS at 15 Years, and More (Sept. 4, 2023)]]></title>
        <id>1a569d832e6d0012825fad5a9dbc82223bec7711</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-farewell-ec2-classic-ebs-at-15-years-and-more-sept-4-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, there was some great reading about Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) and Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) written by AWS tech leaders. Dr. Werner Vogels wrote Farewell EC2-Classic, it’s been swell, celebrating the 17 years of loyal duty of the original version that started what we now know as cloud computing. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join us at CamundaCon 2023 for Everything Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89745</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/09/join-us-camundacon-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2023 is right around the corner. Check out everything there is to see and learn at the leading process orchestration conference.
The post Join us at CamundaCon 2023 for Everything Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-Driven Ansible - ChatOps - From Chat to Action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-chatops-from-chat-to-action</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-ansible-chatops-from-chat-to-action"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implement Automated ChatOps: Learn how to use event-driven automation to take action from chat information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Legacy Package Repositories Will Be Frozen On September 13, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/31/legacy-package-repository-deprecation/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/31/legacy-package-repository-deprecation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Bob Killen (Google), Chris Short (AWS), Jeremy Rickard (Microsoft), Marko Mudrinić (Kubermatic), Tim Bannister (The Scale Factory)
On August 15, 2023, the Kubernetes project announced the general availability of
the community-owned package repositories for Debian and RPM packages available
at pkgs.k8s.io. The new package repositories are replacement for the legacy
Google-hosted package repositories: apt.kubernetes.io and yum.kubernetes.io.
The
announcement blog post for pkgs.k8s.io
highlighted that we will stop publishing packages to the legacy repositories in
the future.
Today, we're formally deprecating the legacy package repositories (apt.kubernetes.io
and yum.kubernetes.io), and we're announcing our plans to freeze the contents of
the repositories as of September 13, 2023.
Ple…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WeatherBench 2: A benchmark for the next generation of data-driven weather models]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/weatherbench-2-benchmark-for-next.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/weatherbench-2-benchmark-for-next.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T17:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Stephan Rasp, Research Scientist, and Carla Bromberg, Program Lead, Google Research





In 1950, weather forecasting started its digital revolution when researchers used the first programmable, general-purpose computer ENIAC to solve mathematical equations describing how weather evolves. In the more than 70 years since, continuous advancements in computing power and improvements to the model formulations have led to steady gains in weather forecast skill: a 7-day forecast today is about as accurate as a 5-day forecast in 2000 and a 3-day forecast in 1980. While improving forecast accuracy at the pace of approximately one day per decade may not seem like a big deal, every day improved is important in far reaching use cases, such as for logistics planning, disaster management, agr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modeling and improving text stability in live captions]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/modeling-and-improving-text-stability.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/modeling-and-improving-text-stability.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T19:34:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Vikas Bahirwani, Research Scientist, and Susan Xu, Software Engineer, Google Augmented Reality





Automatic speech recognition (ASR) technology has made conversations more accessible with live captions in remote conferencing software, mobile applications, and head-worn displays. However, to maintain real-time responsiveness, live caption systems often display interim predictions that are updated as new utterances are received. This can cause text instability (a “flicker” where previously displayed text is updated, shown in the captions on the left in the video below), which can impair users' reading experience due to distraction, fatigue, and difficulty following the conversation.






In “Modeling and Improving Text Stability in Live Captions”, presented at ACM CHI 2023, we f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon Managed Service for Apache Flink Renamed from Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics]]></title>
        <id>e40c4472300bd8097a0fe160c607a0e9eeb6e5d5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-managed-service-for-apache-flink-renamed-from-amazon-kinesis-data-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T17:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the rename of Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics to Amazon Managed Service for Apache Flink, a fully managed and serverless service for you to build and run real-time streaming applications using Apache Flink. We continue to deliver the same experience in your Flink applications without any impact on ongoing operations, developments, or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Azure Infrastructure for High Availability Web Hosting with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-azure-infrastructure-for-high-availability-web-hosting-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-azure-infrastructure-for-high-availability-web-hosting-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it a hassle to set up the infrastructure for a new website every time you need to run a short-term project, such as a marketing campaign or just for testing? Do you spend too much on resources that are only used for a short period? Look no further, because automation is here to save the day!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Leiva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Configuration Service Mesh with On-Demand Cluster Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ac6483b52a51</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/zero-configuration-service-mesh-with-on-demand-cluster-discovery-ac6483b52a51?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T23:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix’s service mesh adoption: history, motivations, and how we worked with the Envoy community on a feature to streamline mesh adoption]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SayTap: Language to quadrupedal locomotion]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/saytap-language-to-quadrupedal.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/saytap-language-to-quadrupedal.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T19:57:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yujin Tang and Wenhao Yu, Research Scientists, Google




Simple and effective interaction between human and quadrupedal robots paves the way towards creating intelligent and capable helper robots, forging a future where technology enhances our lives in ways beyond our imagination. Key to such human-robot interaction systems is enabling quadrupedal robots to respond to natural language instructions. Recent developments in large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated the potential to perform high-level planning. Yet, it remains a challenge for LLMs to comprehend low-level commands, such as joint angle targets or motor torques, especially for inherently unstable legged robots, necessitating high-frequency control signals. Consequently, most existing work presumes the provision of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Gateway API v0.8.0: Introducing Service Mesh Support]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/29/gateway-api-v0-8/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/29/gateway-api-v0-8/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Flynn (Buoyant), John Howard (Google), Keith Mattix (Microsoft), Michael Beaumont (Kong), Mike Morris (independent), Rob Scott (Google)
We are thrilled to announce the v0.8.0 release of Gateway API! With this
release, Gateway API support for service mesh has reached Experimental
status. We look forward to your feedback!
We're especially delighted to announce that Kuma 2.3+, Linkerd 2.14+, and Istio
1.16+ are all fully-conformant implementations of Gateway API service mesh
support.
Service mesh support in Gateway API
While the initial focus of Gateway API was always ingress (north-south)
traffic, it was clear almost from the beginning that the same basic routing
concepts should also be applicable to service mesh (east-west) traffic. In
2022, the Gateway API subproject started the G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – AWS Dedicated Local Zones, Events and More – August 28, 2023]]></title>
        <id>b149aa31ec92d6b50f0246dd76f4b269e108440e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-dedicated-zones-events-and-more-august-28-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T21:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I will meet our customers and partners at the AWS Summit Mexico. If you are around, please come say hi at the community lounge and at the F1 Game Day where I will spend most of my time. I would love to discuss your developer experience on AWS and listen to your stories […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RO-ViT: Region-aware pre-training for open-vocabulary object detection with vision transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/ro-vit-region-aware-pre-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/ro-vit-region-aware-pre-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:59:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dahun Kim and Weicheng Kuo, Research Scientists, Google



The ability to detect objects in the visual world is crucial for computer vision and machine intelligence, enabling applications like adaptive autonomous agents and versatile shopping systems. However, modern object detectors are limited by the manual annotations of their training data, resulting in a vocabulary size significantly smaller than the vast array of objects encountered in reality. To overcome this, the open-vocabulary detection task (OVD) has emerged, utilizing image-text pairs for training and incorporating new category names at test time by associating them with the image content. By treating categories as text embeddings, open-vocabulary detectors can predict a wide range of unseen objects. Various techniqu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: A New (alpha) Mechanism For Safer Cluster Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/28/kubernetes-1-28-feature-mixed-version-proxy-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/28/kubernetes-1-28-feature-mixed-version-proxy-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Richa Banker (Google)
This blog describes the mixed version proxy, a new alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.28. The
mixed version proxy enables an HTTP request for a resource to be served by the correct API server
in cases where there are multiple API servers at varied versions in a cluster. For example,
this is useful during a cluster upgrade, or when you're rolling out the runtime configuration of
the cluster's control plane.
What problem does this solve?
When a cluster undergoes an upgrade, the kube-apiservers existing at different versions in that scenario can serve different sets (groups, versions, resources) of built-in resources. A resource request made in this scenario may be served by any of the available apiservers, potentially resulting in the request ending up at an apiserve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Community Podcast Recap: Inbound and Outbound Connectors: “Woah, it’s so easy!”]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=89567</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/08/camunda-community-podcast-recap-inbound-outbound-connectors-so-easy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T20:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missed the latest episode of the Camunda Community Podcast? Catch up with a quick recap.
The post Camunda Community Podcast Recap: Inbound and Outbound Connectors: “Woah, it’s so easy!” appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Perception Fairness]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T17:38:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Susanna Ricco and Utsav Prabhu, co-leads, Perception Fairness Team, Google Research





Google’s Responsible AI research is built on a foundation of collaboration — between teams with diverse backgrounds and expertise, between researchers and product developers, and ultimately with the community at large. The Perception Fairness team drives progress by combining deep subject-matter expertise in both computer vision and machine learning (ML) fairness with direct connections to the researchers building the perception systems that power products across Google and beyond. Together, we are working to intentionally design our systems to be inclusive from the ground up, guided by Google’s AI Principles.






Perception Fairness research spans the design, development, and deployment of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.28: Introducing native sidecar containers]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/25/native-sidecar-containers/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/25/native-sidecar-containers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Todd Neal (AWS), Matthias Bertschy (ARMO), Sergey Kanzhelev (Google), Gunju Kim (NAVER), Shannon Kularathna (Google)
This post explains how to use the new sidecar feature, which enables restartable init containers and is available in alpha in Kubernetes 1.28. We want your feedback so that we can graduate this feature as soon as possible.
The concept of a “sidecar” has been part of Kubernetes since nearly the very beginning. In 2015, sidecars were described in a blog post about composite containers as additional containers that “extend and enhance the ‘main’ container”. Sidecar containers have become a common Kubernetes deployment pattern and are often used for network proxies or as part of a logging system. Until now, sidecars were a concept that Kubernetes users applied without n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to compare a noisy quantum processor to a classical computer]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/how-to-compare-noisy-quantum-processor.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/how-to-compare-noisy-quantum-processor.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T22:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sergio Boixo and Vadim Smelyanskiy, Principal Scientists, Google Quantum AI Team




A full-scale error-corrected quantum computer will be able to solve some problems that are impossible for classical computers, but building such a device is a huge endeavor. We are proud of the milestones that we have achieved toward a fully error-corrected quantum computer, but that large-scale computer is still some number of years away. Meanwhile, we are using our current noisy quantum processors as flexible platforms for quantum experiments. 



In contrast to an error-corrected quantum computer, experiments in noisy quantum processors are currently limited to a few thousand quantum operations or gates, before noise degrades the quantum state. In 2019 we implemented a specific computational t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching language models to reason algorithmically]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2023/08/teaching-language-models-to-reason.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2023/08/teaching-language-models-to-reason.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T19:33:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hattie Zhou, Graduate Student at MILA, Hanie Sedghi, Research Scientist, Google




Large language models (LLMs), such as GPT-3 and PaLM, have shown impressive progress in recent years, which have been driven by scaling up models and training data sizes. Nonetheless, a long standing debate has been whether LLMs can reason symbolically (i.e., manipulating symbols based on logical rules). For example, LLMs are able to perform simple arithmetic operations when numbers are small, but struggle to perform with large numbers. This suggests that LLMs have not learned the underlying rules needed to perform these arithmetic operations. 



While neural networks have powerful pattern matching capabilities, they are prone to overfitting to spurious statistical patterns in the data. This does…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.28: Beta support for using swap on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/24/swap-linux-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/08/24/swap-linux-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Itamar Holder (Red Hat)
The 1.22 release introduced Alpha support
for configuring swap memory usage for Kubernetes workloads running on Linux on a per-node basis.
Now, in release 1.28, support for swap on Linux nodes has graduated to Beta, along with many
new improvements.
Prior to version 1.22, Kubernetes did not provide support for swap memory on Linux systems.
This was due to the inherent difficulty in guaranteeing and accounting for pod memory utilization
when swap memory was involved. As a result, swap support was deemed out of scope in the initial
design of Kubernetes, and the default behavior of a kubelet was to fail to start if swap memory
was detected on a node.
In version 1.22, the swap feature for Linux was initially introduced in its Alpha stage. This represented
a sign…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>