<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-18T01:19:53.876Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-18T01:19:53.876Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Having fun with seccomp profiles on the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/18/seccomp-profiles-edge/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/18/seccomp-profiles-edge/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
The Security Profiles Operator (SPO) is a feature-rich
operator for Kubernetes to make managing seccomp, SELinux and
AppArmor profiles easier than ever. Recording those profiles from scratch is one
of the key features of this operator, which usually involves the integration
into large CI/CD systems. Being able to test the recording capabilities of the
operator in edge cases is one of the recent development efforts of the SPO and
makes it excitingly easy to play around with seccomp profiles.
Recording seccomp profiles with spoc record
The v0.8.0 release of the Security Profiles Operator shipped a new
command line interface called spoc, a little helper tool for recording and
replaying seccomp profiles among various other things that are out of scope of
this blog post.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retiring the AWS Documentation on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>b7080422d9b11a447cfc260dc7cce95c30bddad8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/retiring-the-aws-documentation-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T23:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About five years ago I announced that AWS Documentation is Now Open Source and on GitHub. After a prolonged period of experimentation we will archive most of the repos starting the week of June 5th, and will devote all of our resources to directly improving the AWS documentation and website. The primary source for most […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside GitHub: Working with the LLMs behind GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-17-inside-github-working-with-the-llms-behind-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-17-inside-github-working-with-the-llms-behind-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T17:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers behind GitHub Copilot discuss what it was like to work with OpenAI’s large language model and how it informed the development of Copilot as we know it today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub Copilot is getting better at understanding your code]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-17-how-github-copilot-is-getting-better-at-understanding-your-code/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-17-how-github-copilot-is-getting-better-at-understanding-your-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T17:32:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a new Fill-in-the-Middle paradigm, GitHub engineers improved the way GitHub Copilot contextualizes your code. By continuing to develop and test advanced retrieval algorithms, they’re working on making our AI tool even more advanced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design&#8217;s journey towards accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-17-designs-journey-towards-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-17-designs-journey-towards-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design can have a significant impact on delivering accessible experiences to our users. It takes a cultural shift, dedicated experts, and permission to make progress over perfection in order to build momentum. We’ve got a long way to go, but we’re starting to see a real shift in our journey to make GitHub a true home for all developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with the Elastic Stack and Docker-Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-with-the-elastic-stack-and-docker-compose</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-with-the-elastic-stack-and-docker-compose"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part one of this two-part series, we’ll dive into configuring the components of a standard Elastic Stack consisting of Elasticsearch, Logstash, Kibana, and Beats (ELK-B), on which we can immediately begin developing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eddie Mitchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with the Elastic Stack and Docker-Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-with-the-elastic-stack-and-docker-compose</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-with-the-elastic-stack-and-docker-compose"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As the Elastic Stack has grown over the years and the feature sets have increased, so has the complexity of getting started or attempting a proof-of-concept (POC) locally. And while Elastic Cloud is still the fastest and easiest way to get started with Elastic, the need for local development and testing is still widely abundant. As developers, we are drawn to quick setups and rapid development with low-effort results. Nothing screams fast setup and POC quite like Docker — which is what we’ll be focusing on to get started with an entire Elastic Stack build-out for your local enjoyment. 

In part one of this two-part series, we’ll dive into configuring the components of a standard Elastic Stack consisting of Elasticsearch, Logstash, Kibana, and Beats (ELK-B), on which we can immediately be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eddie Mitchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Draft to Perfection: Creating Effective Forms for Human Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=81100&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=81100</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/draft-to-perfection-effective-forms-human-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With our Form Editor you can draft, refine, and validate forms with ease. Learn how to design forms to perfectly fit your business needs.
The post From Draft to Perfection: Creating Effective Forms for Human Workflows appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Konrad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the sun is shining]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44442</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/741291896/0/sethsblog~When-the-sun-is-shining/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T08:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our job as professionals is to show up and do the work. Not simply respond to incoming or do the chores, but to create and innovate. And yet, some days feel more conducive than others. There are moments when it simply flows. When the surf’s up, cancel everything else. Don’t waste it. Postpone the dentist, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.2 available now!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/17/spring-batch-5-0-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/17/spring-batch-5-0-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmoud Ben Hassine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 1.1.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/17/spring-authorization-server-1-1-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/17/spring-authorization-server-1-1-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Grandja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.2.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/17/spring-for-graphql-1-2-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/17/spring-for-graphql-1-2-0-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourages you to come as you are: Meet the Accessibles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-accessibles</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-accessibles"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Accessibles work to raise awareness and create community at Elastic for those that are differently abled. Learn more about the group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenges of observing Kubernetes: Understanding a complex and dynamic system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-kubernetes-observability-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-kubernetes-observability-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes can be an important part of your cloud deployment, but the same capabilities that make it resilient and robust can pose challenges when something does go wrong. Let’s take a dive into what IT operations teams often face when managing Kubernetes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel Luna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourages you to come as you are: Meet the Accessibles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-accessibles</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-accessibles"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Our employee resource groups, or as we like to call them, Elastician resource groups, have been an informal part of Elastic’s culture since 2016. While each group started as a Slack channel for any Elastician to join, we formally recognized these groups in 2021.

That allowed us to ensure that the members would have structure, budget, and ultimately, a voice based on any dimension of diversity, allyship, and advocacy. This formalization was an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion journey.

Each ERGs is aligned to a shared identity, interest, affinity, or allyship. We want to create a community of people with something in common and to encourage sharing, learning, and networking among members. While each group has their own goals and vision, they are all working t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenges of observing Kubernetes: Understanding a complex and dynamic system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-kubernetes-observability-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitoring-kubernetes-observability-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As technology evolves in the enterprise, oftentimes the processes and tools used to manage it must also evolve. The increased adoption of Kubernetes has become a major inflection point for those of us in the monitoring and management side of the IT operations world. What has worked for decades (traditional infrastructure monitoring) has to be adjusted to the complexity and ephemeral nature of modern distributed systems where Kubernetes has a prime role.

In my first blog, The basics of observing Kubernetes: A bird-watcher’s perspective, we provided an overview of Kubernetes components and the signals you have to pay attention to. But let’s dig in deeper because the strategies of traditional monitoring need to really be adjusted in the world of cloud computing.
https://static-www.elastic.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel Luna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noise Filter]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2777/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2777/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/noise_filter.png" title="Party Mode also enables the feature, but reverses the slider." alt="Party Mode also enables the feature, but reverses the slider." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using reinforcement learning for dynamic planning in open-ended conversations]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/using-reinforcement-learning-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/using-reinforcement-learning-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T19:22:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Deborah Cohen, Staff Research Scientist, and Craig Boutilier, Principal Scientist, Google Research




As virtual assistants become ubiquitous, users increasingly interact with them to learn about new topics or obtain recommendations and expect them to deliver capabilities beyond narrow dialogues of one or two turns. Dynamic planning, namely the capability to look ahead and replan based on the flow of the conversation, is an essential ingredient for the making of engaging conversations with the deeper, open-ended interactions that users expect.
 

While large language models (LLMs) are now beating state-of-the-art approaches in many natural language processing benchmarks, they are typically trained to output the next best response, rather than planning ahead, which is required fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing GitHub’s recent availability issues]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-16-addressing-githubs-recent-availability-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-16-addressing-githubs-recent-availability-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T18:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub recently experienced several availability incidents, both long running and shorter duration. We have since mitigated these incidents and all systems are now operating normally. Read on for more details about what caused these incidents and what we’re doing to mitigate in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1.2 is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=355597</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/05/intellij-idea-2023-1-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T18:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new bug-fix update – IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1.2 – has arrived! You can get the latest version from inside the IDE, via the Toolbox App, or by using snaps for Ubuntu. It is also possible to download it from our website. Here are the most notable fixes included in this version: For more details, please […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud updates plans with an enhanced Free tier and more flexibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-updates-plans-with-an-enhanced-free-tier-and-more-flexibility</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-updates-plans-with-an-enhanced-free-tier-and-more-flexibility"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud’s Free tier now offers new features — including SSO, policy as code, and cloud agents — while new paid offerings update scaling concurrency and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2023.2 EAP 1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=351503</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2023/05/2023-2-eap-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T16:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Early Access Program (EAP) for DataSpell 2023.2 is now open! The EAP gives you access to pre-release versions of DataSpell, allowing you to evaluate new features, test issues that have been resolved, and provide feedback. EAP builds are free and don’t require a license. All you need is a JetBrains Account. You can learn […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanislav Garkusha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.1.3 Bug-Fix Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=355663</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/05/clion-2023-1-3-bug-fix-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.2 is planned as a quality-focused release and the free Early Access Program is now available! You can download free builds and try them out. Don’t forget to share your feedback with us! In the meantime, we’re continuing to improve v2023.1 with the CLion 2023.1.3 bug-fix update! Download build 231.9011.31 from our website, through […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Achieves ISO 26262 ASIL D level of Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66945</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-achieves-iso-26262-asil-d-level-of-certification/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T15:27:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce that Azure DevOps has successfully passed the ISO 26262 ASIL D certification, the highest level of Functional Safety management process, by TÜV SUD, an international independent third-party testing and certification company. This certification demonstrates Microsoft’s commitment to providing our Automotive customers with the highest level of quality and safety in their software development projects.
The post Azure DevOps Achieves ISO 26262 ASIL D level of Certification appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jorge Minana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Polaris, a New In-IDE Code Search Tool for Plugin Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=344904</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2023/05/introducing-polaris-a-new-in-ide-code-search-tool-for-plugin-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T14:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many resources available to developers extending the IntelliJ Platform, including the IntelliJ Platform SDK documentation, a dedicated Slack community where you can ask fellow developers for advice, and external forums and Q&A platforms.  To discover how others have implemented features using specific extension points, you can browse IntelliJ Platform Explorer and then navigate […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Dart and Flutter Package Repositories in Space]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=355269</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2023/05/16/dart-and-flutter-package-repositories-in-space/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T13:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you worried about the security of your code? No longer want to rely on external sources for your Dart packages? JetBrains Space offers a complete solution for private Dart package storage. Using it, you can securely store and manage your code and package dependencies, and let your team quickly access and share packages within […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgenia Verbina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OS in Go? Why Not?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=351813</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2023/05/16/os-in-go-why-not/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T13:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was written by an external contributor. Operating systems are the heart and soul of a computer system. The operating system manages the computer’s hardware as well as software resources and provides the user with a means to interact with the computer. Traditionally, languages like C and Assembly have been used to write operating […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Receives SOC 2 Type 2 Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=81201&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=81201</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/camunda-soc-2-type-2-certification/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're thrilled to announce that Camunda has achieved SOC 2 Type 2 certification for Camunda Platform 8.
The post Camunda Receives SOC 2 Type 2 Certification appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Grund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ideas shared are exponential]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46005</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/740884874/0/sethsblog~Ideas-shared-are-exponential/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If everyone visits a factory and takes a sample, it goes out of business. But if everyone in the community takes an idea, that idea goes up in value. The best marketing advice I have for someone writing a book is simple: Write a book that people want to share with others. And then make […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.1.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/16/spring-for-graphql-1-1-4-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/16/spring-for-graphql-1-1-4-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 16th 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/16/this-week-in-spring-may-16th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/16/this-week-in-spring-may-16th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Elasticsearch to prompt ChatGPT with natural language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-prompt-chatgpt-natural-language</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-prompt-chatgpt-natural-language"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post presents an experimental project for querying Elasticsearch in natural language using ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enrico Zimuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing 5G: A new era of challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5g-networks-challenges-elastic-wilab</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5g-networks-challenges-elastic-wilab"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the vast amount of data needed to monitor 5G networks, the need for robust, flexible, and scalable solutions to manage and analyze data has become crucial. Wilab and Elastic provide an ideal solution to address these challenges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jürgen Obermann,Piotr Kobziakowski,Tomas Achaval-Palacio,Martin Ferreyra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The impact of NWDAF on telco service providers: Embracing vendor agnostic data analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/nwdaf-telco-vendor-agnostic-data-analytics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/nwdaf-telco-vendor-agnostic-data-analytics"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By combining the power of NWDAF with vendor agnostic data analytics, network operators can obtain a comprehensive and unbiased view of their network performance, empowering them to make better decisions and improve user experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jürgen Obermann,Piotr Kobziakowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trace your Azure Function application with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/trace-azure-function-application-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/trace-azure-function-application-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless applications deployed on Azure Functions are growing in usage. This blog shows how to deploy a serverless application on Azure functions with Elastic Agent and use Elastic's APM capability to manage and troubleshoot issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trent Mick,Bahubali Shetti,Hemant Malik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Elasticsearch to prompt ChatGPT with natural language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-prompt-chatgpt-natural-language</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-prompt-chatgpt-natural-language"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
These days everyone is talking about ChatGPT. One of the cool features of this large language model (LLM) is the ability to generate code. We used it to generate Elasticsearch DSL queries. The goal is to search in Elasticsearch® with sentences like “Give me the first 10 documents of 2017 from the stocks index.” This experiment showed that it is possible, with some limitations. In this post, we describe this experiment and the open source library that we published for this use case.
date,open,high,low,close,volume,name
2013-02-08,15.07,15.12,14.63,14.75,8407500,AAL
2013-02-11,14.89,15.01,14.26,14.46,8882000,AAL
2013-02-12,14.45,14.51,14.1,14.27,8126000,AAL
2013-02-13,14.3,14.94,14.25,14.66,10259500,AAL,
Each line contains the date of the stock, the open value of the day, the high and the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enrico Zimuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing 5G: A new era of challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5g-networks-challenges-elastic-wilab</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5g-networks-challenges-elastic-wilab"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The arrival of 5G networks represents a significant breakthrough in wireless technology, marking a shift toward virtualized, software-based solutions, and cloud-based architecture. However, with this transition comes several challenges that demand a change in mindset from traditional network management and deployment practices.
Operators are shifting from physical infrastructure to virtualized infrastructure and moving from centralized to distributed network architectures. As a result, they must navigate the complexities of new use cases and emerging technologies, such as edge computing and network slicing, to create innovative services that can take advantage of the enhanced network capabilities of 5G networks and ensure a profitable return on their investment.
These challenges are emph…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jürgen Obermann,Piotr Kobziakowski,Tomas Achaval-Palacio,Martin Ferreyra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The impact of NWDAF on telco service providers: Embracing vendor agnostic data analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/nwdaf-telco-vendor-agnostic-data-analytics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/nwdaf-telco-vendor-agnostic-data-analytics"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Network Data Analytics Function (NWDAF) is a key component in 5G networks, designed to collect, analyze, and deliver valuable insights to service providers. NWDAF provides an unbiased, vendor-vendor agnostic view of the network, expanding telco visibility beyond traditional use cases.

As network complexities grow, service providers require unbiased and accurate data to make informed decisions, driving the demand for vendor agnostic data analytics. The data provided by NWDAF is one of the richest sources of this information.

Data-driven decision-making enables service providers to optimize network performance, improve customer experience, and stay ahead in a competitive market. NWDAF enhances new commercial offerings possibilities, opening doors to innovative services and products for c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jürgen Obermann,Piotr Kobziakowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trace your Azure Function application with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/trace-azure-function-application-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/trace-azure-function-application-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Adoption of Azure Functions in cloud-native applications on Microsoft Azure has been increasing exponentially over the last few years. Serverless functions, such as the Azure Functions, provide a high level of abstraction from the underlying infrastructure and orchestration, given these tasks are managed by the cloud provider. Software development teams can then focus on the implementation of business and application logic. Some additional benefits include billing for serverless functions based on the actual compute and memory resources consumed, along with automatic on-demand scaling. 

While the benefits of using serverless functions are manifold, it is also necessary to make them observable in the wider end-to-end microservices architecture context.
,The key components of the solution…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trent Mick,Bahubali Shetti,Hemant Malik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: KMS V2 Moves to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/16/kms-v2-moves-to-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/16/kms-v2-moves-to-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Anish Ramasekar, Mo Khan, and Rita Zhang (Microsoft)
With Kubernetes 1.27, we (SIG Auth) are moving Key Management Service (KMS) v2 API to beta.
What is KMS?
One of the first things to consider when securing a Kubernetes cluster is encrypting etcd data at
rest. KMS provides an interface for a provider to utilize a key stored in an external key service to
perform this encryption.
KMS v1 has been a feature of Kubernetes since version 1.10, and is currently in beta as of version
v1.12. KMS v2 was introduced as alpha in v1.25.
Note
the previous blog post
was written and it is not compatible with the design in this blog post. Attempting to upgrade from
old versions with the alpha feature enabled will result in data loss.

What’s new in v2beta1?
The KMS encryption provider uses an envel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Larger language models do in-context learning differently]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/larger-language-models-do-in-context.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/larger-language-models-do-in-context.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T20:59:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jerry Wei, Student Researcher, and Denny Zhou, Principal Scientist, Google Research




There have recently been tremendous advances in language models, partly because they can perform tasks with strong performance via in-context learning (ICL), a process whereby models are prompted with a few examples of input-label pairs before performing the task on an unseen evaluation example. In general, models’ success at in-context learning is enabled by:
 


Their use of semantic prior knowledge from pre-training to predict labels while following the format of in-context examples (e.g., seeing examples of movie reviews with “positive sentiment” and “negative sentiment” as labels and performing sentiment analysis using prior knowledge).


Learning the input-label mappings in context from …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Livestream: Virtual Threads and Structured Concurrency in Java 2021 With Loom]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=355135</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/05/new-livestream-virtual-threads-and-structured-concurrency-in-java-2021-with-loom/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T20:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for the IntelliJ IDEA livestream with José Paumard to learn about how to work with virtual threads. Date:  Thursday, May 25, 2023 Time: 4:00 pm – 5:00 pm UTC Session abstract Loom brought 2 preview features in Java 19: virtual threads and structured concurrency. Virtual threads are a new model of thread that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zlata Kalyuzhnaya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review –  New Open-Source Updates for Snapchange, Cedar, and Jupyter Community Contributions – May 15, 2023]]></title>
        <id>e8903c7f01bbcc4d30acec4eca295aa082db9119</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-new-open-source-updates-for-snapchange-cedar-and-jupyter-community-contributions-may-15-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T20:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new week has begun. Last week, there was a lot of news related to AWS. I have compiled a few announcements you need to know. Let’s get started right away! Last Week’s Launches Let’s take a look at some launches from the last week that I want to remind you of: New Amazon EC2 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Early Access Program for PyCharm 2023.2 Is Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=354831</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/05/2023-2-eap-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T19:53:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Early Access Program starts today! This program offers you an early glimpse of the new features and improvements expected to land in the next version. If you’re not yet familiar with the EAP concept, check out this blog post for more details. Over the next few weeks, join us in exploring the newest additions […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Global 2023 scholarship program open for applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-scholarship-program-open-for-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-scholarship-program-open-for-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now is your chance to apply for a scholarship to attend the HashiConf Global conference in San Francisco, Oct. 10-12.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consensus and subjectivity of skin tone annotation for ML fairness]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/consensus-and-subjectivity-of-skin-tone_15.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/consensus-and-subjectivity-of-skin-tone_15.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T17:16:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Candice Schumann, Software Engineer, and Gbolahan O. Olanubi, User Experience Researcher, Google Research




Skin tone is an observable characteristic that is subjective, perceived differently by individuals (e.g., depending on their location or culture) and thus is complicated to annotate. That said, the ability to reliably and accurately annotate skin tone is highly important in computer vision. This became apparent in 2018, when the Gender Shades study highlighted that computer vision systems struggled to detect people with darker skin tones, and performed particularly poorly for women with darker skin tones. The study highlights the importance for computer researchers and practitioners to evaluate their technologies across the full range of skin tones and at intersections of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New version of ServiceNow Terraform Catalog enhances workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-of-servicenow-terraform-catalog-enhances-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-of-servicenow-terraform-catalog-enhances-workflows"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ServiceNow Service Catalog integration for Terraform now allows you to select the execution mode for your Terraform workspaces — along with other enhancements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ Starts the 2023.2 Early Access Program]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rscpp&amp;p=354770</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rscpp/2023/05/15/resharper-cpp-2023-2-eap-safe-delete/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ReSharper C++ 2023.2 Early Access Program starts today! Give the free EAP builds a try and let us know what you think about the changes and improvements they introduce. You can download the EAP builds from our website or via the Toolbox App. DOWNLOAD RESHARPER C++ EAP Safe Delete refactoring ReSharper C++ introduces the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elvira Mustafina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.2 EAP Starts Now!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=354408</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/05/clion-2023-2-eap-starts-now/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently shared our plans for the quality-focused CLion 2023.2 release in this roadmap blog post. We plan to refine many of the recently introduced features like vcpkg integration, Disassemble on Demand, and the Clangd-based experimental indexer. We’ll also continue improving Memory View, bringing more to CMake code insight, and reworking the PlatformIO integration. Good […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2023.2 Early Access Program Is Now Open]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=354065</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/05/15/rider-2023-2-eap1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, We hope that you checked out the roadmap blog post we published last week and you’re just as excited about Rider 2023.2 as we are. If so, you’re in luck! The first installment of Rider’s Early Access Program just went live, and you can try out some of the new features. There are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2023.2 Kicks Off the Early Access Program!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=354037</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/05/15/resharper-2023-2-eap1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can download the ReSharper 2023.2 EAP build 1 from www.jetbrains.com or via the JetBrains Toolbox App. Now, let’s take a look at what the first EAP build has in store. C# inspections for #nullable directives and NRT annotations We’re kicking off the new cycle of C# language support development with the introduction of two […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about Network Automation at Red Hat Summit and AnsibleFest 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-network-automation-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-network-automation-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may have heard, AnsibleFest will be taking place at Red Hat Summit in Boston May 23-25. This change will allow you to harness everything that Red Hat technology has to offer in a single place and will give you even more tools to address your automation needs. Join Ansible and automation-focused audiences to hear from Red Hat and Ansible leaders, customers, and partners while getting the latest on the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform product roadmap, community projects, and what’s coming in IT automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The missing post]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44438</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/740752454/0/sethsblog~The-missing-post/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had a great idea for a post, my best blogging of the year, in fact. I worked it all out when I was driving, but when I arrived, it was gone. Vanished. So I went searching for it, trying out dozens of possible ideas. I never found it. But I did find five other […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.1 is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/15/spring-security-6-1-is-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/15/spring-security-6-1-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Riesenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security Kerberos 2.0.0-RC1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/15/spring-security-kerberos-2-0-0-rc1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/15/spring-security-kerberos-2-0-0-rc1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring LDAP 3.1.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/15/spring-ldap-3-1-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/15/spring-ldap-3-1-0-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Cummings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT and Elasticsearch: A plugin to use ChatGPT with your Elastic data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatgpt-elasticsearch-plugin-elastic-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatgpt-elasticsearch-plugin-elastic-data"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to implement a plugin and enable ChatGPT users to extend ChatGPT with any content indexed in Elasticsearch, using the Elastic documentation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baha Azarmi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT and Elasticsearch: A plugin to use ChatGPT with your Elastic data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatgpt-elasticsearch-plugin-elastic-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatgpt-elasticsearch-plugin-elastic-data"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
You may have read this previous blog post about our journey to connect Elasticsearch’s relevance capabilities with OpenAI question-answering capabilities. The key idea in that post was to illustrate how to use Elastic with OpenAI’s GPT model to build a response and return context-relevant content to users.

The application that we built can expose a search endpoint and be called by any front-end service. The good news is that now OpenAI has released a private alpha of the future ChatGPT plugin framework.

In this blog, you will learn how to implement the plugin and extend the use of ChatGPT to any content indexed in Elasticsearch, using the Elastic documentation.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt6f09e155996c7545/64626a36d4a792ec443dd113/blog-elastic-summariz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baha Azarmi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crystal Ball]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2776/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2776/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/crystal_ball.png" title="They often use ball lenses to collect light at the ends of optical fibers, so when you look stuff up on the internet you're actually scrying through a crystal ball." alt="They often use ball lenses to collect light at the ends of optical fibers, so when you look stuff up on the internet you're actually scrying through a crystal ball." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: updates on speeding up Pod startup]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/15/speed-up-pod-startup/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/15/speed-up-pod-startup/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Paco Xu (DaoCloud), Sergey Kanzhelev (Google), Ruiwen Zhao (Google)
How can Pod start-up be accelerated on nodes in large clusters? This is a common issue that
cluster administrators may face.
This blog post focuses on methods to speed up pod start-up from the kubelet side. It does not
involve the creation time of pods by controller-manager through kube-apiserver, nor does it
include scheduling time for pods or webhooks executed on it.
We have mentioned some important factors here to consider from the kubelet's perspective, but
this is not an exhaustive list. As Kubernetes v1.27 is released, this blog highlights
significant changes in v1.27 that aid in speeding up pod start-up.
Parallel container image pulls
Pulling images always takes some time and what's worse is that image pull…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The good china]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44436</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/740619170/0/sethsblog~The-good-china/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-14T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once you use your plates every day, they cease to be the good china. Of course, the plates didn’t change. Your story did. The way you treat them did. The same goes for the red carpet. If you roll it out for every visitor or every customer, it ceases to be red.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chores]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44434</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/740405933/0/sethsblog~Chores/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T08:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They’re essential. The house begins to stink if we don’t take out the garbage. But at work, while they might be essential, they may not be important. At least, not important enough for us to spend a lot of focus on. Chores are: The bills have to get paid. But they might not have to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F-VLM: Open-vocabulary object detection upon frozen vision and language models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/f-vlm-open-vocabulary-object-detection.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/f-vlm-open-vocabulary-object-detection.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Weicheng Kuo and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research






Detection is a fundamental vision task that aims to localize and recognize objects in an image. However, the data collection process of manually annotating bounding boxes or instance masks is tedious and costly, which limits the modern detection vocabulary size to roughly 1,000 object classes. This is orders of magnitude smaller than the vocabulary people use to describe the visual world and leaves out many categories. Recent vision and language models (VLMs), such as CLIP, have demonstrated improved open-vocabulary visual recognition capabilities through learning from Internet-scale image-text pairs. These VLMs are applied to zero-shot classification using frozen model weights without the need for fine-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facilitating Human Workflow Orchestration with Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=81113&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=81113</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/human-workflow-orchestration-generative-ai-openai/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T19:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering how to use generative AI for human workflows? Learn how generative AI tools like ChatGPT can be used to make human-centric processes easier.
The post Facilitating Human Workflow Orchestration with Generative AI appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Modernize Your Applications at AWS Serverless Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>ee829d9b822332b77c6c37976dab86517e596799</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/learn-how-to-modernize-your-applications-at-aws-serverless-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T18:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on Wednesday, May 17, for AWS Serverless Innovation Day, a free full-day virtual event. You will learn about AWS Serverless technologies and event-driven architectures from customers, experts, and leaders. AWS Serverless Innovation Day is an event to empower builders and technical decision-makers with different AWS Serverless technologies, including AWS Lambda, Amazon Elastic Container […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This month on The ReadME Podcast: Balancing openness and control]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-12-this-month-on-the-readme-podcast-balancing-openness-and-control/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-12-this-month-on-the-readme-podcast-balancing-openness-and-control/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T18:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open vs. control: the paradox of open source. We take a look at the expectations of open source, how the definition has evolved, and when ‘closed to contributions’ is the right move. Tune in to the latest episode of The ReadME Podcast for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling conversational interaction on mobile with LLMs]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/enabling-conversational-interaction-on.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/enabling-conversational-interaction-on.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:03:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bryan Wang, Student Researcher, and Yang Li, Research Scientist, Google Research





Intelligent assistants on mobile devices have significantly advanced language-based interactions for performing simple daily tasks, such as setting a timer or turning on a flashlight. Despite the progress, these assistants still face limitations in supporting conversational interactions in mobile user interfaces (UIs), where many user tasks are performed. For example, they cannot answer a user's question about specific information displayed on a screen. An agent would need to have a computational understanding of graphical user interfaces (GUIs) to achieve such capabilities. 



Prior research has investigated several important technical building blocks to enable conversational interaction with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I used GitHub Copilot to build a browser extension]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-12-how-i-used-github-copilot-to-build-a-browser-extension/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-12-how-i-used-github-copilot-to-build-a-browser-extension/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how, in seven steps, I built my first browser extension with GitHub Copilot—and my three major takeaways about learning and pair programming in the age of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s a “techie”?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44425</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/740208491/0/sethsblog~Whats-a-techie/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T08:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend’s email said, “I know many of my readers aren’t techies and you’re thinking of putting this newsletter aside…” We should get clear about what we’re talking about when we say “techie.” I’m going to argue that involves a combination of two things: But someone who says, “I’m not a techie” might actually be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2023.0 goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/12/spring-data-2023-0-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/12/spring-data-2023-0-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data Service Release 2022.0.6 & 2021.2.12 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/12/spring-data-service-release-2022-0-6-and-2021-2-12-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/12/spring-data-service-release-2022-0-6-and-2021-2-12-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christoph Strobl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 tips to excel in technical support from Elastic's Julie Baxter-Rudd]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-4-tips-excel-in-technical-support-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-4-tips-excel-in-technical-support-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic's Vice President of Global Customer Support, Julie Baxter-Rudd, got her start in technical support over two decades ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 tips to excel in technical support from Elastic's Julie Baxter-Rudd]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-4-tips-excel-in-technical-support-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-4-tips-excel-in-technical-support-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic’s Vice President of Global Customer Support, Julie Baxter-Rudd, got her start in technical support over two decades ago.

“I was super lucky to find support early on,” she says with a smile. “It is a people business, from the customers we serve to the teams that help deliver the service. I love people, in all their glorious forms.”

It's the people that led Julie to Elastic, and her face lights up when she starts talking about her team. “Running a global support organization and supporting a global customer base exposes me to so much culture, diversity, and variety of experience. It would be hard to find this in another role,” she says.

You could say that Julie is right where she needs to be, and her wealth of experience in technical support has given her valuable insights on ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Siphon]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2775/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2775/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/siphon.png" title="ADDITIONAL NOTES: Fixed a bug that caused some rocks to generate virtually infinite heat while just sitting there." alt="ADDITIONAL NOTES: Fixed a bug that caused some rocks to generate virtually infinite heat while just sitting there." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: In-place Resource Resize for Kubernetes Pods (alpha)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/12/in-place-pod-resize-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/12/in-place-pod-resize-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Vinay Kulkarni (Kubescaler Labs)
If you have deployed Kubernetes pods with CPU and/or memory resources
specified, you may have noticed that changing the resource values involves
restarting the pod. This has been a disruptive operation for running
workloads... until now.
In Kubernetes v1.27, we have added a new alpha feature that allows users
to resize CPU/memory resources allocated to pods without restarting the
containers. To facilitate this, the resources field in a pod's containers
now allow mutation for cpu and memory resources. They can be changed
simply by patching the running pod spec.
This also means that resources field in the pod spec can no longer be
relied upon as an indicator of the pod's actual resources. Monitoring tools
and other such applications must now look at n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigation and search improvements for accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-11-navigation-and-search-improvements-for-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-11-navigation-and-search-improvements-for-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T20:20:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the accessibility features within our new navigation and code search which make it easier to use for many more people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon Aurora I/O-Optimized Cluster Configuration with Up to 40% Cost Savings for I/O-Intensive Applications]]></title>
        <id>5ec1a9f67d502ffa32d8252cb12b71e213171571</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-aurora-i-o-optimized-cluster-configuration-with-up-to-40-cost-savings-for-i-o-intensive-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T20:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Amazon Aurora launched in 2014, hundreds of thousands of customers have chosen Aurora to run their most demanding applications. Aurora provides unparalleled high performance and availability at global scale with full MySQL and PostgreSQL compatibility at up to one-tenth the cost of commercial databases. Many customers benefit from the cost-effectiveness of Aurora’s current simple, pay-per-request […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking inclusive design: how Primer&#8217;s color system is making GitHub.com more inclusive]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-11-unlocking-inclusive-design-how-primers-color-system-is-making-github-com-more-inclusive/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-11-unlocking-inclusive-design-how-primers-color-system-is-making-github-com-more-inclusive/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T17:56:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Primer’s updated light and dark theme color contrast strategy resolved hundreds of color-contrast-related accessibility issues over one thousand use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform integrations from Dell, Fortinet, GitHub, Harness, Snyk, Splunk, and Zscaler]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-from-dell-fortinet-github-harness-snyk-splunk-and-zsca</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-integrations-from-dell-fortinet-github-harness-snyk-splunk-and-zsca"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 24 new Terraform partner integrations make their debut on the Terraform registry, simplifying customers’ cloud infrastructure management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful assumptions for teachers]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45978</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/740038919/0/sethsblog~Useful-assumptions-for-teachers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not simply in the classroom, but anywhere we hope to inform, inspire or educate: Assume enrollment. Either someone is committed to learning or they’re not. While many situations place people into a spot where they are compelled to show up (exhibit A: learning arithmetic in grade school), it’s almost impossible to teach well if people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skipping the good days]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45680</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/740035154/0/sethsblog~Skipping-the-good-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T08:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of the luxury of living near the ocean or the mountains is that you can be picky. If the surf or the powder isn’t great, leave it for the tourists. Good is insufficient, wait for the great moments… When we’re young, or the project is going really well, it’s easy to waste the good […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A taxonomy of endpoint security detection bypasses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/edr-bypass-taxonomy</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/edr-bypass-taxonomy"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post breaks down a taxonomy for endpoint security products. It suggests using complementary feature set descriptions, each with strengths and weaknesses, rather than a generational definition with concentric features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Uhlmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A taxonomy of endpoint security detection bypasses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/edr-bypass-taxonomy</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/edr-bypass-taxonomy"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
I often see “EDR” used as a synonym for “industry-leading endpoint security solution.” There are times when this is accurate, but there are also times when I believe that this generalization stymies discourse around current capability gaps in the endpoint security ecosystem.
In this blog post, I want to share my personal taxonomy for endpoint security products — albeit one that perhaps confusingly reuses existing terminology. The proposed taxonomy suggests using complementary feature set descriptions, each with strengths and weaknesses, rather than a generational definition with concentric features. This allows a more nuanced discussion about the specific defensive feature at play in a given scenario.
So yes, the “EDR” was bypassed at a point in time — but which set(s) of detection featu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Uhlmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Avoid Collisions Assigning Ports to NodePort Services]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/11/nodeport-dynamic-and-static-allocation/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/11/nodeport-dynamic-and-static-allocation/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Xu Zhenglun (Alibaba)
In Kubernetes, a Service can be used to provide a unified traffic endpoint for
applications running on a set of Pods. Clients can use the virtual IP address (or VIP) provided
by the Service for access, and Kubernetes provides load balancing for traffic accessing
different back-end Pods, but a ClusterIP type of Service is limited to providing access to
nodes within the cluster, while traffic from outside the cluster cannot be routed.
One way to solve this problem is to use a type: NodePort Service, which sets up a mapping
to a specific port of all nodes in the cluster, thus redirecting traffic from the
outside to the inside of the cluster.
How Kubernetes allocates node ports to Services?
When a type: NodePort Service is created, its corresponding port(s) are al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionize your open source workflows: the top 3 reasons why GitHub Codespaces is a must-have for maintainers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-10-revolutionize-your-open-source-workflows-the-top-3-reasons-why-github-codespaces-is-a-must-have-for-maintainers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-10-revolutionize-your-open-source-workflows-the-top-3-reasons-why-github-codespaces-is-a-must-have-for-maintainers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T19:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Codespaces is reliable, accessible, and always-ready. Try it out during Maintainer Month and take your projects to new heights!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell, Marvell, NetApp, and SUSE expand Vault support with new integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dell-marvell-netapp-and-suse-expand-vault-support-with-new-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dell-marvell-netapp-and-suse-expand-vault-support-with-new-integrations"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Vault partner ecosystem continues to show strong growth with the addition of more than a dozen new Vault integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · May 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-10-game-bytes-may-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-10-game-bytes-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building better pangenomes to improve the equity of genomics]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/building-better-pangenomes-to-improve.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/building-better-pangenomes-to-improve.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:03:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Andrew Carroll, Product Lead, and Kishwar Shafin, Research Scientist, Genomics






For decades, researchers worked together to assemble a complete copy of the molecular instructions for a human — a map of the human genome. The first draft was finished in 2000, but with several missing pieces.  Even when a complete reference genome was achieved in 2022, their work was not finished. A single reference genome can’t incorporate known genetic variations, such as the variants for the gene determining whether a person has a blood type A, B, AB or O. Furthermore, the reference genome didn’t represent the vast diversity of human ancestries, making it less useful for detecting disease or finding cures for people from some backgrounds than others. For the past three years, we have been pa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about Event-Driven Ansible at Red Hat Summit and AnsibleFest 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-event-driven-ansible-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-event-driven-ansible-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may have heard, AnsibleFest will be taking place at Red Hat Summit in Boston May 23-25. This change will allow you to harness everything that Red Hat technology has to offer in a single place and give you even more tools to address your automation needs. Join Ansible and automation-focused audiences to hear from Red Hat and Ansible leaders, customers, and partners while getting the latest on future Ansible product updates, community projects, and what’s coming in IT automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing your pacemaker]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44411</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/739805867/0/sethsblog~Choosing-your-pacemaker/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roger Bannister ran a four-minute mile by having a relay race of pace runners next to him. If he could keep up with his pacer, he’d finish the run in record time. If you work in an office where people are regularly shipping breakthrough work, it’s likely your work will ship as well. If you’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taxiing]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2774/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2774/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/taxiing.png" title="I don't understand why anyone would pay full price for a flatbed truck rental when you can buy 'DETOUR' signs online for like $10." alt="I don't understand why anyone would pay full price for a flatbed truck rental when you can buy 'DETOUR' signs online for like $10." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Unified Camunda Platform 8 SDK for Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80952&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80952</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/unified-camunda-8-sdk-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T21:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Camunda Platform 8 SDK for Node.js provides a single high-level API to interact with many components of Camunda Platform 8.
The post A Unified Camunda Platform 8 SDK for Node.js appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Storage-Optimized Amazon EC2 I4g Instances: Graviton Processors and AWS Nitro SSDs]]></title>
        <id>fa9f4d36a6cc0d15999ca03edf1ef668d2028f09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-storage-optimized-amazon-ec2-i4g-instances-graviton-processors-and-aws-nitro-ssds/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T21:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are launching I4g instances powered by AWS Graviton2 processors that deliver up to 15% better compute performance than our other storage-optimized instances. With up to 64 vCPUs, 512 GiB of memory, and 15 TB of NVMe storage, one of the six instance sizes is bound to be a great fit for your storage-intensive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66918</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/now-available-azure-devops-server-2022-0-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T17:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we released Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RTW. This is our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1. You can directly install Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 or upgrade from Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC, Azure DevOps Server 2022, Team Foundation Server 2015 or newer versions of the product.
The post Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.20.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80942&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80942</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/camunda-automation-platform-7-20-0-alpha1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T15:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first alpha release of Camunda Automation Runtime 7.20, you can find a new JUEL module based on Jakarta EL 4.0 and many bug fixes.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.20.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What comes after trust?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45952</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/739399478/0/sethsblog~What-comes-after-trust/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walk into a bank with a stocking on your head and you’re probably going to get arrested. Civil society as we know it is dependent on identity and responsibility. A person does something and owns the consequences. This requirement of identity leads to the dynamic of the free market that we call trust. Even companies, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Safer, More Performant Pruning in kubectl apply]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/09/introducing-kubectl-applyset-pruning/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/09/introducing-kubectl-applyset-pruning/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Katrina Verey (independent) and Justin Santa Barbara (Google)
Declarative configuration management with the kubectl apply command is the gold standard approach
to creating or modifying Kubernetes resources. However, one challenge it presents is the deletion
of resources that are no longer needed. In Kubernetes version 1.5, the --prune flag was
introduced to address this issue, allowing kubectl apply to automatically clean up previously
applied resources removed from the current configuration.
Unfortunately, that existing implementation of --prune has design flaws that diminish its
performance and can result in unexpected behaviors. The main issue stems from the lack of explicit
encoding of the previously applied set by the preceding apply operation, necessitating
error-prone dynam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – AWS User Notifications, Serverless event, and More – May 8, 2023]]></title>
        <id>4e74355f2ac25e5c1b2a61d6decd0116b526557f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-aws-notifications-serverless-event-and-more-may-8-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T21:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of this week, I’m flying to Seattle to take part in the AWS Serverless Innovation Day. Along with many customers and colleagues from AWS, we are going to be live on May 17 at a virtual free event. During the AWS Serverless Innovation Day we will share best practices related to building […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start a Camunda Platform 8 Process via REST with Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80864&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80864</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/start-camunda-8-process-rest-webhooks/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T19:19:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can use the Camunda Platform 8 REST API to start a process using the latest Connectors.  
The post Start a Camunda Platform 8 Process via REST with Webhooks appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Introducing An API For Volume Group Snapshots]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/08/kubernetes-1-27-volume-group-snapshot-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/08/kubernetes-1-27-volume-group-snapshot-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Xing Yang (VMware)
Volume group snapshot is introduced as an Alpha feature in Kubernetes v1.27.
This feature introduces a Kubernetes API that allows users to take crash consistent
snapshots for multiple volumes together. It uses a label selector to group multiple
PersistentVolumeClaims for snapshotting.
This new feature is only supported for CSI volume drivers.
An overview of volume group snapshots
Some storage systems provide the ability to create a crash consistent snapshot of
multiple volumes. A group snapshot represents “copies” from multiple volumes that
are taken at the same point-in-time. A group snapshot can be used either to rehydrate
new volumes (pre-populated with the snapshot data) or to restore existing volumes to
a previous state (represented by the snapshots).
Why ad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How is Camunda Platform 8 Professional Edition Helping Companies Accelerate their Projects?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80806&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80806</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/camunda-professional-edition-accelerate-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T20:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've spoken with our early adopters, who shared with us what they like about the pay-as-you-go model and powerful features of our Professional Edition.
The post How is Camunda Platform 8 Professional Edition Helping Companies Accelerate their Projects? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joao Oliveira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Quality-of-Service for Memory Resources (alpha)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/05/qos-memory-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/05/qos-memory-resources/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Dixita Narang (Google)
Kubernetes v1.27, released in April 2023, introduced changes to
Memory QoS (alpha) to improve memory management capabilites in Linux nodes.
Support for Memory QoS was initially added in Kubernetes v1.22, and later some
limitations
around the formula for calculating memory.high were identified. These limitations are
addressed in Kubernetes v1.27.
Background
Kubernetes allows you to optionally specify how much of each resources a container needs
in the Pod specification. The most common resources to specify are CPU and Memory.
For example, a Pod manifest that defines container resource requirements could look like:
apiVersion: v1
kind: Pod
metadata:
name: example
spec:
containers:
- name: nginx
resources:
requests:
memory: "64Mi"
cpu: "250m"
limits:
memory: "6…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MaMMUT: A simple vision-encoder text-decoder architecture for multimodal tasks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/mammut-simple-vision-encoder-text.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/mammut-simple-vision-encoder-text.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T21:59:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by AJ Piergiovanni and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research




Vision-language foundational models are built on the premise of a single pre-training followed by subsequent adaptation to multiple downstream tasks. Two main and disjoint training scenarios are popular: a CLIP-style contrastive learning and next-token prediction. Contrastive learning trains the model to predict if image-text pairs correctly match, effectively building visual and text representations for the corresponding image and text inputs, whereas next-token prediction predicts the most likely next text token in a sequence, thus learning to generate text, according to the required task. Contrastive learning enables image-text and text-image retrieval tasks, such as finding the image that best match…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating Critical Traffic At Scale with No Downtime — Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ba1c7a1c7835</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/migrating-critical-traffic-at-scale-with-no-downtime-part-1-ba1c7a1c7835?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T21:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shyam Gala, Javier Fernandez-Ivern, Anup Rokkam Pratap, Devang Shah]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: StatefulSet PVC Auto-Deletion (beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/04/kubernetes-1-27-statefulset-pvc-auto-deletion-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/04/kubernetes-1-27-statefulset-pvc-auto-deletion-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Matthew Cary (Google)
Kubernetes v1.27 graduated to beta a new policy mechanism for
StatefulSets that controls the lifetime of
their PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs). The new PVC
retention policy lets users specify if the PVCs generated from the StatefulSet spec template should
be automatically deleted or retrained when the StatefulSet is deleted or replicas in the StatefulSet
are scaled down.
What problem does this solve?
A StatefulSet spec can include Pod and PVC templates. When a replica is first created, the
Kubernetes control plane creates a PVC for that replica if one does not already exist. The behavior
before the PVC retention policy was that the control plane never cleaned up the PVCs created for
StatefulSets - this was left up to the cluster administrator, or to some add-on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Bob’s Used Books—a New, Real-World, .NET Sample Application]]></title>
        <id>1c00c599af66e56a57ee408b24db5dd4f41dfeec</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-bobs-used-books-a-new-real-world-net-sample-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T20:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to announce that a new open-source sample application, a fictitious used books eCommerce store we call Bob’s Used Books, is available for .NET developers working with AWS. The .NET advocacy and development teams at AWS talk to customers regularly and, during those conversations, often receive requests for more in-depth samples. Customers tell […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Set Up Your AWS Notifications in One Place]]></title>
        <id>01ea65c02e7f25c9e84ec4d664b25ae3dc22c87a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-set-up-your-aws-notifications-in-one-place/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T17:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are launching AWS User Notifications, a single place in the AWS console to set up and view AWS notifications across multiple AWS accounts, Regions, and services. You can centrally set up and view notifications from over 100 AWS services, such as Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) objects events, Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IndoorSim-to-OutdoorReal: Learning to navigate outdoors without any outdoor experience]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/indoorsim-to-outdoorreal-learning-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/indoorsim-to-outdoorreal-learning-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Joanne Truong, Student Researcher, and Wenhao Yu, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google





Teaching mobile robots to navigate in complex outdoor environments is critical to real-world applications, such as delivery or search and rescue. However, this is also a challenging problem as the robot needs to perceive its surroundings, and then explore to identify feasible paths towards the goal. Another common challenge is that the robot needs to overcome uneven terrains, such as stairs, curbs, or rockbed on a trail, while avoiding obstacles and pedestrians. In our prior work, we investigated the second challenge by teaching a quadruped robot to tackle challenging uneven obstacles and various outdoor terrains. 



In “IndoorSim-to-OutdoorReal: Learning to Navigate Outdoors without an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging the gap between technology and FinOps with HashiCorp and Intel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/bridging-the-gap-between-technology-and-finops-with-hashicorp-and-intel</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/bridging-the-gap-between-technology-and-finops-with-hashicorp-and-intel"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Cloud Optimized Modules for Terraform and Sentinel standardize infrastructure deployment and increase performance with purpose-built policy as code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take Ansible validated content to the next level with Event-Driven Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-with-event-driven-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-with-event-driven-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing has become an essential factor in IT transformation and business innovation. The highly dynamic nature of cloud environments, where new resources are constantly being added and removed, poses new challenges. One of the main challenges organizations face is the lack of visibility into the cloud environment. As cloud computing continues to grow in complexity, it can be challenging to keep track of all the different resources and applications that make up the infrastructure. This lack of visibility can make it difficult to maintain security policies and configurations, making the infrastructure vulnerable to attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第229話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361192645271</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361192645271"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: HorizontalPodAutoscaler ContainerResource type metric moves to beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/02/hpa-container-resource-metric/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/02/hpa-container-resource-metric/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Kensei Nakada (Mercari)
Kubernetes 1.20 introduced the ContainerResource type metric
in HorizontalPodAutoscaler (HPA).
In Kubernetes 1.27, this feature moves to beta and the corresponding feature gate (HPAContainerMetrics) gets enabled by default.
What is the ContainerResource type metric
The ContainerResource type metric allows us to configure the autoscaling based on resource usage of individual containers.
In the following example, the HPA controller scales the target
so that the average utilization of the cpu in the application container of all the pods is around 60%.
(See the algorithm details
to know how the desired replica number is calculated exactly)
type: ContainerResource
containerResource:
 name: cpu
 container: application
 target:
 type: Utilization
 averageUtilizatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Review – AWS Verified Access, Java 17, Amplify Flutter, Conferences, and More – May 1, 2023]]></title>
        <id>ae3f62fcbec27e6f57598f0de24b8a0e4fcfbe7e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/week-in-review-aws-verified-access-java-17-amplify-flutter-conferences-and-more-may-1-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T22:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conference season has started and I was happy to meet and talk with iOS and Swift developers at the New York Swifty conference last week. I will travel again to Turino (Italy), Amsterdam (Netherlands), Frankfurt (Germany), and London (UK) in the coming weeks. Feel free to stop by and say hi if you are around. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Winning Process Orchestration Plays for Financial Services]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80223&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80223</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/process-orchestration-plays-financial-services/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To improve a business, improve its processes. But how? Here are some proven process orchestration patterns to follow for financial services. 
The post Four Winning Process Orchestration Plays for Financial Services appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason English</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 221]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66868</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-221/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our team remains dedicated to improving New Boards Hub by addressing any issues that may arise. We’re happy to report that the New Boards Hub has been steadily progressing with each sprint. Although it is not quite ready for general availability yet,
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 221 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you should run your platform team like a product team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/why-you-should-run-your-platform-team-like-a-product-team</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/why-you-should-run-your-platform-team-like-a-product-team"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like a product team, a successful platform team must understand the needs of its "customers" and stakeholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ICLR 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-iclr-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-iclr-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T06:37:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Catherine Armato, Program Manager, Google




The Eleventh International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR 2023) is being held this week as a hybrid event in Kigali, Rwanda. We are proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of ICLR 2023, a premier conference on deep learning, where Google researchers contribute at all levels. This year we are presenting over 100 papers and are actively involved in organizing and hosting a number of different events, including workshops and interactive sessions.

 

If you’re registered for ICLR 2023, we hope you’ll visit the Google booth to learn more about the exciting work we’re doing across topics spanning representation and reinforcement learning, theory and optimization, social impact, safety and privacy, and applications from generative AI to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Athena Provisioned Capacity]]></title>
        <id>17b4867be4eb5a35b07009ae78749bcc1c401801</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-athena-provisioned-capacity/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T19:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we launch the ability to provision capacity to run your Athena queries. Athena is a query service that makes it simple to analyze data in Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) data lakes and 30 different data sources, including on-premises data sources or other cloud systems, using standard SQL queries. Athena is serverless, so […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: StatefulSet Start Ordinal Simplifies Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/28/statefulset-start-ordinal/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/28/statefulset-start-ordinal/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Peter Schuurman (Google)
Kubernetes v1.26 introduced a new, alpha-level feature for
StatefulSets that controls
the ordinal numbering of Pod replicas. As of Kubernetes v1.27, this feature is
now beta. Ordinals can start from arbitrary
non-negative numbers. This blog post will discuss how this feature can be
used.
Background
StatefulSets ordinals provide sequential identities for pod replicas. When using
OrderedReady Pod management
Pods are created from ordinal index 0 up to N-1.
With Kubernetes today, orchestrating a StatefulSet migration across clusters is
challenging. Backup and restore solutions exist, but these require the
application to be scaled down to zero replicas prior to migration. In today's
fully connected world, even planned application downtime may not allow you to
me…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Alerting with Atlas Streaming Eval]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e691c60dc61e</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/improved-alerting-with-atlas-streaming-eval-e691c60dc61e?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ruchir Jha, Brian Harrington, Yingwu Zhao]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An ML-based approach to better characterize lung diseases]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/an-ml-based-approach-to-better.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/an-ml-based-approach-to-better.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:24:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Babak Behsaz, Software Engineer, and Andrew Carroll, Product Lead, Genomics




The combination of the environment an individual experiences and their genetic predispositions determines the majority of their risk for various diseases. Large national efforts, such as the UK Biobank, have created large, public resources to better understand the links between environment, genetics, and disease. This has the potential to help individuals better understand how to stay healthy, clinicians to treat illnesses, and scientists to develop new medicines.


One challenge in this process is how we make sense of the vast amount of clinical measurements — the UK Biobank has many petabytes of imaging, metabolic tests, and medical records spanning 500,000 individuals. To best use this data, we nee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CyberGRX cut ML processing time from 8 days to 56 minutes with AWS Step Functions Distributed Map]]></title>
        <id>6ca49d44c0bb9aa0d343f5673699f5a7fe73ca58</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-cybercrx-cut-ml-processing-time-from-8-days-to-56-minutes-with-aws-step-functions-distributed-map/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T19:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last December, Sébastien Stormacq wrote about the availability of a distributed map state for AWS Step Functions, a new feature that allows you to orchestrate large-scale parallel workloads in the cloud. That’s when Charles Burton, a data systems engineer for a company called CyberGRX, found out about it and refactored his workflow, reducing the processing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust and efficient medical imaging with self-supervision]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robust-and-efficient-medical-imaging.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robust-and-efficient-medical-imaging.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T20:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shekoofeh Azizi, Senior Research Scientist, and Laura Culp, Senior Research Engineer, Google Research
  
  
  
Despite recent progress in the field of medical artificial intelligence (AI), most existing models are narrow, single-task systems that require large quantities of labeled data to train. Moreover, these models cannot be easily reused in new clinical contexts as they often require the collection, de-identification and annotation of site-specific data for every new deployment environment, which is both laborious and expensive. This problem of data-efficient generalization (a model’s ability to generalize to new settings using minimal new data) continues to be a key translational challenge for medical machine learning (ML) models and has in turn, prevented their broad uptak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud no-code provisioning is now GA with new features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-no-code-provisioning-is-now-ga-with-new-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-no-code-provisioning-is-now-ga-with-new-features"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No-code provisioning is now GA for Terraform Cloud Business, providing validated self-service infrastructure, additional security through more granular permissions, and ease of use with variable options as dropdowns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to call the Camunda Inbound Webhook from Postman]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=79381&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=79381</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/how-to-call-camunda-inbound-webhook-postman/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to create processes using the Camunda Webhook Connector and to start them via Postman both in unauthenticated and authenticated modes.
The post How to call the Camunda Inbound Webhook from Postman appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Pappas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LayerNAS: Neural architecture search in polynomial complexity]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/layernas-neural-architecture-search-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/layernas-neural-architecture-search-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T17:20:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yicheng Fan and Dana Alon, Software Engineers, Google Research




Every byte and every operation matters when trying to build a faster model, especially if the model is to run on-device. Neural architecture search (NAS) algorithms design sophisticated model architectures by searching through a larger model-space than what is possible manually. Different NAS algorithms, such as MNasNet and TuNAS, have been proposed and have discovered several efficient model architectures, including MobileNetV3, EfficientNet. 

 


Here we present LayerNAS, an approach that reformulates the multi-objective NAS problem within the framework of combinatorial optimization to greatly reduce the complexity, which results in an order of magnitude reduction in the number of model candidates that must be …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sentinel and control groups now available in HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/sentinel-and-control-groups-now-available-in-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/sentinel-and-control-groups-now-available-in-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Plus Clusters add support for Sentinel policies and control groups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Updates to the Auto-refreshing Official CVE Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/25/k8s-cve-feed-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/25/k8s-cve-feed-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Cailyn Edwards (Shopify), Mahé Tardy (Isovalent), Pushkar Joglekar
Since launching the Auto-refreshing Official CVE feed as an alpha
feature in the 1.25 release, we have made significant improvements and updates. We are excited to announce the release of the
beta version of the feed. This blog post will outline the feedback received, the changes made, and talk about how you can help
as we prepare to make this a stable feature in a future Kubernetes Release.
Feedback from end-users
SIG Security received some feedback from end-users:
The JSON CVE Feed did not comply
with the JSON Feed specification as its name would suggest.
The feed could also support RSS
in addition to JSON Feed format.
Some metadata could be added to indicate the freshness of
the feed overall, or specific CVEs. A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 24, 2023: Amazon CodeCatalyst, Amazon S3 on Snowball Edge, and More…]]></title>
        <id>f99637a00ba132ddbd2ab3f3ddf491e8cdcc7989</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-24-2023-amazon-codecatalyst-amazon-s3-on-snowball-edge-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T21:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As always, there’s plenty to share this week: Amazon CodeCatalyst is now generally available, Amazon S3 is now available on Snowball Edge devices, version 1.0.0 of AWS Amplify Flutter is here, and a lot more. Let’s dive in! Last Week’s Launches Here are some of the launches that caught my eye this past week: Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Power Automate to update Azure DevOps queries]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66806</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/use-power-automate-to-update-azure-devops-queries/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T21:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I’ll explain how to set up automation to automatically update Azure DevOps (ADO) queries. Using an automated Power Automate flow, you save time by not having to manually update your queries for each sprint. Everyone using your queries benefits by having data and details that are always current and accurate.
The post Use Power Automate to update Azure DevOps queries appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Reitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choose Korean in AWS Support as Your Preferred Language]]></title>
        <id>3fd49d6f464a65c650e1d14d5e7d7c56e29331bc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/choose-korean-in-aws-support-as-your-preferred-language/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T20:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the general availability of AWS Support in Korean as your preferred language, in addition to English, Japanese, and Chinese. As the number of customers speaking Korean grows, AWS Support is invested in providing the best support experience possible. You can now communicate with AWS Support engineers and agents in Korean when you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds Vault-backed dynamic credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-vault-backed-dynamic-credentials</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-vault-backed-dynamic-credentials"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic provider credentials in HashiCorp Terraform Cloud now supports Vault dynamic secrets engines to consolidate cloud access for Terraform runs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at CHI 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-chi-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-chi-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T02:26:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Malaya Jules, Program Manager, Google




This week, the Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI 2023) is being held in Hamburg, Germany. We are proud to be a Hero Sponsor of CHI 2023, a premier conference on human-computer interaction, where Google researchers contribute at all levels. This year we are presenting over 30 papers and are actively involved in organizing and hosting a number of different events across workshops, courses, and interactive sessions.


 


If you’re registered for CHI 2023, we hope you’ll visit the Google booth to learn more about the exciting work across various topics, including language interactions, causal inference, question answering and more. Take a look below to learn more about the Google research being presented at CHI 2023 (Goog…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Server Side Field Validation and OpenAPI V3 move to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/24/openapi-v3-field-validation-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/24/openapi-v3-field-validation-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jeffrey Ying (Google), Antoine Pelisse (Google)
Before Kubernetes v1.8 (!), typos, mis-indentations or minor errors in
YAMLs could have catastrophic consequences (e.g. a typo like
forgetting the trailing s in replica: 1000 could cause an outage,
because the value would be ignored and missing, forcing a reset of
replicas back to 1). This was solved back then by fetching the OpenAPI
v2 in kubectl and using it to verify that fields were correct and
present before applying. Unfortunately, at that time, Custom Resource
Definitions didn’t exist, and the code was written under that
assumption. When CRDs were later introduced, the lack of flexibility
in the validation code forced some hard decisions in the way CRDs
exposed their schema, leaving us in a cycle of bad validation causing
bad O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Blocks for ML: Accelerating machine learning prototyping with interactive tools]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/visual-blocks-for-ml-accelerating.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/visual-blocks-for-ml-accelerating.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T19:01:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ruofei Du, Interactive Perception & Graphics Lead, Google Augmented Reality, and Na Li, Tech Lead Manager, Google CoreML

  



  Update — 2023/05/08: This post has been updated to include open-source details for the Visual Blocks framework. 
human body segmentation for video and teleconferencing, depth estimation for 3D reconstruction, hand and body tracking for interaction, and audio processing for remote communication.



However, developing and iterating on these ML-based multimedia prototypes can be challenging and costly. It usually involves a cross-functional team of ML practitioners who fine-tune the models, evaluate robustness, characterize strengths and weaknesses, inspect performance in the end-use context, and develop the applications. Moreover, models are frequently …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Query Node Logs Using The Kubelet API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/21/node-log-query-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/21/node-log-query-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aravindh Puthiyaparambil (Red Hat)
Kubernetes 1.27 introduced a new feature called Node log query that allows
viewing logs of services running on the node.
What problem does it solve?
Cluster administrators face issues when debugging malfunctioning services
running on the node. They usually have to SSH or RDP into the node to view the
logs of the service to debug the issue. The Node log query feature helps with
this scenario by allowing the cluster administrator to view the logs using
kubectl. This is especially useful with Windows nodes where you run into the
issue of the node going to the ready state but containers not coming up due to
CNI misconfigurations and other issues that are not easily identifiable by
looking at the Pod status.
How does it work?
The kubelet already has a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep long-horizon forecasting]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/recent-advances-in-deep-long-horizon.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/recent-advances-in-deep-long-horizon.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T20:26:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rajat Sen and Abhimanyu Das, Research Scientists, Google Research




Time-series forecasting is an important research area that is critical to several scientific and industrial applications, like retail supply chain optimization, energy and traffic prediction, and weather forecasting. In retail use cases, for example, it has been observed that improving demand forecasting accuracy can meaningfully reduce inventory costs and increase revenue. 
 

Modern time-series applications can involve forecasting hundreds of thousands of correlated time-series (e.g., demands of different products for a retailer) over long horizons (e.g., a quarter or year away at daily granularity). As such, time-series forecasting models need to satisfy the following key criterias:



Ability to handle auxi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 Compatible Storage on AWS Snowball Edge Compute Optimized Devices Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>3a5f9a4909fe852e7ed6cc8ac314d50e62bf28b1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-compatible-storage-on-aws-snowball-edge-compute-optimized-devices-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T18:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have added a collection of purpose-built services to the AWS Snow Family for customers, such as Snowball Edge in 2016 and Snowcone in 2020. These services run compute intensive workloads and stores data in edge locations with denied, disrupted, intermittent, or limited network connectivity and for transferring large amounts of data from on-premises and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Human Approach to Process Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78911&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78911</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/human-approach-process-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chances of success are significantly higher when you put humans in the center of your orchestration projects.
The post A Human Approach to Process Automation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Single Pod Access Mode for PersistentVolumes Graduates to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/20/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/20/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chris Henzie (Google)
With the release of Kubernetes v1.27 the ReadWriteOncePod feature has graduated
to beta. In this blog post, we'll take a closer look at this feature, what it
does, and how it has evolved in the beta release.
What is ReadWriteOncePod?
ReadWriteOncePod is a new access mode for
PersistentVolumes (PVs)
and PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs)
introduced in Kubernetes v1.22. This access mode enables you to restrict volume
access to a single pod in the cluster, ensuring that only one pod can write to
the volume at a time. This can be particularly useful for stateful workloads
that require single-writer access to storage.
For more context on access modes and how ReadWriteOncePod works read
What are access modes and why are they important?
in the Introducing Single Pod Acces…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Building without Limits at AWS Developer Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>5642e5e26f54b4e2d613344cf7fb6a8727367ef7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/discover-building-without-limits-at-aws-developer-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T18:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We hope you can join us on Wednesday, April 26, for a free-to-attend online event, AWS Developer Innovation Day. AWS will stream the event simultaneously across multiple platforms, including LinkedIn Live, Twitter, YouTube, and Twitch. Developer Innovation Day is a brand-new event designed specifically for developers and development teams. In the event, sessions throughout the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Technology, AI, Society and Culture]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T18:12:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lauren Wilcox, Senior Staff Research Scientist, on behalf of the Technology, AI, Society, and Culture Team




Google sees AI as a foundational and transformational technology, with recent advances in generative AI technologies, such as LaMDA, PaLM, Imagen, Parti, MusicLM, and similar machine learning (ML) models, some of which are now being incorporated into our products. This transformative potential requires us to be responsible not only in how we advance our technology, but also in how we envision which technologies to build, and how we assess the social impact AI and ML-enabled technologies have on the world. This endeavor necessitates fundamental and applied research with an interdisciplinary lens that engages with — and accounts for — the social, cultural, economic, and ot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第228話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361158146336</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361158146336"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differentially private heatmaps]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/differentially-private-heatmaps.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/differentially-private-heatmaps.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T20:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Badih Ghazi, Staff Research Scientist, and Nachiappan Valliappan, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research






Recently, differential privacy (DP) has emerged as a mathematically robust notion of user privacy for data aggregation and machine learning (ML), with practical deployments including the 2022 US Census and in industry. Over the last few years, we have open-sourced libraries for privacy-preserving analytics and ML and have been constantly enhancing their capabilities. Meanwhile, new algorithms have been developed by the research community for several analytic tasks involving private aggregation of data. 
 

One such important data aggregation method is the heatmap. Heatmaps are popular for visualizing aggregated data in two or more dimensions. They are widely used in ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Efficient SELinux volume relabeling (Beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/18/kubernetes-1-27-efficient-selinux-relabeling-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/18/kubernetes-1-27-efficient-selinux-relabeling-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jan Šafránek (Red Hat)
The problem
On Linux with Security-Enhanced Linux (SELinux) enabled, it's traditionally
the container runtime that applies SELinux labels to a Pod and all its volumes.
Kubernetes only passes the SELinux label from a Pod's securityContext fields
to the container runtime.
The container runtime then recursively changes SELinux label on all files that
are visible to the Pod's containers. This can be time-consuming if there are
many files on the volume, especially when the volume is on a remote filesystem.
Note
subPath of a volume, only that subPath of the whole
volume is relabeled. This allows two pods that have two different SELinux labels
to use the same volume, as long as they use different subpaths of it.

If a Pod does not have any SELinux label assigned in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s happening at KubeCon Europe 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-s-happening-at-kubecon-europe-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-s-happening-at-kubecon-europe-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attending KubeCon EU, either in person or online? Check out what HashiCorp is doing and talking about at the event, and learn about recent Kubernetes-related product features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.16 improves automatic HCL conversion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-16-improves-automatic-hcl-conversion</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-16-improves-automatic-hcl-conversion"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform v0.16 improves automatic conversion of configuration code from HCL to supported languages by enabling type coercion and providing better support for iterators and functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>