<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-08-10T01:49:14.836Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-08-10T01:49:14.836Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Speak Math? So Does YouTrack!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=youtrack&amp;p=271821</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/youtrack/2022/08/do-you-speak-math-so-does-youtrack/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T19:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of academic institutions and students across the globe use YouTrack for software development and project management courses, as well as in research. If you’re working in this field and searching for a tool that, like you and your colleagues or your fellow students, speaks the language of mathematics, look no further than YouTrack. LaTeX […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Pishkova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Azure DevOps Server 2022 RC1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65570</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-azure-devops-server-2022-rc1/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T18:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re very excited to announce the first release candidate (RC) of Azure DevOps Server 2022!
Delivery Plans
There are many more features with this release and you can read all about those features in our release notes.
The post Introducing Azure DevOps Server 2022 RC1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Video-Text Learning with Iterative Co-tokenization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/efficient-video-text-learning-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/efficient-video-text-learning-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T17:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by AJ Piergiovanni and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Video is an ubiquitous source of media content that touches on many aspects of people’s day-to-day lives. Increasingly, real-world video applications, such as video captioning, video content analysis, and video question-answering (VideoQA), rely on models that can connect video content with text or natural language. VideoQA is particularly challenging, however, as it requires grasping both semantic information, such as objects in a scene, as well as temporal information, e.g., how things move and interact, both of which must be taken in the context of a natural-language question that holds specific intent. In addition, because videos have many frames, processing all of them to learn spatio-temp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[August patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65582</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/august-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T16:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Fix identity value error while assigning a work item to an identity which appears in different domains.
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2 Patch 2
The post August patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot now alerts for vulnerable GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-09-dependabot-now-alerts-for-vulnerable-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-09-dependabot-now-alerts-for-vulnerable-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T15:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions gives teams access to powerful, native CI/CD capabilities right next to their code hosted in GitHub. Starting today, GitHub will send a Dependabot alert for vulnerable GitHub Actions, making it even easier to stay up to date and fix security vulnerabilities in your actions workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha4 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=59448</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/camunda-automation-platform-7180-alpha4-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.18. This release features the following improvements: Support for H2 2.1 Traditional Chinese translations are available Improved status monitoring of batch jobs Improved safety of executing a batch operation on the Batch Operation page 8 Bug Fixes You can download Camunda for free or run it with Docker. For a complete list of all improvements, take a look at the release notes. Please also see the list of known issues. If you want to dig in deeper, you can find the source code on GitHub. Support for H2 2.1 This release adds support for the H2 database in version 2.1, which provides fixes for vulnerabilities. Enterprise customers...
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha4 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0 alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=59822</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce a new release of Camunda Optimize. Camunda Optimize provides business activity monitoring for workflows, supporting continuous process improvement by providing transparency into your automated workflows and decisions. Business-friendly reports, dashboards, and alerts make it possible to identify process bottlenecks, improve end-to-end processes, and evaluate the success of your process automation initiative. In the rest of this post, we’ll highlight some of the new capabilities introduced in Optimize 3.9.0 alpha3. What’s new? Ease of adding new reports to dashboard Reports are added to dashboards to design an individual overview of the performance of your processes. Adding reports to dashboards was already possible with previous versions of Optimize, but now we’ve reduced the number of steps to do...
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0 alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Apps Contest: Create Apps and Win Prizes]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=272480</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2022/08/09/space-apps-contest/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T08:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the release of Space Marketplace, we’d like to invite you to take part in the Space Apps Contest!  Applications are the main way to extend the functionality of Space, a complete software development platform. With apps in Space, you can adjust the platform to the needs of your team and introduce more advanced workflows […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgenia Verbina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indispensable or irreplaceable]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42471</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/705634210/0/sethsblog~Indispensable-or-irreplaceable/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T08:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are 1,000 other high schools, and each one has a vice principal who isn’t you. No, you’re not irreplaceable. No one is, not really. But if we work at it, we might become indispensable. The linchpin, someone who would be missed if they were gone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 9th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/09/this-week-in-spring-august-9th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/09/this-week-in-spring-august-9th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you this fine Tuesday? I’m in Kansas City for the Kansas City Developer Conference. It’s a crazy fun show, and I’m glad to be here. I only wish the rest of you were here, too! We’ve got a packed This Week in Spring, however, so let’s dive right into it.


  
snicoll/demo-aot-native: Demo of a basic webapp using Ahead-Of-Time compilation

  
A Bootiful Podcast: Observability guru Jonatan Ivanov on the future of observability in Spring Boot

  
Blog: Kubernetes Removals and Major Changes In 1.25

  
Building a Topic Exchange with RabbitMQ and .NET 6

  
Display Logged-in User’s Information in Thymeleaf

  
Dockerizing a Java Application

  
Get Started with Spring Boot and SAML

  
Resilient Kafka Consumers With Reactor Kafka - DZone Java

  
Spring Batch + Karp Rabin = How CRISPR CAS9 Works

  
Spring Tools 4.15.2 released

  
Upload Image With Spring Boot and Thymeleaf]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting U.S. veteran heroes through Operation Giving Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/supporting-us-veteran-heroes-through-operation-giving-back</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/supporting-us-veteran-heroes-through-operation-giving-back"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about how Elastic is giving back to America's heroes by providing access to a customized free training program, career support, and resources and a special place in our community to network build connections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Raiguel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting U.S. veteran heroes through Operation Giving Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/supporting-us-veteran-heroes-through-operation-giving-back</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/supporting-us-veteran-heroes-through-operation-giving-back"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Launched in September 2021, Operation Giving Back provides all U.S. veterans and active duty military personnel with access to Elastic training to help them grow and diversify their technical skill set.  

Operation Giving Back is about Elastic saying thank you to all military personnel by providing a leg up when it comes to technical skills development.
,Customize your training experience
Designed to support individuals looking to develop their Elastic skills in a variety of areas, participants in the program have access to a customized training program that includes the following courses:

Data Analysis with Kibana
Observability Fundamentals
App Search Fundamentals
App Search Web Crawler Fundamentals
Workplace Search Fundamentals
ECE Fundamentals
Kibana Fundamentals
Kibana for Splunk S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Raiguel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 8, 2022]]></title>
        <id>5368b5f3eeaf1b269292cf7fe2e8e38eb5b9e360</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-8-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T20:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an ex-.NET developer, and now Developer Advocate for .NET at AWS, I’m excited to bring you this week’s Week in Review post, for reasons that will quickly become apparent! There are several updates, customer stories, and events I want to bring to your attention, so let’s dive straight in! Last Week’s launches .NET developers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Platform Teams Are Everywhere — Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cloud-platform-teams-are-everywhere-heres-why</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cloud-platform-teams-are-everywhere-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HashiCorp’s new State of Cloud Strategy survey, 86% of respondents said they rely on cloud platform teams — for a wide variety of very good reasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New request for comments on improving npm security with Sigstore is now open]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-08-new-request-for-comments-on-improving-npm-security-with-sigstore-is-now-open/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-08-new-request-for-comments-on-improving-npm-security-with-sigstore-is-now-open/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T16:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supply chain attacks exploit our implicit trust of open source to hurt developers and our customers. Read our proposal for how npm will significantly reduce supply chain attacks by signing packages with Sigstore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All GitHub Enterprise users now have access to the security overview]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-08-all-github-enterprise-users-now-have-access-to-the-security-overview/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-08-all-github-enterprise-users-now-have-access-to-the-security-overview/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T15:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re expanding access to the GitHub security overview! All GitHub Enterprise customers now have access to the security overview, not just those with GitHub Advanced Security. Additionally, all users within an enterprise can now access the security overview, not just admins and security managers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO Digest #2: Top 5 Tips for Angular Development With JetBrains IDEs]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=271913</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/08/fomo-digest-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how much familiarity you have with Angular, or how you feel about it, JetBrains IDEs can make your experience with this framework much better. In today’s FOMO digest, we’ll tell you about the features for working in Angular that you can find in JetBrains IDEs, such as WebStorm, IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate, PhpStorm, Rider, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Content reuse – a productivity booster or a vicious circle?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=writerside&amp;p=267281</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/writerside/2022/08/content-reuse-a-productivity-booster-or-a-vicious-circle/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T11:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Single-source publishing is a powerful must-have feature that is normally among the top three competitive advantages for any professional help authoring solution – and for good reason. Single-sourcing reusable content lets you: Maintain consistency throughout your documentation in terms of style, terminology, the level of detail, and so on.  Avoid making multiple updates when a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Gasparyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | August 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=272373</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/08/08/net-annotated-monthly-august-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T11:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? ASP.NET was originally called ASP, which stands for Active Server Pages. It was released in December 1996 and was the pre-.NET version of this popular web framework. Read more about the history of Active Server Pages on Wikipedia.   .NET news .NET July 2022 Updates – .NET 6.0.7 and .NET Core 3.1.27 .NET […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not All Databases/Schemas Are Displayed by Default. Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=272555</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/08/08/not-all-databases-schemas-are-displayed-by-default-why/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T10:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is one thing which makes DataGrip different from many other database tools: DataGrip doesn’t show all schemas and databases by default in the database explorer. In this post we’ll briefly describe why it’s designed like this and what you can do if this doesn’t suit your workflow. The most important thing about DataGrip is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maksim Sobolevskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Absolute and relative]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42469</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/705511208/0/sethsblog~Absolute-and-relative/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn’t matter that it’s not the Super Bowl or the World Cup. For this twelve-year old, tomorrow’s game is the big game, the biggest ever, and the emotional stakes are just as high. It doesn’t matter that this illness isn’t going to be life or death in the next few days. For this patient, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving quantified success with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how Elastic’s Security solution helps customers realize and quantify outcomes and satisfaction in decision-making, customer churns, the impact of security threats, and overall risk reduction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Fernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving quantified success with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Regardless of geography, industry, sector, or use cases, most would agree that reducing risk is a top priority for their organization. Whether it’s decreasing phishing scams, ransomware, and malware attacks or reducing the risk of customer churn due to breaches, security is everyone’s concern. As leaders working toward strategic initiatives around security, we should be asking how we can improve security and modernize our tech stack to drive organizational resiliency and efficiency, while reducing risk and spend.  

For more than a decade, Elastic has been solving complex data problems for customers that increase productivity, drive down tool sprawl, and reduce risk of revenue disruption. Since the time I have been at Elastic, we have focused on building out-of-the-box content around sec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Fernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientific Field Prefixes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2656/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2656/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/scientific_field_prefixes.png" title="Massage: Theoretical (10), Quantum (6), High-energy (2), Computational (1), Marine (1), Astro- (None)" alt="Massage: Theoretical (10), Quantum (6), High-energy (2), Computational (1), Marine (1), Astro- (None)" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The PyCharm 2022.2.1 Release Candidate Is Now Available!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=272446</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/08/2022-2-1-rc/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T08:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re working closely with your feedback on the PyCharm 2022.2 version that was released last week. Thank you for sharing with us! If you encounter an issue in PyCharm 2022.2, please reach out to our support team. We are actively fixing regressions, and will be delivering a minor bug-fix release soon. You can get the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Bhutan, they dream of rainbows]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42465</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/705428508/0/sethsblog~In-Bhutan-they-dream-of-rainbows/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T08:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In countries throughout the world, even in countries where there are no snakes, the most common dream is one based on our (it must be) genetic fear of snakes. But in Bhutan, they dream of rainbows. The dreams might be consistent, but the way we talk about them clearly isn’t. Perhaps the dreams we remember […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crickets]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42462</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/705352012/0/sethsblog~Crickets/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T08:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we sing in the shower, we hardly expect applause. In fact, that would be awfully weird. But online, when just about anyone might be clicking, watching or sharing, it’s disappointing to put your work into the world and hear nothing. Nothing but a black hole that absorbs your best work and reflects nothing back. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · July 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-05-release-radar-jul-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-05-release-radar-jul-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T17:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While some of us have been wrapping up the financial year, and enjoying vacation time, others have been hard at work shipping open source projects and releases. These projects include everything from world-changing technology to developer tooling, and weekend hobbies. Here are some of the open source projects that released major version updates this July. [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qodana 2022.2 Is Available: CircleCI Orb and 50+ New Inspections]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=qodana&amp;p=272242</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/qodana/2022/08/qodana-2022-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T15:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qodana 2022.2 is now available! We’ve added CircleCI Orb to the Qodana integration toolset, and brought new and improved code inspections for Java, Kotlin, Android, PHP, JavaScript, and Python. GET STARTED WITH QODANA More CIs to run Qodana with Qodana already has plugins for Azure Pipelines, GitHub Actions, and TeamCity. Starting from 2022.2, we’ve prepared […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Viktor Tiulpin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2.1 Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=272170</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/08/phpstorm-2022-2-1-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T11:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A preview build for PhpStorm 2022.2.1, the upcoming minor release of PhpStorm, is now available. It brings a fixed for a broken step over in debugger. Read on to see a detailed post-mortem of the issue. Post-mortem for broken debugging in PhpStorm 2022.2 In PhpStorm 2022.2, we’ve implemented WI-56517 Display __toString() representation on an object […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to count]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41583</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/705285166/0/sethsblog~What-to-count/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T09:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So many choices. So many sorts of metrics, critics and measures. Perhaps it makes sense to count things where the counting tells us how to do better next time. And to count things that let us know how much risk we can take next time. Or to calibrate our judgment about the market. But it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some README.md Love: Markdown Support Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=271198</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/08/markdown-support-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T08:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers and other users of JetBrains IDEs have been using the integrated Markdown support for a long time. It is great for editing your project’s README.md file, as well as any documentation that comes with the source code, or even your static web site sourced in Markdown. You can also use Markdown scratch files to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksei Zhebel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Mother of Four Claims Her Seat at the Tech Table]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/claiming-her-seat-at-the-tech-table</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/claiming-her-seat-at-the-tech-table"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zoraya Sanchez De La Vega Cayero makes a mid-career transition to tech via the HashiCorp Early Careers program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asking Scientists Questions]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2655/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2655/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/asking_scientists_questions.png" title="'Does the substance feel weird to the touch?' is equally likely to get the answers 'Don't be ridiculous, you would never put your hand near a sample. We have safety protocols.' and 'Yeah, and it tastes AWFUL.'" alt="'Does the substance feel weird to the touch?' is equally likely to get the answers 'Don't be ridiculous, you would never put your hand near a sample. We have safety protocols.' and 'Yeah, and it tastes AWFUL.'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Google Universal Image Embedding Challenge]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/introducing-google-universal-image.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/introducing-google-universal-image.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T17:47:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bingyi Cao, Software Engineer, Google Research, and Mário Lipovský, Software Engineer, Google Lens 
Computer vision models see daily application for a wide variety of tasks, ranging from object recognition to image-based 3D object reconstruction. One challenging type of computer vision problem is instance-level recognition (ILR) — given an image of an object, the task is to not only determine the generic category of an object (e.g., an arch), but also the specific instance of the object (”Arc de Triomphe de l'Étoile, Paris, France”).  
Previously, ILR was tackled using deep learning approaches. First, a large set of images was collected. Then a deep model was trained to embed each image into a high-dimensional space where similar images have similar representations. Finally, the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 simple things you can do with GitHub Packages to level up your workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-04-5-simple-things-you-can-do-with-github-packages-to-level-up-your-workflows/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-04-5-simple-things-you-can-do-with-github-packages-to-level-up-your-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T16:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From hosting private packages in a private repository to tightening your security profile with GITHUB_TOKEN, here are five simple ways you can streamline your workflow with GitHub Packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey 2022: Multi-Cloud Is Working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2022-multi-cloud-is-working</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2022-multi-cloud-is-working"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-cloud approaches — and platform teams — are helping 90% of respondents achieve their goals. But watch out for challenges around security, skills, and spending.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Next: GoLand Roadmap 2022.3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=272167</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/08/04/goland-roadmap-2022-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T14:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released a new version of GoLand and are ready to share our plans for the next major update. If you haven’t yet checked out what we packed into GoLand 2022.2, here’s a brief overview. The second release brings: New quick-fixes, a bunch of code inspections, and other improvements for generics. A quick-fix for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Zharova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin API for Apache Spark v1.2: UDTs, UDFs, RDDs, Compatibility, and More!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=271568</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/08/kotlin-api-for-apache-spark-v1-2-udts-udfs-rdds-compatibility-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T14:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, Jolan here, with my first actual blog post! It’s been a couple of months since the last release of the Kotlin API for Apache Spark and we feel like all of the exciting changes since then are worth another announcement. Let me remind you what the Kotlin API for Apache Spark is and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jolan Rensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Observability guru Jonatan Ivanov on the future of observability in Spring Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/04/a-bootiful-podcast-observability-guru-jonatan-ivanov-on-the-future-of-observability-in-spring-boot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/04/a-bootiful-podcast-observability-guru-jonatan-ivanov-on-the-future-of-observability-in-spring-boot"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring observability guru Jonatan Ivanov (@jonatan_ivanov)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting for a miracle?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42434</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/705196140/0/sethsblog~Waiting-for-a-miracle/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T08:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every year, tens of thousands of people get into a famous college of their choice. It’s not unlikely that someone will get in, it’s simply not certain that you will. But someone will, so getting isn’t a miracle, it’s simply a long shot. If you add a pound a day to the leg press machine […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.15.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/04/spring-tools-4-15-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/04/spring-tools-4-15-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.15.2 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: Validation errors on @@ placeholders in YAML editor (#711)

  
(VSCode) fixed: Live process is not auto connected when app is launched in internalConsole (#794)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Cleanup / reduce verbosity of diagnostic output in Eclipse logs (#798)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Not properly disposed SWT resource was caused Spring Starter Project (#797)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: avoid live hover connection attempt when deploying app to docker without actuator (#716)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Devtools integration with boot dash docker is broken (#724)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Pause / Resume for docker boot dash malfunctions (#783)

  
(Concourse) fixed: Concourse extension (in vscode) doesn’t allow on_error in Steps (#737)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-08-03-4152-release-incl-language-servers-version-1370

Spring Tools 4.16.0 is scheduled to be released in mid September 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graviton Fast Start – A New Program to Help Move Your Workloads to AWS Graviton]]></title>
        <id>d6058242a768258e28607ce3481412188bae9244</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/graviton-fast-start-a-new-program-to-help-move-your-workloads-to-aws-graviton/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T20:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the Graviton Challenge last year, we helped customers migrate to Graviton-based EC2 instances and get up to 40 percent price performance benefit in as little as 4 days. Tens of thousands of customers, including 48 of the top 50 Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) customers, use AWS Graviton processors for their workloads. In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Efficient Multiple Visual Domain Models with Multi-path Neural Architecture Search]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/building-efficient-multiple-visual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/building-efficient-multiple-visual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T19:57:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Qifei Wang, Senior Software Engineer, and Feng Yang, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research 
Deep learning models for visual tasks (e.g., image classification) are usually trained end-to-end with data from a single visual domain (e.g., natural images or computer generated images). Typically, an application that completes visual tasks for multiple domains would need to build multiple models for each individual domain, train them independently (meaning no data is shared between domains), and then at inference time each model would process domain-specific input data. However, early layers between these models generate similar features, even for different domains, so it can be more efficient — decreasing latency and power consumption, lower memory overhead to store parameter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Sequence Modeling for On-Device ML]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/efficient-sequence-modeling-for-on.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/efficient-sequence-modeling-for-on.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Arun Kandoor, Software Engineer, Google Research  
The increasing demand for machine learning (ML) model inference on-device (for mobile devices, tablets, etc.) is driven by the rise of compute-intensive applications, the need to keep certain data on device for privacy and security reasons, and the desire to provide services when a network connection may not be available. However, on-device inference introduces a myriad of challenges, ranging from modeling to platform support requirements. These challenges relate to how different architectures are designed to optimize memory and computation, while still trying to maintain the quality of the model. From a platform perspective, the issue is identifying operations and building on top of them in a way that can generalize well across …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: July 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-03-github-availability-report-july-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-03-github-availability-report-july-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T16:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July, we experienced one incident that resulted in degraded performance for Codespaces. This report also acknowledges two incidents that impacted multiple GitHub.com services in June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Surprising Things Consul Service Mesh Can Do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/3-surprising-things-consul-service-mesh-can-do</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/3-surprising-things-consul-service-mesh-can-do"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul has evolved into a comprehensive networking platform that bolsters zero trust networking, works well with Kubernetes, and is remarkably easy to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第214話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270375685396151729</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270375685396151729"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time and focus and energy]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43493</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/704989038/0/sethsblog~Time-and-focus-and-energy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sooner or later, they’re all finite. And the way we allocate our time and emotional energy determines what gets done. If we audited your day in six-minute increments, what would we find? By the clock, how did you actually spend the time given to you (we each get the same 24 hours). How much was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continued leadership in open and transparent security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/continued-leadership-in-open-and-transparent-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/continued-leadership-in-open-and-transparent-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security has long had open source roots. Learn how we're continuing to build on that foundation today by opening a new public repo, protection-artifacts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Dufresne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continued leadership in open and transparent security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/continued-leadership-in-open-and-transparent-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/continued-leadership-in-open-and-transparent-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Security has long been open — with open source roots, open development, and the release of our SIEM in 2019. In 2020, we further embraced the openness of Elastic and released our open detection-rules repo to collaborate with our users and be transparent about how we protect customers. That repo is focused on our SIEM and Security Analytics use cases and did not yet include Elastic Endpoint Security artifacts. We continue to build on that foundation today by opening a new public repo, protections-artifacts.


In the protections-artifacts repo, you’ll find protection logic utilized by Elastic Endpoint Security to stop threats on Windows, macOS, and Linux operating systems. This includes malware behavior protection rules written in EQL as well as YARA signatures applied to both file…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Dufresne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chemtrails]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2654/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2654/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/chemtrails.png" title="Ants have reverse chemtrails--regular citizens spraying chemicals everywhere they go to control the government." alt="Ants have reverse chemtrails--regular citizens spraying chemicals everywhere they go to control the government." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Run Visual Studio Software on Amazon EC2 with User-Based License Model]]></title>
        <id>c9b4d0c62bc0acd424a612d9281c227e53c86a7c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-run-visual-studio-software-on-amazon-ec2-with-user-based-license-model/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T23:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the general availability of license-included Visual Studio software on Amazon Elastic Cloud Compute (Amazon EC2) instances. You can now purchase fully compliant AWS-provided licenses of Visual Studio with a per-user subscription fee. Amazon EC2 provides preconfigured Amazon Machine Images (AMIs) of Visual Studio Enterprise 2022 and Visual Studio Professional 2022. You […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 208 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65387</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-208-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T17:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the March announcement of the New Boards Hub, our team has collected a lot of your feedback. Thank you! We have been hard at work addressing the issues. Every week the experience gets better and better. The issues backlog is getting smaller,
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 208 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Kafka 2.9.0 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/02/spring-for-apache-kafka-2-9-0-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/02/spring-for-apache-kafka-2-9-0-available"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T16:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that Spring for Apache Kafka 2.9.0 is now available.



This version is not provided by Spring Boot dependency management, but it can be used with Boot 2.7 (or 2.6), as long as you override the Kafka dependencies to 3.2.0 as described in this appendix, especially if you are using the embedded Kafka broker.



Please see the release candidate announcement for notable changes in this release.



For information about all changes in this release, see What’s New.



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline virtual hackathon events with the new Hackathon in the Cloud Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-08-02-streamline-virtual-hackathon-events-with-the-new-hackathon-in-the-cloud-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-02-streamline-virtual-hackathon-events-with-the-new-hackathon-in-the-cloud-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T13:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attention all students! Make managing your virtual hackathon events even easier with the new Hackathon in the Cloud Experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS Skill Builder Subscriptions]]></title>
        <id>aff220b67001fae8fec9dc52e8fe845d58be9d9e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-skill-builder-subscriptions/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T10:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am excited to announce AWS Skill Builder Individual and Team subscriptions. This is a new way for you to learn about cloud technologies and get practical experience with hands-on training. Between 2013 and 2016, I spent three years delivering AWS Training classes to customers in Europe, North America, and Asia. At the time, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unavailable options]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42430</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/704782990/0/sethsblog~Unavailable-options/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T08:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“What other colors do you have that are not currently in stock?” There are always more options. If exploring them is the goal, please explore. And sometimes, the unavailable can lead to a breakthrough. But if the job is to simply get the work done, it might be worth pretending that the unexplored options don’t […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 1st, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/02/this-week-in-spring-august-1st-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/02/this-week-in-spring-august-1st-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring!

I’m still on vacation on the beautiful island of Maui, Hawaii, but I wanted to say hello (“aloha!”) and share this week’s latest roundup of all that’s good and glorious in the wide and wonderful world of Springdom.

Funny thing, today - the 2nd of August, 2022 - is also my 12-year anniversary on the Spring team. It continues to be a helluva ride, and I so look forward to all that lies ahead. Thank you, Spring team, for everything. Also, sort of coincidentally, I just got a nice promotion. (Thanks, Spring team and VMware). I’m also just about to hit 60,000 followers on Twitter. It’s been a weird, wonderful week, and not just because of all that, but because we’ve got a ton of great stuff to dive into this week (be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the best kind of cybersecurity is Open Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-the-best-kind-of-cybersecurity-is-open-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-the-best-kind-of-cybersecurity-is-open-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for a new paradigm in the world of cybersecurity. Rather than closed systems that show no signs of abating the ever-increasing cycle of vulnerability, intrusion, patch, and repeat, we propose a model of Open Security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Santosh Krishnan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is search-powered technology and why do 84% of execs say it's the key to digital transformation?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-search-powered-technology-and-why-do-84-of-execs-say-its-the-key-to-digital-transformation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-search-powered-technology-and-why-do-84-of-execs-say-its-the-key-to-digital-transformation"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Search-powered technology enables the search of data across multiple sources — a critical functionality that helps organizations drive speed, scale, and productivity in the next wave of digital transformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Radogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the best kind of cybersecurity is Open Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-the-best-kind-of-cybersecurity-is-open-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-the-best-kind-of-cybersecurity-is-open-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For too long, the idea of security in digital systems has been accompanied by another idea: secrecy. 

To have true security, some argue, the technology that provides it must be kept a secret, even from the customers who use it. Just trust us, they say — our software is constantly updated by the best developers out there. We’re monitoring for threats before anyone else knows they exist. And we patch them up before they ever create a problem for your systems. All you have to do is install our software and leave what happens on the inside of it to us.

Unfortunately, this black-box approach to security is, in an era of committed, well-resourced attackers who seek to do great harm, a huge vulnerability in itself. By closing off their code from the community, these security firms themselves …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Santosh Krishnan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is search-powered technology and why do 84% of execs say it's the key to digital transformation?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-search-powered-technology-and-why-do-84-of-execs-say-its-the-key-to-digital-transformation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-search-powered-technology-and-why-do-84-of-execs-say-its-the-key-to-digital-transformation"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We all know that too much of a good thing can quickly backfire. In today’s business world, many companies are finding that they’re hitting a tipping point in terms of data. 

Data creates the potential for informed business decisions that drive speed, productivity, and digital transformation, but not without introducing a series of challenges. Managing data across silos and disparate environments, unstructured data, and storage issues are just a few of the complications that arise from generating and collecting more data. 

So how can organizations realize the benefits of more data without becoming overwhelmed? A new global study conducted by Forrester Consulting, commissioned by Elastic, analyzed one method organizations have applied to harness the power of their data: search-powered te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Radogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M4 (codename Kilburn) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/01/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m4-codename-kilburn-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/01/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m4-codename-kilburn-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Milestone 4 (M4) of the Spring Cloud 2022.0.0 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2022.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2022.0.0 Release Train

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.

Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M4 is compatible with Spring Boot 3.0.0-M4.
Spring Cloud Stream


  
Initial version of fully reactive Kafka binder

  
Improved support for Kafka tombstone records via BiFunction

  
Spring Native improvements


Spring Cloud Config


  
Moved to AWS SDK V2 (#2111)

  
Moved from JSCH to Apache MINA (#1901)


Spring Cloud Gateway


  
Adds JSON to gRPC filter (#2657)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 1, 2022]]></title>
        <id>0f24a0fdd5f7ab793f757ad334ae2cdb84629c3b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-1-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T19:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS re:Inforce returned to Boston last week, kicking off with a keynote from Amazon Chief Security Officer Steve Schmidt and AWS Chief Information Security officer C.J. Moses: Be sure to take some time to watch this video and the other leadership sessions, and to use what you learn to take some proactive steps to improve […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Mesh — A Data Movement and Processing Platform @ Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1288bcab2873</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/data-mesh-a-data-movement-and-processing-platform-netflix-1288bcab2873?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T18:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Bo Lei, Guilherme Pires, James Shao, Kasturi Chatterjee, Sujay Jain, Vlad Sydorenko]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform (CDKTF) has reached its first GA release, adding full support for Go and providing a GitHub action to use with Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and AWS Serverless Application Repository (SAR): Speed time to actionable insights with frictionless log ingestion from Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-serverless-application-repository-speed-time-to-actionable-insights-with-frictionless-log-ingestion-from-amazon-s3</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-serverless-application-repository-speed-time-to-actionable-insights-with-frictionless-log-ingestion-from-amazon-s3"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ingest logs frictionlessly from Amazon S3 with Elastic’s new serverless forwarder available in the AWS Serverless Application Repository (SAR). Accelerate actionable insights with a unified view across your multi-cloud environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravi Kesarwani,Udayasimha Theepireddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and AWS Serverless Application Repository (SAR): Speed time to actionable insights with frictionless log ingestion from Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-serverless-application-repository-speed-time-to-actionable-insights-with-frictionless-log-ingestion-from-amazon-s3</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-serverless-application-repository-speed-time-to-actionable-insights-with-frictionless-log-ingestion-from-amazon-s3"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As companies leverage the Amazon Web Services (AWS) cloud platform and services to drive operational efficiency and bring products to market, logs are often stored in Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) then shipped to an external monitoring and analysis solution. Now AWS users can quickly ingest logs stored in Amazon S3 with the new Elastic serverless forwarder, an AWS Lambda application, and view them in the Elastic Stack alongside other logs and metrics for centralized analytics. 
Skip lengthy processes like provisioning a VM or installing data shippers — and reduce management overhead by ingesting data directly from AWS to Elastic. 
In this blog, we will teach you how to use the Elastic serverless forwarder —  that is published in the AWS Serverless Application Repository (SAR …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravi Kesarwani,Udayasimha Theepireddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peeling back the layers and understanding automation mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/peeling-back-the-layers-and-understanding-automation-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/peeling-back-the-layers-and-understanding-automation-mesh"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 features an awesome new way to scale out your automation workloads: automation mesh.  If you are unfamiliar with automation mesh, I highly recommend reading Craig Brandt’s blog post What's new: an introduction to automation mesh which outlines how automation mesh can simplify your operations and scale your automation globally.  For this blog post, I want to focus on the technical implementation of automation mesh, what network ports it is using and how you can secure it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long will this take?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42426</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/704580202/0/sethsblog~How-long-will-this-take/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That depends. Will the spec change after we begin? Are we depending on supplies or inputs from other people? Will the budget change? Is this work that has been done by anyone before? Is this work that has been done by this team before? Is finishing it fast more important than doing it well or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 tips and tricks for preparing for the Elastic Certified Engineer Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/7-tips-and-tricks-for-preparing-for-the-elastic-certified-engineer-exam</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/7-tips-and-tricks-for-preparing-for-the-elastic-certified-engineer-exam"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Certified Engineer Exam is one of several certifications available to users of Elastic products. Learn about tips and resources to help you prepare for and succeed with the exam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 tips and tricks for preparing for the Elastic Certified Engineer Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/7-tips-and-tricks-for-preparing-for-the-elastic-certified-engineer-exam</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/7-tips-and-tricks-for-preparing-for-the-elastic-certified-engineer-exam"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Gaining certifications in key technologies is a great way for developers to showcase their skills and progress in their technology careers. The Elastic Certified Engineer exam is one of several certifications that users of Elastic products can complete to flaunt their skills.

Just like back in school, preparing for certification exams can be a nerve-wracking experience — as members of our community can attest. 

As a new community advocate, I have been learning about the latest Elastic products, as well as drawing on my previous developer experience on how I would use them. Here I share tips and resources that can help set you up for success with the Elastic Certified Engineer exam.

[Related article: Becoming an Elastic Certified Engineer pays dividends]
1) Embrace using multiple conte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Omnitaur]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2653/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2653/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/omnitaur.png" title="&quot;My parents were both omnitaurs, which is how I got interested in recombination,&quot; said the normal human." alt="&quot;My parents were both omnitaurs, which is how I got interested in recombination,&quot; said the normal human." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to integrate Hibernates Multitenant feature with Spring Data JPA in a Spring Boot application]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/31/how-to-integrate-hibernates-multitenant-feature-with-spring-data-jpa-in-a-spring-boot-application</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/31/how-to-integrate-hibernates-multitenant-feature-with-spring-data-jpa-in-a-spring-boot-application"/>
        <updated>2022-07-31T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For quite some time now, Hibernate has offered a Multitenant feature.
It integrates nicely with Spring, but there is not much information about how to actually set it up, so I thought an example or two or three could help.



There is already an excellent blog article, but it is a little dated and it covers a lot of specifics to the business problems the author tried to solve.
This approach hides a little of the actual integration, which will be the focus of this article.



Do not worry about the code in this post. You can find links to the full code examples at the end of this blog post.



What Does Multitenant Mean?



Imagine you build an application. You want to host it yourself and offer the service provided by the application to multiple companies.
But the data of th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A good spec]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42409</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/704412634/0/sethsblog~A-good-spec/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-31T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you hand a good spec to three providers, you’ll get three variations back in return. The way you know your spec is worthwhile is that you can live with the differences between them. If it’s worth caring about, it’s worth writing down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Backpropagation via Local Loss Optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/enhancing-backpropagation-via-local.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/enhancing-backpropagation-via-local.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T17:02:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ehsan Amid, Research Scientist, and Rohan Anil, Principal Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
While model design and training data are key ingredients in a deep neural network’s (DNN’s) success, less-often discussed is the specific optimization method used for updating the model parameters (weights). Training DNNs involves minimizing a loss function that measures the discrepancy between the ground truth labels and the model’s predictions. Training is carried out by backpropagation, which adjusts the model weights via gradient descent steps. Gradient descent, in turn, updates the weights by using the gradient (i.e., derivative) of the loss with respect to the weights. 
The simplest weight update corresponds to stochastic gradient descent, which, in every step, moves the weights…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KNOTWEED Assessment Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/knotweed-assessment-summary</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/knotweed-assessment-summary"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KNOTWEED deploys the Subzero spyware through the use of 0-day exploits for Adobe Reader and the Windows operating system. Once initial access is gained, it uses different sections of Subzero to maintain persistence and perform actions on the host.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Pease</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KNOTWEED Assessment Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/knotweed-assessment-summary</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/knotweed-assessment-summary"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Key Takeaways

KNOTWEED is an activity group sponsored by the PSOA entity DSIRF


KNOTWEED uses 0-day exploits to load custom malware and frameworks onto victim systems


Elastic Endpoint Security prevents the execution chain of the VBA from infecting the host with spyware associated with KNOTWEED

Summary
On July 27, 2022, Microsoft Threat Intelligence Center (MSTIC) disclosed a private-sector offensive actor (PSOA) that is using 0-day exploits in targeted attacks against European and Central American victims. MSTIC and others are tracking this activity group as KNOTWEED.
PSOAs sell hacking tools, malware, exploits, and services. KNOTWEED is produced by the PSOA named DSIRF. DSIRF has been linked to the sale of a malicious toolset (among others) called Subzero which has been observed be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Pease</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marketing for maintainers: Promote your project to users and contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-28-marketing-for-maintainers-how-to-promote-your-project-to-both-users-and-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-28-marketing-for-maintainers-how-to-promote-your-project-to-both-users-and-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T17:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marketing your open source project can be intimidating, but three experts share their insider tips and tricks for how to get your hard work on the right people’s radars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Some of HashiCorp’s Talented 2022 Interns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/meet-hashicorp-2022-interns</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/meet-hashicorp-2022-interns"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six interns in HashiCorp’s Early Career Program share their expectations, highs and lows, how they’ve built relationships, and advice for future interns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Technical Sneak Peek into Camunda’s Connector Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=59035</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/a-technical-sneak-peek-into-camundas-connector-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what a connector is made of, how the code for a connector roughly looks, and how connectors can be operated in various scenarios. Since this is a preview, details are subject to change.
The post A Technical Sneak Peek into Camunda’s Connector Architecture appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Sponsors available in 30 new regions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-28-github-sponsors-available-in-30-new-regions-2/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-28-github-sponsors-available-in-30-new-regions-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Sponsors expands globally with 30 newly supported regions, bringing the total to 68.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: RabbitMQ rabbit-herder Dan Carwin]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/28/a-bootiful-podcast-rabbitmq-rabbit-herder-dan-carwin</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/28/a-bootiful-podcast-rabbitmq-rabbit-herder-dan-carwin"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to a very busy rabbit-herder on the RabbitMQ team, Dan Carwin (@dcarwin)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server Is Going 1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/28/spring-authorization-server-is-going-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/28/spring-authorization-server-is-going-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that we’ve started preparing for Spring Authorization Server 1.0 with plans to release the GA version in November 2022. It has been just over two years since we initially announced this new project, and we have come a long way since its initial development. The project has a full feature set, and the APIs have stabilized and matured over this time. A lot of effort and care was put into this project to ensure that it can grow and adapt over the next few years.



Spring Authorization Server 1.0 will be based on Spring Security 6.0, which will be based off of Spring Framework 6.0 and will require a minimum of Java 17 at runtime, as well as a minimum of Tomcat 10 or Jetty 11 (for Jakarta EE 9 compatibility). This major release will inherit the VMware Tanzu OSS su…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud OpenFeign 3.0.8 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/27/spring-cloud-openfeign-3-0-8-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/27/spring-cloud-openfeign-3-0-8-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce the Spring Cloud OpenFeign 3.0.8 is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. This version is compatible with 2020.0.6 Spring Cloud release, but it’s not included in the bom, so it has to be set up manually in project build files.
Notable Changes in the 3.0.8 Release

This is primarily a bugfix and documentation release, that backports fixes over from 3.1.x releases. The most notable backport is the Fix related to cascading Spring Data’s Page deserialisation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic enables financial services customers to react faster with data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-enables-financial-services-customers-to-react-faster-with-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-enables-financial-services-customers-to-react-faster-with-data"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic initiated a customer study through a survey managed and analyzed by Socratic Technologies. The findings show that for financial services customers, Elastic has strong quantified benefits across all solution areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.3.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Drengenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic enables financial services customers to react faster with data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-enables-financial-services-customers-to-react-faster-with-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-enables-financial-services-customers-to-react-faster-with-data"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Organizations wanting to improve their data-driven transformation need to deliver data as a strategic asset that creates value for their customers and partners. Instant visibility across data and information silos is the key.

Elastic initiated a customer study through a survey managed and analyzed by Socratic Technologies. Its purpose was to take a closer look at the problems financial services customers are solving with Elastic. The findings show that with Elastic, financial industry professionals can improve customer experiences, offer greater IT visibility, and elevate the security posture for institutions and their customers.

[Download the Results That Matter study.]

So, how are financial services institutions leveraging Elastic to better meet their goals? 
Enhancing customer and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.3.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 8.3.3 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.3.3 over the previous patch versions in 8.3.x.

For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes:
8.3.3 Release Notes
Elastic Stack

Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash

Elastic Enterprise Search

Enterprise Search

Elastic Observability

APM

Elastic Security

Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Drengenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look and Talk: Natural Conversations with Google Assistant]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/look-and-talk-natural-conversations.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/look-and-talk-natural-conversations.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T18:34:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tuan Anh Nguyen, Staff Software Engineer, Google Assistant, and Sourish Chaudhuri, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research 
In natural conversations, we don't say people's names every time we speak to each other. Instead, we rely on contextual signaling mechanisms to initiate conversations, and eye contact is often all it takes. Google Assistant, now available in more than 95 countries and over 29 languages, has primarily relied on a hotword mechanism ("Hey Google" or “OK Google”) to help more than 700 million people every month get things done across Assistant devices. As virtual assistants become an integral part of our everyday lives, we're developing ways to initiate conversations more naturally. 
At Google I/O 2022, we announced Look and Talk, a major development in our jou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for AWS Global Accelerator – Internet Protocol Version 6 (IPv6) Support]]></title>
        <id>9bec03501b8ca4c7c824bf930c12e92ad2e6bc59</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-aws-global-accelerator-internet-protocol-version-6-ipv6-support/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T18:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IPv6 adoption has consistently increased over the last few years, especially among mobile networks. The main reasons to move to IPv6 are: The limited availability of IPv4 addresses can limit the ability to scale up public-facing web and applications servers. IPv6 users from mobile networks experience better performance when their network traffic doesn’t need to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · June 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-27-release-radar-jun-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-27-release-radar-jun-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T17:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It&#8217;s been a crazy couple of months with the end of financial year and lots of products shipping. Our community has been hard at work shipping projects too. These projects can include everything from world-changing technology to developer tooling, and weekend hobbies. Here are some of these open source projects that released major updates this [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution of Service Networking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-evolution-of-service-networking</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-evolution-of-service-networking"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the journey toward a modern service-based networking solution, core workflows are needed for discovering services, securing service communications, automating networking tasks, and controlling access.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet FortiCNP – Now Available in AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>228b9e3ad02e93f0f9bad62933e4749660f6d29e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/fortinet-forticnp-now-available-in-aws-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T13:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started to talk about AWS in front of IT professionals, they would always listen intently and ask great questions. Invariably, a seasoned pro would raise there hand and ask “This all sounds great, but have you thought about security?” Of course we had, and for a while I would describe our principal […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ML-Enhanced Code Completion Improves Developer Productivity]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/ml-enhanced-code-completion-improves.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/ml-enhanced-code-completion-improves.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T20:59:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Maxim Tabachnyk, Staff Software Engineer and Stoyan Nikolov, Senior Engineering Manager, Google Research 
The increasing complexity of code poses a key challenge to productivity in software engineering. Code completion has been an essential tool that has helped mitigate this complexity in integrated development environments (IDEs). Conventionally, code completion suggestions are implemented with rule-based semantic engines (SEs), which typically have access to the full repository and understand its semantic structure. Recent research has demonstrated that large language models (e.g., Codex and PaLM) enable longer and more complex code suggestions, and as a result, useful products have emerged (e.g., Copilot). However, the question of how code completion powered by machine learnin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Azure is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Microsoft Azure is now generally available and capable of supporting production workloads running on Azure. Get started today with a secure, resilient service mesh for connecting applications running in Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for Amazon GuardDuty – Malware Protection for Amazon EBS Volumes]]></title>
        <id>2ea8dcba424be2adb64f4bd1b985f6e4e93d2055</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-amazon-guardduty-malware-detection-for-amazon-ebs-volumes/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T14:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 1st, 2022: Post updated to clarify how GuardDuty Malware Protection works with KMS keys. With Amazon GuardDuty, you can monitor your AWS accounts and workloads to detect malicious activity. Today, we are adding to GuardDuty the capability to detect malware. Malware is malicious software that is used to compromise workloads, repurpose resources, or gain […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Detective Supports Kubernetes Workloads on Amazon EKS for Security Investigations]]></title>
        <id>6277ac078919bdf2ef27a28e6d7e8244d9993147</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-detective-supports-kubernetes-workloads-on-amazon-eks-for-security-investigations/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T14:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In March 2020, we introduced Amazon Detective, a fully managed service that makes it easy to analyze, investigate, and quickly identify the root cause of potential security issues or suspicious activities. Amazon Detective continuously extracts temporal events such as login attempts, API calls, and network traffic from Amazon GuardDuty, AWS CloudTrail, and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 26th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/26/this-week-in-spring-july-26th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/26/this-week-in-spring-july-26th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, Spring fans! I’m on vacation, reporting to you from the paradise-like island of Maui, Hawaii, and hoping that you’re having a wonderful day! My family and I love Hawaii. It’s brimming with beauty and serenity, and while the island of Maui, in the state of Hawaii, is very small, the islands are humbling. They make you feel so very small. It’s surreal to sit there on the beach as the sun creeps down beyond the horizon and to realize there’s nothing but pitch black darkness and water for as far as you can see, starting just a few meters away. It’s endless. It has no end. Like the bugs in code. Endless. And humbling. 

I’ve spent so much time on the beach with my partner and our daughter that it actually feels kind of weird just to sit here at the keyboard and write out this blog! But …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – July 25, 2022]]></title>
        <id>68fcf959f2f14ba13ce1cef8a22f31dccb956bd7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-july-25-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, we hosted the first EMEA AWS Heroes Summit in Milan, Italy. This past week, I had the privilege to join the Americas AWS Heroes Summit in Seattle, Washington, USA. Meeting with our community experts is always inspiring and a great opportunity to learn from each other. During the Summit, AWS Heroes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Day 2022 – AWS for the Win!]]></title>
        <id>98646721b4ebacd2a86061013ed5679a8d425663</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-prime-day-2022-aws-for-the-win/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of my annual tradition to tell you about how AWS makes Prime Day possible, I am happy to be able to share some chart-topping metrics (check out my 2016, 2017, 2019, 2020, and 2021 posts for a look back). My purchases this year included a first aid kit, some wood brown filament for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform to Enable a Policy as Code Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-to-enable-a-policy-as-code-solution</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-to-enable-a-policy-as-code-solution"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nelson, the director of operations of a large manufacturing company, told me that he has a highly leveraged staff. That is, most of the work on the company's critical cloud project is being done by consultants and vendors, and not by their team members. Unfortunately, much of the staff’s time is spent making sure that the infrastructure as code (IaC) implementation is in compliance with the standards and policies that his company has for cloud resources. Nelson said, “Oftentimes the code works, but doesn’t conform to naming conventions, or is missing labels, or has security issues, which impacts downstream workflows and applications. We need the environment to conform to our policies, and I don’t want my staff burning cycles to ensure that this is the case.” This was the reason why he brought me in to run a proof of concept (POC). The POC would validate what would become a Policy as Code solution based on one of the common IaC products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tcoulter@redhat.com (Tim Coulter)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.0 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/25/spring-shell-2-1-0-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/25/spring-shell-2-1-0-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T07:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.0 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

Earlier this year we started an effort align the project with latest Spring Boot and Spring Framework versions as it was difficult to use existing Spring Shell release of a spring family.

Originally the main issue we wanted to address was a removal of a bean cycles which Spring Boot is now enforcing by default. While this feature can be turned off it is not something Spring Shell should require. This required a lot of changes and we chose to handle it with rework of a shell interna…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Training Generalist Agents with Multi-Game Decision Transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/training-generalist-agents-with-multi.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/training-generalist-agents-with-multi.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T22:17:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Winnie Xu, Student Researcher and Kuang-Huei Lee, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
Current deep reinforcement learning (RL) methods can train specialist artificial agents that excel at decision-making on various individual tasks in specific environments, such as Go or StarCraft. However, little progress has been made to extend these results to generalist agents that would not only be capable of performing many different tasks, but also upon a variety of environments with potentially distinct embodiments. 
Looking across recent progress in the fields of natural language processing, vision, and generative models (such as PaLM, Imagen, and Flamingo), we see that breakthroughs in making general-purpose models are often achieved by scaling up Transformer-based models an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formulating ‘Out of Memory Kill’ Prediction on the Netflix App as a Machine Learning Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/989599029109</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/formulating-out-of-memory-kill-prediction-on-the-netflix-app-as-a-machine-learning-problem-989599029109?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T21:16:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Aryan Mehra,  with Farnaz Karimdady Sharifabad, Prasanna Vijayanathan, Chaïna Wade, Vishal Sharma and Mike Schassberger]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Sent an AWS Snowcone into Orbit]]></title>
        <id>d05b293512d0481393cd06a097706cb42601bfa4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-we-sent-an-aws-snowcone-into-orbit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T18:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been a fan of space travel and the US space program since I was 4 or 5 years old. I remember reading about the Mercury and Gemini programs, and watched with excitement as Lunar Module Eagle landed on the Moon. Today, with the cost to reach Low Earth Orbit (LEO) seemingly declining with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Process Orchestration Needs Advanced Workflow Patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58811</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/why-process-orchestration-needs-advanced-workflow-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life is seldom a straight line, and the same is true for processes. Therefore, you must be able to accurately express all the things happening in your business processes for proper end-to-end process orchestration. This requires workflow patterns that go beyond basic control flow patterns (like sequence or condition). If your orchestration tool does not provide those advanced workflow patterns, you will experience confusion amongst developers, you will need to implement time-consuming workarounds, and you will end up with confusing models. Let’s explore this by examining an example of why these advanced workflow patterns matter in today’s blog post. Initial process example Let’s assume you’re processing incoming orders of hand-crafted goods to be shipped individually. Each order consists of many...
The post Why Process Orchestration Needs Advanced Workflow Patterns appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-M4 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-3-0-0-m4-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-3-0-0-m4-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T11:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-M4 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 161 enhancements, documentation improvements, dependency upgrades, and bug fixes. Notable new features include:


  
Support for Elasticsearch’s new Java client

  
Support for Flyway 9

  
Support for Hibernate 6.1


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-2-7-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-2-7-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T10:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.2 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 40 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud and Spring Cloud Kubernetes contributor Ryan Baxter]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-and-spring-cloud-kubernetes-contributor-ryan-baxter</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-and-spring-cloud-kubernetes-contributor-ryan-baxter"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to a person who knows more than most about the awesome implications of both the words “Spring” and “Cloud,” Spring Cloud Kubernetes lead Ryan Baxter (@ryanjbaxter).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.10 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-2-6-10-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/21/spring-boot-2-6-10-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T08:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.10 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 30 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.0-M4 available now!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-batch-5-0-0-m4-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-batch-5-0-0-m4-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T19:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M4 is now available from our milestone repository.

This fourth milestone introduces several improvements for Java Records support. It also comes with a number of enhancements, bug fixes, dependency upgrades, and documentation updates. For more details about all the changes, see the release notes.
Java Records Support Improvement

The support for Java records as items in a chunk-oriented step was initially introduced in v4.3, but that support was limited, due to the fact that v4 has Java 8 as a baseline. In Java 8, records were not even in preview yet. That initial support was based on reflection tricks to create Java records and populate them with data, without having access to the j…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-for-graphql-1-0-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-for-graphql-1-0-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of everyone involved, I’m pleased to announce the first maintenance release of Spring for GraphQL, it is now available from Maven Central. This version will be shipped with Spring Boot 2.7.2.

This release includes 10 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-graphql tag.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cribl, MongoDB, and Thales Highlight New HCP and Enterprise Vault Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cribl-mongodb-thales-highlight-new-hcp-enterprise-vault-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cribl-mongodb-thales-highlight-new-hcp-enterprise-vault-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Vault ecosystem continues to show strong growth with 12 new HCP, Enterprise, and OSS integrations added this quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第213話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270375685361384268</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270375685361384268"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Cloud Automation with amazon.aws 4.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-4.0.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-4.0.0"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post goes through what has changed and highlights what’s new in the 4.0.0 release of this Content Collection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Kubernetes Native Java (Redux, 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-tips-kubernetes-native-java-redux-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/20/spring-tips-kubernetes-native-java-redux-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) looks at some of the amazing opportunities for building Spring Boot applications intended for production in Kubernetes in mid 2022. 

The code, as usual, is available on the spring-tips Github organization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 R6a Instances Powered by 3rd Gen AMD EPYC Processors for Memory-Intensive Workloads]]></title>
        <id>644f029ceb1ef3d47149b3db6e5a0d485f62f874</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-r6a-instances-powered-by-3rd-gen-amd-epyc-processors-for-memory-intensive-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T22:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched the general-purpose Amazon EC2 M6a instances at AWS re:Invent 2021 and compute-intensive C6a instances in February of this year. These instances are powered by the 3rd Gen AMD EPYC processors running at frequencies up to 3.6 GHz to offer up to 35 percent better price performance versus the previous generation instances. Today, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplified Transfer Learning for Chest Radiography Model Development]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/simplified-transfer-learning-for-chest.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/simplified-transfer-learning-for-chest.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Akib Uddin, Product Manager and Andrew Sellergren, Software Engineer, Google Health 
Every year, nearly a billion chest X-ray (CXR) images are taken globally to aid in the detection and management of health conditions ranging from collapsed lungs to infectious diseases. Generally, CXRs are cheaper and more accessible than other forms of medical imaging. However, existing challenges continue to impede the optimal use of CXRs. For example, in some areas, trained radiologists that can accurately interpret CXR images are in short supply. In addition, interpretation variability between experts, workflow differences between institutions, and the presence of rare conditions familiar only to subspecialists all contribute to making high-quality CXR interpretation a challenge. 
 Recent res…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring Azure Application Gateway with Consul-Terraform-Sync]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/configuring-azure-application-gateway-with-consul-terraform-sync</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/configuring-azure-application-gateway-with-consul-terraform-sync"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synchronize HCP Consul services as backend address pools for Microsoft Azure Application Gateway using Consul-Terraform-Sync (CTS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 19th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/19/this-week-in-spring-july-19th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/19/this-week-in-spring-july-19th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! This week I’m trying to wind down some threads and take some vacation with my family. It’s going to be an amazing time, indeed! But that doesn’t stop the deluge of novelties and news in the wide world of Springdom, so we’ve got a lot to cover this week. Let’s get to it!

Before I go, though, I have a new “Spring Tips” episode dropping Wednesday morning, at midnight, so be on the look out :) 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Nate Schutta: The Thinking Person’s Architect, My Friend, and Teammate

  
Blog: Kubernetes Gateway API Graduates to Beta

  
JWT Authentication with OAuth2 Resource Server and an external Authorization Server

  
Kotlin & Spring Boot: Building a Rest API

  
Release v1.5.1 · toedter/spring-hateoas-jsonapi

  
Spring Boot – Keycloak Integration Testing with Testcontainers

  
Spring Boot – Testing Redis With Testcontainers

  
Spring Data 2022.0.0-M5 2021.2.2 and 2021.1.6 released

  
Spring Data Rest – Serializing the Entity ID

  
Spring Framework 6.0.0-M5 and 5.3.22 available now

  
Spring Native 0.12.1 available now

  
Spring Security 5.8.0-M1 and 6.0.0-M6 are released

  
Spring Tips: Kubernetes Native Java (Redux, 2022)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ICML 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/google-at-icml-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/google-at-icml-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:54:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cat Armato, Program Manager, University Relations 
Google is a leader in machine learning (ML) research with groups innovating across virtually all aspects of the field, from theory to application. We build machine learning systems to solve deep scientific and engineering challenges in areas of language, music, visual processing, algorithm development, and more. Core to our approach is to actively engage with the broader research community by open-sourcing datasets and models, publishing our discoveries, and actively participating in leading conferences. 
Google is proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of the thirty-ninth International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML 2022), a premier annual conference, which is being held this week in Baltimore, Maryland. Google has a strong presenc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recruiting for Early Careers at HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/recruiting-for-early-careers-at-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/recruiting-for-early-careers-at-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second year of HashiCorp’s Early Career Program includes some 70 interns. The Early Career recruiting team shares details and offers tips for prospective candidates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – July 18, 2022]]></title>
        <id>0d85312f4833bb666f3613acb995ab332f610620</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-july-18-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, AWS Summit New York was held in person at the Javits Center with thousands of attendees and over 100 sponsors and partners. During the keynote, Martin Beeby, AWS Principal Developer Advocate, talked about how innovations in cloud infrastructure enable customers to adapt to challenges and seize new opportunities. It included Liz Fong-Jones‘s great […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Boards Summer Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64636</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-boards-summer-update-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over these last few months, our team has been working hard at delivering new value in Azure Boards. We would like to take a moment to highlight some of the most recently released features. Be sure to check out the Features Timeline for updates and our product roadmap.
The post Azure Boards Summer Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards Reliability in Deep Learning Systems]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/towards-reliability-in-deep-learning.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/towards-reliability-in-deep-learning.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T17:07:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dustin Tran and Balaji Lakshminarayanan, Research Scientists, Google Research 
Deep learning models have made impressive progress in vision, language, and other modalities, particularly with the rise of large-scale pre-training. Such models are most accurate when applied to test data drawn from the same distribution as their training set. However, in practice, the data confronting models in real-world settings rarely match the training distribution. In addition, the models may not be well-suited for applications where predictive performance is only part of the equation. For models to be reliable in deployment, they must be able to accommodate shifts in data distribution and make useful decisions in a broad array of scenarios.  
In “Plex: Towards Reliability Using Pre-trained Larg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Azure Stack Hub Provider 1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-azure-stack-hub-provider-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-azure-stack-hub-provider-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new HashiCorp Terraform Azure Stack provider 1.0 includes several provider behavior improvements, 19 new resources, and supports a new service for Key Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Wins Microsoft Azure OSS US Partner of the Year for 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-microsoft-azure-oss-us-partner-of-the-year-for-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-wins-microsoft-azure-oss-us-partner-of-the-year-for-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp has been chosen as the 2022 Microsoft US (MSUS) Partner Award winner OSS on Azure and a 2022 Microsoft OSS on Azure Partner of the Year Award finalist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rewriting Image Captions for Visual Question Answering Data Creation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/rewriting-image-captions-for-visual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/rewriting-image-captions-for-visual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T19:24:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Soravit Beer Changpinyo and Doron Kukliansky‎, Senior Software Engineers, Google Research 
Visual Question Answering (VQA) is a useful machine learning (ML) task that requires a model to answer a visual question about an image. What makes it challenging is its multi-task and open-ended nature; it involves solving multiple technical research questions in computer vision and natural language understanding simultaneously. Yet, progress on this task would enable a wide range of applications, from assisting the blind and the visually-impaired or communicating with robots to enhancing the user’s visual experience with external knowledge. 
Effective and robust VQA systems cannot exist without high-quality, semantically and stylistically diverse large-scale training data of image-questio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When localhost isn't what it seems in Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/when-localhost-isnt-what-it-seems-in-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/when-localhost-isnt-what-it-seems-in-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2  and the advent of automation execution environments, some behaviors are now different for. This blog explains the use case around using localhost and options for sharing data and persistent data storage, for VM-based Ansible Automation Platform 2  deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Gruner + Jahr Chose Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58130</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/why-gruner-jahr-chose-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new blog series, we explore the reasons why customers are migrating to Camunda 8. For our first installment of Why Camunda 8, we talked to Gruner + Jahr, one of the largest premium magazine publishers in Europe. G+J includes such established (German) print and digital brands as STERN, GEO, BRIGITTE, ESSEN & TRINKEN, and SCHÖNER WOHNEN, as well as younger brands such as CHEFKOCH, BARBARA, BEEF, 11FREUNDE. In addition to the numerous print and digital media offerings, G+J offers products and licenses such as the SCHÖNER WOHNEN collection. The digital business contributes more than half of revenues and is exhibiting continued strong growth. Indeed, the company’s digital products lead the rankings in all publishing segments, from news through...
The post Why Gruner + Jahr Chose Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Schroth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Content archived for Azure DevOps previous versions]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64684</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/content-archived-for-azure-devops-previous-versions/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T21:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​In April of this year, we completed a major project to archive older versions of our content. 
The post Content archived for Azure DevOps previous versions appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[July patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64626</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/july-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T18:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
In Test Runs APIs, the continuation token being returned was greater than the “maxLastUpdatedDate” value that was specified.
The post July patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisiting Mask Transformer from a Clustering Perspective]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/revisiting-mask-transformer-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/revisiting-mask-transformer-from.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Qihang Yu, Student Researcher, and Liang-Chieh Chen, Research Scientist, Google Research 
Panoptic segmentation is a computer vision problem that serves as a core task for many real-world applications. Due to its complexity, previous work often divides panoptic segmentation into semantic segmentation (assigning semantic labels, such as “person” and “sky”, to every pixel in an image) and instance segmentation (identifying and segmenting only countable objects, such as “pedestrians” and “cars”, in an image), and further divides it into several sub-tasks. Each sub-task is processed individually, and extra modules are applied to merge the results from each sub-task stage. This process is not only complex, but it also introduces many hand-designed priors when processing sub-tasks and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Detect and Resolve Issues Quickly with Log Anomaly Detection and Recommendations from Amazon DevOps Guru]]></title>
        <id>f8f3e67b2d22e5494e1d6a32842aa2c9ac55f021</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-detect-and-resolve-issues-quickly-with-log-anomaly-detection-and-recommendations-from-amazon-devops-guru/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T15:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing a new feature, Log Anomaly Detection and Recommendations for Amazon DevOps Guru. With this feature, you can find anomalies throughout relevant logs within your app, and get targeted recommendations to resolve issues. Here’s a quick look at this feature: AWS launched DevOps Guru, a fully managed AIOps platform service, in December […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift Serverless – Now Generally Available with New Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>ab73365aa62a13a08dcff00f5a2037ca5ae573ee</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-redshift-serverless-now-generally-available-with-new-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T15:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year at re:Invent, we introduced the preview of Amazon Redshift Serverless, a serverless option of Amazon Redshift that lets you analyze data at any scale without having to manage data warehouse infrastructure. You just need to load and query your data, and you pay only for what you use. This allows more companies to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Cloud WAN : A Managed WAN Service]]></title>
        <id>e70e25bfbed198650cc3b5bd252108ee9fcb14b5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-cloud-wan-a-managed-wan-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T14:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update July 13, 2022 – we have added a list of blog posts and technical resources provided by our partners, in order to provide readers with additional information on this service. I am pleased to announce the availability of AWS Cloud WAN, a new network service that makes it easy to build and operate wide […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58431</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-platform-8-1-0-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3. If you’d like to get started with Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3 right away, you can sign up for a free trial now. Create Process Instance Starting at User-Defined Elements An often requested feature is now available as a preview with Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3: create a process instance starting at user-defined elements. When creating a process instance through the CreateProcessInstance RPC, the process instance is started at the default none start event. For testing purposes, you may want to start at one (or multiple) of the other elements. This feature is now available through both the CreateProcessInstance RPC and the CreateProcessInstanceWithResult RPC. It is available for use in the Zeebe Java client...
The post Camunda Platform 8.1.0-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58439</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-preview1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1. Camunda Optimize provides business activity monitoring for workflows, supporting continuous process improvement by providing transparency into your automated workflows and decisions. Business-friendly reports, dashboards, and alerts make it possible to identify process bottlenecks, improve end-to-end processes, and evaluate the success of your process automation initiative. If you’re a user of Camunda 7 – Enterprise Edition, you can download the Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 release right away with your customer credentials. If not, start your free 30-day trial of Camunda Platform 8, which includes Optimize. What’s New? Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 makes the process overview more readable, introduces one-click collection and dashboard creation, and provides an advanced look at a feature that lets you...
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-preview1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58401</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-desktop-modeler-5-1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce the release of Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.1. This release focuses on providing a smooth and intuitive modeling experience through several minor and major enhancements, such as the new multi-select context pad.
The post Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Modeler Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=58296</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/07/camunda-automation-platform-7-18-0-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.18. 
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – July 11, 2022]]></title>
        <id>29f6affb960d165cfdeb50c0f58bea5e4ec5c744</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-july-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T18:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! In France, we know summer has started when you see the Tour de France bike race on TV or in a city nearby. This year, the tour stopped in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>