<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-02-26T01:06:22.584Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-02-26T01:06:22.584Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul-Terraform-Sync 0.5 Adds New APIs and UX Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-terraform-sync-0-5-adds-new-apis-and-ux-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-terraform-sync-0-5-adds-new-apis-and-ux-improvements"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul-Terraform-Sync (CTS) 0.5 adds improvements to task lifecycle management and new ecosystem integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Voices: How the Blacksmiths ERG Supports the Community]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-voices-how-the-blacksmiths-erg-supports-the-community</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-voices-how-the-blacksmiths-erg-supports-the-community"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three members of HashiCorp’s Blacksmiths ERG talk about the outside projects they’re working on to support their communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Additional Checksum Algorithms for Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>c087e4b8f683c9847a7242660d3729c6a4fb3a22</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-additional-checksum-algorithms-for-amazon-s3/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T16:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) is designed to provide 99.999999999% (11 9s) of durability for your objects and for the metadata associated with your objects. You can rest assured that S3 stores exactly what you PUT, and returns exactly what is stored when you GET. In order to make sure that the object is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.0-M3 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/25/spring-shell-2-1-0-m3-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/25/spring-shell-2-1-0-m3-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T14:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.0-M3 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

Notable changes include:


  
Usual small fixes

  
UI Component model




Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.25.02 are here!]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63512</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-azuredevops-community-for-2022-25-02/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T13:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! I am April Edwards and every week I try to bring you the latest updates from around the DevOps on Azure community. If you have a post you’d like to have me include, I am always listening. You can reach out on Twitter or LinkedIn and I will be sure to share your latest post with the community.
The post Top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.25.02 are here! appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common pitfalls and myths of the new economy]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42260</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/683568488/0/sethsblog~Common-pitfalls-and-myths-of-the-new-economy/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not high school. But some of the advice that people are embracing reminds us of those days… Things that everyone tells you that aren’t true: It’s possible to get rich quickly without taking risks (not really) Just because someone bought some crazy dog currency or NFT and got lucky doesn’t mean that you will. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: InfoQ editor and Java Champion, Dr. Alex Blewitt]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/a-bootiful-podcast-infoq-editor-and-java-champion-dr-alex-blewitt</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/a-bootiful-podcast-infoq-editor-and-java-champion-dr-alex-blewitt"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to InfoQ editor and contributor, fellow Java Champion, and an all-around amazing human being Dr. Alex Blewitt.


  
the creator of bash, readline, etc.: Brian Fox

  
Reload4j is the version which has Log4j 1.x compatibility with CVEs fixed 

  
Alex’s blog  and speaker deck

  
Magic number (programming) - Wikipedia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-7-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-7-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T21:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0-M2 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 137 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Test slices for Couchbase and Elasticsearch

  
Enhancements to auto-configuration registration and ordering

  
Support for OkHttp4


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests. 
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Consul API Gateway has now reached its first GA release, adding TCPRoute support, Helm chart support, and a new HashiCorp Learn tutorial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce Provider for HashiCorp Terraform Now in Tech Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/salesforce-provider-for-hashicorp-terraform-now-in-tech-preview</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/salesforce-provider-for-hashicorp-terraform-now-in-tech-preview"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Salesforce users, roles, and profiles with HashiCorp Terraform using the new Salesforce provider — now in tech preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s in Your Hyperautomation Tech Stack?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=41879</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/whats-in-your-hyperautomation-tech-stack/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As much as we’d all like to operate at the automation levels of an organization like Amazon, most organizations are relatively early in their process automation maturity journey. That’s where a universal process orchestrator like the Camunda Platform comes in.
The post What’s in Your Hyperautomation Tech Stack? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.4 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-6-4-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-6-4-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.4 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 61 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and AWS: Seamlessly ingest logs and metrics into a unified platform with ready-to-use integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-seamlessly-ingest-logs-and-metrics-into-a-unified-platform-with-ready-to-use-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-seamlessly-ingest-logs-and-metrics-into-a-unified-platform-with-ready-to-use-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and AWS offer integrations that streamline data ingestion across AWS services into a unified platform so organizations can monitor, analyze, and protect their environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uday Theepireddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and AWS: Seamlessly ingest logs and metrics into a unified platform with ready-to-use integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-seamlessly-ingest-logs-and-metrics-into-a-unified-platform-with-ready-to-use-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-aws-seamlessly-ingest-logs-and-metrics-into-a-unified-platform-with-ready-to-use-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Many organizations are using Amazon Web Services (AWS) for agility and cost-efficiency benefits.  As you quickly spin-up applications, instances, and containers  it is critical to be able maintain a comprehensive view of operations across your environment and  ingest data from different sources in real-time. 

Elastic and AWS are working together to bring you a single unified platform that allows you to monitor, analyze, secure and protect your AWS and on-premises data sets. As AWS continues to expand, Elastic continues to add product integrations with AWS to streamline data ingestion and simplify the path to actionable insights.
With 23 out-of-the-box integrations for AWS services and more under development, DevOps and security experts can seamlessly ship AWS logs, metrics, and events i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uday Theepireddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.10 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-5-10-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/24/spring-boot-2-5-10-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T11:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.10 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 52 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be careful what you wish for]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40545</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/683455330/0/sethsblog~Be-careful-what-you-wish-for/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T10:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might not get it. But as you pursue this wish, you’ll change what you do, what you see, who you connect with and the sacrifices you make along the way. Our wishes change us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 factors to consider when migrating Elastic to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-factors-to-consider-when-migrating-elastic-to-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-factors-to-consider-when-migrating-elastic-to-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Elastic addresses these five key factors —business continuity during migration, total cost of ownership optimization, disaster recovery, compliance, and security — to ensure your smooth transition to the cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How visualization tools can unlock the potential of a truly data-driven organization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-visualization-tools-can-unlock-the-potential-of-a-truly-data-driven-organization</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-visualization-tools-can-unlock-the-potential-of-a-truly-data-driven-organization"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest generation of data viz brings together teams and data sources to surface insights or risks to improve business results]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Null, journalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 factors to consider when migrating Elastic to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-factors-to-consider-when-migrating-elastic-to-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-factors-to-consider-when-migrating-elastic-to-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As organizations continue migrating to the cloud to benefit from a flexible, affordable and scalable infrastructure, they need to examine all the interdependencies and consider several factors to ensure a smooth transition.
When you migrate your Elastic workloads to the cloud, you should take several factors into consideration so you can maximize your investments and minimize disruption — business continuity during migration, total cost of ownership optimization, disaster recovery, compliance, and security. Read on to learn more about the five factors to consider when moving Elastic workloads to the cloud and the ways that you can address them. 
Business continuity for Elastic workloads during migration
Cloud migration does not happen overnight, in fact, according to a report from McKins…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How visualization tools can unlock the potential of a truly data-driven organization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-visualization-tools-can-unlock-the-potential-of-a-truly-data-driven-organization</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-visualization-tools-can-unlock-the-potential-of-a-truly-data-driven-organization"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Leading a data-driven organization is table stakes when it comes to competing in the cloud era. But the way that executives choose to set that table — and where that data comes from — differentiates leaders from laggards. 
Data-visualization tools, especially when they’re built-in to the systems that IT teams are already using and can pull from all their various clouds and sources, make data more accessible and actionable to practitioners, shareable to business teams, and insightful for organizational leadership. In other words, data visualization can define whether your organization is actually data-driven. 
“Most companies are data companies now and want to be thought of that way,” says Scott Berinato, a senior editor at Harvard Business Review and author of Good Charts: The HBR Guide …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Null, journalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 4.3.5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-batch-4-3-5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-batch-4-3-5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T21:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 4.3.5 has been released to Maven Central repository. This patch release comes with a number of bug fixes, enhancements and dependency updates. You can find the complete change logs here: 4.3.5.

I would like to thank all contributors who had a role in this release!

Spring Batch Home | Source on Github | Reference Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4D-Net: Learning Multi-Modal Alignment for 3D and Image Inputs in Time]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/4d-net-learning-multi-modal-alignment.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/4d-net-learning-multi-modal-alignment.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T20:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by AJ Piergiovanni and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research 
While not immediately obvious, all of us experience the world in four dimensions (4D). For example, when walking or driving down the street we observe a stream of visual inputs, snapshots of the 3D world, which, when taken together in time, creates a 4D visual input. Today’s autonomous vehicles and robots are able to capture much of this information through various onboard sensing mechanisms, such as LiDAR and cameras. 
 LiDAR is a ubiquitous sensor that uses light pulses to reliably measure the 3D coordinates of objects in a scene, however, it is also sparse and has a limited range — the farther one is from a sensor, the fewer points will be returned. This means that far-away objects might only get a hand…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new way to understand your GitHub-hosted runner capacity]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-23-new-way-understand-github-hosted-runner-capacity/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-23-new-way-understand-github-hosted-runner-capacity/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T19:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore and understand your overall GitHub-hosted Actions runner capacity with the new runner view.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codespaces for the largest repositories just got faster]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-23-codespaces-largest-repositories-faster/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-23-codespaces-largest-repositories-faster/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T18:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ability to prebuild codespaces is entering public beta. Enable fast environment creation times, regardless of the size and complexity of your repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 68 – Progressive Delivery with @SplitSoftware and @AzureDevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63499</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-68-progressive-delivery-with-splitsoftware-and-azuredevops/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T16:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 68 – Progressive Delivery with @SplitSoftware and @AzureDevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第204話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496777629727</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496777629727"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge Automation with NetGitOps on Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/edge-automation-with-netgitops-on-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/edge-automation-with-netgitops-on-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network edge automation challenges 
 
As organizations grow and expand geographi cally, they start extending their IT infrastructure into the distributed and far edge layers through opening new branch offices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paulo Seguel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Session 2021.0.5 and 2021.1.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-session-2021-0-5-and-2021-1-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-session-2021-0-5-and-2021-1-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Session 2021.0.5 and 2021.1.2. These releases deliver bug fixes and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot will pick up these artifacts with its upcoming releases.

The following modules were updated as part of 2021.0.5:


  
Spring Session Core 2.5.5 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 2.5.5 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 2.5.5 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 2.5.5 - release notes


The following modules were updated as part of 2021.1.2:


  
Spring Session Core 2.6.2 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 2.6.2 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 2.6.2 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 2.6.2 - release notes

  
Spring Session MongoDB 2.6.2 - release notes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A little more or a little less]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41512</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/683324456/0/sethsblog~A-little-more-or-a-little-less/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T10:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The producer of a successful product has a choice to make. If you put a little less in the box, people will run out sooner and have to buy more. If you give people a little more for their money, they’ll purchase less often, but become more loyal. It turns out that in most markets […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: easy IOT integration with HiveMQ, Spring Integration MQTT, and Spring Native]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-tips-easy-iot-integration-with-hivemq-spring-integration-mqtt-and-spring-native</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/23/spring-tips-easy-iot-integration-with-hivemq-spring-integration-mqtt-and-spring-native"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment I’m joined by my friend, fellow Java Champion, and Developer Advocate at HiveMQ, Mary Grygleski (@mgrygles), and we look at easy Internet of Things (IOT) integration with HiveMQ, Spring Integration MQTT, Spring Boot, and Spring Native]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - 22/2/22]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/22/this-week-in-spring-22-2-22</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/22/this-week-in-spring-22-2-22"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T06:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you? I’m doing alright, thank you! I’m really excited about this week, too, because it features a ton of cool stuff. Also, it’s 22/2/22! And I posted this at 22:22! :D


  
Spring Tips: Spring Native and MyBatis

  
A Bootiful Podcast: Java team luminary Sharat Chander

  
Announcing ListCrudRepository and Friends for Spring Data 3.0

  
Azure Spring Cloud Enterprise is now available in preview

  
Matt Raible on Twitter talking about getting a full JHipster application working with Spring Native :-) 

  
I worked with the folks behind the Flowable BPMN workflow engine and helped them get their Spring Boot integration working in Spring Native. They wrote about the whole thing in this wonderful blog, Runn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rounding]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2585/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2585/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/rounding.png" title="I've developed a novel propulsion system powered by loss of precision in unit conversion." alt="I've developed a novel propulsion system powered by loss of precision in unit conversion." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Region Replication Now Available with HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multi-region-replication-now-available-with-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/multi-region-replication-now-available-with-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New HCP Vault Plus Clusters adds high availability replication of secrets and policies across cloud regions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with ease using security workflows!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-22-get-started-using-security-workflows/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-22-get-started-using-security-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T17:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions workflows in the Security category will now appear among the workflow recommendations based on a repository's content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Glue Code without Java Delegates in Camunda Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=43978</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/how-to-write-glue-code-without-java-delegates-in-camunda-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T17:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the benefits of external tasks in Camunda Cloud and how you can still call your service endpoints via any protocol.
The post How to Write Glue Code without Java Delegates in Camunda Cloud appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Advisory Database now open to community contributions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-22-github-advisory-database-now-open-to-community-contributions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-22-github-advisory-database-now-open-to-community-contributions/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T17:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone can now provide additional information to further the community’s understanding and awareness of security advisories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A second opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40558</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/683199344/0/sethsblog~A-second-opinion/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend is selling his house. Apparently, real estate brokers now have a way of reporting the comments (reviews) from potential buyers at open houses, and he was crazy enough to read them. Of course, this is incredibly unhelpful. He can’t rebuild his house to sell it. Hearing that people don’t like his custom cabinets […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing ListCrudRepository & Friends for Spring Data 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/22/announcing-listcrudrepository-friends-for-spring-data-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/22/announcing-listcrudrepository-friends-for-spring-data-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T09:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spring Data CrudRepository has various methods that return multiple instances of the entity managed by the repository.
It does so by using Iterable and not List, as one might expect.
In many cases, that is of no consequence, since you typically want to iterate over the result anyway.
However, you might occasionally prefer a List. In these cases, Iterable is annoying.



I will write more about why that choice was made in the first place and how you can deal with it as long as you are on Spring Data 2.x. However, let me get the good news out first:



Repositories returning Lists



Spring Data 3.0.0-M2 now offers a ListCrudRepository,
which returns a List where CrudRepository returns an Iterable.



Example 1. CrudRepository versus ListCrudRepository




@NoReposito…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dbt® deeper concepts: materialization]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=big-data-tools&amp;p=231334</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/big-data-tools/2022/02/22/dbt-deeper-concepts-materialization/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T07:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of this blog series, I described basic dbt® concepts such as installation, creation of views, and describing models. I could have stopped there, but indeed, there are some drawbacks to only using views to build the whole transformation layer in our database. Sometimes we don’t really need to use a view […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pasha Finkelshteyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observability: A Swiss Army knife for success in the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-a-swiss-army-knife-for-success-in-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-a-swiss-army-knife-for-success-in-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the cloud era, this rising capability can make digital experiences more reliable, innovative and profitable]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Palmquist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four ways to get the most out of cloud data storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/four-ways-to-get-the-most-out-of-cloud-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/four-ways-to-get-the-most-out-of-cloud-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Storing enterprise data in the cloud can reduce costs and boost productivity—especially if you follow these guidelines]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observability: A Swiss Army knife for success in the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-a-swiss-army-knife-for-success-in-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-a-swiss-army-knife-for-success-in-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
When a kid gets a Swiss Army knife, she can suddenly accomplish more tasks more quickly — from whittling a stick to mending clothes to any job requiring a plastic toothpick. Observability, one of the hottest trends in IT, gives a growing number of IT organizations a similar empowered feeling: an ability to improve their systems and applications in a multiplicity of ways.
Observability is a software layer that can be built into a company’s IT infrastructure to better understand the performance of its systems and applications, including ones running in the cloud. Observability tools gather data from a multiplicity of sources to generate insights that were not previously possible. As a result, IT teams can spend less time hunting for needles in digital haystacks when problems arise and can …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Palmquist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four ways to get the most out of cloud data storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/four-ways-to-get-the-most-out-of-cloud-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/four-ways-to-get-the-most-out-of-cloud-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,Cloud data services make a seductive promise to CIOs and CISOs: All your enterprise data is available any time from anywhere, and you can search, run queries, and perform sophisticated analytics without the headaches and costs of maintaining your own data infrastructure. 

Pulling that off, however, depends on how and where you store your data. To make the right calls, CIOs must consider a number of factors tied to a company’s business needs, application demands, and resources.
As more companies accelerate their investment in the cloud — today, roughly half of all corporate data is stored there — many are under pressure to develop a clear framework and strategy for making those decisions. 
Here are a few recommendations that can help guide the process.
1. Consider the right PACE for core …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.0-M2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/21/spring-security-5-7-0-m2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/21/spring-security-5-7-0-m2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T15:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce the release of Spring Security 5.7.0-M2.



You can find the complete list of dependency updates, bug fixes and enhancements in the release notes.



Among the enhancements you will find we have deprecated the WebSecurityConfigurerAdapter. For additional details you can check out this blog post on the future of Spring Security without the WebSecurityConfigurerAdapter.



We look forward to hearing your feedback.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.5.5 and 5.6.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/21/spring-security-5-5-5-and-5-6-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/21/spring-security-5-5-5-and-5-6-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Security 5.5.5 (release notes) and Spring Security 5.6.2 (release notes). These releases deliver bug fixes along with some minor improvements. Users are encouraged to update to the latest patch release.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security without the WebSecurityConfigurerAdapter]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/21/spring-security-without-the-websecurityconfigureradapter</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/21/spring-security-without-the-websecurityconfigureradapter"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Spring Security 5.7.0-M2 we deprecated the WebSecurityConfigurerAdapter, as we encourage users to move towards a component-based security configuration.

To assist with the transition to this new style of configuration, we have compiled a list of common use-cases and the suggested alternatives going forward.

In the examples below we follow best practice by using the Spring Security lambda DSL and the method HttpSecurity#authorizeHttpRequests to define our authorization rules. If you are new to the lambda DSL you can read about it in this blog post. If you would like to learn more about why we choose to use HttpSecurity#authorizeHttpRequests you can check out the reference documentation.
Configuring HttpSecurity

In Spring Security 5.4 we introduced the ability to configure HttpSecur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five ways to get started with network automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/five-ways-to-get-started-with-network-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/five-ways-to-get-started-with-network-automation"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many of you know, Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform is a highly flexible IT automation platform that can automate your Linux and Windows instances, your VMware private cloud, your AWS, Azure or Google public cloud, and even your security infrastructure.  Today I want to write about one of my favorite use-cases; using Ansible Automation Platform for network automation. It provides easy, highly customizable automation for your routers and switches so you can automate them just like any other IT infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sales and the story of money]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41493</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/683077539/0/sethsblog~Sales-and-the-story-of-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T10:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Twenty-four ninety-five.” I was on the phone hearing a pitch for a service I needed. I had reached out to a recommended vendor, and was now sitting through a pitch from a salesperson who had a script but no listening skills. I had figured that the service was probably $300 if I shopped around, but […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Windows UAC bypasses: Techniques and detection strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/exploring-windows-uac-bypasses-techniques-and-detection-strategies</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/exploring-windows-uac-bypasses-techniques-and-detection-strategies"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Security Research team has identified new detection strategies to overcome the bypass methodologies used by adversaries to silently deploy malware onto an endpoint and elevate privileges without the end-user knowing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Windows UAC bypasses: Techniques and detection strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/exploring-windows-uac-bypasses-techniques-and-detection-strategies</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/exploring-windows-uac-bypasses-techniques-and-detection-strategies"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The Elastic Security Research team has identified new detection strategies to overcome the bypass methodologies used by adversaries to silently deploy malware onto an endpoint and elevate privileges without the end-user knowing. Malware often requires full administrative privileges on a machine to perform more impactful actions, such as adding an antivirus exclusion, encrypting secured files, or injecting code into system processes. Even if the targeted user has administrative privileges, the prevalence of User Account Control (UAC) means that the malicious application will often default to medium integrity, preventing write access to resources with higher integrity levels. Mandatory Integrity Levels (MIC) provides a mechanism for controlling access to securable objects.
This work builds…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headline Words]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2584/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2584/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/headline_words.png" title="Roundly-condemned headlinese initiative shuttered indefinitely." alt="Roundly-condemned headlinese initiative shuttered indefinitely." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Begrudgingly]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42323</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/682989502/0/sethsblog~Begrudgingly/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-20T09:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social niceties are easy to do half-heartedly. But they’re not for us, they’re for the other person. When you show up begrudgingly, it’s not half-hearted, it’s cold hearted. A handshake, a greeting, the way we sit in a meeting or wear a mask–it’s a chance to connect and to make a difference for the person […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who chooses?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42353</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/682905153/0/sethsblog~Who-chooses/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-19T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Google or Facebook or Spotify decide what you’ll see next, they’re making a choice. That’s very different from an open platform like “podcasting” or “blogging” (in quotes with no capital letters, because no one is in charge.) Being in charge implies that choices are being made. And people who are in charge–even if it’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 10th Birthday, DynamoDB! 🎉🎂🎁]]></title>
        <id>6a6363a6fd2f05ad00504fbee779ecb0f06a2c82</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-birthday-dynamodb/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T23:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 18th 2012, Jeff and Werner announced the general availability of Amazon DynamoDB, a fully managed flexible NoSQL database service for single-digit millisecond performance at any scale. During the last 10 years, hundreds of thousands of customers have adopted DynamoDB. It regularly reaches new peaks of performance and scalability. For example, during the last […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.1 EAP3: Enhanced Type Hints, Fixes in Auto-Import and Navigation, and More Flexible Reset Options in Embedded GDB Server Configurations]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=231233</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/02/clion-2022-1-eap3/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T20:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, The new CLion 2022.1 EAP build, 221.4501.161, is now available from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package (if you are using Ubuntu). Note that if you are on macOS, there is a separate build for Apple Silicon (M1 chip). Those who are already using EAP2 can apply a patch […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Security Automation using Cisco Secure Firewall and HashiCorp Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/network-security-automation-using-cisco-secure-firewall-and-hashicorp-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/network-security-automation-using-cisco-secure-firewall-and-hashicorp-consul"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how  Consul-Terraform-Sync can be used to auto-update values of objects in Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust Routing Using Electrical Flows]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/robust-routing-using-electrical-flows.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/robust-routing-using-electrical-flows.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T19:58:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ali Kemal Sinop and Kostas Kollias, Research Scientists, Google Research 
In the world of networks, there are models that can explain observations across a diverse collection of applications. These include simple tasks such as computing the shortest path, which has obvious applications to routing networks but also applies in biology, e.g., where the slime mold Physarum is able to find shortest paths in mazes. Another example is Braess’s paradox — the observation that adding resources to a network can have an effect opposite to the one expected — which manifests not only in road networks but also in mechanical and electrical systems. For instance, constructing a new road can increase traffic congestion or adding a new link in an electrical circuit can increase voltage. Such connec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.1 EAP #3: Enhanced Array Shapes]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=231063</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/02/phpstorm-2022-1-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T17:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third build of our Early Access Program for PhpStorm 2022.1 is now available! This blog post will cover enhanced support for array shape annotations that improve code completion for object-like arrays. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep your stable and EAP versions up to date. You […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid Event Notification System at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6deb1d2b57d1</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/rapid-event-notification-system-at-netflix-6deb1d2b57d1?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T15:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post gives an overview of the Rapid Event Notification System at Netflix and shares some of the learnings gained while building it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Design Conf ‘22: Join the Two-Day Live Stream on March 3–4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=231033</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/blog/2022/02/18/jetbrains-design-conf-22-join-the-two-day-live-stream-on-march-3-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T12:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might think that JetBrains is all about software development, project planning and coding. We invite you to join us for a look at different aspects of the software business – design, branding, and UX. Introducing the first public JetBrains Design Conf! Last year, we stepped out of the ‘designers box’ and held a company-wide […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Repina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 EAP 3: Kotlin 1.6.20-M1 Plugin, Enhanced Markdown Editor, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=229616</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/02/intellij-idea-2022-1-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T12:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third week of the IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 Early Access Program is underway! The new EAP build brings the bundled Kotlin 1.6.20-M1 plugin, UI enhancements to the Debugger, improvements for the Markdown editor, and more. You can get the latest build from our website, the free Toolbox App, or via snaps for Ubuntu users. Read […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1 EAP #3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=230351</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/02/webstorm-2022-1-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T12:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1 EAP build #3 is now available! To catch up on all the new features, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. You can also manually download the EAP builds from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Ryabukha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet Below Deck, Part II – Breaking down the editor]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=fleet&amp;p=230801</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/fleet/2022/02/fleet-below-deck-part-ii-breaking-down-the-editor/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T10:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a multipart series on building Fleet, a next generation IDE by JetBrains. Part I – Architecture Overview Part II – Breaking down the editor In the first part of this series we looked at an overview of the Fleet architecture. In this second part we’re going to cover the algorithms and data structures […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hadi Hariri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.2.0-M3, 2021.1.2, and 2021.0.9 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/18/spring-data-2021-2-0-m3-2021-1-2-and-2021-0-9-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/18/spring-data-2021-2-0-m3-2021-1-2-and-2021-0-9-released"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T10:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce Spring Data service releases 2021.1.2 and 2020.0.9.
Both releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot 2.6.4 respective 2.5.10 are going to pick up these releases in the upcoming days.

Along with the service releases, we released the next milestone 2021.2.0-M3 of the 2021.2 release train. We have summarized the new and noteworthy changes in our release notes.

To round things off, here are the links to the individual modules, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.2.0-M3


  
Spring Data Commons 2.7 M3 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.4 M3 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.7 M3 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Oxford comma, trap]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42340</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/682819008/0/sethsblog~The-Oxford-comma-trap/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T09:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to accept the limits that are implied when someone asks us for advice and feedback. Fix the typos, sure. That’s important. But perhaps you have something bigger to add. A friend shares plans to launch a new retail website. It’s tempting to fix the small errors on the page, but perhaps it’s more […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.02.18]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63477</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-02-18/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T09:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.02.18 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.02.18 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.1 Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/18/spring-cloud-2021-0-1-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/18/spring-cloud-2021-0-1-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T08:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Service Release 1 of the Spring Cloud 2021.0 Release Train is available today. This was primarily a bug fix release. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2021.0.1 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0.1 Release Train

See the project page for all issues included in the release.
Spring Cloud Config


  
Fix pattern matching bug with JSON, YAML, and properties files (2020)


Spring Cloud Sleuth


  
Numerous bug fixes


Spring Cloud Contract


  
Bug fixes


Spring Cloud Gateway


  
A new route predicate that checks for allowed values for the X-Forwarded-For header, similar to the RemoteAddr predicate. (783)

  
Allows setting of the order of the Gateway Handler…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring LDAP 2.3.6 and 2.4.0-M2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/17/spring-ldap-2-3-6-and-2-4-0-m2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/17/spring-ldap-2-3-6-and-2-4-0-m2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T04:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring LDAP 2.3.6 (release notes) and 2.4.0-M2 (release notes) are available now.



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chorded Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2583/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2583/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/chorded_keyboard.png" title="And even though it all went wrong / I'll stand before the lord of song / with nothing on my tongue but 'I don't understand, I swear I backed up my keyboard config before messing with it'" alt="And even though it all went wrong / I'll stand before the lord of song / with nothing on my tongue but 'I don't understand, I swear I backed up my keyboard config before messing with it'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning for Mechanical Ventilation Control]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/machine-learning-for-mechanical.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/machine-learning-for-mechanical.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Daniel Suo, Software Engineer and Elad Hazan, Research Scientist, Google Research, on behalf of the Google AI Princeton Team 
  Mechanical ventilators provide critical support for patients who have difficulty breathing or are unable to breathe on their own. They see frequent use in scenarios ranging from routine anesthesia, to neonatal intensive care and life support during the COVID-19 pandemic. A typical ventilator consists of a compressed air source, valves to control the flow of air into and out of the lungs, and a "respiratory circuit" that connects the ventilator to the patient. In some cases, a sedated patient may be connected to the ventilator via a tube inserted through the trachea to their lungs, a process called invasive ventilation. 


A mechanical ventilator takes br…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HPE, ServiceNow, JFrog Among New Verified Terraform Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hpe-servicenow-jfrog-among-new-verified-terraform-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hpe-servicenow-jfrog-among-new-verified-terraform-providers"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We welcome 15 new verified providers to the growing HashiCorp Terraform ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Java team luminary Sharat Chander]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/17/a-bootiful-podcast-java-team-luminary-sharat-chander</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/17/a-bootiful-podcast-java-team-luminary-sharat-chander"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of A Bootiful Podcast! This week, Josh Long (@starbuxman)  talks to @Java team luminary and community legend Sharat Chander (@sharat_chander).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Balloon Learning Environment]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/the-balloon-learning-environment.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/the-balloon-learning-environment.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T18:11:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Joshua Greaves, Software Engineer and Pablo Samuel Castro, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
Benchmark challenges have been a driving force in the advancement of machine learning (ML). In particular, difficult benchmark environments for reinforcement learning (RL) have been crucial for the rapid progress of the field by challenging researchers to overcome increasingly difficult tasks. The Arcade Learning Environment, Mujoco, and others have been used to push the envelope in RL algorithms, representation learning, exploration, and more.  
 In “Autonomous Navigation of Stratospheric Balloons Using Reinforcement Learning”, published in Nature two years ago, we demonstrated how deep RL can be used to create a high-performing flight agent that can control stratosph…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning finds more vulnerabilities using machine learning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-17-code-scanning-finds-vulnerabilities-using-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-17-code-scanning-finds-vulnerabilities-using-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T18:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we launched new code scanning analysis features powered by machine learning. The experimental analysis finds more of the most common types of vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging machine learning to find security vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-17-leveraging-machine-learning-find-security-vulnerabilities/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-17-leveraging-machine-learning-find-security-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T17:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A behind-the-scenes peek into the machine learning framework powering new code scanning security alerts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Comes Kotlin Heroes:  Episode 9!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=230823</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/02/kotlin-heroes-episode-9/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T17:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin Heroes is our Kotlin-only contest hosted by the Codeforces. It is a great way to play around with Kotlin’s features, learn something new, and practice using the language by solving fun problems. It is great for programmers of any level! Everyone has a chance to win some cool prizes: exclusive Kotlin Heroes t-shirts, stickers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ksenia Shneyveys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.1 EAP #3 is Out with New Features for Working with Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=230494</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/02/17/goland-2022-1-eap-3-is-out-with-new-features-for-working-with-microservices/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T13:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go is undoubtedly one of the most popular languages for writing microservices. In this EAP build, you will find some great features that will make working with microservices easier.  You can get the EAP build via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package (for Ubuntu), or from inside GoLand select […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our new project]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42254</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/682709050/0/sethsblog~Our-new-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T09:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s something I’ve been working on as a full-time volunteer for the last five months. And it’s something that three hundred people are building together. But I say “our” because it’s bigger than me or the three hundred of us or even the people who are reading this blog. Like it or not, this is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.16 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/17/spring-framework-5-3-16-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/17/spring-framework-5-3-16-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T09:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.16 is available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.16 includes 33 fixes and improvements.

Stay tuned for follow-up Spring Boot releases next week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains .NET Day Online 2022 – Call for Speakers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=228047</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/02/17/jetbrains-net-day-online-2022-call-for-speakers/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T07:12:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s that time of the year again! Back in 2019, we held our first JetBrains .NET Day Online — a free, live, virtual event where community speakers cover topics they are passionate about, ranging from deep technical .NET content and speakers’ experiences with specific tools and technologies, to personal development. After a successful 2020 and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maarten Balliauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t run AWS without monitoring it with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-elastic-observability-monitoring-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-elastic-observability-monitoring-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T00:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s solution works with Amazon’s AWS S3 service to ingest and read performance data and metrics, to create a clear, actionable dashboard of system performance, allowing developers to see baseline performance and instantly detect anomalies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t run AWS without monitoring it with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-elastic-observability-monitoring-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-elastic-observability-monitoring-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T00:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In 2022, it’s hard to find places in the business and technology ecosystem where performance is not measured, where lots of data is not collected and where insights are not analyzed to improve operational and business performance and trace accountability.
In a world where every click and interaction matters, business leaders know it’s not enough to have retrospective reports of infrastructure and application performance impact on business KPIs, or worse, long drawn post-mortems when systems fail. They need live windows into their business and systems performance , to catch  issues before they start to degrade the customer experience.
Cloud adoption has mushroomed, with Gartner estimating public cloud spending will approach half a trillion dollars this year. The shift to the cloud provide…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Annotated January 2022: C++20 to Eliminate Runtime Bugs and Achieve Better Design, Full Test Coverage, and a New QML Compiler]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=230331</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/02/cpp-annotated-january-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T21:17:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have all of the January news for you in our latest monthly C++ Annotated digest and its companion, the No Diagnostic Required show. If you have already subscribed, feel free to skip straight to the news. If this is your first time here, let us quickly take you through all the formats we offer. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Amazon Reach Agreement on Trademark Infringement Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-amazon-reach-agreement-on-trademark-infringement-lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-amazon-reach-agreement-on-trademark-infringement-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T21:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to share that Elastic and Amazon have resolved the trademark infringement lawsuit related to the term Elasticsearch. Now the only Elasticsearch service on AWS and the AWS Marketplace is Elastic Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shay Banon,Ashutosh Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Amazon Reach Agreement on Trademark Infringement Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-amazon-reach-agreement-on-trademark-infringement-lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-amazon-reach-agreement-on-trademark-infringement-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T21:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re pleased to share that Elastic and Amazon have resolved the trademark infringement lawsuit related to the term Elasticsearch. Now the only Elasticsearch service on AWS and the AWS Marketplace is Elastic Cloud. 
This resolution follows the change to the license of Elasticsearch and Kibana in 2021, and Amazon’s subsequent actions, including renaming their service. We believe this resolution will remove confusion in the marketplace and provide much-needed clarity to our community and customers.  
There is only one Elasticsearch, and it comes from Elastic. This means when you use Elasticsearch, whether as the Elastic Cloud service in AWS, Azure, or Google Cloud, or when you download and run Elasticsearch yourself, you can be sure that you’re getting the best possible experience because …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shay Banon,Ashutosh Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make the most out of a mentoring relationship]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-16-how-to-make-the-most-out-of-a-mentoring-relationship/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-16-how-to-make-the-most-out-of-a-mentoring-relationship/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T18:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tips from our developer advocates on how and why to find a mentor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encoding and escaping untrusted data to prevent injection attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-16-encoding-escaping-untrusted-data-prevent-injection-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-16-encoding-escaping-untrusted-data-prevent-injection-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T17:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical tips on how to apply OWASP Top 10 Proactive Control C4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Spring Cloud Enterprise is now available in preview]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/16/azure-spring-cloud-enterprise-is-now-available-in-preview</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/16/azure-spring-cloud-enterprise-is-now-available-in-preview"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! I wanted to share this post by Julia Liuson, President, Developer Division at Microsoft. 

When we launched Azure Spring Cloud with VMware in 2019, we set out to solve common challenges developers, IT operators, and DevOps teams face when running Spring Boot applications at scale. Since then we’ve had the opportunity to work with many customers to help them adopt the service including Bosch, Digital Realty, Kroger, Liantis, Morgan Stanley, National Life, Raley’s, and Swiss Re. They value the fully managed infrastructure of Azure Spring Cloud that lets them focus on their apps, while the service manages dynamic scaling, security patching, out-of-the-box instrumentation for monitoring, and more.

Many organizations are running thousands of Spring Boot applications on-premi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Elastic Observability?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-observability-why-use-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-observability-why-use-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability helps DevOps organizations correlate limitless telemetry data, including metrics, logs and traces, using the power of search to break down silos and turn data into insights. Elastic Observability is built on the Elastic Stack, a proven, search-based solution used by customers all over the world in mission-critical applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Elastic Observability?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-observability-why-use-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-is-observability-why-use-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Welcome to Elastic’s observability information and resource hub. Here you’ll find the latest and most important blogs, resources, web content and information about Elastic Observability.
We’ll provide information for how your IT DevOps (or DevSecOps) teams can use observability to detect and solve issues across complex environments, including single and multi-cloud. We’ll also explain what observability is and why it is critical to the success of your business or organization.
What is observability?
Observability is the method by which IT organizations gain actionable insights across the increasingly complex distributed systems and applications they develop, deploy and manage.
Observability is a key initiative of any organization’s application and infrastructure modernization journey. Co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from Python virtual environments to automation execution environments in Ansible Automation Platform 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/migrating-from-python-virtual-environments-to-automation-execution-environments-in-ansible-automation-platform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/migrating-from-python-virtual-environments-to-automation-execution-environments-in-ansible-automation-platform-2"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Tower (included in Ansible Automation Platform 1.x) used Python virtual environments to manage dependencies and implement consistent automation execution across multiple Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform instances. This method of managing dependencies came with its own set of limitations:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2021.2.3 is here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=228416</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2022/02/teamcity-2021-2-3-is-here/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T13:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third bugfix update for TeamCity 2021.2 is already available for download! Version 2021.2.3 contains a fix important for all TeamCity users who connect their projects to GitHub.com repositories via SSH. Beginning March 2022, GitHub will stop supporting deprecated SSH protocols. Make sure to upgrade TeamCity to the new version by this point – otherwise, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Dvoriadkina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t guard your luck]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=32055</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/682545902/0/sethsblog~Dont-guard-your-luck/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T09:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe we don’t want to talk about it. Perhaps we believe that unexamined luck isn’t quite as fragile. Perhaps we don’t want to let anyone else in. It could be that we think that success is scarce, and scarcity will somehow preserve it. Or maybe we want to insist that it’s all due to skill […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Spring Native and MyBatis]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/16/spring-tips-spring-native-and-mybatis</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/02/16/spring-tips-spring-native-and-mybatis"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, we look at how to use the MyBatis data mapper project’s new Spring Native hints to build GraalVM native images]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Trap]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2582/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2582/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/data_trap.png" title="It's important to make sure your analysis destroys as much information as it produces." alt="It's important to make sure your analysis destroys as much information as it produces." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.4 improves developer productivity and adds reusable workflows to CI/CD]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-15-ghes-3-4-developer-productivity-reusable-workflows-ci-cd/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-15-ghes-3-4-developer-productivity-reusable-workflows-ci-cd/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T23:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.4 release candidate delivers enhancements to make life easier and more productive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good News About the Carbon Footprint of Machine Learning Training]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/good-news-about-carbon-footprint-of.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/good-news-about-carbon-footprint-of.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T20:36:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by David Patterson, Distinguished Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team  
Machine learning (ML) has become prominent in information technology, which has led some to raise concerns about the associated rise in the costs of computation, primarily the carbon footprint, i.e., total greenhouse gas emissions. While these assertions rightfully elevated the discussion around carbon emissions in ML, they also highlight the need for accurate data to assess true carbon footprint, which can help identify strategies to mitigate carbon emission in ML.
 
In “The Carbon Footprint of Machine Learning Training Will Plateau, Then Shrink”, accepted for publication in IEEE Computer, we focus on operational carbon emissions — i.e., the energy cost of operating ML hardware, including data center overhead…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Stars in our eyes ⭐️]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-02-15-the-github-stars-in-our-eyes/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-02-15-the-github-stars-in-our-eyes/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T17:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past year, the GitHub Stars have made a tremendous impact in the community with their influence, inspiring and building communities and creating content to help everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for Amazon CodeGuru Reviewer – Detector Library and Security Detectors for Log-Injection Flaws]]></title>
        <id>4431491871a4ee3d928576163daaa289ff9714db</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-amazon-codeguru-reviewer-detector-library-and-security-detectors-for-log-injection-flaws/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T16:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeGuru Reviewer is a developer tool that detects security vulnerabilities in your code and provides intelligent recommendations to improve code quality. For example, CodeGuru Reviewer introduced Security Detectors for Java and Python code to identify security risks from the top ten Open Web Application Security Project (OWASP) categories and follow security best practices for AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving from Embedded to Remote Workflow Engines]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=43376</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/moving-from-embedded-to-remote-workflow-engines/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prefer embedded workflow engines? So did we. Learn our reasoning behind why we now recommend a remote engine instead. 
The post Moving from Embedded to Remote Workflow Engines appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic File System Update – Sub-Millisecond Read Latency]]></title>
        <id>9453612a47b3048c109c3b2d7b4e5054b089e439</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-elastic-file-system-update-sub-millisecond-read-latency/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T22:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) was announced in early 2015 and became generally available in 2016. We launched EFS in order to make it easier for you to build applications that need shared access to file data. EFS is (and always has been) simple and serverless: you simply create a file system, attach it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 C6a Instances Powered By 3rd Gen AMD EPYC Processors for Compute-Intensive Workloads]]></title>
        <id>d0be7f91366e127f0cb3c4144bb5a5b8910d05be</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c6a-instances-powered-by-3rd-gen-amd-epyc-processors-for-compute-intensive-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T21:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2021, we launched Amazon EC2 M6a instances powered by the 3rd Gen AMD EPYC processors, running at frequencies up to 3.6 GHz, which offer customers up to 35 percent improvement in price-performance compared to M5a instances. Many customers are looking for ways to optimize their cloud utilization, and they are taking advantage […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Automation Platform - A video tour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-a-video-tour</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-a-video-tour"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people are familiar with the community version of Ansible, the command line automation tool, but I wanted to elaborate on how our enterprise offering, Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, and how it expands the possibilities of Ansible for our customers in Red Hat's most recent release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An International Scientific Challenge for the Diagnosis and Gleason Grading of Prostate Cancer]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/an-international-scientific-challenge.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/an-international-scientific-challenge.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Po-Hsuan Cameron Chen, Software Engineer, Google Health and Maggie Demkin, Program Manager, Kaggle 
In recent years, machine learning (ML) competitions in health have attracted ML scientists to work together to solve challenging clinical problems. These competitions provide access to relevant data and well-defined problems where experienced data scientists come to compete for solutions and learn new methods. However, a fundamental difficulty in organizing such challenges is obtaining and curating high quality datasets for model development and independent datasets for model evaluation. Importantly, to reduce the risk of bias and to ensure broad applicability of the algorithm, evaluation of the generalisability of resulting algorithms should ideally be performed on multiple indepe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Azure AD Identity with HashiCorp Vault — Part 3: Azure Managed Identity Auth via Azure Auth Method]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/integrating-azure-ad-identity-vault-part-3-azure-managed-identity-via-azure-auth-method</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/integrating-azure-ad-identity-vault-part-3-azure-managed-identity-via-azure-auth-method"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to achieve machine authentication to HashiCorp Vault with the Azure auth method using Microsoft Azure managed identity — and set it up with Terraform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Into Azure Using Pulumi and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63458</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-into-azure-using-pulumi-and-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T14:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week’s episode of The DevOps Lab we have Kat Cosgrove and Matty Stratton from Pulumi joining us!
02:45 –
The post Deploy Into Azure Using Pulumi and GitHub Actions appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Reasons to join the Elastic Contributor Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-reasons-to-join-the-elastic-contributor-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-reasons-to-join-the-elastic-contributor-program"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now you’ve heard of Elastic’s recognition and rewards program, the Elastic Contributor Program. But why should you join? Here are five things you may not have realized about participating in the program, along with more information about the work and success that our current contributors in the Elastic community have experienced:
**Get recognized for your participation in the Elastic Community ** 
Do you speak at meetups about Elasticsearch? Contribute code to Elastic repos? Write articles about Kibana? Create video tutorials on logstash? Turn all of those projects into points and compete to earn recognition as an Elastic Contributor. Gold, Silver, and Bronze winners receive LinkedIn virtual badges acknowledging their status as Elastic Contributor Program winners. 
Gain a network of sup…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ully Sampaio,Faith Westdorp,Elyssa Emrich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Reasons to join the Elastic Contributor Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-reasons-to-join-the-elastic-contributor-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-reasons-to-join-the-elastic-contributor-program"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch pros and beginners helping each other out. The Elastic Contributor Program helps to broadcast your ideas and projects for the benefit of the wider Elastic community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ully Sampaio,Faith Westdorp,Elyssa Emrich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring Continuous Support of AngularJS in Camunda Platform 7.17]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=43297</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/ensuring-continuous-support-of-angularjs-in-camunda-platform-7-17/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn more about our search and discovery of a solution to protect the integrity of the web apps for all our users. 
The post Ensuring Continuous Support of AngularJS in Camunda Platform 7.17 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.02.11]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63450</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-02-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T10:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.02.11 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.02.11 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guiding Frozen Language Models with Learned Soft Prompts]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/guiding-frozen-language-models-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/guiding-frozen-language-models-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-10T23:22:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brian Lester, AI Resident and Noah Constant, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research 
Large pre-trained language models, which are continuing to grow in size, achieve state-of-art results on many natural language processing (NLP) benchmarks. Since the development of GPT and BERT, standard practice has been to fine-tune models on downstream tasks, which involves adjusting every weight in the network (i.e., model tuning). However, as models become larger, storing and serving a tuned copy of the model for each downstream task becomes impractical. 
 An appealing alternative is to share across all downstream tasks a single frozen pre-trained language model, in which all weights are fixed. In an exciting development, GPT-3 showed convincingly that a frozen model can be conditio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AWS Provider 4.0 Refactors S3 Bucket Resource]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-aws-provider-4-0-refactors-s3-bucket-resource</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-aws-provider-4-0-refactors-s3-bucket-resource"/>
        <updated>2022-02-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.0 of the HashiCorp Terraform AWS provider brings usability improvements to data sources and attribute validations along with a refactored S3 bucket resource.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nested Hierarchical Transformer: Towards Accurate, Data-Efficient, and Interpretable Visual Understanding]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/nested-hierarchical-transformer-towards.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/nested-hierarchical-transformer-towards.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-09T19:34:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zizhao Zhang, Software Engineer, Google Research, Cloud AI Team 
In visual understanding, the Vision Transformer (ViT) and its variants have received significant attention recently due to their superior performance on many core visual applications, such as image classification, object detection, and video understanding. The core idea of ViT is to utilize the power of self-attention layers to learn global relationships between small patches of images. However, the number of connections between patches increases quadratically with image size. Such a design has been observed to be data inefficient — although the original ViT can perform better than convolutional networks with hundreds of millions of images for pre-training, such a data requirement is not always practical, and it sti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data pipeline asset management with Dataflow]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/86525b3e21ca</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/data-pipeline-asset-management-with-dataflow-86525b3e21ca?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-02-09T17:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Sam Setegne, Jai Balani, Olek Gorajek]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 67 – What’s New With @AzureCosmosDB?]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63432</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-67-whats-new-with-azurecosmosdb/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-09T16:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 67 – What’s New With @AzureCosmosDB? appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第203話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496750858664</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496750858664"/>
        <updated>2022-02-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private automation hub - Multi-Hub for resilience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/private-automation-hub-multi-hub-for-resilience</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/private-automation-hub-multi-hub-for-resilience"/>
        <updated>2022-02-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Content Collections have become the new standard for distributing Ansible content (playbooks, roles, modules, and plugins). Collections have been fully supported since Ansible 2.9 and for the last 2 years, the Ansible community has been on a journey to move to this new way of packaging and consuming Ansible content. With Ansible 2.9, Collections were optional, but as of 2.10 they are a requirement. The ability to be able to install and use Collections as needed is increasingly important.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for App Runner – VPC Support]]></title>
        <id>1a0c9699248dcff7d4e49cd723b6f6e98e0095bc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-app-runner-vpc-support/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-08T23:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With AWS App Runner, you can quickly deploy web applications and APIs at any scale. You can start with your source code or a container image, and App Runner will fully manage all infrastructure including servers, networking, and load balancing for your application. If you want, App Runner can also configure a deployment pipeline for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW – Replicate Existing Objects with Amazon S3 Batch Replication]]></title>
        <id>7e71881223eb44bfabf748e3a1abfc1ec501c525</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-replicate-existing-objects-with-amazon-s3-batch-replication/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-08T23:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can replicate existing Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) objects and synchronize your buckets using the new Amazon S3 Batch Replication feature. Amazon S3 Replication supports several customer use cases. For example, you can use it to minimize latency by maintaining copies of your data in AWS Regions geographically closer to your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robot See, Robot Do]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/robot-see-robot-do.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/robot-see-robot-do.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kevin Zakka, Student Researcher and Andy Zeng, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google 
People learn to do things by watching others — from mimicking new dance moves, to watching YouTube cooking videos. We’d like robots to do the same, i.e., to learn new skills by watching people do things during training. Today, however, the predominant paradigm for teaching robots is to remote control them using specialized hardware for teleoperation and then train them to imitate pre-recorded demonstrations. This limits both who can provide the demonstrations (programmers & roboticists) and where they can be provided (lab settings). If robots could instead self-learn new tasks by watching humans, this capability could allow them to be deployed in more unstructured settings like the home, and ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the Full Potential of Datacenter ML Accelerators with Platform-Aware Neural Architecture Search]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/unlocking-full-potential-of-datacenter.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/unlocking-full-potential-of-datacenter.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-08T18:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sheng Li, Staff Software Engineer and Norman P. Jouppi, Google Fellow, Google Research    
Continuing advances in the design and implementation of datacenter (DC) accelerators for machine learning (ML), such as TPUs and GPUs, have been critical for powering modern ML models and applications at scale. These improved accelerators exhibit peak performance (e.g., FLOPs) that is orders of magnitude better than traditional computing systems. However, there is a fast-widening gap between the available peak performance offered by state-of-the-art hardware and the actual achieved performance when ML models run on that hardware.  
 One approach to address this gap is to design hardware-specific ML models that optimize both performance (e.g., throughput and latency) and model quality. Recen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.8.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=43055</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/camunda-optimize-3-8-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-08T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.8.0-alpha1. Download the release or sign up for a free 30-day trial. today. 
The post Camunda Optimize 3.8.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17.0-alpha4 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=43083</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/camunda-platform-runtime-7-17-0-alpha4-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-08T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17.0. You can download it for free or run it with Docker. 
The post Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17.0-alpha4 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.4.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=43106</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/camunda-cloud-1-4-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited about the release of Camunda Cloud 1.4.0-alpha1. Get started with it now, or sign up for Camunda Cloud!
The post Camunda Cloud 1.4.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copy Dashboard Public Preview Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63408</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/copy-dashboard-public-preview-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-07T17:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Copy Dashboard public preview now includes the ability to select a folder to store queries and configuration carried over with the copy operation. It took a little longer than expected, sorry about that, and thanks for your patience.
The post Copy Dashboard Public Preview Part 3 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving Multi-Tenancy with Consul Administrative Partitions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/achieving-multi-tenancy-with-consul-administrative-partitions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/achieving-multi-tenancy-with-consul-administrative-partitions"/>
        <updated>2022-02-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using multiple dedicated service meshes can pose resource-inefficiency challenges — learn how HashiCorp Consul’s new Administrative Partitions can help solve them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Demand execution with Red Hat OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/on-demand-execution-with-red-hat-openshift</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/on-demand-execution-with-red-hat-openshift"/>
        <updated>2022-02-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to dynamically scale infrastructure is no longer a nice-to-have - it is a requirement. The advent of cloud and container platforms have shifted the expectations in terms of consuming IT infrastructure and services. As a result, any tool that is used to manage infrastructure needs to be able to handle this ever-changing landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.02.04]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63392</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-02-04/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-04T11:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.02.04 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.02.04 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demonstrate your AWS Cloud Storage knowledge and skills with new digital badges!]]></title>
        <id>7575cda5d88818dd7121ef796bc78e85c48004ec</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/demonstrate-your-aws-cloud-storage-knowledge-and-skills-with-new-digital-badges/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T16:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a cloud storage professional or an on-premises storage pro who’s curious about cloud storage? Are you interested in demonstrating your AWS Storage knowledge and skills with potential employers and your community of peers? If so, I’d like to bring to your attention the recent launch of digital badges aligned to Learning Plans for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Overcame Long-Running Job Limitations in Jenkins Declarative Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=42944</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/02/how-we-overcame-long-running-job-limitations-in-jenkins-declarative-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T21:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get the technical details about the challenges we faced while building advanced declarative pipelines for our workflow and decision engine. 
The post How We Overcame Long-Running Job Limitations in Jenkins Declarative Pipelines appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed AbouZaid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Robots Follow Instructions for New Tasks?]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/can-robots-follow-instructions-for-new.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/can-robots-follow-instructions-for-new.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T18:47:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Chelsea Finn, Research Adviser and Eric Jang, Senior Research Scientist, Robotics at Google 
People can flexibly maneuver objects in their physical surroundings to accomplish various goals. One of the grand challenges in robotics is to successfully train robots to do the same, i.e., to develop a general-purpose robot capable of performing a multitude of tasks based on arbitrary user commands. Robots that are faced with the real world will also inevitably encounter new user instructions and situations that were not seen during training. Therefore, it is imperative for robots to be trained to perform multiple tasks in a variety of situations and, more importantly, to be capable of solving new tasks as requested by human users, even if the robot was not explicitly trained on those t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Observability at Scale Using Datadog’s Vector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-observability-at-scale-using-datadog-s-vector</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-observability-at-scale-using-datadog-s-vector"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get technical insight into how HCP Vault uses Datadog’s Vector integration to meet the observability needs of customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Activate Red Hat Insights for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/activate-insights-for-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/activate-insights-for-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T19:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: This blog refers to Red Hat Insights using Ansible Automation Platform 2.1. Automation controller is the control plane for Ansible Automation Platform, formerly known as Red Hat Ansible Tower. 
An indispensable but sometimes overlooked tool included with an Ansible Automation Platform subscription is the cloud-based service, Red Hat Insights for Ansible Automation Platform.
 
Insights is a suite of reporting and analytics tools to help you identify, troubleshoot, and resolve operational, business, and security issues across your entire ecosystem. You can also use Insights to track the ROI of your automation investment and plan future automation projects to prioritize your efforts where they will have the biggest impact on your business.
 
Before you can start using Insights to better understand your automation estate and make data-driven decisions, you need to set up the flow of information from your enterprise into the Red Hat Hybrid Cloud Console.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Differential Privacy to Large Scale Image Classification]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/applying-differential-privacy-to-large.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/applying-differential-privacy-to-large.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alexey Kurakin, Software Engineer and Roxana Geambasu, Visiting Faculty Researcher, Google Research 
Machine learning (ML) models are becoming increasingly valuable for improved performance across a variety of consumer products, from recommendations to automatic image classification.  However, despite aggregating large amounts of data, in theory it is possible for models to encode characteristics of individual entries from the training set.  For example, experiments in controlled settings have shown that language models trained using email datasets may sometimes encode sensitive information included in the training data and may have the potential to reveal the presence of a particular user’s data in the training set. As such, it is important to prevent the encoding of such charac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling Transparent Data Encryption for Microsoft SQL with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/enabling-transparent-data-encryption-for-microsoft-sql-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/enabling-transparent-data-encryption-for-microsoft-sql-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HashiCorp Vault can help secure data in Microsoft SQL Server using a defense-in-depth encryption strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying Interviewing for Backend Engineers @ Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/aceb26a83495</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/demystifying-interviewing-for-backend-engineers-netflix-aceb26a83495?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T14:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Karen Casella, Director of Engineering, Access & Identity Management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controlling Neural Networks with Rule Representations]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/controlling-neural-networks-with-rule.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/controlling-neural-networks-with-rule.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T18:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sungyong Seo, Software Engineer and Sercan O. Arik, Research Scientist, Google Research, Cloud AI Team  
Deep neural networks (DNNs) provide more accurate results as the size and coverage of their training data increases. While investing in high-quality and large-scale labeled datasets is one path to model improvement, another is leveraging prior knowledge, concisely referred to as “rules” — reasoning heuristics, equations, associative logic, or constraints. Consider a common example from physics where a model is given the task of predicting the next state in a double pendulum system. While the model may learn to estimate the total energy of the system at a given point in time only from empirical data, it will frequently overestimate the energy unless also provided an equation th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.9 Adds Cross-Stack References and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-9-adds-cross-stack-references-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-9-adds-cross-stack-references-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform 0.9 (CDKTF) enables cross-stack references and improves generated resources for providers and modules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.28]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63348</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-01-28/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T09:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.01.28 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.28 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Modeler 5.0.0-alpha.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=41898&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=41898</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/camunda-modeler-5-0-0-alpha-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're happy to announce the Camunda Modeler 5.0 release. It provides Camunda Cloud 1.1 support, BPMN in color support, and more improvements.
The post Camunda Modeler 5.0.0-alpha.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andreas Geier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate Your Camunda Modeler Plugins to Work with Camunda Modeler 5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=41903&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=41903</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/how-to-migrate-your-camunda-modeler-plugins-to-work-with-camunda-modeler-5-x/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to update Camunda Modeler plugins to benefit from its new features and make them compatible with Camunda Modeler 5 and subsequent versions. 
The post How to Migrate Your Camunda Modeler Plugins to Work with Camunda Modeler 5.0 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maximilian Trumpf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Your Medical Image Classifier Know What It Doesn’t Know?]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/does-your-medical-image-classifier-know.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/does-your-medical-image-classifier-know.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T18:01:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Abhijit Guha Roy, Research Software Engineer and Jie Ren, Research Scientist, Google Research    
Deep machine learning (ML) systems have achieved considerable success in medical image analysis in recent years. One major contributing factor is access to abundant labeled datasets, which are used to train highly effective supervised deep learning models. However, in the real-world, these models may encounter samples exhibiting rare conditions that are individually too infrequent for per-condition classification. Nevertheless, such conditions can be collectively common because they follow a long-tail distribution and when taken together can represent a significant portion of cases — e.g., in a recent deep learning dermatological study, hundreds of rare conditions composed around 20%…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul on Amazon ECS 0.3 Adds Extended Configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-3-adds-extended-configuration</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-3-adds-extended-configuration"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T17:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest version of HashiCorp Consul on Amazon ECS adds extended configuration to support more deployment scenarios along with several other new features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第202話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496725200155</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496725200155"/>
        <updated>2022-01-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>