<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-01-22T01:01:22.933Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-01-22T01:01:22.933Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.12.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · December 2021 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-01-21-release-radar-dec-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-01-21-release-radar-dec-2021/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T23:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of us were wrapping up projects, emails, events, and getting ready for Christmas. While we were all busy getting ready for the festive season, our community was still hard at work shipping open source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LaMDA: Towards Safe, Grounded, and High-Quality Dialog Models for Everything]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/lamda-towards-safe-grounded-and-high.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/lamda-towards-safe-grounded-and-high.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T19:00:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Heng-Tze Cheng, Senior Staff Software Engineer and Romal Thoppilan, Senior Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
Language models are becoming more capable than ever before and are helpful in a variety of tasks — translating one language into another, summarizing a long document into a brief highlight, or answering information-seeking questions. Among these, open-domain dialog, where a model needs to be able to converse about any topic, is probably one of the most difficult, with a wide range of potential applications and open challenges. In addition to producing responses that humans judge as sensible, interesting, and specific to the context, dialog models should adhere to Responsible AI practices, and avoid making factual statements that are not supported by external …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty Enhances Detection of EC2 Instance Credential Exfiltration]]></title>
        <id>515d068b8af84fffa0abe6327c926b5299f1a638</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-guardduty-enhances-detection-of-ec2-instance-credential-exfiltration/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T18:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty is a threat detection service that continuously monitors for malicious activity and unauthorized behavior to protect your AWS accounts, workloads, and data stored in Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3). Informed by a multitude of public and AWS-generated data feeds and powered by machine learning, GuardDuty analyzes billions of events in pursuit of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your control preference]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41272</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/678872762/0/sethsblog~Your-control-preference/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would you rather write the script, read the script, watch the movie or write the review? When someone commutes by train, they’re giving up control over the journey. On one hand, that means that they can’t actively impact how fast the train arrives. On the other hand, it means that they don’t have to be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.21]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63278</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-01-21/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T09:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.01.21 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.21 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-M1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-3-0-0-m1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-3-0-0-m1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-M1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This milestone starts our exciting journey to the next generation of the Spring Framework and raises our baseline from Java 8 to Java 17. We are planning to release a new milestone of Spring Boot 3.0 every two months. M2 should arrive on March 24 and we are planning on a GA release in late November.

If you are trying an existing application with Spring Boot 3.0 you’ll need to be aware that we’ve migrated all Java EE APIs to their equivalent Jakarta EE variant. For most users, this means you’ll need to replace any javax imports with jakarta. For example, javax.servlet.Filter would be replaced with jakarta.servlet.Filter.

We’re still waiting for a few third-party libraries to release Jakarta EE compatible versions, so not all Spring Boot 2.x features are available with this first milestone. We plan to reintroduce features as and when libraries provide appropriate releases.

Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

If you’re interested in trying this new release, you can easily generate a project from start.spring.io (remember to select Java 17).
Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests. 
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: RedHat's Kate Stanley on the distinction between traditional brokers and Apache Kafka]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/a-bootiful-podcast-redhat-s-kate-stanley-on-the-distinction-between-traditional-brokers-and-apache-kafka</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/a-bootiful-podcast-redhat-s-kate-stanley-on-the-distinction-between-traditional-brokers-and-apache-kafka"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to returning guest RedHat’s Kate Stanley (@KateStanley91) on the distinction between traditional brokers and Apache Kafka.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0-M1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-7-0-m1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-7-0-m1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T19:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0-M1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 111 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Spring GraphQL starter

  
Operating system and Java vendor information in actuator info endpoint

  
Support for RabbitStreamTemplate


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests. 
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing home the beacon (from Cobalt Strike)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-home-the-beacon-cobalt-strike</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-home-the-beacon-cobalt-strike"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to extract Cobalt Strike beacon payloads from memory and use open source tools to analyze and group threat activity clusters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Ditch,Daniel Stepanic,Andrew Pease,Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing home the beacon (from Cobalt Strike)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-home-the-beacon-cobalt-strike</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-home-the-beacon-cobalt-strike"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Security engineers have documented a less tedious way to find network beaconing from Cobalt Strike. In their full analysis ([1] [2]), Elastic Security team researchers Andrew Pease, Derek Ditch, and Daniel Stepanic walk users through the Elastic fleet policy, how to collect the beacon, beacon configuration, how to analyze its activity, and how you can set it up in your organization’s environment.
These two articles ([1] [2]) are ideal for helping security analysts identify, collect, and configure Cobalt Strike beacon payloads from an endpoint using Elastic. It is often difficult to collect the Cobalt Strike beacon payload from memory and extract its configuration to identify observables and cluster group activities, partially due to the tremendous amount of metadata the beacon’s configurations include.
The early stages of an intrusion usually include initial access, execution, persistence, and command-and-control (C2) beaconing. When structured threats use zero-days, these first two stages are often not detected, and it can often be challenging and time-consuming to identify persistence mechanisms left by an advanced adversary. 
The information helps threat hunters and analysts monitor Cobalt Strike beaconing activity, but also provides useful indicators of compromise (IoCs) with which to start an investigation.
If you don’t have an Elastic Cloud cluster but would like to collect and configure the Cobalt Strike beacon, you can start a free 14-day trial of Elastic Cloud today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Ditch,Daniel Stepanic,Andrew Pease,Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HCP Consul UI Feature Speeds Setup with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-consul-ui-feature-speeds-setup-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-consul-ui-feature-speeds-setup-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul users can now auto-generate ready-to-apply Terraform configurations to deploy HCP Consul end-to-end with a demo application in less than 20 minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source creates value, but how do you measure it?]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-01-20-open-source-creates-value-but-how-do-you-measure-it/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-01-20-open-source-creates-value-but-how-do-you-measure-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T16:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When digital infrastructure is overlooked by governments, it isn't just a missed opportunity: policies may inadvertently endanger open source collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.3 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-6-3-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-6-3-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.3 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 39 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three ways we've improved Elasticsearch scalability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/three-ways-improved-elasticsearch-scalability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/three-ways-improved-elasticsearch-scalability"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scale to new heights with Elasticsearch! In 7.16, we made several improvements for faster search, more stable clusters, and a reduced heap footprint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Armin Braun,Leaf Lin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three ways we've improved Elasticsearch scalability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/three-ways-improved-elasticsearch-scalability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/three-ways-improved-elasticsearch-scalability"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One finds limits by pushing them. –Herbert A. Simon,,,
At Elastic, we focus on bringing value to users through fast results that operate at scale and are relevant — speed, scale, and relevance are in our DNA. In Elasticsearch 7.16, we focused on scale, pushing the limits of Elasticsearch to make search even faster, memory less demanding, and clusters more stable. Along the way, we uncovered a range of dimensions on sharding and in the process sped up Elasticsearch to new heights. 
Historically, we’ve recommended avoiding creating a gazillion shards in your cluster due to the resource overhead involved. However, with the new data streams indexing strategy in Fleet, more and more smaller shards will be generated from security and observability use cases, so it’s essential that we find new wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Armin Braun,Leaf Lin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Automation Trends, Questions and Answers]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=41026</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/2022-automation-trends-questions-and-answers/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into our answers for the top-ranked questions from our recent webinar, Looking Back to the Future: 5 Process Automation Trends in 2022.
The post 2022 Automation Trends, Questions and Answers appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevRel Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data JDBC - How Can I Do a Partial Update of an Aggregate Root?]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-data-jdbc-how-can-i-do-a-partial-update-of-an-aggregate-root</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-data-jdbc-how-can-i-do-a-partial-update-of-an-aggregate-root"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T13:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the fourth article of a series about how to tackle various challenges you might encounter when using Spring Data JDBC.
The series consists of:





Spring Data JDBC - How to Use Custom ID Generation.



Spring Data JDBC - How Do I Make Bidirectional Relationships?



Spring Data JDBC - How Do I Implement Caching?



Spring Data JDBC - How Can I Do a Partial Update of an Aggregate Root? (this article)





If you are new to Spring Data JDBC, you should start by reading introduction and this article, which explains the relevance of aggregates in the context of Spring Data JDBC. Trust me. It is important.



Spring Data JDBC is built around the idea of aggregates and repositories.
Repositories are collection-like objects that find, load, save, and delete aggreg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.9 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-5-9-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/20/spring-boot-2-5-9-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T11:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.9 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 32 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fear of strangers]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42172</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/678728744/0/sethsblog~Fear-of-strangers/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T09:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why are we more likely to take off our masks or avoid social distancing with a group of friends at a party instead of strangers on the train? Why do we drive more carefully in a new neighborhood instead of near our home? Why trust the advice of a doctor who looks like us, or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch’s new range enrich policy enables a new level of contextual data analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-range-enrich-policy-elasticsearch-contextual-data-analysis</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-range-enrich-policy-elasticsearch-contextual-data-analysis"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 7.16 introduced a new enrich policy: range. We’ll showcase a fictional example matching incidents with on-call schedules using the date_range type.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Bischoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch’s new range enrich policy enables a new level of contextual data analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-range-enrich-policy-elasticsearch-contextual-data-analysis</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/new-range-enrich-policy-elasticsearch-contextual-data-analysis"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elasticsearch 7.16 introduced a new enrich policy: range. The range policy allows one to match a number, date, or IP address in incoming documents to a range of the same type in the enrich index. Being able to match against an IP range can be specifically useful in security use cases where the additional metadata can be used to further refine detection rules. As we’ve already added an example to our documentation using IP ranges, we’ll go through an example here using the date_range type.
Our fictional example: incidents and on-call schedules
Say we have a number of on-call schedules and we want to add them to Elasticsearch so that each continuous shift is a document. Let’s introduce our fictional test cases: Bob, Alice, Dan, Matt and Lizzie.
Bob likes to work Nine-to-Six taking an hour …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Bischoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0 M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/spring-batch-5-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/spring-batch-5-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T23:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who contributed, I am pleased to announce that the first milestone release of Spring Batch 5.0 is available now from https://repo.spring.io/milestone. This first milestone includes a number of major changes such as requiring Java 17+, migrating to Jakarta EE 9 APIs as well as upgrading our dependencies across the portfolio to major versions such as Spring Framework 6.0. For a complete list of changes, please check the change log.

We also took the opportunity of this major version to remove deprecated APIs and fix some issues that require non backward compatible changes. The migration guide contains more details about these changes and provides the upgrade instructions.

As we continue our work on Spring Batch 5, we look forward to your feedback on this first milestone!

Spring Batch Home | Source on GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security verifies new destructive malware targeting Ukraine: Operation Bleeding Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-verifies-operation-bleeding-bear</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-verifies-operation-bleeding-bear"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security has verified a multi-stage malware attack targeting the Ukraine government: Operation Bleeding Bear. Learn more in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security verifies new destructive malware targeting Ukraine: Operation Bleeding Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-verifies-operation-bleeding-bear</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-verifies-operation-bleeding-bear"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Security has verified a new destructive malware targeting Ukraine: Operation Bleeding Bear.
Over the weekend, Microsoft released details about this multi-stage and destructive malware campaign that the Ukrainian National Cyber Security Coordination Center has been referring to as Operation Bleeding Bear. 
Elastic users are fully protected from attacks like these through our advanced malware detection and Ransomware Protection capabilities, and the Elastic Security team continues to monitor these events. This case highlights the importance of prevention when it’s up against ransomware and malware with destructive capabilities.
In this full-length article, we break down the involved malware providing new insights and highlighting behaviors that can be used to help identify this activity.
Elastic Security researchers provide an overview of Operation Bleeding Bear, including how it wipes the Master Boot Record, uses tampering techniques such as disabling Windows Defender, leverages process hollowing, and corrupts files across the file system. We also outline defensive recommendations, specific Indicators of Compromise (IoCs) and a how-to-locate and remediate guide using Elastic Security and the MITRE ATT&CK® framework — identifying malware components at each stage. 
Existing Elastic Security users can access these capabilities within the product. If you’re new to Elastic Security, take a look at our Quick Start guides (bite-sized training videos to get you started quickly). And you can always get started with a free 14-day trial of Elastic Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Adopt a Producer-Consumer Model for HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-adopt-a-producer-consumer-model-for-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-adopt-a-producer-consumer-model-for-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn our best practices and get customer-tested templates that help HashiCorp Vault users adopt efficient producer-consumer models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0.0-M5 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/spring-for-graphql-1-0-0-m5-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/spring-for-graphql-1-0-0-m5-released"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T15:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring for GraphQL 1.0.0-M5 is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

The M5 release is a quick follow-on after the feature-rich M4 release from December. The main goal for M5 was to move the Boot starter out of the Spring GraphQL repository and into Spring Boot proper, ahead of the first Spring Boot 2.7 milestone this Thursday. In addition to that, as always, there was plenty of feedback leading to a number of refinements and fixes.
Spring Boot GraphQL Starter

The GraphQL starter has moved out of the Spring for GraphQL project repository and into the Spring Boot repository, from where it will be made available in the upcoming 2.7.0-M1 release. Here is the GraphQL section in the Spring B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40654</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/camunda-automation-platform-7170-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T15:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the third alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17. This release features the following improvements: Camunda Run improvements 3 Bug Fixes You can download Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17.0 for free or run it with Docker. For a complete list of all improvements, take a look at the release notes. Please also see the list of known issues. If you want to dig in deeper, you can find the source code on GitHub. Camunda Run improvements We are constantly working to get the Camunda Run distro closer to what is offered from our other Camunda distros. The 7.17.0-alpha3 release provides a start to the improvements of the Camunda Run distro. Groovy scripting engine included A large...
The post Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing security risk in open source software with GitHub Actions and OpenSSF Scorecards V4]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-01-19-reducing-security-risk-oss-actions-opensff-scorecards-v4/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-01-19-reducing-security-risk-oss-actions-opensff-scorecards-v4/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T15:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the V4 release of the OpenSSF’s Scorecard project in partnership with Google.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Microsoft Azure - Unified Observability for Spring Boot applications]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/elastic-and-microsoft-azure-unified-observability-for-spring-boot-applications</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/19/elastic-and-microsoft-azure-unified-observability-for-spring-boot-applications"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Today, we are excited to announce the availability of Elastic integrations for unified observability of Spring Boot applications on Azure. You can seamlessly ship Microsoft Azure Spring Cloud logs and metrics into Elastic, instrument Spring Boot apps, and monitor every step of your cloud journey. And gain a holistic view across Spring Boot applications and other logs and metrics in your cloud and on-premises environments.

Over the past two years, we worked with many enterprise customers to learn about the scenarios they face. Many of these customers have thousands of Spring Boot applications running in on-premises data centers. As they migrate these applications to the cloud, they need to aggregate logs and metrics from these applications and instrument them for applicat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Microsoft Azure: Unified observability for Spring Boot applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-microsoft-azure-unified-observability-for-spring-boot-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-microsoft-azure-unified-observability-for-spring-boot-applications"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seamlessly ship Microsoft Azure Spring Cloud logs and metrics into Elastic and monitor every step of your cloud journey. Gain a holistic view across Spring Boot applications and other data sets in your cloud and on-premises environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemant Malik,Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Microsoft Azure: Unified observability for Spring Boot applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-microsoft-azure-unified-observability-for-spring-boot-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-microsoft-azure-unified-observability-for-spring-boot-applications"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,Elastic can now seamlessly ingest data from Microsoft Azure Spring Cloud so DevOps and SREs can monitor their Spring Boot applications to increase operational efficiency and developer productivity. ,
Azure Spring Cloud is a fully managed service for Spring applications that simplifies infrastructure management. A 2021 survey from Microsoft indicated that “end-to-end monitoring” is the second biggest challenge DevOps and IT managers face as they migrate Spring Boot applications to the cloud.
Now DevOps and SREs can monitor both Spring Boot logs and application metrics across all environments by automatically shipping them to Elastic. Teams can also correlate and add context to their observability data from Spring Boot applications with other observability data sets across their environment…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemant Malik,Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The myth about the apples]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41261</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/678594420/0/sethsblog~The-myth-about-the-apples/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T09:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In settings where sorting is difficult, half a bushel of perfect apples is worth more than a full bushel with a rotten apple in it. One bad apple can spoil a whole bunch. We pay a significant premium for pre-selection, confidence and a guarantee. Sorting adds value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic Maps can be used to track the devastating eruption of a volcano, or any natural event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/understanding-evolution-volcano-eruption-elastic-maps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/understanding-evolution-volcano-eruption-elastic-maps"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La Palma, in the Canary Islands (Spain), faced a major natural disaster with the eruption of the Cumbre Vieja volcano. Learn how Elastic Maps and Kibana were used to display and animate the evolution of lava flows on top of drone imagery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jorge Sanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic Maps can be used to track the devastating eruption of a volcano, or any natural event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/understanding-evolution-volcano-eruption-elastic-maps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/understanding-evolution-volcano-eruption-elastic-maps"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
It began with an earthquake swarm. More than 22,000 seismic events were recorded, at up to 3.5 on the Richter scale, beginning on September 11th, 2021. Just 8 days later, the first eruption on La Palma since 1971, and the largest in recorded history, commenced. For three months, lava ran out of the Cumbre Vieja volcano, pouring into the Atlantic Ocean surrounding the Canary Islands. 
The eruption destroyed more than 3,000 homes in a torrent of fire and liquid rock and caused untold impact on the islands’ fragile ecosystem and economy. Mercifully, only one death has been linked to this devastating event.
To track the path of destruction so that experts could raise awareness of the ongoing impact of the geothermal event, employees at Elastic used Elastic Maps’ time slider feature, which wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jorge Sanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Captain Picard Tea Order]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2570/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2570/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/captain_picard_tea_order.png" title="We can ask the Earl for his order once he's fully extruded from the dispenser." alt="We can ask the Earl for his order once he's fully extruded from the dispenser." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing StylEx: A New Approach for Visual Explanation of Classifiers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/introducing-stylex-new-approach-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/introducing-stylex-new-approach-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Oran Lang and Inbar Mosseri, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Neural networks can perform certain tasks remarkably well, but understanding how they reach their decisions — e.g., identifying which signals in an image cause a model to determine it to be of one class and not another —  is often a mystery. Explaining a neural model’s decision process may have high social impact in certain areas, such as analysis of medical images and autonomous driving, where human oversight is critical. These insights can also be helpful in guiding health care providers, revealing model biases, providing support for downstream decision makers, and even aiding scientific discovery. 
Previous approaches for visual explanations of classifiers, such as attention maps (e.g., Grad-CAM), highlight whic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - January 18th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/18/this-week-in-spring-january-18th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/18/this-week-in-spring-january-18th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another jam-packed, fun-filled, rock’em sock’em installment of This Week in Spring! It’s the 18th of January and I’m feelin’ great because I just got back from a three-day weekend. Here in the US, we celebrated on Monday the life of the good Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., a civil rights activist who advanced the plight of African American civil rights. Dr. King is another one of my favorite doctors, along with Drs. Syer, Strange, Who, Subramaniam, and Pollack.

How’re you? We’ve got a lot to cover so let’s get to it! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud Data Flow legend Sabby Anandan

  
First Spring Data 2022.0.0 and 2021.2.0 milestones released

  
Michael Coté on Twitter

  
the Oracle Java team’s Sharat Chander (@sharat_chandler) recently took time to thank me, along with my heroes and Bootiful Podcast guests Dr. Venkat Subramaniam (@venkat_s) and Matt Raible (@mraible), for our contributions to the Java ecosystem. I want to return the favor, Sharat, here on this very large platform: thank YOU for all you’ve done for the community. You’re an inspiration.

  
Spring Data 2021.1 SR1 and 2021.0 SR8 released

  
Spring Framework 6.0.0-M2 and 5.3.15 available now

  
Spring REST Docs 2.0.6.RELEASE

  
Spring REST Docs 3.0.0-M1

  
Spring Security 6.0.0-M1 and 5.7.0-M1 available now

  
An update about the rollout of the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK on Azure Platform Services]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How open source is supporting NASA’s new eyes in space]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-01-18-how-open-source-is-supporting-nasas-new-eyes-in-space/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-01-18-how-open-source-is-supporting-nasas-new-eyes-in-space/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T17:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the successful liftoff of the James Webb Space Telescope, we ask our very own Arfon Smith about the history of open source and space science.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 65 – @Azure Durable Functions For Automation With @LBugnion]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63268</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-65-azure-durable-functions-for-automation-with-lbugnion/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T16:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 65 – @Azure Durable Functions For Automation With @LBugnion appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chief Customer Success Officer Rick Laner has a map and mission for customer success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-welcomes-rick-laner-as-chief-customer-officer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-welcomes-rick-laner-as-chief-customer-officer"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rick Laner has built a career out of relentless focus on the customer, scaling high growth organizations to match their ambitions. Now he brings that experience to Elastic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chief Customer Success Officer Rick Laner has a map and mission for customer success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-welcomes-rick-laner-as-chief-customer-officer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-welcomes-rick-laner-as-chief-customer-officer"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Before Rick Laner joined Elastic as our new Chief Customer Success Officer, he wanted to confirm if the company was committed to scaling, focusing on the customer experience, and whether the culture is really as advertised. 
“Firstly, I really dug into the culture and tried to understand, ‘is it really how people operate? Are all the good things I heard true?’ After talking to more than 80 people in my first 8 weeks and observing how teams function, I realized it is absolutely the case,” said Rick. “People take pride in their innovation, uniqueness, making complex tasks simple, taking calculated risks, being humble and respectful. It is truly the way people operate, and the leadership do the same and reward it.  It is all true.”
Rick has made a career out of customer success, services, p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: How Can I Complete a Service Task via the REST API?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40667</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/qa-how-can-i-complete-a-service-task-via-the-rest-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let us help you make your external client claim a task, complete it, and return control to your Camunda process.
The post Q&A: How Can I Complete a Service Task via the REST API? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“The dog ate my homework”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=29666</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/678483792/0/sethsblog~The-dog-ate-my-homework/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T09:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did the dog become your teacher’s problem? When we’re actively enrolled in a journey, it’s on us. That’s the requirement once you choose to act professionally. You know the terms, the dates, the structure. It wasn’t even fine print. It’s simply the structure you agreed to be part of. Of course, enrollment is frightening. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring REST Docs 3.0.0-M1]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/17/spring-rest-docs-3-0-0-m1</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/17/spring-rest-docs-3-0-0-m1"/>
        <updated>2022-01-17T17:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring REST Docs 3.0.0-M1 is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This initial 3.0 milestone contains 13 enhancements, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. It covers the baseline upgrade efforts, in particular requiring JDK 17 and Spring Framework 6 and migrating to the Jakarta EE 9 APIs as announced in this blog post.

Please note that support for REST Assured has been removed temporarily as it is not yet compatible with Jakarta EE 9. We hope to reinstate support in a subsequent milestone prior to 3.0’s release towards the end of this year.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safely Upgrade Your Pipelines from Azure DevOps Server 2019 to Server 2020]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63226</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/safely-upgrade-from-azure-devops-server-2019-to-server-2020/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-17T16:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2019 and 2020 use two different models for retaining builds. In Azure DevOps Server 2019, users configure retention settings for each pipeline. Organization-level defaults are applied if a pipeline is not explicitly configured for retention. Builds that are retained indefinitely or by releases are marked and handled using a common bit in the build record.
The post Safely Upgrade Your Pipelines from Azure DevOps Server 2019 to Server 2020 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silviu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.0.0-M1 and 5.7.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/17/spring-security-6-0-0-m1-and-5-7-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/17/spring-security-6-0-0-m1-and-5-7-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-01-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 6.0.0-M1 and 5.7.0-M1 are available now.



This initial 6.0 milestone covers the baseline upgrade efforts, in particular requiring JDK 17+ and migrating to the Jakarta EE 9 APIs, required by Spring Framework 6, as announced in this blog post.



For the release changes, please refer to the releases page.



Stay tuned for the announcement of Spring Boot 3.0.0-M1 this week!



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring REST Docs 2.0.6.RELEASE]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/17/spring-rest-docs-2-0-6-release</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/17/spring-rest-docs-2-0-6-release"/>
        <updated>2022-01-17T13:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring REST Docs 2.0.6.RELEASE has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 18 bug fixes and documentation improvements. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“The way things are”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42143</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/678378312/0/sethsblog~The-way-things-are/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-17T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s how culture perpetuates injustice and indignity. Because that’s just the way things are around here. But the status quo isn’t permanent. The world doesn’t stay the way it was. It changes. And it’s been changing faster than ever. It doesn’t change because the status quo sub-committee had a meeting and decided to change it. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hypothesis Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2569/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2569/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/hypothesis_generation.png" title="Frazzled scientists are requesting that everyone please stop generating hypotheses for a little bit while they work through the backlog." alt="Frazzled scientists are requesting that everyone please stop generating hypotheses for a little bit while they work through the backlog." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s responsible?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42159</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/678279682/0/sethsblog~Whos-responsible/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-16T09:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freedom without consequences is a myth. Our actions always have consequences. The question is: who will bear them?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harsh feedback]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41223</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/678180744/0/sethsblog~Harsh-feedback/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-15T09:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It often comes from one of two kinds of people: People who give themselves feedback in the same heartless tone. They don’t hesitate to brutally lash out, because that’s the noise they often hear inside. And folks who honestly believe that their work is flawless. They can’t understand how anyone else can fail to measure […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Route by Task for Efficient Inference]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/learning-to-route-by-task-for-efficient.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/learning-to-route-by-task-for-efficient.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T19:10:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sneha Kudugunta, Research Software Engineer and Orhan Firat, Research Scientist, Google Research   
Scaling large language models has resulted in significant quality improvements in natural language understanding (T5), generation (GPT-3) and multilingual neural machine translation (M4). One common approach to building a larger model is to increase the depth (number of layers) and width (layer dimensionality), simply enlarging existing dimensions of the network. Such dense models take an input sequence (divided into smaller components, called tokens) and pass every token through the full network, activating every layer and parameter. While these large, dense models have achieved state-of-the-art results on multiple natural language processing (NLP) tasks, their training cost incre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s Security and Compliance Program Takes Another Step Forward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-s-security-and-compliance-program-takes-another-step-forward</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-s-security-and-compliance-program-takes-another-step-forward"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp has renewed its SOC II Type II report for HCP Vault and HCP Consul, and obtained ISO 27017 and ISO 27018 certificates for its cloud products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why it’s time for more CISOs to embrace DevSecOps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-its-time-for-cisos-embrace-devsecops</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-its-time-for-cisos-embrace-devsecops"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pairing DevOps with security offers efficiency gains, reduced risks, and cultural advantages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christine Kent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Banking: Building customer trust through secure experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/building-customer-trust-through-secure-experiences-with-open-banking</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/building-customer-trust-through-secure-experiences-with-open-banking"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Banking drives a need for fast and secure access to core bank data at scale. This creates significant opportunities to make better banking and personalized solutions for money management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why it’s time for more CISOs to embrace DevSecOps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-its-time-for-cisos-embrace-devsecops</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-its-time-for-cisos-embrace-devsecops"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
While nearly one in five companies say they are releasing code 10 times faster than in the past, more software means more security flaws, and greater opportunity for bad actors to take advantage of them. 
The faster pace and increasing risks highlight the need for IT leaders to get serious about embracing DevSecOps, a management approach that makes security a shared responsibility among development, security, and IT operations teams. One indication that DevSecOps is gaining traction in the enterprise: Nearly half of development teams used application security tools in 2020, compared to just under 30% in 2015, according to 451 Research, part of S&P Global Market Intelligence.
DevSecOps is the methodology and practice of addressing security alongside both development and operations from th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christine Kent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Banking: Building customer trust through secure experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/building-customer-trust-through-secure-experiences-with-open-banking</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/building-customer-trust-through-secure-experiences-with-open-banking"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The rise of “Open Banking” has enabled banking customers to choose to share their previously inaccessible, locked down data with all sorts of third parties — from budgeting apps to mobile wallets, to peer to peer payment providers. This revolution has been a welcome boon for banks, customers, and financial services innovators alike. The ability to securely share access and permissions to accounts has fueled the rise and growth of an entire new industry — FinTech —  as retail and institutional customers finally have the power of choice. The result has been the creation of an ever-growing ecosystem of new players constructing applications, modernizing infrastructure, and accelerating the pace of change. 
Open Banking, the catchall name for the movement in which banks offer API access to cu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.1 SR1 and 2021.0 SR8 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/14/spring-data-2021-1-sr1-and-2021-0-sr8-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/14/spring-data-2021-1-sr1-and-2021-0-sr8-released"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T15:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce Spring Data service releases 2021.1.1 and 2020.0.8.
Both releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot will pick up the artifacts with its upcoming releases.

To round things off, here are the links to the artifacts, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.1.1


  
Spring Data Commons 2.6.1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.3.1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.6.1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data MongoDB 3.3.1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data KeyValue 2.6.1 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data for Apache Geode 2.6.1 - Art…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Spring Data 2022.0.0 and 2021.2.0 milestones released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/14/first-spring-data-2022-0-0-and-2021-2-0-milestones-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/14/first-spring-data-2022-0-0-and-2021-2-0-milestones-released"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T15:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who contributed, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the first round of milestones of the Spring Data 2022.0 and 2021.2 release trains.
2021.x vs. 2022.x

You might now ask why is there a new release in the calver 2021.x version and why is there already a 2022.x release?

In parallel to working on Spring Data 3.x, aka 2022.0.0, we continue to invest in the support of the Spring Data 2.x development line. We already expect Spring Data 2.7 and 2.8 releases. So, if you want to continue using Spring Boot 2 for an extended period of time, stick to the 2021.x release trains (which are based on Spring Framework 5.3 and Java 8). That’s the reason we chose to continue with calver 2021.x, which, hopefully, makes understanding version compatibilities easie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Zeebe’s gRPC Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40630</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/securing-zeebes-grpc-communication/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curious about security between components? Take a look at Zeebe’s communication channels and how to secure them in a production deployment.
The post Securing Zeebe’s gRPC Communication appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Portfolio thinking]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=31605</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/678070900/0/sethsblog~Portfolio-thinking/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we’re not certain of the right answer, the best approach is to have a portfolio, a range of bets that reward us with resilience and significant upside. An example can be something as simple as what to put on the buffet–if you’re not sure who’s coming to the meeting, it makes sense to have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.14]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63237</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-01-14/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T09:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.01.14 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.14 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-Diagnosis and Remediation in Netflix Data Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5bcc52d853d1</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/auto-diagnosis-and-remediation-in-netflix-data-platform-5bcc52d853d1?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T04:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Vikram Srivastava and Marcelo Mayworm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinthariscope]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2568/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2568/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/spinthariscope.png" title="Other high scorers are melt-in-your-hand aluminum-destroying gallium and tritium-powered glowsticks. Lawn darts are toward the other end." alt="Other high scorers are melt-in-your-hand aluminum-destroying gallium and tritium-powered glowsticks. Lawn darts are toward the other end." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud Data Flow legend Sabby Anandan]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/13/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-data-flow-legend-sabby-anandan</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/13/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-data-flow-legend-sabby-anandan"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring Cloud Data Flow legend Sabby Anandan (@sabbyanandan).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigate Log4Shell exploits with Elastic Security and Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/investigate-log4shell-exploits-with-elastic-security-and-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/investigate-log4shell-exploits-with-elastic-security-and-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As news of Log4shell emerged, security teams all around the globe scrambled to detect, mitigate and contain the vulnerability. This blog highlights how teams can use the Elastic Search platform to detect Log4shell exploit attempts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Spiteri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigate Log4Shell exploits with Elastic Security and Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/investigate-log4shell-exploits-with-elastic-security-and-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/investigate-log4shell-exploits-with-elastic-security-and-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Overview
Following the discovery of Log4Shell, a vulnerability in Log4J2, Elastic released a blog post describing how users of our platform can leverage Elastic Security to help defend their networks. We also released an advisory detailing how Elastic products and users are impacted.
In this blog, we expand on these initial posts and highlight how the combination of security and observability solutions can provide deep visibility into the exploited vulnerability and arm security analysts with valuable data for root cause analysis.
Gaining the upper hand - combining Observability and Security data
Along with Elastic Security, we provide a comprehensive Observability suite within Kibana. Observability is primarily referring to the combination of application performance monitoring (APM), lo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Spiteri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.7 Reimagines UI and Extends Deployment Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-7-reimagines-ui-and-extends-deployment-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-7-reimagines-ui-and-extends-deployment-workflows"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.7 focuses on enhancing user experience with a significant UI redesign, improved support for more complex deployment workflows, and extensible CI integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top-rated entries from Game Off 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-01-13-top-entries-from-game-off-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-01-13-top-entries-from-game-off-2021/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T20:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the top games created in our annual game jam as rated and reviewed by the developers that made them. Game On! 🤘🏻]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Vision with Sparse Mixture of Experts]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/scaling-vision-with-sparse-mixture-of.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/scaling-vision-with-sparse-mixture-of.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T18:04:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Carlos Riquelme, Research Scientist and Joan Puigcerver, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
Advances in deep learning over the last few decades have been driven by a few key elements. With a small number of simple but flexible mechanisms (i.e., inductive biases such as convolutions or sequence attention), increasingly large datasets, and more specialized hardware, neural networks can now achieve impressive results on a wide range of tasks, such as image classification, machine translation, and protein folding prediction. 
However, the use of large models and datasets comes at the expense of significant computational requirements. Yet, recent works suggest that large model sizes might be necessary for strong generalization and robustness, so training large models whil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How five open source communities are using GitHub Discussions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-01-13-how-five-open-source-communities-are-using-github-discussions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-01-13-how-five-open-source-communities-are-using-github-discussions/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T17:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From answering questions about a new release to fielding feature requests, here’s how five open source communities use GitHub Discussions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第201話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496701320583</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496701320583"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.0-M2 and 5.3.15 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/13/spring-framework-6-0-0-m2-and-5-3-15-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/13/spring-framework-6-0-0-m2-and-5-3-15-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T12:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.0-M2 and 5.3.15 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.15 includes 17 fixes and improvements as a recommended upgrade for all Spring production scenarios. Spring Framework 6.0.0-M2 includes 6 additional fixes and improvements specific to the 6.0 branch.

Stay tuned for the announcement of Spring Boot 3.0.0-M1 next week!

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Source Software Security Summit: securing the world’s code together]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-01-13-open-source-software-security-summit-securing-the-worlds-code-together/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-01-13-open-source-software-security-summit-securing-the-worlds-code-together/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T10:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My colleague Stormy Peters and I are proud to represent GitHub at the White House’s Open Source Software Security Summit to share how securing open source begins by empowering developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harder, easier and more convenient]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=31822</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/677940676/0/sethsblog~Harder-easier-and-more-convenient/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T09:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider the windows on a car. First, they were manually clipped into place. And then they were hand-rolled into position. But that was too difficult. So the electric window was born. But holding your finger on the button for 10 seconds was onerous, so now, it’s automatic. It’s easy to see the trend toward convenience […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we ship GitHub Mobile every week]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-01-12-how-we-ship-github-mobile-every-week/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-01-12-how-we-ship-github-mobile-every-week/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-12T17:56:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how the GitHub Mobile Team automates their release process with GitHub Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Azure AD Identity with HashiCorp Vault — Part 2: Vault OIDC Auth Method]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/integrating-azure-ad-identity-with-hashicorp-vault-part-2-vault-oidc-auth-method</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/integrating-azure-ad-identity-with-hashicorp-vault-part-2-vault-oidc-auth-method"/>
        <updated>2022-01-12T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to configure HashiCorp Vault’s OIDC auth method to use Azure as an identity provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New AWS Console Home Experience]]></title>
        <id>0cf5407d49bfeca70f467a351f1a027b407f2638</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/a-new-aws-console-home-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-12T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are reading this blog, there is a high chance you frequently use the AWS Management Console. I taught AWS classes for years. During classes, students’ first hands-on experience with the AWS Cloud happened on the console, and I bet yours did too. Until today, the home page of the console showed your most […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 64 – Building SOC Efficiency with @Azure Sentinel with @rodtrent]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63217</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-64-building-soc-efficiency-with-azure-sentinel-with-rodtrent/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-12T16:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 64 – Building SOC Efficiency with @Azure Sentinel with @rodtrent appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CB radio]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=29897</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/677811912/0/sethsblog~CB-radio/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-12T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was huge and kept growing by leaps and bounds. Until it didn’t. (My license was KFV2338, a number I haven’t said out loud in 40 years). CB radio took off because human beings desperately want to connect with people they know and be heard by people they don’t. And then it went away because […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Language Development]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2567/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2567/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/language_development.png" title="The worst is the Terrible Twos, when they're always throwing things and shrieking, &quot;forsooth, to bed thou shalt not take me, cur!&quot;" alt="The worst is the Terrible Twos, when they're always throwing things and shrieking, &quot;forsooth, to bed thou shalt not take me, cur!&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Processes for Camunda Cloud and Zeebe]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40582</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/testing-processes-for-camunda-cloud-and-zeebe/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T21:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Zeebe-Process-Test featured in the 1.3.0 release. Learn how you can unit test BPMN processes for Camunda Cloud and Zeebe.
The post Testing Processes for Camunda Cloud and Zeebe appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research: Themes from 2021 and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/google-research-themes-from-2021-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/01/google-research-themes-from-2021-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T19:01:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeff Dean, Senior Fellow and SVP of Google Research, on behalf of the entire Google Research community
Over the last several decades, I've witnessed a lot of change in the fields of machine learning (ML) and computer science. Early approaches, which often fell short, eventually gave rise to modern approaches that have been very successful. Following that long-arc pattern of progress, I think we'll see a number of exciting advances over the next several years, advances that will ultimately benefit the lives of billions of people with greater impact than ever before. In this post, I’ll highlight five areas where ML is poised to have such impact. For each, I’ll discuss related research (mostly from 2021) and the directions and progress we’ll likely see in the next few years. 
      …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experimentation is a major focus of Data Science across Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f67923f8e985</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/experimentation-is-a-major-focus-of-data-science-across-netflix-f67923f8e985?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T16:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Tingley with Wenjing Zheng, Simon Ejdemyr, Stephanie Lane, Colin McFarland, Andy Rhines, Sophia Liu, Mihir Tendulkar, Kevin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - January 11th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/11/this-week-in-spring-january-11th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/11/this-week-in-spring-january-11th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How’re you? I’m fresh off my three weeks respite and this is my first blog back on the clock officially! It’s so good to be back. I’ve been busy over the break, working on updating my blog and on updating the Reactive Spring book. Fun, fun! Anyway, we’ve got a fun week to recap, so let’s get right to it! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud co-founder Spencer Gibb (and happy new year!)

  
Blog: Kubernetes is Moving on From Dockershim: Commitments and Next Steps

  
My talk from the last Brighton Kotlin session of 2021 is up: Bootiful Kotlin with Josh Long 

  
Improving Micrometer’s Build with Gradle Enterprise | Gradle Enterprise

  
Introducing the Spring Integration Groovy DSL

  
JDK 18 Early-Access Builds

  
Spring Framework CVE-2021-22060 has been published

  
Uploading Media in Spring Boot Programmatically With Cloudinary - DEV Community

  
There’s a new release of Project Reactor, that brings various libraries up to date!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cawemo Enterprise (On-Premises) 1.9.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40505</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/cawemo-enterprise-on-premises-1-9-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re happy to announce the 1.9.0 release of Cawemo Enterprise On-Premises. If you’re not yet a Camunda customer, sign up for a free trial.
The post Cawemo Enterprise (On-Premises) 1.9.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cawemo Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.7.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40396</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/camunda-optimize-3-7-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.7.0. Download the release today or get a free 30-day trial.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.7.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.3.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40556</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/camunda-cloud-1-3-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how the Camunda Cloud 1.3.0 release allows Java developers to add automated testing of BPMN process diagrams to their CI/CD pipelines.
The post Camunda Cloud 1.3.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 Hpc6a Instance Optimized for High Performance Computing]]></title>
        <id>0a641a338fac9c602c3f4814b6c048cf09fa4740</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-hpc6a-instance-optimized-for-high-performance-computing/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-11T00:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Performance Computing (HPC) allows scientists and engineers to solve complex, compute-intensive problems such as computational fluid dynamics (CFD), weather forecasting, and genomics. HPC applications typically require instances with high memory bandwidth, a low latency, high bandwidth network interconnect and access to a fast parallel file system. Many customers have turned to AWS to run […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.07]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63171</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-01-07/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T11:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.01.07 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.07 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DiscoverDev - curated engineering articles for Fri, 07 Jan 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://discoverdev.io/archive/2022-01-07.html</id>
        <link href="http://discoverdev.io/archive/2022-01-07.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shops on Facebook and Instagram: Understanding relationships between products to improve buyer and seller experience 
 
          
            
 General and Scalable Parallelization for Neural Networks 
 
          
            
 Video: Understanding Queuing Theory and Software Performance 
 
          
            
 Snaring the Bad Folks 
 
          
            
 Deep Learning vs Machine Learning Challenger Models for Default Risk with Explainability]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud cofounder Spencer Gibb (and happy new year!)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/06/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-cofounder-spencer-gibb-and-happy-new-year</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/06/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-cofounder-spencer-gibb-and-happy-new-year"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans, and happy new year! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring Cloud co-founder, legend, and the all-around nice guy Spencer Gibb (@spencerbgibb).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Spring Integration Groovy DSL]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/06/introducing-spring-integration-groovy-dsl</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/01/06/introducing-spring-integration-groovy-dsl"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T17:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year, Spring community!



Hope you had great holidays and ready for new excitements in front of us.



After the rest and recharging during Christmas break I decided to pay honor to my favorite language back in days - Groovy.



And now it’s my pleasure to present you a brand new Groovy DSL for Spring Integration.
You perhaps heard about our old attempt to make a Groovy DSL on top of Spring Integration XML support.
But the solution was pretty cumbersome (especially for protocol-specific channel adapters) and support burden has grown tremendously.
This my latest implementation is fully based on already mature Java DSL and its builder pattern support.



Having 10 years experience with Gradle I thought that it is going be easy enough for me to prepare quickly someth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service Adds IPv6 Networking]]></title>
        <id>a25768b407b6c7537fa13a1b030520c8673d316b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-elastic-kubernetes-service-adds-ipv6-networking/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T17:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can deploy applications that use IPv6 address space on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS). Many of our customers are standardizing Kubernetes as their compute infrastructure platform for cloud and on-premises applications. Amazon EKS makes it easy to deploy containerized workloads. It provides highly available clusters and automates tasks such as patching, node […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reselling Made Easy: BuyBay Automates E-commerce Process with Camunda]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40270</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/reselling-made-easy-buybay-automates-e-commerce-process-with-camunda/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how BuyBay worked with Camunda to enable more efficient operations of the reselling journey and automate key decision-making tasks.  
The post Reselling Made Easy: BuyBay Automates E-commerce Process with Camunda appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: December 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-01-05-github-availability-report-december-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-01-05-github-availability-report-december-2021/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T21:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December, we experienced no incidents resulting in service downtime to our core services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the community powers GitHub Advanced Security with CodeQL queries]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-01-05-how-the-community-powers-github-advanced-security-with-codeql-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-01-05-how-the-community-powers-github-advanced-security-with-codeql-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T18:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Security Lab’s CodeQL bounty program fuels GitHub Advanced Security with queries written by the open source community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp 2021 Year in Review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2021-year-in-review</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-2021-year-in-review"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look back at some of the most important moments of a very eventful 2021 for HashiCorp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Azure AD Identity with HashiCorp Vault — Part 1: Azure Application Auth via OIDC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/integrating-azure-ad-identity-hashicorp-vault-part-1-application-auth-oidc</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/integrating-azure-ad-identity-hashicorp-vault-part-1-application-auth-oidc"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to achieve user authentication to HashiCorp Vault with OIDC using Microsoft Azure AD as a central identity provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Ambassador Call for Submissions 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-ambassador-call-for-submissions-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-ambassador-call-for-submissions-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are once again calling for nominations and applications to the HashiCorp Ambassadors program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Overcome a Legacy Mindset]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=40145</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/01/how-to-overcome-a-legacy-mindset/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have a truly innovative enterprise? Explore what exactly a legacy mindset is, and how to overcome one in your organization.
The post How to Overcome a Legacy Mindset appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 63 – Getting Started with @Azure and WebAssembly with @StevenMurawski]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63156</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-63-getting-started-with-azure-and-webassembly-with-stevenmurawski/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T16:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 63 – Getting Started with @Azure and WebAssembly with @StevenMurawski appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book Review: The Future of Fusion Energy]]></title>
        <id>http://martin.kleppmann.com/2022/01/03/future-of-fusion-energy.html</id>
        <link href="http://martin.kleppmann.com/2022/01/03/future-of-fusion-energy.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I give a five-star ⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️ rating to the following book: Jason Parisi and Justin Ball. The Future of Fusion Energy. World Scientific, 2019. ISBN 978-1-78634-749-7. Available from Amazon US, Amazon UK, and many other retailers. I came to this book looking for answers to questions such as: Is there still...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Kleppmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[年賀状] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496666439231</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496666439231"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo – Culture and Mindset]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63045</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-culture-and-mindset/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T11:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before we discuss culture and mindset in Dojo, let’s begin with quizzes on culture.
a. Using Agile Methodology
The post DevOps Dojo – Culture and Mindset appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.12.31]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63121</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-12-31/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T10:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.12.31 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.12.31 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>