<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-12T00:15:27.175Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-12T00:15:27.175Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.6.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Create Microsoft SQL Server Instances of Amazon RDS on AWS Outposts]]></title>
        <id>ac7cf694748e381f3ecd13f45c5f0e00f775e991</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/olh38OAOylQ/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T19:32:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, we announced Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) on AWS Outposts, which allows you to deploy fully managed database instances in your on-premises environments. AWS Outposts is a fully managed service that extends AWS infrastructure, AWS services, APIs, and tools to virtually any datacenter, co-location space, or on-premises facility for a truly consistent […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes – Microsoft Identity with Christos Matskas!]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61625</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-microsoft-identity-with-christos-matskas/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It&#8217;s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific / 2 PM Eastern on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes &#8211; Microsoft Identity with Christos Matskas! appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 11th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/11/this-week-in-spring-may-11th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/11/this-week-in-spring-may-11th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! First: a happy belated mother&rsquo;s day to you! Being a mom is already the hardest job, and it got considerably harder this last year as a global pandemic descended on the world forcing so many new complications on an already fraught enterprise: raising a family. So, thank you, moms. (Also: you deserve far more than just a day!) 


  
Have you registered for tomorrow&rsquo;s brand new (_free_!) SpringOne Tour installment? Don&rsquo;…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61694</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/may-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Inconsistent Test Results data when using Microsoft.TeamFoundation.TestManagement.Client.
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.1 Patch 3
The post May patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explore HashiCorp Consul with Docker Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/explore-hashicorp-consul-with-docker-compose</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/explore-hashicorp-consul-with-docker-compose"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Compose provides a way to quickly explore HashiCorp Consul’s core concepts such as service discovery, service mesh, and secure datacenter deployment on your local system. If you're looking for a quick and simple way to learn Consul concepts or you want a simple testing environment for quickly trying out new configurations, Consul’s Docker compose resources can help you achieve your goals.
To get started, check out the Deploy a Secure Datacenter with Docker Compose tutorial. This tutorial will guide y…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Local Zones Are Now Open in Boston, Miami, and Houston]]></title>
        <id>59a17c201dc1612c584da4671571f6299a3cc1bc</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/AMAVyWivYOA/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Local Zones place select AWS services (compute, storage, database, and so forth) close to large population, industry, and IT centers. They support use cases such as real-time gaming, hybrid migrations, and media &amp; entertainment content creation that need single-digit millisecond latency for end-users in a specific geographic area. Last December I told you about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nextmv: Optimization in Fluid Work Environments with Carolyn Mooney]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10908</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/10/nextmv-optimization-in-fluid-work-environments-with-carolyn-mooney/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=nextmv-optimization-in-fluid-work-environments-with-carolyn-mooney"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T02:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The traveling salesman problem is a classic challenge of finding the shortest and most efficient route for a person to take given a list of destinations. This is one of many real-world optimization problems that companies encounter. How should they schedule product distribution, or promote product bundles, or define sales territories? The answers to these
The post Nextmv: Optimization in Fluid Work Environments with Carolyn Mooney appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpringOne Tour Booternetes Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/10/springone-tour-booternetes-europe</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/10/springone-tour-booternetes-europe"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T00:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Cote, Hannah Foxwell, and Jakub Pilimon talk about application modernization strategies while driving production outcomes with Spring on Kubernetes. For more great Tanzu, Kubernetes, and Spring content, check out our VMware Tanzu channel: https://www.youtube.com/c/VMwareTanzu

VMware Tanzu helps you modernize your applications and infrastructure with a common goal: deliver better software to production, continuously. The portfolio simplifies multi-cloud operations while freeing developers to move f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resolve IT Incidents Faster with Incident Manager, a New Capability of AWS Systems Manager]]></title>
        <id>a782aff927c5ec2c0d1bc4c64000011ddc707801</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/JJ_9Uim_LcM/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T22:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT engineers pride themselves on the skill and care they put into building applications and infrastructure. However, as much as we all hate to admit it, there is no such thing as 100% uptime. Everything will fail at some point, often at the worst possible time, leading to many a ruined evening, birthday party, or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Network Resource Purge parameter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-network-resource-purge-parameter</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-network-resource-purge-parameter"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Network Automation continues to be a popular domain for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. We have continually developed additional resource modules to make automating network appliances easier, and more approachable, for novices and experts alike. These resource modules provide a consistent experience across multiple network vendors. There are seven main state parameters for resource modules: merged, replaced, overridden, deleted, gathered, rendered and parsed. The Ansible network team is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.1.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/10/spring-authorization-server-0-1-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/10/spring-authorization-server-0-1-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.1.1.



You can download it from repo.spring.io and Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




compile 'org.springframework.security.experimental:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.1.1'




For additional details on this new project, see the initial announcement and project page.



The main features delivered in this release are:

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[90's Kid Space Program]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2461/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2461/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temporal Product: Managing State with Ryland Goldstein]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10893</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/08/temporal-product-managing-state-with-ryland-goldstein/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=temporal-product-managing-state-with-ryland-goldstein"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T09:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microservice architecture has become very common over the past few years because of the availability of containers and container orchestrators like Kubernetes. While containers are overall positive for scaling apps and making them more available, they’ve also introduced hurdles like persisting data and state, and container restarts or pod failures. Development teams put significant work
The post Temporal Product: Managing State with Ryland Goldstein appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Botpress: Natural Language Processing with Sylvain Perron]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10892</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/07/botpress-natural-language-processing-with-sylvain-perron/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=botpress-natural-language-processing-with-sylvain-perron"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T22:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Natural Language Processing (NLP) is a branch of artificial intelligence concerned with giving computers the ability to understand text and spoken words. “Understanding” includes intent, sentiment, and what’s important in the message. NLP powers things like voice-operated software, digital assistants, customer service chat bots, and many other academic, consumer and enterprise tools. The company Botpress
The post Botpress: Natural Language Processing with Sylvain Perron appeared first on Software Engineerin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.05.07]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61670</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-05-07/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Friday everyone! This week was overflowing with awesome blog posts, and it was hard to narrow them down to just a handful! This week&#8217;s top posts cover reporting in Azure, publishing packages to Azure Pipelines, how we can create diagrams with code in Pipelines,
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.05.07 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary Deptawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro of DevOps Dojo]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61643</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/intro-of-devops-dojo/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[&#8220;From taking once a year to release a packaged software in 2015,
We were sitting with a group of CxOs from Germany at the Redmond Executive Briefing Center in February 2019,
The post Intro of DevOps Dojo appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vaccinated]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2460/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2460/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Friend, fellow Spring Developer Advocate, Kotlin Google Developer Expert, and Java Champion, Mark Heckler]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/06/a-bootiful-podcast-friend-fellow-spring-developer-advocate-kotlin-google-developer-expert-and-java-champion-mark-heckler</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/06/a-bootiful-podcast-friend-fellow-spring-developer-advocate-kotlin-google-developer-expert-and-java-champion-mark-heckler"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T22:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of A Bootiful Podcast! This week, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to his friend, fellow Spring Developer Advocate, Kotlin Google Developer Expert, and Java Champion: Mark Heckler (@mkheck). Mark has also just written a well-recommended book from O&rsquo;Reilly called Spring Boot: Up and Running.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Querying a petabyte of cloud storage in 10 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/querying-a-petabyte-of-cloud-storage-in-10-minutes</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/querying-a-petabyte-of-cloud-storage-in-10-minutes"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic's new frozen data tier decouples compute from storage and leverages low-cost object stores such as Google Cloud Storage, Azure Blob Storage, or Amazon S3 to directly power searches. It provides unlimited scaling of storage while preserving the ability to efficiently query the data without any need to rehydrate it first, making it easier and cheaper to manage data at scale.

In this blog post we compare search performance on the new frozen tier with the existing Elasticsearch data tiers, and we show …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yannick Welsch,Dimitrios Liappis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Auto Scaling Strategy with HashiCorp Nomad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-auto-scaling-strategy-with-hashicorp-nomad</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-auto-scaling-strategy-with-hashicorp-nomad"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nomad Autoscaler enables automated application and cluster scaling of your Nomad workloads and infrastructure. Adapting quickly to changes is crucial for serving users and meeting business goals and requirements. Cluster scaling can also help reduce infrastructure costs and remove the manual work that slows down your team.
In its latest release as part of the Nomad 1.1 beta, the Nomad Autoscaler brings new plugins and capabilities that aim to expand when and where autoscaling can be used, making it easi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How finding time for cooking and culture helps forge better connections at work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-finding-time-for-cooking-and-culture-helps-forge-better-connections-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-finding-time-for-cooking-and-culture-helps-forge-better-connections-at-work"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic is committed to providing a flexible, balanced home life for our Elasticians. It’s in our Source Code. And part of that Source Code — Home, Dinner — has helped Kathy Chen, visual designer on our in-house design team, to reconnect with her mother’s cooking and her Chinese culture.

“When I was a kid my mom used to make dumplings for my packed lunch,” says Kathy. “Other kids would make fun of it. At the time I was embarrassed, but now I appreciate how much effort she put into giving me those tastes of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Frazer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Relic: Telemetry and Intelligent Observability with Zain Asgar and Ishan Mukherjee]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10885</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/05/05/new-relic-telemetry-and-intelligent-observability-with-zain-asgar-and-ishan-mukherjee/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=new-relic-telemetry-and-intelligent-observability-with-zain-asgar-and-ishan-mukherjee"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T23:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In software engineering, telemetry is the data that is collected about your applications. Unlike logging, which is used in the development of apps to pinpoint errors and code flows, telemetry data includes all operational data including logs, metrics, events, traces, usage, and other analytical data. Companies usually visualize this information to troubleshoot problems and understand
The post New Relic: Telemetry and Intelligent Observability with Zain Asgar and Ishan Mukherjee appeared first on Software En…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perspectives from the federal public sector: Enable mission success with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/perspectives-from-the-federal-public-sector-enable-mission-success-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/perspectives-from-the-federal-public-sector-enable-mission-success-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a year of accelerated change in the federal industry, the Federal Public Sector event focused on the progress you’ve made, the trends demanding your attention, and the Elastic capabilities that continue to guide federal agencies, offices, and departments towards a search-enabled future.&nbsp;

With a theme of&nbsp;Accelerate the mission. Start with search, the ElasticON US Federal event centered around some key takeaways:&nbsp;

Data volumes will increase regardless of the size, scape, or scope of you…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Coles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNCF Technology Radar Highlights HashiCorp Vault’s Broad Multi-Cloud Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cncf-technology-radar-highlights-vault-broad-multi-cloud-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cncf-technology-radar-highlights-vault-broad-multi-cloud-adoption"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) Technology Radar team started work on its latest edition focusing on secrets management, they “expected the results to overwhelmingly show that organizations are using the offering of the public cloud they are already using,” recalled Steve Nolen, a site reliability engineer (SRE) at RStudio and a Radar team member, in the CNCF Radar report. But the survey results upended that expectation.
The survey asked CNCF end users what they currently use and recommend…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieve HashiCorp Vault Secrets with Kubernetes CSI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/retrieve-hashicorp-vault-secrets-with-kubernetes-csi</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/retrieve-hashicorp-vault-secrets-with-kubernetes-csi"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of HashiCorp Vault 1.7, we have removed the “experimental” note from our Vault Provider for Secrets Store CSI Driver project and it is now in beta. This project started with this request to gauge the level of interest in using CSI to expose secrets on a volume within a Kubernetes pod.
In this article, I’ll give some background on CSI drivers, compare the sidecar and Vault CSI provider methods for Vault secrets retrieval in Kubernetes, and then walk through the process of implementing the Va…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding free and open Elastic APM as part of your Elastic Observability deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post we showed you how to get started with the free and open tier of Elastic Observability. Today we'll walk through what you need to do to expand your deployment so you can start gathering metrics from application performance monitoring (APM), or "tracing" data in your observability cluster, for free.

What is APM?
Application performance monitoring lets you see where your applications spend their time, what they are doing, what other applications or services they are calling, and what errors o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring as code with Sensu + Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/monitoring-as-code-with-sensu-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/monitoring-as-code-with-sensu-ansible"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive infrastructure as code (IaC) initiative should include monitoring and observability. Incorporating the active monitoring of the infrastructure under management results in a symbiotic relationship in which failures are detected automatically, enabling event-driven code changes and new deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jef@sensu.io (Jef Spaleta)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 4th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/04/this-week-in-spring-may-4th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/04/this-week-in-spring-may-4th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T00:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How&rsquo;re you doing? I hope you&rsquo;re doing well, and that the Fourth (of May) is with you. 

Today may be the 4th, but yesterday was the third of May, and that marks the 20th anniversary of the JdbcTemplate, which I think is super cool! Happy birthday, JdbcTemplate! The JdbcTemplate was important to a lot of people because it&rsquo;s one of those great little utilities that made it easy to justify pulling Spring into application…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 2020]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2459/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2459/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Gateway for Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/04/spring-cloud-gateway-for-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/04/spring-cloud-gateway-for-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T21:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spring Cloud Gateway (SCG) open-source project has been extended and offered commercially for the Kubernetes platform. This new offering lets you automate the deployment of an API gateway service by applying YAML configuration objects to a Kubernetes cluster. You can also update the routes of API gateways in Kubernetes by applying YAML configuration to the cluster.

Spring Cloud Gateway for Kubernetes supports routing to services that are written in any language, as long as they expose HTTP endpoints. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Prem To The Cloud (episode 7): Migrating to Azure SQL]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61621</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/on-prem-to-the-cloud-episode-7-migrating-to-azure-sql/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T18:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our customers have been wanting some more basic, getting started material on taking their on-prem applications and moving them to the cloud. This video series does just that. Starting with a simple on-prem solution, lifting and shifting and then slowly evolving the app through its many stages until it is a 100% cloud native app.
The post On-Prem To The Cloud (episode 7): Migrating to Azure SQL appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Resources for Workloads with Nomad 1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-for-workloads-with-nomad-1-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-resources-for-workloads-with-nomad-1-1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.1 introduces several new resource control mechanisms to unlock higher efficiency and better performance, including memory oversubscription, reserved CPU cores, and improved UI visibility into resource utilization. This blog post takes a closer look at each of those new features.
Learn more: Announcing HashiCorp Nomad 1.1. Beta
»Memory Oversubscription
Setting task memory limits is a challenging act of balance. Job authors must set a memory limit for each task — if it’s too low, the task ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Controlled Remote State Access for Terraform Cloud and Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-controlled-remote-state-access-for-terraform-cloud-and-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-controlled-remote-state-access-for-terraform-cloud-and-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many security challenges to consider when running an infrastructure provisioning workflow based on infrastructure as code. Assessing who has access to what information at every step of the workflow should be a primary focus. For example, state files can contain information such as passwords or private keys and, in many cases, should be considered sensitive. We recommend securely storing state files remotely through a backend, like Terraform Cloud, which offers encrypted transmission and storage. H…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to HashiCorp at KubeCon Europe Virtual 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-guide-to-hashicorp-at-kubecon-europe-virtual-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-guide-to-hashicorp-at-kubecon-europe-virtual-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe Virtual kicks off this week, HashiCorp will once again be sponsoring the event, hosting informative deep-dive sessions (YouTube playlist here), and answering questions at our digital booth. Our technical experts will also be on-hand to do product demos.
HashiCorp continues to make Kubernetes a first-class citizen in our ecosystem with ongoing roadmaps for Kubernetes integrations within HashiCorp Terraform, Vault, and Consul. Over a year ago, we deepened our commitment with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon FinSpace Simplifies Data Management and Analytics for Financial Services]]></title>
        <id>5d9d7901c0f2a705e6da6f3a3ee45368c37c33ff</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/TtNYudIv4iI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T22:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing data is the core of the Financial Services Industry (FSI). I worked for private banking and fund management companies and helped analysts to collect, aggregate, and analyze hundreds of petabytes of data from internal data sources, such as portfolio management, order management, and accounting systems, but also from external data sources, such as real-time […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CloudFront Functions – Run Your Code at the Edge with Low Latency at Any Scale]]></title>
        <id>6a19c82bf6ccb578a508a38136408971f389d9da</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/5mteSKBDr8Q/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T21:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Amazon CloudFront, you can securely deliver data, videos, applications, and APIs to your customers globally with low latency and high transfer speeds. To offer a customized experience and the lowest possible latency, many modern applications execute some form of logic at the edge. The use cases for applying logic at the edge can be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.5.0-RC2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/03/spring-security-5-5-0-rc2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/05/03/spring-security-5-5-0-rc2-released"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T20:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Security 5.5.0-RC2!



After releasing 5.5.0-RC1 we received some feedback on our APIs that required further refinements. This release finalizes the APIs for the 5.5.0 release later this month.



You can find the complete details in the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IPv6 fencing Conditional Access Policies now supported]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61632</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/ipv6-fencing-conditional-access-policies-now-supported/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T16:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies are placing increasing importance on ensuring that only authorized team members are allowed to access valuable company resources on Azure DevOps. One such way they have been able to do so is through conditional access policies (CAPs) they have set in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).
The post IPv6 fencing Conditional Access Policies now supported appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 10th Birthday – AWS Identity and Access Management]]></title>
        <id>5c30cc5211fd69350e157ce3a7d2124b4431379f</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/JisYEOZh878/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T16:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 turned 15 earlier this year, and Amazon EC2 will do the same in a couple of months. Today we are celebrating the tenth birthday of AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM). The First Decade Let’s take a walk through the last decade and revisit some of the most significant IAM launches: May 2011 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Nomad 1.1 Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-nomad-1-1-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-nomad-1-1-beta"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that the beta release of HashiCorp Nomad 1.1 is now available. Nomad is a simple and flexible orchestrator used to deploy and manage containers and non-containerized applications across on-premises and cloud environments. Nomad is widely adopted and used in production by organizations such as Cloudflare, Roblox, Q2, Pandora, and GitHub.
Nomad 1.1 delivers more than 10 new features to enable more flexible scheduling and a simplified operator experience. The core Nomad scheduler has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handling OOB Network Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/handling-oob-network-changes</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/handling-oob-network-changes"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog I would like to showcase the power of Ansible Content Collections to build powerful abstractions. Collections are a distribution format for Ansible content that can include playbooks, roles, modules and plugins. For this blog post, let us address an Infrastructure as Code(IaC) use case for network configuration management of BGP. We will walk through examples for both Cisco IOS and Arista EOS devices. 
First, let us define a data-model that encapsulates the vendor-agnostic configuration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>achenamp@redhat.com (Ajay Chenampara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble Wrap]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2458/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2458/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[User Survey: How Do You Connect with Consul?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/user-survey-how-you-connect-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/user-survey-how-you-connect-consul"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul is one of our most widely downloaded tools — it was downloaded some 16 million times in 2020. It doesn’t draw a lot of attention to itself in the IT world, but it quietly gets the job done and enjoys substantial popularity..
To bring Consul’s usefulness into greater focus, we wanted to ask users to tell us how they use Consul. We created a simple survey form to make it easy for you to tell us how you’re deploying Consul in production, your home labs, or in proof of concepts at work. It shou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.04.30]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61603</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-04-30/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T15:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Friday! If you didn&#8217;t catch it, we recently ran an online event &#8211; All Around Azure: DevOps with GitHub. The recorded sessions will be posted early next week, so check it out! Until then, there&#8217;s these great community posts to take us into the weekend.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.04.30 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Murawski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delivery Plans 2.0 is now GA!]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61579</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/delivery-plans-2-0-is-now-ga/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T15:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure Boards team is thrilled to announce the GA of Delivery Plans in the Azure DevOps Service!
The post Delivery Plans 2.0 is now GA! appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Oracle's Dilip Krishnan about Spring Fox, the Oracle Cloud Lift team, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/29/a-bootiful-podcast-oracle-s-dilip-krishnan-about-spring-fox-the-oracle-cloud-lift-team-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/29/a-bootiful-podcast-oracle-s-dilip-krishnan-about-spring-fox-the-oracle-cloud-lift-team-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T22:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of A Bootiful Podcast. In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talk to Oracle&rsquo;s Dilip Krishnan (@dilipkrish) about Spring Fox, the Oracle Cloud Lift team, and so much more. 


  
SpringFox website - http://springfox.io

  
Oracle cloud lift - https://www.oracle.com/cloud/cloud-lift/


A cool project that needs some love - ohm from OSS contributor Christophe Bornet, one of the key contributors to JHipster and OpenAPI Generator]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The essentials of central log collection with WEF and WEC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-essentials-of-central-log-collection-with-wef-wec</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-essentials-of-central-log-collection-with-wef-wec"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week we covered the essentials of event logging: Ensuring that all your systems are writing logs about the important events or activities occurring on them. This week we will cover the essentials of centrally collecting these Event Logs on a Window Event Collector (WEC) server, which then forwards all logs to Elastic Security. 
 
WEF and WEC
 
Modern versions of Windows include the Windows Remote Management (WinRM) services that implement the WS-Management (WSman) protocol, and just to add to the acron…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thorben Jändling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring as Code with Terraform Cloud and Checkly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/monitoring-as-code-with-terraform-cloud-and-checkly</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/monitoring-as-code-with-terraform-cloud-and-checkly"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guest post was written by Hannes Lenke, co-founder and CEO at Checkly, the active monitoring platform for developers.
HashiCorp Terraform Cloud enables you to seamlessly provision infrastructure as code, consolidating configurations in source control and bringing transparency and replayability to a previously manual workflow. The same approach can be used to define the way our APIs and web apps are monitored.
In this blog post, you will learn how to use Terraform together with Checkly to provision your…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Career Stories | Tom Wilde and Jan Kumorowicz on growing their sales careers with cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-career-stories-tom-wilde-and-jan-kumorowicz-on-growing-their-sales-careers-with-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-career-stories-tom-wilde-and-jan-kumorowicz-on-growing-their-sales-careers-with-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does a career journey into the inside sales team look like at Elastic? We talked to two of our own — Tom Wilde and Jan Kumorowicz — about moving from user success manager roles into cloud sales, and what it’s like to be at the start of a customer’s journey.
Tom Wilde, inside cloud account executive

After about two years as a user success manager, I began to master the art of outbound sales — cold calling potential enterprise customers, working to find new leads via LinkedIn, and having proof-of-concep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network MOP's as automated workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/network-mops-as-automated-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/network-mops-as-automated-workflows"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does successful network automation look like? What are the metrics that can measure the effectiveness of this practice and its business value?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Leiva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Accelerate Spring Apps to Cloud at Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/28/webinar-accelerate-spring-apps-to-cloud-at-scale</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/28/webinar-accelerate-spring-apps-to-cloud-at-scale"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ready to take Spring Boot apps to the happiest place on earth - production at enterprise scale - with Azure Spring Cloud and without worrying about infrastructure, application life cycle, monitoring, container intricacies, Kubernetes. Join Microsoft&rsquo;s Asir Vedamuthu Selvasingh (@asirselvasingh), next week, at 10-11 AM CT, May 4th, 2021, and learn how enterprise leaders:


  
Run Spring apps in the cloud at enterprise scale.

  
Improve developer productivity with DevOps tooling integration and cont…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Nimble Studio – Build a Creative Studio in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>c5f7296ceaa558434411523945f3624ed8a2b4c6</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/_T_wMsOQObs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T21:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Nimble Studio is a new service that creative studios can use to produce visual effects, animations, and interactive content entirely in the cloud with AWS, from the storyboard sketch to the final deliverable. Nimble Studio provides customers with on-demand access to virtual workstations, elastic file storage, and render farm capacity. It also provides built-in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rearchitecting for MicroServices: Featuring Windows & Linux Containers]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61545</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/rearchitecting-for-microservices-featuring-windows-linux-containers/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T20:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you following our On-Prem to the Cloud Series via the DevOps Lab on Channel 9? If not, you should be! In this week&#8217;s episode, which falls right at number 8, we continue to build on the skills we have learned throughout each episode.
The post Rearchitecting for MicroServices: Featuring Windows &#038; Linux Containers appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Deen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridgecrew: Cloud Security with Barak Schoster]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10858</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/28/bridgecrew-cloud-security-with-barak-schoster/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=bridgecrew-cloud-security-with-barak-schoster"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T18:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing provides tools, storage, servers, and software products through the internet. Securing these resources is a constant process for companies deploying new code to their cloud environments. It’s easy to overlook security flaws because company applications are very complex and many people work together to develop them. Wyze Labs, for example, had millions of
The post Bridgecrew: Cloud Security with Barak Schoster appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks 2021 Highlights: Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2021-highlights-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2021-highlights-terraform"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For our final HashiTalks 2021 highlights blog, we're showcasing HashiCorp Terraform talks — our largest group of talks. If you've been following our highlights series, we've already published our videos covering HashiCorp Vagrant, Packer, Boundary, Waypoint, Nomad, Consul, and Vault.
To recap: this was our largest number of HashiTalks ever. We received so many high-quality submissions this year that we decided to increase the length of the virtual livestream from 24 hours to 48 hours. More than 10,000 peopl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Searching through logs with the free and open Logs app in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/searching-logs-free-open-logs-app-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/searching-logs-free-open-logs-app-kibana"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Log exploration and analysis is a key step in troubleshooting performance issues in IT environments — from understanding application slow downs to investigating misbehaving containers. Did you get an alert that heap usage is spiking on a specific server? A quick search of the logs filtered from that host shows that cache misses started around the same time as the initial spike. Digging into the metadata (date and version) of the highlighted logs from that time period show us that this was likely due to a re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Renuka Gough</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic for Education: How we support students and educators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-for-education-how-we-support-students-and-educators</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-for-education-how-we-support-students-and-educators"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Launched in May 2020, the Elastic for students and educators&nbsp;program provides the resources and support necessary to bring our products and solutions into classrooms around the world. Whether it’s through provisioning Elastic Cloud accounts for students to use during their course, extending access to premium features like&nbsp;machine learning to propel research, or working with universities to design partnership programs to help prepare students for their future careers, Elastic is committed to educat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Nissen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 27th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/27/this-week-in-spring-april-27th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/27/this-week-in-spring-april-27th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T22:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We&rsquo;ve got a ton to get into, so let&rsquo;s gooo!


  
Learn how to enable asynchronous messaging at cloud scale in Spring Boot Java apps using Java Message Service (JMS) API and Azure Service Bus. 

  
In last week&rsquo;s, A Bootiful Podcast, I talked to Reliably CEO Russ Miles

  
An awesome hands-on-lab of using Cloud Native buildpacks with Spring Boot by Toshiaki Maki

  
Check out Sam Brannan’s epic wiki page on meta pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uber Mobile Engineering: Distributed Payment Systems with Gergely Orosz]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10857</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/27/uber-mobile-engineering-distributed-payment-systems-with-gergely-orosz/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uber-mobile-engineering-distributed-payment-systems-with-gergely-orosz"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T21:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern applications are increasingly built as large, distributed systems. A distributed system is a program where its components are located on different machines that communicate with one another to create a single cohesive app. Components may exist as multiple instances across “nodes,” the computers hosting them, which form clusters of nodes that span across geographic
The post Uber Mobile Engineering: Distributed Payment Systems with Gergely Orosz appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started Using Amazon FSx File Gateway for Fast, Cached Access to File Server Data in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>2ac5431cd0d3eac3ca1b84f2650a4b5ceee2797b</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/orXgBfNnEyg/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T20:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As traditional workloads continue to migrate to the cloud, some customers have been unable to take advantage of cloud-native services to host data typically held on their on-premises file servers. For example, data commonly used for team and project file sharing, or with content management systems, has needed to reside on-premises due to issues of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.12.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-12-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-12-1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.12.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
The 7.12.1 patch contains fixes and small enhancements for the stack. Notable bug fixes are:
Kibana does not recognize a valid geo_shape index when attempting to create a Tracking Containment alert. (#95418
Kibana fails to update or delete sessions in non-default space (#96124\
For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
7.12.1 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clint Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing and troubleshooting Elasticsearch memory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/managing-and-troubleshooting-elasticsearch-memory</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/managing-and-troubleshooting-elasticsearch-memory"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hiya! With Elastic’s expansion of our Elasticsearch Service Cloud offering and automated onboarding, we’ve expanded the Elastic Stack audience from full ops teams to data engineers, security teams, and consultants. As an Elastic support rep, I’ve enjoyed interacting with more user backgrounds and with even wider use cases.&nbsp;

With a wider audience, I’m seeing more questions about managing resource allocation, in particular the mystical shard-heap ratio and avoiding circuit breakers. I get it! When I sta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stef Nestor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes – Azure Static Web Apps with Anthony Chu!]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61531</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-azure-static-web-apps-with-nthonychu/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It&#8217;s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes &#8211; Azure Static Web Apps with Anthony Chu! appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Template Files with HashiCorp Packer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-template-files-with-hashicorp-packer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-template-files-with-hashicorp-packer"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HashiCorp Packer 1.7, we tagged HCL2 as stable and implemented HCL2-only functions. You can use one such function, the templatefile function to build multiple operating systems with less duplication of configuration.
Currently, you need to use the boot_command argument to configure an OS before you connect to the machine. You can use it with many builders, including the vmware-iso or virtualbox-iso builders. A boot_command mimicks manual keystrokes and sends them at a regular cadence. You aggregate these…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Alibaba Cloud: Reflecting on our partnership and looking to the future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-alibaba-cloud-reflecting-on-our-partnership-and-looking-to-the-future</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-alibaba-cloud-reflecting-on-our-partnership-and-looking-to-the-future"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba Cloud is an important partner to us here at Elastic. We officially started our collaboration and strategic partnership with Alibaba Cloud back in 2017, when we announced the Alibaba Cloud Elasticsearch service. Since then, we’ve seen rapid adoption and growth of the service, which now supports more than 10 petabytes of data. This year, we’ve recognized Alibaba Cloud as our Ecosystem Partner of the Year to acknowledge their contributions in advocating for free and open technology and developing value…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Khushani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Makepath: Geospatial Technology with Brendan Collins]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10845</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/26/makepath-geospatial-technology-with-brendan-collins/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=makepath-geospatial-technology-with-brendan-collins"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T09:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geospatial technology impacts every person who uses a smartphone, drives a car, or flies in airplanes. It refers to all of the technology used to acquire and interpret geographic information. In more advanced settings, geospatial technology is used for constructing dynamic maps, 3D visualizations, and scientific and governmental simulations.  The company Makepath specializes in geospatial
The post Makepath: Geospatial Technology with Brendan Collins appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speedscale: Automated Testing with Ken Ahrens and Matt LeRay]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10844</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/23/speedscale-automated-testing-with-ken-ahrens-and-matt-leray/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=speedscale-automated-testing-with-ken-ahrens-and-matt-leray"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T17:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large portions of software development budgets are dedicated for testing code. A new component may take weeks to thoroughly test, and even then mistakes happen. If you consider software defects as security issues then the concern goes well beyond an application temporarily crashing. Although even minor bugs can cost companies a lot of time to
The post Speedscale: Automated Testing with Ken Ahrens and Matt LeRay appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Tutorial: Manage Private Environments using Terraform Cloud Agents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-tutorial-manage-private-environments-using-terraform-cloud-agents</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-tutorial-manage-private-environments-using-terraform-cloud-agents"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud’s Business Tier offering allows you to manage resources in private data centers using self-hosted agents. The standard Terraform Cloud setup requires that any resources managed by remote execution are accessible over public internet. With agents, you can also manage infrastructure in private environments without modifying your network perimeter to allow for public ingress. The agent runs within your environment and polls Terraform Cloud for workloads to execute. It is available as both a Doc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Reliably CEO Russ Miles]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/22/a-bootiful-podcast-reliably-ceo-russ-miles</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/22/a-bootiful-podcast-reliably-ceo-russ-miles"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T00:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Reliably CEO Russ Miles (@russmiles) about COVID, chaos engineering, reliable systems engineering and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated Canary Deployment with HashiCorp Consul and Spinnaker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/automated-canary-deployment-with-hashicorp-consul-and-spinnaker</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/automated-canary-deployment-with-hashicorp-consul-and-spinnaker"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you update an application or system, you likely push the changes to production and manually verify whether or not it works. If the changes fail, they could have a wide impact across your system and users. Instead, you can use a canary deployment to send a small percentage of traffic to new versions of an application or system. This reduces the blast radius of any problems because you can check if the change failed with a smaller subset of users. But canary deployments often require someone to analyze a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The essentials of Windows event logging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-essentials-of-windows-event-logging</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-essentials-of-windows-event-logging"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most prevalent log sources in many enterprises is Windows Event Logs. Being able to collect and process these logs has a huge impact on the effectiveness of any cybersecurity team.

In this multi-part blog series, we will be looking at all things related to Windows Event Logs. We will begin our journey with audit policies and generating event logs, then move through collecting and analysing logs, and finally to building use cases such as detection rules, reports, and more.

The purpose of these i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thorben Jändling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Snowflake Secrets Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-snowflake-secrets-engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-snowflake-secrets-engine"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of our recent release of Vault 1.7 and general availability launch of HCP Vault, we are excited to announce the Snowflake Secrets Engine for self-managed HashiCorp Vault and HCP Vault. The secrets engine is packaged as part of the general database secrets engine and supports root credential rotation as well as dynamic and static roles (these are not to be confused with roles in Snowflake such as accountadmin).
»What is Vault?
HashiCorp Vault is a tool for securely accessing secrets. A secret is anyt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud is now available on Microsoft Azure in South Central US (Texas)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-available-on-microsoft-azure-in-south-central-us-texas</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-available-on-microsoft-azure-in-south-central-us-texas"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce you can now run Elastic Cloud on Microsoft Azure in the South Central US (Texas) region.

Elastic Cloud gives you the power of enterprise search, observability, and security in the South Central US (Texas) region of Azure. Easily search applications, websites, and workplace content platforms for information. Quickly gain deep insights into your environment by monitoring applications and uptime as well as analyzing centralized logs and metrics. You can also help protect your technol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helper Node Series | Diana Tuck on MYCAT and Wolf Haven International]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-helper-node-series-diana-tuck-on-mycat-and-wolf-haven-international</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-helper-node-series-diana-tuck-on-mycat-and-wolf-haven-international"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic believes in giving back by supporting the communities in which we live and work and recognizing that participating in these activities can inspire and enrich our lives in unexpected ways. That’s why we offer our Elasticians volunteer time off (VTO) to foster a culture of caring.
The Helper Node blog series shines a light on the inspiring ways our Elasticians use their volunteer hours to help their community and the world at large. In this special Earth Day edition of the Helper Node series, we hear …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Cares</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skiff: Secure Document Collaboration with Andrew Milich]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10816</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/22/skiff-secure-document-collaboration-with-andrew-milich/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=skiff-secure-document-collaboration-with-andrew-milich"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T09:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Encryption algorithms provide the means to secure and transfer sensitive information by taking input and transforming it into an unreadable output. Usually a special key, or multiple keys, are needed to unscramble the information back to the original input. These algorithms power the security of everything from our cell phone lock screens to Fortune 500
The post Skiff: Secure Document Collaboration with Andrew Milich appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Hoxton.SR11 has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/21/spring-cloud-hoxton-sr11-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/21/spring-cloud-hoxton-sr11-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T22:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Service Release 11 (SR11) of the Spring Cloud Hoxton Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the Hoxton release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the Hoxton Release Train

See all issues included in this release here.

This was primarily a bug fix and documentation release. Hoxton.SR11 is compatible with Spring Boot 2.3.x and 2.2.x.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Add LoadBalancerR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap: Creating Liquidity in DeFi with Noah Zinsmeister]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10815</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/21/uniswap-creating-liquidity-in-defi-with-noah-zinsmeister/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uniswap-creating-liquidity-in-defi-with-noah-zinsmeister"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T19:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A liquid market enables individuals or groups to quickly buy and sell assets. Decentralized platforms can struggle to execute trades when their platform does not have much liquidity for a specific token. Newer tokens or tokens with limited supply are most often the least liquid because there might be an imbalance of buyers and sellers.
The post Uniswap: Creating Liquidity in DeFi with Noah Zinsmeister appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul Global Scale Benchmark]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-consul-global-scale-benchmark</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-consul-global-scale-benchmark"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often get asked, “How does HashiCorp Consul scale when there is a large number of nodes and services?” The reason this comes up is because when talking about service mesh, we often have this idea of thousands of microservices seamlessly connecting through the mesh, but we don’t always talk about the expected performance of these environments. In an effort to test and document what running a Consul service mesh at enterprise scale would look like, we teamed up with our friends at Datadog and Amazon Web Se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a customer turned digital transformation success with Elastic into a partnership opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-a-customer-turned-digital-transformation-success-with-elastic-into-a-partnership-opportunity</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-a-customer-turned-digital-transformation-success-with-elastic-into-a-partnership-opportunity"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our journey with Elastic began with a search for a single monitoring platform service for all kinds of applications and infrastructure across geographies and in the cloud. Like many other organizations who use Elastic, our story does not end there.&nbsp; 
 Instead, it has evolved to support new use cases and to secure us a managed security service provider partnership (MSSP) with Elastic so that we can help our own customers experience the same digital transformation success we’ve realized along the way.
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pramod Venkatesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with free and open Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-with-free-and-open-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/getting-started-with-free-and-open-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unify and contextualize your logs, metrics, application trace data, and availability data behind a single pane of glass. Elastic Observability provides a unified view into the health and performance of your entire digital ecosystem. With easy ingest of multiple kinds of data via pre-built collectors for hundreds of data sources, Elastic Observability delivers seamless integration between the facets of observability. Built-in alerting allows you to see when you're nearing your SLAs, and purpose-built applica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep dive into Trend Micro Deep Security integration modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/deep-dive-into-trend-micro-deep-security-integration-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/deep-dive-into-trend-micro-deep-security-integration-modules"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AnsibleFest 2020, we announced the extension of our security automation initiative to support endpoint protection use cases. If you have missed it, check out the recording of the talk “Automate your endpoint protection using Ansible” on the AnsibleFest page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sjaiswal@redhat.com (Sumit Jaiswal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Spring Data 2021.0?]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/20/what-s-new-in-spring-data-2021-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/20/what-s-new-in-spring-data-2021-0"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T06:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.0, codenamed Pascal, is the second release following the new six-month cadence.
It ships with refinements to many existing interfaces and programming models.
This blog post explains the following topics:





Introduce deleteAllById for CrudRepository and ReactiveCrudRepository.



Support for Spring Core Java Flight Recorder (JFR) metrics.



QueryByExample for R2DBC and Oracle support.



Enable Type- and Refactoring-safe Use of KProperty and KPropertyPath for Property Pat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MITRE Engenuity ATT&CK® Round 3: Carbanak + FIN7 vs. the free and open capabilities in Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/mitre-engenuity-attck-round-3-carbanak-fin7-vs-free-open-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/mitre-engenuity-attck-round-3-carbanak-fin7-vs-free-open-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to jump right into the MITRE Engenuity ATT&CK® Eval Round 3 Kibana dashboards? Skip ahead to see the results.



Fresh out: the latest MITRE Engenuity Evaluation

Whether this is the third time you are looking at the MITRE Engenuity ATT&CK® evaluation results or your first, you may be asking yourself: what was unique about this year’s evaluation?

Well, let’s first start with: who is MITRE Engenuity? They are a tech foundation that collaborates with the private sector on many initiatives — most notably…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ewing,James Spiteri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Showtime: Crypto Art and NFTs with Alex Masmejean]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10814</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/20/showtime-crypto-art-and-nfts-with-alex-masmejean/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=showtime-crypto-art-and-nfts-with-alex-masmejean"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T20:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-fungible tokens are proofs of authenticity that are stored on a blockchain. Unlike fungible tokens, such as cryptocurrencies which are interchangeable, non-fungible tokens aren’t inherently equivalent to any other token. Because they are unique, they can be used to represent any unique asset. Their presence on a blockchain enables an NFT owner to trade the
The post Showtime: Crypto Art and NFTs with Alex Masmejean appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrease Your Machine Learning Costs with Instance Price Reductions and Savings Plans for Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>3999c9a5075e2e23583462d6d5c4a6003bd0276b</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/eeRsFkqp-1U/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T19:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Launched at AWS re:Invent 2017, Amazon SageMaker is a fully-managed service that has already helped tens of thousands of customers quickly build and deploy their machine learning (ML) workflows on AWS. To help them get the most ML bang for their buck, we’ve added a string of cost-optimization services and capabilities, such as Managed Spot […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How attackers abuse Access Token Manipulation (ATT&CK T1134)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-attackers-abuse-access-token-manipulation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-attackers-abuse-access-token-manipulation"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our previous blog post on Windows access tokens for security practitioners, we covered:


	
The relationship between logon sessions and access tokens
How network authentication works in Windows environments
Having covered some of the key concepts in Windows security, we will now build on this knowledge and start to look at how attackers can abuse legitimate Windows functionality to move laterally and compromise Active Directory domains.

This blog has deliberately attempted to abstract away the workings …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with  HCP Consul: Frequently Asked Questions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/getting-started-with-hcp-consul-frequently-asked-questions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/getting-started-with-hcp-consul-frequently-asked-questions"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Cloud Platform (HCP) Consul became generally available in early March. Since then, many users have leveraged this fully managed service mesh to discover and secure their services running on Amazon Web Services. Along the way, we’ve fielded some good questions from early users. Now we’re sharing the answers with you so that everyone’s HCP Consul onboarding experience is just a little bit smoother. We look forward to continued feedback and questions so we can all learn more as HCP Consul continues t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the team @ Elastic | EMEA go-to-market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-the-team-at-elastic-emea-go-to-market</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-the-team-at-elastic-emea-go-to-market"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Field Operations is an important team here at Elastic. They cover all go-to-market (GTM) functions related to customer acquisition, expansion, and retention. As a team, they think globally and act locally with teams covering every major international market.

Our Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) sales team is rapidly growing, so we wanted to take a moment to highlight some of our GTM Elasticians working in the region and hear a bit about the work they do and why they value Elastic as an employer.

Cha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 20th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/20/this-week-in-spring-april-20th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/20/this-week-in-spring-april-20th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T07:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! This week we&rsquo;ve got a ton of stuff to get to so let&rsquo;s dive right in! 


  
5 WAYS to go to PRODUCTION with SPRING BOOT (ft. surprise guest)! - YouTube

  
A Bootiful Podcast: Biden campaign CTO, Spinnaker cofounder, Target distinguished engineer, and all around epic guy Dan Woods

  
A cool sample Spring Boot app from Oracle

  
A nice blog on Spring HATEOAS

  
An interesting use case with Azure Spring Cloud and Swiss…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Consul 1.10 Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-consul-1-10-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-consul-1-10-beta"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the beta release of HashiCorp Consul 1.10. This release is yet another step forward in our effort to help organizations run Consul efficiently at scale and seamlessly integrate service mesh into their application workflows. Consul 1.10 contains a number of exciting features that we will review in this blog. If you are interested in trying out the beta, it is now available on our GitHub release page.
»Transparent Proxy
As with any service mesh, Consul facilitates secure service-to-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HireVue Uses HashiCorp Vault to Enable Faster, More Secure Candidate Recruitment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hirevue-uses-hashicorp-vault-enable-faster-more-secure-candidate-recruitment</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hirevue-uses-hashicorp-vault-enable-faster-more-secure-candidate-recruitment"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recruiting high-quality talent is the front line of the battle for corporate supremacy. Organizations of all sizes and across every industry are looking for new and inventive ways to identify and hire qualified candidates before their competitors do &mdash;&nbsp;and they&rsquo;re looking to HireVue for help.
For nearly 15 years, the company has provided enterprises large and small, as well as government contractors and agencies, with a range of AI-powered interview scheduling, video interviewing, and skills…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Packer Data Source Component Type]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-packer-data-source-component-type</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-packer-data-source-component-type"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Packer team is excited to announce the release of Data Source, a new component type to fetch or compute data for use elsewhere in a Packer configuration.
Starting in Packer 1.7.0, users and plugin developers will use data source plugins within HCL2-enabled build templates. As we continue to focus on favoring HCL2 over legacy JSON templates, data source components will be the first Packer feature exclusively available to HCL2.
Data sources in Packer function similarly to Terraform’s data source…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Endpoint Protection with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-endpoint-protection-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-endpoint-protection-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise security isn’t a homogeneous entity; it’s a portfolio of multi-vendor solutions run by disparate and often siloed teams. With so many different layers, automation proved to be effective in helping security operations teams to integrate and share accountability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rwolters@redhat.com (Roland Wolters)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synthetix: Derivatives Trading in DeFi with Justin Moses]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10777</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/19/synthetix-derivatives-trading-in-defi-with-justin-moses/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=synthetix-derivatives-trading-in-defi-with-justin-moses"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T09:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volatility is the degree of fluctuation of something’s price. Highly volatile assets may see rapid and large price changes, while less volatile assets will maintain a steady price. This concept is important in decentralized finance because cryptocurrencies tend to be volatile assets.  The company Synthetix provides assets called Synths that provide exposure to an asset
The post Synthetix: Derivatives Trading in DeFi with Justin Moses appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1inch Exchange: Decentralized Exchange Aggregation with Anton Bukov]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10776</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/17/1inch-exchange-decentralized-exchange-aggregation-with-anton-bukov/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=1inch-exchange-decentralized-exchange-aggregation-with-anton-bukov"/>
        <updated>2021-04-17T09:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decentralized exchange, usually referred to as a DEX, is a platform for exchanging cryptocurrencies. Depending on trading volume for different coins, some DEXs are more liquid than others. On the one hand you can freely swap unlisted tokens and maintain full control over your private keys and wallet information. On the other hand, without
The post 1inch Exchange: Decentralized Exchange Aggregation with Anton Bukov appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Census: Data Accessibility with Boris Jabes]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10788</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/16/census-data-accessibility-with-boris-jabes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=census-data-accessibility-with-boris-jabes"/>
        <updated>2021-04-16T09:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A data warehouse is a data management system that often contains large amounts of historical data and is used for business intelligence activities like analytics. It centralizes customer data from multiple sources to be an organization’s single source of truth. Getting the data from your data warehouse into the different applications used by your organization
The post Census: Data Accessibility with Boris Jabes appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.0-RC1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/15/spring-boot-2-5-0-rc1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/15/spring-boot-2-5-0-rc1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-04-16T03:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In preparation for the GA release on May 20 2021, I am pleased to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.0-RC1 has been released and is available from our milestone repository. This release adds a number of new features and bug fixes.

Highlights of the RC include:


  
A new actuator endpoint for Quartz

  
Support for database initialization with R2DBC

  
Micometer metrics support for Spring Data repositories and MongoDB

  
Support for Gradle 7.0


For a complete list of changes and upgrade instructions,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Biden campaign CTO, Spinnaker cofounder, Target distinguished engineer, and all around epic guy Dan Woods]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/15/a-bootiful-podcast-biden-campaign-cto-spinnaker-cofounder-target-distinguished-engineer-and-all-around-epic-guy-dan-woods</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/15/a-bootiful-podcast-biden-campaign-cto-spinnaker-cofounder-target-distinguished-engineer-and-all-around-epic-guy-dan-woods"/>
        <updated>2021-04-16T02:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Netflixer, Spinnaker continuous delivery platform co-founder, Target distinguished engineer, Biden campaign CTO, RatPack contributor, and an all-around epic guy Dan Woods (@danveloper).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Kibana dashboards more efficiently]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-kibana-dashboards-more-efficiently</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-kibana-dashboards-more-efficiently"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating dashboards is quicker and easier than before with a new streamlined navigation experience, now available in Kibana 7.12. This dashboard-first approach makes it simple for you to create and add visualizations without leaving your dashboard-building flow.&nbsp;

Get started directly from a Kibana dashboard with a few simple steps: Select Create Panel and choose what type of visual you want to build. (In the following visual, we selected Kibana Lens.)&nbsp;Then once you’ve completed your analysis, sim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Marten,Kaarina Tungseth,Devon Thomson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.4.5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/15/spring-boot-2-4-5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/15/spring-boot-2-4-5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I&rsquo;m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.4.5 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 57 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you&rsquo;re interested in helping out, check out the &ldquo;ideal for contribution&rdquo; tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, pl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Fig Labs: Cloud Infrastructure Security with Vikrum Nijjar and Greg Soltis]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10775</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/15/gold-fig-labs-cloud-infrastructure-security-with-vikrum-nijjar-and-greg-soltis/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=gold-fig-labs-cloud-infrastructure-security-with-vikrum-nijjar-and-greg-soltis"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T09:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT infrastructure are the components required to operate IT environments, like networks, virtual machines or containers, an operating system, hardware, data storage, etc…. As companies build out different deployment environments with infrastructure configurations, they must maintain the different environments, replicate them, and update them. The management of infrastructure, often automated to some extent, is referred
The post Gold Fig Labs: Cloud Infrastructure Security with Vikrum Nijjar and Greg Soltis …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.3.10 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/15/spring-boot-2-3-10-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/15/spring-boot-2-3-10-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T07:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I&rsquo;m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.3.10 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 78 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you&rsquo;re interested in helping out, check out the &ldquo;ideal for contribution&rdquo; tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration 5.5 RC1, 5.4.6 & 5.3.7 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/14/spring-integration-5-5-rc1-5-4-6-5-3-7-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/14/spring-integration-5-5-rc1-5-4-6-5-3-7-available"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T01:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring community,



On behalf of the team and all the contributors, it&#8217;s my pleasure to announce a Release Candidate 1 for Spring Integration 5.5, plus Spring Integration 5.4.6 &amp; 5.3.7 patch versions.



The latest two can be downloaded from Maven Central and it is recommended to upgrade your projects or just pull them transitively from respective latest Spring Boot patch versions!



The Release Candidate is available from the https://repo.spring.io/milestone/ repository:




c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Apps Live: Learn Serverless, Containers and More in May]]></title>
        <id>8f8cd920b823bd0afa8360fd2c80c0bc001b47b2</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/0OjLEuoTcsw/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T18:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Apps Live is a series of events about&nbsp;modern application development that will be live-streaming on&nbsp;Twitch in May.&nbsp;Session topics include serverless, containers, and mobile and front-end development. If you’re not familiar, modern applications are those that: Can scale quickly to millions of users. Have global availability. Manage a lot of data (we’re talking exabytes of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Kafka 2.7.0 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/14/spring-for-apache-kafka-2-7-0-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/04/14/spring-for-apache-kafka-2-7-0-available"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that Spring for Apache Kafka 2.7.0 is now available.



This release contains a significant enhancement, which is a community contribution.
Failed deliveries can be forwarded to a series of topics for delayed redelivery.



It is best described with an example:




@RetryableTopic(attempts = "5", backoff = @Backoff(delay = 1000, multiplier = 2.0))
@KafkaListener(id = "sk270", topics = "sk270")
public void listen(String in, @Header(KafkaHeaders.RECEIVED_TOPIC) String top…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AQUA (Advanced Query Accelerator) – A Speed Boost for Your Amazon Redshift Queries]]></title>
        <id>98eed36d79f53edec4d0e4bed0e9485bbdc3d2e6</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/uh_R_Zc0YwE/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T16:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Redshift already provides up to 3x better price-performance at any scale than any other cloud data warehouse. We do this by designing our own hardware and by using Machine Learning (ML). For example, we launched the SSD-based RA3 nodes for Amazon Redshift at the end of 2019 (Amazon Redshift Update – Next-Generation Compute Instances […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compound: Cryptocurrency Interest Rates with Jared Flatow]]></title>
        <id>http://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=10754</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/04/14/compound-cryptocurrency-interest-rates-with-jared-flatow/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=compound-cryptocurrency-interest-rates-with-jared-flatow"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T09:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized applications, termed “dApps,” are applications that feel like normal apps but are actually deployed (mostly) on the Ethereum blockchain. This means dApps can’t be taken down, can’t be censored or blocked, typically use Ethereum accounts as identity, and would only experience downtime if Ethereum itself went down. There are a lot of things you
The post Compound: Cryptocurrency Interest Rates with Jared Flatow appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating ServiceNow with Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/certified-collection-servicenow</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/certified-collection-servicenow"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT service management (ITSM) is a collection of policies and processes for the management and support of IT services. The main focus of ITSM is increasing the value of the customers’ service chain. But without the proper automation support, providing IT services can quickly become a major time-sink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>steampunk@xlab.si (XLAB Steampunk)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating a RHEL 8 Installation Using the VMware REST Ansible Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-a-rhel-8-installation-using-the-vmware-rest-ansible-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-a-rhel-8-installation-using-the-vmware-rest-ansible-collection"/>
        <updated>2021-04-12T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing virtual machines in an IT infrastructure is often a common task, specifically VMware virtualization technology has been around for over 20 years. VMware administrators spend a lot of their time in automating the creation, management, and removal of virtual instances that contain various operating systems. One operating system that often resides on VMware infrastructure is Red Hat Enterprise Linux.&nbsp;]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhijeet Kasurde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>