<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-10-03T02:01:43.311Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-03T02:01:43.311Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: alpha support for running Pods with user namespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/03/userns-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/03/userns-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Rodrigo Campos (Microsoft), Giuseppe Scrivano (Red Hat)
Kubernetes v1.25 introduces the support for user namespaces.
This is a major improvement for running secure workloads in
Kubernetes. Each pod will have access only to a limited subset of the
available UIDs and GIDs on the system, thus adding a new security
layer to protect from other pods running on the same system.
How does it work?
A process running on Linux can use up to 4294967296 different UIDs and
GIDs.
User namespaces is a Linux feature that allows mapping a set of users
in the container to different users in the host, thus restricting what
IDs a process can effectively use.
Furthermore, the capabilities granted in a new user namespace do not
apply in the host initial namespaces.
Why is it important?
There are mainly t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For the good of the community]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41944</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/714030826/0/sethsblog~For-the-good-of-the-community/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-02T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One way to serve the community is to see it as a market and solve one of its problems. When people choose to buy something, it’s ostensibly because the thing you sell is worth more to them than it costs. And so value is created. And when you make a profit selling something and pay […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The way it’s done]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41942</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/713913222/0/sethsblog~The-way-its-done/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people say, “we’re not changing it, because this is the way it’s done.” And some people say, “the way it’s done isn’t good enough, let’s make it better.” In a given situation, you might encounter one or the other type of response. In fact, each of us might adopt one posture or the other. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using FEEL with Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=64132</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/using-feel-with-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T16:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is FEEL As a part of the Decision Model and Notation (DMN) specification, the OMG also defined the Friendly Enough Expression Language (FEEL).  Since DMN is intended to be used by designers and business analysts who would like to build decision tables, FEEL needed to be designed as an uncomplicated and human-readable expression language that would help readers understand the logic being described or executed by the DMN table.  Expression languages are typically used by developers to evaluate data to produce a result based on query parameters or conditions. This means it’s syntactically closer to code than human-readable sentences. Since one of the goals of FEEL is to be “process analyst friendly,” it prioritizes readability more than other expression...
The post Using FEEL with Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon File Cache – A High Performance Cache On AWS For Your On-Premises File Systems]]></title>
        <id>5ab6ca4c7fbca6e707e93106cb015a859442a687</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-file-cache-a-high-performance-cache-on-aws-for-your-on-premises-file-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T14:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce today the availability of Amazon File Cache, a new high-speed cache service on AWS designed for processing file data stored in disparate locations—including on premises. File Cache accelerates and simplifies your most demanding cloud bursting and hybrid workflows by giving your applications access to files using a fast and familiar […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novelty vs action]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42905</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/713757642/0/sethsblog~Novelty-vs-action/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nerds, geeks, early adopters: they do things because they’re fresh and new and might not work. They’re novel. Most people, though, hesitate in the face of novelty. Because novelty is risky. Shoes with goldfish in the heels. The latest techno-ska-punk track. The new kind of phone… The reason we haven’t taken systemic action is that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in Datalore Community and Pro: The Report Builder]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=283629</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2022/09/30/new-in-datalore-community-and-pro-the-report-builder/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T07:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Datalore team is getting ready for the major release of Datalore Enterprise 2022.3 (the self-hosted version of Datalore). As always, Datalore Community and Professional users will get to see the new features first! We’ve been working on redesigning the reporting workflow and making Datalore notebooks and reports even more interactive.  In this blogpost we’ll […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantified Self]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2679/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2679/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/quantified_self.png" title="It's made me way more excited about ferris wheels, subways, car washes, waterslides, and store entrances that have double doors with a divider in the middle." alt="It's made me way more excited about ferris wheels, subways, car washes, waterslides, and store entrances that have double doors with a divider in the middle." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Camunda 8 supports process automation at enterprise scale]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63983</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/how-camunda-8-supports-process-automation-at-enterprise-scale/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling process automation across an enterprise naturally includes a wide array of challenges. To counter these challenges, more and more organizations are evolving their organizational structures accordingly, often creating Centers of Excellence (CoE) and/or communities of practice (CoP). Please note that during this post we will use the term CoE, but keep in mind your organization might call this very differently. That said, in Camunda Platform 8, we included new functionalities that will help companies to scale process automation successfully.  This blog post discusses different aspects of scaling process automation, the role of CoEs, and how new Camunda 8 features support those initiatives.  What does scaling mean? Organizations that want to create a competitive edge through digital transformation (and frankly: which...
The post How Camunda 8 supports process automation at enterprise scale appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub supports internet freedom and global availability in Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-29-github-supports-internet-freedom-and-global-availability-in-iran/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-29-github-supports-internet-freedom-and-global-availability-in-iran/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T19:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access to the open internet is essential to defending human rights, and developers have an important role in promoting freedom of expression and transparency. GitHub is committed to keeping Iranians connected to the global developer community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon WorkSpaces Introduces Ubuntu Desktops]]></title>
        <id>f345653beefe2e326410b05edcca8bc0fdf98a41</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-workspaces-introduces-ubuntu-desktops/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T16:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS, we love to give our customers choices: the choice of infrastructure to deploy your workloads, to store your most important data, or the operating systems for your virtual desktops. Many of you choose Amazon Workspaces to provision and distribute virtual desktops securely and at scale to your workforce. Our customers choose Workspaces when […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After the offer: staying in tech long-term]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-29-after-the-offer-staying-in-tech-long-term/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-29-after-the-offer-staying-in-tech-long-term/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T16:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech can be a tricky industry (to say the least). We talked with three tech professionals who share why they stay, what has helped them the most, and the power of switching things up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dungeons & Dragons for Team Building]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dungeons-dragons-for-team-building</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dungeons-dragons-for-team-building"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Community team used a custom Dungeons & Dragons campaign as a team building exercise. Check out the highlights and then try it yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin 1.7.20 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=281868</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/09/kotlin-1-7-20-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T14:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kotlin 1.7.20 release is out! Here are some highlights from this release: The new Kotlin K2 compiler supports all-open, no-arg, Lombok, and other compiler plugins. We introduced the preview of the ..< operator for creating open-ended ranges. The new Kotlin/Native memory manager is enabled by default. We introduced a new experimental feature for JVM: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrey Polyakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools 2022.9 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=283218</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/09/29/edutools-plugin-2022-9-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T14:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2022.9 of the EduTools plugin is now available! With this update, our goal has been to implement features to help you stay well-informed, including Change notes functionality for Marketplace courses and specific notifications for Codeforces users. We’ve also improved the overall quality of the plugin by fixing a number of bugs. Read on to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasiia Pogorelova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Programming Languages for Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63832</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/seven-best-programming-languages-for-microservices/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices are an architectural style that structures an application as a collection of services that are: Highly maintainable and testable Loosely coupled Independently deployable Organized around business capabilities Owned by a small team Conway’s Law states that “any organization that designs a system (defined broadly) will produce a design whose structure is a copy of the organization’s communication structure”. If your organization has multiple teams working on different parts of a larger system, then microservices can serve as a separation of concerns that map an independent, encapsulated service to a specific team. These teams have clear boundaries of responsibility and can deploy on their own schedule. These factors lend themselves to a polyglot approach. What this means is that because...
The post 7 Best Programming Languages for Microservices appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2.3 Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=283182</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/09/phpstorm-2022-2-3-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T12:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a preview available of PhpStorm 2022.2.3, the upcoming minor release of PhpStorm. It brings a number of bug fixes and quality-of-life improvements. Here are the most notable changes and bug fixes in this build: Fixed: Language Injection causes large slowdowns (IDEA-292182)  Fixed: Quick Documentation popup doesn’t go away with ESC when using the Emacs […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.2.5]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=283174</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/09/29/datagrip-2022-2-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T10:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! A new DataGrip 2022.2.5 bugfix update is available. Here are the most notable changes and bug fixes: DBE-16324: Fixed the DataGrip freezing issue that occurred due to INSERT AS SELECT queries. DBE-12680: Database renaming now works correctly. DBE-16462 [PostgreSQL]: Fixed the bug with incorrect max values for BIGINT identity columns. DBE-15560 [Microsoft SQL Server]: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extensions and souvenirs]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43900</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/713592854/0/sethsblog~Extensions-and-souvenirs/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When a brand is successful, there’s often a desire to extend it. Disneyland was an extension of Disney movies. It reflected some of the magic of the movies, but created something new and valuable as well. Disneyland had some of the Disney essence and then built something additive and new. Apple did the same thing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast:   thought leader Chris Richardson (and no, I'm not using that title ironically!)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/29/a-bootiful-podcast-thought-leader-chris-richardson-and-no-i-m-not-using-that-title-ironically</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/29/a-bootiful-podcast-thought-leader-chris-richardson-and-no-i-m-not-using-that-title-ironically"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to his friend Chris Richardson (@crichardson), who helped articulate and advance cloud computing, reactive programming, microservices, domain-driven design, event sourcing, and so much more years before the zeitgeist. Also, we used to work together! 


Want to meet more amazing people in our ecosystem, like Chris? SpringOne 2022 is almost here! I feel like it’s that anxious, exciting time before, sort of important holiday where you get given gifts! And with it, Spring Boot 3 and Spring Framework 6. We’re going to be announcing everything right here on the Spring blog, of course, but if you want a chance to learn from the source, then I hope you’ll join us 6-8 December 2022, right here in my hometown of San Francisco, my favorite west coast city in the USA, and my hometown. (Psst.: If you register now, there’s a $200 discount from the pass price with this code S1VM22_Advocate_200.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on support: Elastic's support team treats one another—and its customers—like humans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-spotlight-on-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-spotlight-on-support"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support teams are the unsung heroes who keep customers happy and help them to get the most out of a product. Learn more about our team of support engineers and how they marry excellent customer service skills with product expertise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on support: Elastic's support team treats one another—and its customers—like humans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-spotlight-on-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-spotlight-on-support"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Support teams are a company’s backbone—they’re the unsung heroes who keep the customers happy and help them to get the most out of a product. We pride ourselves on our team of support engineers who marry excellent customer service skills with product expertise. 
Our support engineers have to be analytical, detail oriented, and manage different personalities in order to solve the problem, says Julie Rudd, VP of Global Support at Elastic. 
François Conil, Senior Support Engineer, sees his role as a customer advocate. “It’s not just answering questions, you wear so many hats,” he says. You can have the best product but if you have no one to support it, then you will lose it all.”
Kesia Milesi, Support Engineer, says she helps customers achieve the best they can from Elastic’s product suite.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Enforce CRD Immutability with CEL Transition Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/29/enforce-immutability-using-cel/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/29/enforce-immutability-using-cel/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alexander Zielenski (Google)
Immutable fields can be found in a few places in the built-in Kubernetes types.
For example, you can't change the .metadata.name of an object. Specific objects
have fields where changes to existing objects are constrained; for example, the
.spec.selector of a Deployment.
Aside from simple immutability, there are other common design patterns such as
lists which are append-only, or a map with mutable values and immutable keys.
Until recently the best way to restrict field mutability for CustomResourceDefinitions
has been to create a validating
admission webhook:
this means a lot of complexity for the common case of making a field immutable.
Beta since Kubernetes 1.25, CEL Validation Rules allow CRD authors to express
validation constraints on their fields…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices on rolling out code scanning at enterprise scale]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-28-best-practices-on-rolling-out-code-scanning-at-enterprise-scale/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-28-best-practices-on-rolling-out-code-scanning-at-enterprise-scale/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn best practices on how to roll out centrally managed, developer-centric application security with a third party CI/CD system like Jenkins or ADO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timestone: Netflix’s High-Throughput, Low-Latency Priority Queueing System with Built-in Support…]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1abf249ba95f</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/timestone-netflixs-high-throughput-low-latency-priority-queueing-system-with-built-in-support-1abf249ba95f?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T15:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Kostas Christidis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting the Power of Vim in WebStorm and Other JetBrains IDEs]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=280788</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/09/ideavim-in-webstorm/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T14:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IdeaVim plugin has been around for a while now, helping developers extend their JetBrains IDEs with the power of Vim. We have a dedicated team inside JetBrains maintaining this plugin to provide you with the best of both worlds – a keyboard-centric editor with the support of an IDE. Vim provides a lot of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic inventory plugin collection for network device management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/dynamic-inventory-plugin-collection-for-network-device-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/dynamic-inventory-plugin-collection-for-network-device-management"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tackling the complexities of enterprise inventories
 
One common challenge our customers face is the need to track hosts from multiple sources: LDAP, cloud providers, and enterprise CMDB systems. Using a dynamic inventory allows users to integrate with these systems and update the Ansible inventory as it varies over time, with hosts spinning up and shutting down in response to business demands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric McLeroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With Sven Reinck, XSD / WSDL Visualizer Plugin Author]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=282649</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2022/09/interview-sven-reinck-xsd-wsdl-visualizer-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T10:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are speaking with Sven Reinck, author of the XSD / WSDL Visualizer Plugin that allows visualizing XML files without leaving your IntelliJ-based IDE. Welcome to the JetBrains Platform Blog, Sven! Before we discuss the plugin, would you tell us a bit about yourself and your background? I learned to program when I was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logistics vs (and) innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43095</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/713418636/0/sethsblog~Logistics-vs-and-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T09:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When innovation arrives, the logistics people have to scramble to keep up, because innovation always makes it hard to do things the way we used to. Over time, an innovative company thrives if it can get its logistics in order. Ship the right stuff to the right people on time and on budget. Once this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research is key to a strong cybersecurity program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-is-key-to-a-strong-cybersecurity-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-is-key-to-a-strong-cybersecurity-program"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity research sets organizations apart. How can you integrate it into your program?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emma Siemasko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research is key to a strong cybersecurity program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-is-key-to-a-strong-cybersecurity-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-is-key-to-a-strong-cybersecurity-program"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Cybersecurity is no longer just an IT issue — it’s become a strategic initiative for the entire business. To protect from threats, organizations of all kinds must not only find ways to protect themselves, but also remain abreast of the newest findings in cybersecurity research.

New data shows that organizations that are most advanced, and therefore the most protected, have optimized their cybersecurity research function. 

Sixty-eight percent of the most advanced organizations, defined as those that have best optimized their security posture against the NIST framework, proactively manage security risk through research, according to a research by ThoughtLab. However, less than half (45%) of all organizations excel at research as a means to proactively manage security risk.
,Tips on setti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emma Siemasko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wing Lift]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2678/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2678/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/wing_lift.png" title="Once the air from the top passes below the plane of the wing and catches sight of the spooky skulls, it panics, which is the cause of turbulent vortices." alt="Once the air from the top passes below the plane of the wing and catches sight of the spooky skulls, it panics, which is the cause of turbulent vortices." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zbchaos — A new fault injection tool for Zeebe]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63238</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/zbchaos-a-new-fault-injection-tool-for-zeebe/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During Summer Hackdays 2022, I worked on a project called “Zeebe chaos” (zbchaos), a fault injection command-line interface (CLI) tool. This allows us engineers to more easily run chaos experiments against Zeebe, build up confidence in the system’s capabilities, and discover potential weaknesses. Requirements To understand this blog post, it is useful to have a certain understanding of Kubernetes and Zeebe itself. Summer Hackdays: Hackdays are a regular event at Camunda, where people from different departments (engineering, consulting, DevRel, etc.) work together on new ideas, pet projects, and more. Often, the results are quite impressive and are also presented in the following CamundaCon. For example, check out the agenda of this year’s CamundaCon 2022. Check out previous Summer Hackdays here:...
The post Zbchaos — A new fault injection tool for Zeebe appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Zell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantization for Fast and Environmentally Sustainable Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/quantization-for-fast-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/quantization-for-fast-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T17:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Srivatsan Krishnan, Student Researcher, and Aleksandra Faust, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team   
Deep reinforcement learning (RL) continues to make great strides in solving real-world sequential decision-making problems such as balloon navigation, nuclear physics, robotics, and games. Despite its promise, one of its limiting factors is long training times. While the current approach to speed up RL training on complex and difficult tasks leverages distributed training scaling up to hundreds or even thousands of computing nodes, it still requires the use of significant hardware resources which makes RL training expensive, while increasing its environmental impact. However, recent work [1, 2] indicates that performance optimizations on existing hardware …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IoT FleetWise Now Generally Available – Easily Collect Vehicle Data and Send to the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>852c2e070c6cea86911d87c790881d8de55886cb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-iot-fleetwise-now-generally-available-easily-collect-vehicle-data-and-send-to-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T16:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we announce the general availability of AWS IoT FleetWise, a fully managed AWS service that makes it easier to collect, transform, and transfer vehicle data to the cloud. Last AWS re:Invent 2021, we previewed AWS IoT FleetWise, heard customer feedback, and improved features for various use cases of near-real-time vehicle data processing. With AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise Adds Run Metrics, Versioned Docs, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-run-metrics-versioned-docs-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-run-metrics-versioned-docs-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise enhances observability and cuts operational burden with improved run metrics, identity-based storage authentication, and versioned documentation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delete Passwords: Passwordless Connections for Spring Boot  Apps to Azure Services]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/27/delete-passwords-passwordless-connections-for-spring-boot-apps-to-azure-services</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/27/delete-passwords-passwordless-connections-for-spring-boot-apps-to-azure-services"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T09:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using username/password credentials to access one application from another presents a huge security risk for many
    reasons. Today, we are announcing the preview of passwordless connections for Java applications to Azure database
    and eventing services, letting you finally shift away from using passwords. 

Security Challenges with Passwords

Passwords should be used with caution, and developers must never place passwords in an unsecure location. Many Java
    applications connect to backend data, cache, messaging, and eventing services using usernames and passwords, or other sensitive credentials such as access tokens or connection strings.
    If exposed, the passwords could be used to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information such as a sales catalog
    that you…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retribution, revenge, and especially, remorse]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43874</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/713241536/0/sethsblog~Retribution-revenge-and-especially-remorse/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T09:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When an organization has caused harm (through error or intent), it’s tempting to be sure they learned a lesson. We want folks to take responsibility, to admit culpability and to be sure they won’t do it again. But if you need those things to happen to make things better for all of us, we’re going […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 27th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/27/this-week-in-spring-september-27th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/27/this-week-in-spring-september-27th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring!

It’s the last week of September, already! The year’s more done than not. The days are receding into darkness earlier. And the Pumpkin Spice Lattes are upon us. The darker and colder days are kind of a bummer, but I’m stil excited and overjoyed this time of year. You know why?

SpringOne 2022 is almost here! I feel like it’s that anxious, exciting time before sort of important holiday where you get given gifts! And with it, Spring Boot 3 and Spring Framework 6. We’re going to be announcing everything right here on the Spring blog, of course, but if you want a chance to learn from the source, then I hope you’ll join us 6-8 December, 2022, right here in my hometown of San Francisco, my favorite west coast city in the U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to leverage RSS feeds to inform the possibilities with Elastic Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-leverage-rss-feeds-to-inform-the-possibilities-with-elastic-stack</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-leverage-rss-feeds-to-inform-the-possibilities-with-elastic-stack"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are several ways to consolidate RSS feeds. Learn how we built an Elastic-based Open Source Intelligence Tool (OSINT).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordyn Short,Dave Sanchez,Connie Crites</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to leverage RSS feeds to inform the possibilities with Elastic Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-leverage-rss-feeds-to-inform-the-possibilities-with-elastic-stack</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-leverage-rss-feeds-to-inform-the-possibilities-with-elastic-stack"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As Elasticians, we have the opportunity to observe various Elastic use cases. As former SOC analysts, we find ourselves drawn to the security use cases. We are always looking for ways to leverage the Elastic Stack to add value to the Elastic and cybersecurity community. We are constantly researching — sifting through news articles, white papers, databases, etc. We realized that we were spending a lot of time visiting the same sites and needed to consolidate the feeds (duh!). 

Below, we’ll break down how we used RSS feeds, Logstash, Elasticsearch, and Kibana to ingest, consolidate, aggregate, visualize, and search cybersecurity content of interest — and how you can do the same.

[Related article: Cybersecurity is a data challenge, and better search technology is key to improving visibili…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordyn Short,Dave Sanchez,Connie Crites</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review — September 26, 2022]]></title>
        <id>7ba7c22c89a95d2ced12a3220867b6146d0a2db5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-september-26-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T23:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like my travel schedule is coupled with this Week In Review series of blog posts. This week, I am traveling to Fort-de-France in the French Caribbean islands to meet our customers and partners. I enjoy the travel time when I am offline. It gives me the opportunity to reflect on the past or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.3 EAP Is Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=281721</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/09/phpstorm-2022-3-eap-is-open/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T15:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Early Access Program (EAP) for the next major PhpStorm release starts today! In this first EAP build, you’ll get many new features related to PHP 8.2 support, quick-fix previews, and a bunch of quality-of-life improvements. Download PhpStorm 2022.3 EAP #1 If you’re not familiar with our EAP, here’s a quick recap… We publish new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ 2022.3 Early Access Program Is Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rscpp&amp;p=282013</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rscpp/2022/09/26/resharper-cpp-2022-3-eap/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T15:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ opens its EAP with improvements for C++ support and new formatting options. Read on for details and give the new build a try! If you’re not familiar with our Early Access Program (EAP), we roll out free-to-use preview builds each week for developers to test with their code. The EAP builds let you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elvira Mustafina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2022.3 Early Access Program Is Now Open]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=282028</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/09/26/rider-2022-3-early-access-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T14:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, Last week we shared our roadmap plans with you, and today we’re revealing the first EAP build for Rider 2022.3!  Before you download it, let’s take a look at what awaits you inside.  Startup performance improvements Everyone likes to get news about performance improvements in their favorite tools, and today, that’s just what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2022.3 Early Access Program Is Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=282044</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/09/26/resharper-2022-3-early-access-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T14:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, The Early Access Program for ReSharper 2022.3 has started! Before you download the first EAP build, let’s take a look at what it has in store for you. C# support With this first EAP build, we are introducing a couple of changes to the support for language injections: Language injections now work inside […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to configure Auth0 SSO with Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-configure-auth0-sso-with-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-configure-auth0-sso-with-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We will look at integrating identity services provider Auth0 with Elastic Cloud and enabling the social login on Kibana, so that you can log in to Kibana with your Gmail, GitHub, or Microsoft account without creating any additional credentials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aravind Putrevu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to configure Auth0 SSO with Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-configure-auth0-sso-with-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-configure-auth0-sso-with-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In this blog, we will look at integrating identity services provider Auth0 with Elastic Cloud and enabling the social login on Kibana, so that you can log in to Kibana with your Gmail, GitHub, or Microsoft account without creating any additional credentials.

Elastic Cloud supports three types of SSO protocols:

Secure Access Markup Language (SAML)
OpenID
Kerberos

We are going to configure the Auth0 integration via SAML (Security Assertion Markup Language) protocol. And we need to create some identifiers and register them on Elasticsearch and Kibana. Without going into the details of SAML, the most important part is: You need an Identity Provider that performs the authentication and authorization — that’s Auth0 in this example. And you need a Service Provider that trusts the Identity Pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aravind Putrevu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrate to Azure Monitor Agent on Azure Arc using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/migrate-to-azure-monitor-agent-on-azure-arc-using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/migrate-to-azure-monitor-agent-on-azure-arc-using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Arc is becoming the default Microsoft Azure service for connecting non-Azure infrastructure into Azure monitoring and administration.  Azure has also issued a deprecation notice for the Azure Log Analytics Agents; Microsoft Monitoring Agent and Log Analytics (OMS).  Azure Monitor Agent replaces these agents, introducing a simplified, flexible method of configuring collection configuration called Data Collection Rules. To leverage Azure Monitor Agent with their non-Azure servers, customers will need to onboard their machines to Azure Arc-enabled servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Harwell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Support in Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/26/native-support-in-spring-boot-3-0-0-m5</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/26/native-support-in-spring-boot-3-0-0-m5"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spring Team has been working on native image support for Spring Applications for quite some time. After 3+ years of incubation in the Spring Native experimental project with Spring Boot 2, native support is moving to General Availability with Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3!

Native images provide almost instant startup time and reduced memory consumption for Java applications. The recent Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5 release marks the first time we’re asking for broader community feedback on our native story. If you need to catch-up on the basics, please refer to the Ahead Of Time basics blog post from late March. You can also learn how to prepare your applications for Spring Boot 3.0.

A lot has happened since March! We’ve improved compatibility with a larger number of use cases and li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social pressure]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42855</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/713092222/0/sethsblog~Social-pressure/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T08:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s normal to feel it. It changes our careers, our dress and even the way we live our lives. The question is: is it caused by external or internal forces? More often than not, it’s simply something we invent. The people we imagine are busy watching and judging us might not even know we exist. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Key System]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2677/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2677/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/two_key_system.png" title="Our company can be your one-stop shop for decentralization." alt="Our company can be your one-stop shop for decentralization." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: Kubernetes In-Tree to CSI Volume Migration Status Update]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/26/storage-in-tree-to-csi-migration-status-update-1.25/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/26/storage-in-tree-to-csi-migration-status-update-1.25/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jiawei Wang (Google)
The Kubernetes in-tree storage plugin to Container Storage Interface (CSI) migration infrastructure has already been beta since v1.17. CSI migration was introduced as alpha in Kubernetes v1.14.
Since then, SIG Storage and other Kubernetes special interest groups are working to ensure feature stability and compatibility in preparation for CSI Migration feature to go GA.
SIG Storage is excited to announce that the core CSI Migration feature is generally available in Kubernetes v1.25 release!
SIG Storage wrote a blog post in v1.23 for CSI Migration status update which discussed the CSI migration status for each storage driver. It has been a while and this article is intended to give a latest status update on each storage driver for their CSI Migration status in Ku…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The parts between]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42842</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/712980640/0/sethsblog~The-parts-between/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T09:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Listen to one musician’s track in isolation on any record (like this one) and you might be amazed at how trivial they sound. Paul McCartney, one of the great bass players, in one the great groups of all time–it sounds a bit like a school music recital. But we don’t listen to the tracks in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White glove service]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43849</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/712851540/0/sethsblog~White-glove-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T10:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not about the gloves. The pointlessness of the white gloves is actually a big part of it. Good service meets expectations. It is the fulfillment of a promise to the customer. White glove service goes far beyond that. It is designed to surprise and delight. It creates a connection with the recipient that goes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GoLand 2022.3 Early Access Program Has Started!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=281409</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/09/23/the-goland-2022-3-early-access-program-has-started/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T18:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the beginning of our third and final Early Access Program for 2022. If you want to find out what we have planned for version 2022.3, check out our roadmap blog post.  You can get this EAP build via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package (for Ubuntu), or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the GitHub Campus Experts selected for the fall 2022 MLH Fellowship Cohort, powered by GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-23-meet-the-github-campus-experts-selected-for-the-fall-2022-mlh-fellowship-cohort-powered-by-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-23-meet-the-github-campus-experts-selected-for-the-fall-2022-mlh-fellowship-cohort-powered-by-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T16:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three new Campus Experts are joining the fall 2022 batch of the MLH Fellowship to work with open source maintainers and get real-world experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Process Orchestration be the “Glue” for the API Economy?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63178</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/process-orchestration-api-econom/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The API economy is taking off, propelled by an explosion of activity across API tools and platforms. According to a 2021 report from Postman, developers reported spending nearly half of their time working on APIs, and 94% of companies planned to increase their investments in APIs in 2022. API-first development is also gaining traction, with an impressive 67% of companies embracing this methodology. Companies like Twilio and Stripe emerged as early winners in this new economy, with the promise of many more to come.  APIs offer organizations an opportunity to tap into best-of-breed software components without having to spend precious time or development resources creating them from scratch. With that said, an often-overlooked aspect of the API economy is how...
The post Could Process Orchestration be the “Glue” for the API Economy? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The chief hype officer]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43838</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/712670216/0/sethsblog~The-chief-hype-officer/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T08:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chief marketing officer at a big company has an impossible job. The typical duration of a CMO is 18 months because once the CEO realizes that hype for money can’t solve their problems, they get restless. The problem lies in what people think “marketing” is. Marketing isn’t paying for ads, changing the logo or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My SpringOne 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/23/my-springone-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/23/my-springone-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has taken me an embarrassingly long time to appreciate and understand that the devil is in the details regarding software development. Writing happy-path business logic isn’t the hard part! It’s the failure cases, observability, resilience, and process. It’s security and other so-called non-functional requirements. It’s architecting for agility. It’s production. Spring is unique because it sits at the crossroads of many exciting application development discussions. 

Spring’s community contains multitudes and is one of the key defining features. This diversity of discussion means that any conference that endeavors to cover the full sweep of ideas has its work cut out. I don’t know of any other show - and I’ve spoken at many thousands of shows and events in my life! - that completely co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash your data’s power to ensure reliability and cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-unleash-your-datas-power-to-ensure-reliability-and-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-unleash-your-datas-power-to-ensure-reliability-and-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magnify the business impact of your data by consolidating platforms with search-powered technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Mangan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Strategies for CIOs to safely and smartly move to the cloud and speed digital transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/key-strategies-for-cios-to-safely-and-smartly-move-to-the-cloud-and-speed-digital-transformation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/key-strategies-for-cios-to-safely-and-smartly-move-to-the-cloud-and-speed-digital-transformation"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud adoption in the financial, insurance, manufacturing, and public sectors need not be slowed down by outmoded thinking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susanna Camp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash your data’s power to ensure reliability and cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-unleash-your-datas-power-to-ensure-reliability-and-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-unleash-your-datas-power-to-ensure-reliability-and-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today’s distributed IT systems need to bring order to chaos. CIOs are tasked with managing seemingly endless amounts of data, but they can’t unlock insights without a system that breaks down silos to provide a unified view.

One solution many CIOs are considering, according to a recent study by Forrester Consulting commissioned by Elastic, is to deploy a consolidated platform based on search-powered technology that can analyze log data to simplify and optimize IT environments.

This creates a powerful one-two punch for IT teams: an observability and APM solution, combined with a security solution, both running on the same unified, search-powered technology platform.

A consolidated observability and security platform uses one of the most basic technology outputs — the log file — to revea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Mangan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Strategies for CIOs to safely and smartly move to the cloud and speed digital transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/key-strategies-for-cios-to-safely-and-smartly-move-to-the-cloud-and-speed-digital-transformation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/key-strategies-for-cios-to-safely-and-smartly-move-to-the-cloud-and-speed-digital-transformation"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
While many IT leaders in highly-regulated sectors have opted for a slow pace of public cloud adoption, organizations that are more advanced on their journey are reaping the rewards.



McKinsey found through a series of surveys that large companies put up to 15% of their applications in the cloud, but continue to host the core of their technology environment in traditional data centers. The data shows that a lift-and-shift model of select applications offers limited payback. But, payback increases as organizations shift to a broader PaaS model. And, another study from Wipro showed that the speedy adoption of cloud by retail and CPG sectors have actually driven revenue gains.



What can, for example, financial or manufacturing sectors learn from retail, then?



Today, “data storage is g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susanna Camp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Historical Dates]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2676/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2676/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/historical_dates.png" title="Evidence suggests the 1899 transactions occurred as part of a global event centered around a deity associated with the lotus flower." alt="Evidence suggests the 1899 transactions occurred as part of a global event centered around a deity associated with the lotus flower." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: CustomResourceDefinition Validation Rules Graduate to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/23/crd-validation-rules-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/23/crd-validation-rules-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Joe Betz (Google), Cici Huang (Google), Kermit Alexander (Google)
In Kubernetes 1.25, Validation rules for CustomResourceDefinitions (CRDs) have graduated to Beta!
Validation rules make it possible to declare how custom resources are validated using the Common Expression Language (CEL). For example:
apiVersion: apiextensions.k8s.io/v1
kind: CustomResourceDefinition
 ...
 openAPIV3Schema:
 type: object
 properties:
 spec:
 type: object
 x-kubernetes-validations:
 - rule: "self.minReplicas <= self.replicas && self.replicas <= self.maxReplicas"
 message: "replicas should be in the range minReplicas..maxReplicas."
 properties:
 replicas:
 type: integer
 ...


Validation rules support a wide range of use cases. To get a sense of some of the capabilities, let's look at a few examples:
V…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/spring-boot-3-0-0-m5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/spring-boot-3-0-0-m5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T22:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 153 enhancements, documentation improvements, dependency upgrades, and bug fixes. Notable new features include:


  
Improved Ahead-of-Time (AOT) processing and native image support

  
Improved actuator endpoints sanitization

  
Jersey support re-instated


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TensorStore for High-Performance, Scalable Array Storage]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/tensorstore-for-high-performance.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/tensorstore-for-high-performance.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T21:33:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeremy Maitin-Shepard and Laramie Leavitt, Software Engineers, Connectomics at Google
Many exciting contemporary applications of computer science and machine learning (ML) manipulate multidimensional datasets that span a single large coordinate system, for example, weather modeling from atmospheric measurements over a spatial grid or medical imaging predictions from multi-channel image intensity values in a 2d or 3d scan. In these settings, even a single dataset may require terabytes or petabytes of data storage. Such datasets are also challenging to work with as users may read and write data at irregular intervals and varying scales, and are often interested in performing analyses using numerous machines working in parallel.  
Today we are introducing TensorStore, an open-source…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Couchbase and Cloud legend Laurent Doguin]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/a-bootiful-podcast-couchbase-and-cloud-legend-laurent-doguin</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/a-bootiful-podcast-couchbase-and-cloud-legend-laurent-doguin"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to his friend, fellow Java Champion, and director of developer relations and strategy at Couchbase, Laurent Doguin (@ldoguin)


SpringOne 2022 is almost here! This is our first in-person event since the pandemic and it’s when we release Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3, the next generation of Spring and Spring Boot respectively. It’s running 6-8 December in my sunny San Francisco, CA! Register now at SpringOne.io and use the code S1VM22_Advocate_200 to get $200 off the current registration price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub for Startups is generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-22-github-for-startups-is-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-22-github-for-startups-is-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re launching GitHub for Startups to give your startup the tools needed to go from idea to unicorn status on the world's largest developer platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FEEL more confident transforming data]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63034</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/feel-more-confident-transforming-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FEEL (Friendly Enough Expression Language) was created by the Object Management Group (OMG) “as part of the DMN standard”. Its goal is to be easy to understand, and at the same time, be full-featured enough to handle decision tables and literal expressions. When business and IT often work together on complex projects, writing expressions in a (relatively) accessible way reduces miscommunications and helps align teams. Camunda uses FEEL to map and transform business process data dynamically. For example, a loan application process pulls a credit score from an API call into a decision table. The decision table automates the next step of the process depending on the rules in the table. The data from the decision automation can then be...
The post FEEL more confident transforming data appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.4 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/spring-boot-2-7-4-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/spring-boot-2-7-4-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.4 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 48 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
Java 19

Following its GA release earlier this week, Java 19 is now supported.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.12 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/spring-boot-2-6-12-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/spring-boot-2-6-12-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T09:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.12 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 33 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
Java 19

Following its GA release earlier this week, Java 19 is now supported.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.0-M6 and 4.3.7 are out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/spring-batch-5-0-0-m6-and-4-3-7-are-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/spring-batch-5-0-0-m6-and-4-3-7-are-out"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M6 is now available from our milestone repository and that 4.3.7 is available from Maven Central. Version 4.3.7 is a patch release that can be used as a drop-in replacement for 4.3.6. You can find its release notes here. This blog post is more about the new milestone release, version 5.0.0-M6. In this milestone, we focused on improving the configuration process of Spring Batch to make it more flexible and straightforward. This blog post walks through the major changes in this area of the framework and presents the new features introduced in this milestone release. For the complete list of changes, see the release notes.
New Annotation Attributes in EnableBatchProcessing

In this release, the @EnableBatchProcessing annotation introduced new …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security alert: new phishing campaign targets GitHub users]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-21-security-alert-new-phishing-campaign-targets-github-users/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-21-security-alert-new-phishing-campaign-targets-github-users/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T21:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 16, GitHub Security learned that threat actors were targeting GitHub users with a phishing campaign by impersonating CircleCI to harvest user credentials and two-factor codes. While GitHub itself was not affected, the campaign has impacted many victim organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View Synthesis with Transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/view-synthesis-with-transformers.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/view-synthesis-with-transformers.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T19:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Carlos Esteves and Ameesh Makadia, Research Scientists, Google Research 
A long-standing problem in the intersection of computer vision and computer graphics, view synthesis is the task of creating new views of a scene from multiple pictures of that scene. This has received increased attention [1, 2, 3] since the introduction of neural radiance fields (NeRF). The problem is challenging because to accurately synthesize new views of a scene, a model needs to capture many types of information — its detailed 3D structure, materials, and illumination —  from a small set of reference images.  
In this post, we present recently published deep learning models for view synthesis. In “Light Field Neural Rendering” (LFNR), presented at CVPR 2022, we address the challenge of accurately repro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration 6.0.0-M5 and 5.5.15 Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/21/spring-integration-6-0-0-m5-and-5-5-15-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/21/spring-integration-6-0-0-m5-and-5-5-15-available"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T17:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring community,



I’d like to share with you an availability of the latest Milestone 5 of new Spring Integration 6.0 generation.



It can be obtained from Spring Milestone repository:




dependencyManagement {
    imports {
        mavenBom 'org.springframework.integration:spring-integration-bom:6.0.0-M5'
    }
}




Also, Spring Integration 5.5.15 has been released with some critical bug fixed and upstream dependencies deprecation resolutions.
It is recommended to upgrade if you have missed some intermediate releases before or just pull it transitively from upcoming Spring Boot 2.6.12 or 2.7.4!



With the whole Spring portfolio move to Java 17 and Jakarta EE, it was a tremendous internal framework refactoring to support new Java language level and jakarta …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applications for micro-mentoring at GitHub Universe 2022 are now live]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-21-applications-for-micro-mentoring-at-github-universe-2022-are-now-live/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-21-applications-for-micro-mentoring-at-github-universe-2022-are-now-live/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T16:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students have the opportunity to connect with GitHub employees at GitHub Universe 2022 through Micro-Mentoring sessions hosted by GitHub Social Impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.3 Improves Extensibility and Maintainability of Terraform Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-3-improves-extensibility-and-maintainability-of-terraform-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-3-improves-extensibility-and-maintainability-of-terraform-modules"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now generally available, HashiCorp Terraform 1.3 introduces optional object type attributes with defaults, and enhancements to moved blocks, improving extensibility and maintainability of Terraform modules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第216話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316112896867289136</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316112896867289136"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ReadME Project: Built for you!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-21-the-readme-project-built-for-you/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-21-the-readme-project-built-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T14:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ReadME Project &#038; Podcast evolve with community expert voices and topics to stoke discussion about the culture and craft of software development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/21/spring-authorization-server-1-0-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/21/spring-authorization-server-1-0-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M2.



You can download it from repo.spring.io milestone repository by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:1.0.0-M2'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/21/spring-authorization-server-0-4-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/21/spring-authorization-server-0-4-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M2.



You can download it from repo.spring.io milestone repository by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.4.0-M2'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why we signed the Copenhagen Pledge on Tech for Democracy]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-21-why-we-signed-the-copenhagen-pledge-on-tech-for-democracy/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-21-why-we-signed-the-copenhagen-pledge-on-tech-for-democracy/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T13:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the home for developers, we understand the key role our communities play in steering digital transformation and maintaining societal infrastructure. That's why we choose to drive and support policies and initiatives like the Copenhagen Pledge on Tech for Democracy. We're committed to working with like-minded organizations, governments, and civil society to make digital technologies work for democracy and human rights, and we encourage you to join us in this pledge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Event-Driven Automation Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/why-event-driven-matters</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/why-event-driven-matters"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life comes down to moments. These events are often how we define our achievements, successes, and failures throughout life. Just like our daily lives, IT organizations and teams can also have these defining moments, where you will often hear phrases like the "great database crash of '98." Many of these memorable IT  moments occur from limiting ourselves to a reactive approach when it comes to managing our IT assets. This is where event-driven automation can help us move from reactive to proactive IT management – well before we have the next great issue or moment in our IT teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Session 2022.0.0-M3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/spring-session-2022-0-0-m3-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/spring-session-2022-0-0-m3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T04:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Session 2022.0.0-M3. These releases deliver, enhancements, bug fixes, and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot will pick up these artifacts with its upcoming releases.

The following modules were updated as part of 2022.0.0-M3:


  
Spring Session Core 3.0.0-M4 - release notes

  
Spring Session Data Redis 3.0.0-M4 - release notes

  
Spring Session JDBC 3.0.0-M4 - release notes

  
Spring Session Hazelcast 3.0.0-M4 - release notes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase the velocity of your digital transformation through search-powered tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/increase-the-velocity-of-your-digital-transformation-through-search-powered-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/increase-the-velocity-of-your-digital-transformation-through-search-powered-tech"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations in the midst of digital transformation are dealing with huge amounts of data. Data quality, access, and usability can improve with the help of search-powered technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Radogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beat the holiday rush with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/beat-the-holiday-rush-with-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/beat-the-holiday-rush-with-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Surviving Black Friday, Cyber Weekend, and the holiday rush as an online retailer has never been more challenging or more important. But Elastic Observability and Consulting can help you breathe a bit easier and keep your business humming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Hansen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase the velocity of your digital transformation through search-powered tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/increase-the-velocity-of-your-digital-transformation-through-search-powered-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/increase-the-velocity-of-your-digital-transformation-through-search-powered-tech"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
According to a survey conducted by Forrester Consulting, commissioned by Elastic, 84% of data leaders agree that the success of digital transformation initiatives relies on search-powered technology.
That’s likely because search-powered technology can enable the foundational first steps for realizing a range of digitization initiatives and accelerating the results that matter for your organization. Read here three key strategies gleaned from a survey of 800+ IT and cybersecurity executives.
[Virtual event: Tune into a conversation with guest Boris Evelson, VP & Principal Analyst at Forrester, about how search-powered technology drives digital transformation]
1. Data quality: Improve data storage
The survey asked data leaders to consider issues their organizations had experienced as a res…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Radogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beat the holiday rush with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/beat-the-holiday-rush-with-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/beat-the-holiday-rush-with-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
September is here, and that means many retailers have already begun preparing for the upcoming holiday season. One weekend in particular tends to be the real-life stress test that companies have come to develop a love-hate relationship with: Cyber Weekend. Or more specifically, Black Friday, Cyber Monday, and the weekend in between. 

In this article, we will cover how Elastic Observability can be leveraged to provide the data insights needed to prepare for and react to the holiday rush of traffic that will be hitting ecommerce infrastructure around the globe in just two short months. If this is the first time you’re reading about Elastic Observability, my colleague Paul Smalera, wrote a fantastic article that provides a complete overview of the solution.

Read on and learn how Elastic O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Hansen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: Use Secrets for Node-Driven Expansion of CSI Volumes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/21/kubernetes-1-25-use-secrets-while-expanding-csi-volumes-on-node-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/21/kubernetes-1-25-use-secrets-while-expanding-csi-volumes-on-node-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Humble Chirammal (Red Hat), Louis Koo (deeproute.ai)
Kubernetes v1.25, released earlier this month, introduced a new feature
that lets your cluster expand storage volumes, even when access to those
volumes requires a secret (for example: a credential for accessing a SAN fabric)
to perform node expand operation. This new behavior is in alpha and you
must enable a feature gate (CSINodeExpandSecret) to make use of it.
You must also be using CSI
storage; this change isn't relevant to storage drivers that are built in to Kubernetes.
To turn on this new, alpha feature, you enable the CSINodeExpandSecret feature
gate for the kube-apiserver and kubelet, which turns on a mechanism to send secretRef
configuration as part of NodeExpansion by the CSI drivers thus make use of
the same to perfor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.10.0-M2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-10-0-m2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/spring-cloud-dataflow-2-10-0-m2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.10.0-M2 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release contains an update of the Spring Boot version and adds back in support for MySQL. See the release notes for more information.
Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on Stackoverflow or GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transform your software engineering practices with GitHub Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-20-transform-your-software-engineering-practices-with-github-enterprise/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-20-transform-your-software-engineering-practices-with-github-enterprise/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T18:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go beyond knowing GitHub as the home of open source and explore how GitHub Enterprise can help you transform your software engineering organization and practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FindIt: Generalized Object Localization with Natural Language Queries]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/findit-generalized-object-localization.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/findit-generalized-object-localization.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T17:00:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Weicheng Kuo and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team  
Natural language enables flexible descriptive queries about images. The interaction between text queries and images grounds linguistic meaning in the visual world, facilitating a better understanding of object relationships, human intentions towards objects, and interactions with the environment. The research community has studied object-level visual grounding through a range of tasks, including referring expression comprehension, text-based localization, and more broadly object detection, each of which require different skills in a model. For example, object detection seeks to find all objects from a predefined set of classes, which requires accurate localization and classification, while referr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy your Amazon EKS Clusters Locally on AWS Outposts]]></title>
        <id>44f16a5754d845987d5a9cddff8e927e1897ca2b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/deploy-your-amazon-eks-clusters-locally-on-aws-outposts/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T16:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce the availability of local clusters for Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) on AWS Outposts. It means that starting today, you can deploy your Amazon EKS cluster entirely on Outposts: both the Kubernetes control plane and the nodes. Amazon EKS is a managed Kubernetes service that makes it easy for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for Apache Pulsar 0.1.0-M1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/spring-for-apache-pulsar-0-1-0-m1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/spring-for-apache-pulsar-0-1-0-m1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring for Apache Pulsar 0.1.0-M1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.



This is the first milestone for the newly introduced Spring for Apache Pulsar framework and is based on Java17, Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5 and Spring Framework 6.0.0-M5.



Please see our previous blog post to learn more about the background/details of the project and the release notes for details on this milestone.



If you’re interested in trying this new release, you can follow the Quick Tour section in the reference docs.



While the project is in the experimental phase, there is a high level of unit and integration test coverage and we expect you to have  a solid and smooth experience. That being said, when/if you run into any problems please report them on our Github issue tracker. If you have general feedback or want to discuss something else related to the release please use the Github release discussion or for other general feedback feel free to open a new discussion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.1.0-M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/spring-for-graphql-1-1-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/spring-for-graphql-1-1-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pleased to announce the first milestone release of Spring for GraphQL 1.1.0 is now available from our Milestone repository. This version will be shipped with Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5 due for release later this week.

Spring Boot 3.0 is around the corner and the community is expecting a compatible Spring for GraphQL version to go with it. Currently, the best way to prepare for the Spring Boot 3.0 upgrade is to upgrade to Spring Boot 2.7 and Java 17, but Spring Boot 3.0 has new baseline requirements, namely Java 17, Jakarta APIs and Spring Framework 6.0.

Given that Spring for GraphQL 1.0.0 was released towards the end of May this year, we didn’t feel we would have enough time nor feedback to go with a major release of the project for Boot 3.0. This is why the goal of the 1.1 release is simply to adapt to the new baseline requirements and provide a smooth upgrade to Spring Boot 3.0 for existing projects.

This first milestone brings those foundational changes: the Java 17, Jakarta APIs, and a Spring Framework 6.0 baseline. We’re also taking the opportunity to upgrade to GraphQL Java 19.x – a painless upgrade on our side, thanks to the GraphQL Java team! We’ve also replaced our internally developed context propagation mechanism with the new Micrometer Context Propagation library, that’s intended for use broadly across Spring projects. It allows Spring applications to propagate context across various such mechanisms, e.g. ThreadLocal, Reactor Context, GraphQLContext, and others.

In the next milestones, we will consider how we can adapt our current arrangement with important themes in Spring Boot 3.0: GraalVM native image and Micrometer Observability support. Given the short timeline, we might schedule some changes for a future version – again, a smooth upgrade is our top priority here.
How can you help?

If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-graphql tag.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/spring-for-graphql-1-0-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/spring-for-graphql-1-0-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of everyone involved, I’m pleased to announce that Spring for GraphQL 1.0.2 is now available from Maven Central. This version will be shipped with Spring Boot 2.7.4 due for release later this week.

This release includes a number of enhancements, documentation improvements, dependency upgrades, and a couple of bug fixes. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

We’ve also published today a first milestone for the 1.1.0 release, targeting Spring Boot 3.0.
How can you help?

If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-graphql tag.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you the next Camunda Champion?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=62440</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/are-you-the-next-camunda-champion/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T09:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the first day I joined Camunda (which is already over four years ago – time really does fly when you are having fun), I was amazed at how many dedicated, passionate, and invested Camunda Community members there are. Numerous times, I have met individuals who spoke with such excitement about Camunda’s technologies and what the community means to them, that you had to believe it even if you would have never heard of Camunda before. Not only are Camunda Community members passionate about the products, many also actively contribute and give back to the community in several ways. Just to name a few examples: they contribute code and help improve Camunda products, organize meetups, answer questions from fellow users...
The post Are you the next Camunda Champion? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Buchholz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 20th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/this-week-in-spring-september-20th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/20/this-week-in-spring-september-20th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring wherein I endeavor as best as I can to capture the latest-and-greatest in the wide, wacky, and wonderful world of Springdom! Naturally, I fail miserably basically every week. There’s no way I could hope to capture everything of note. But I persist… 

Are you coming to SpringOne 2022? This is our first in-person event since the pandemic and it’s when we release Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3, the next generation of Spring and Spring Boot respectively. It’s running 6-8 December here in my hometown of sunny San Francisco, CA! Register now at SpringOne.io and use the code S1VM22_Advocate_200 to get $200 off the current registration price.

So, without further ado, yet another wonderful week’s roundup! 


  
[A Bootiful Podcast: big data legend, former Pivot, and friend to the Spring community, Tim Spann](https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/15/

  
Spring Cloud Dataflow 2.9.6 Released

  
Spring Data 2022.0.0-M6, 2021.2.3, and 2021.1.7 released

  
Spring Data REST Vulnerability (CVE-2022-31679)

  
Spring Framework 6.0.0-M6 and 5.3.23 available now

  
Spring Security 6.0.0-M7 and 5.8.0-M3 are released

  
Spring Tools 4.16.0 released

  
15 Best Spring Framework Blogs and Websites in 2022
a-bootiful-podcast-big-data-legend-former-pivot-and-friend-to-the-spring-community-tim-spann)

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: Two Features for Apps Rollouts Graduate to Stable

  
Difference Between Class.getResource() and ClassLoader.getResource()

  
Map a JSON POST to Multiple Spring MVC Parameters

  
I’m honored to be included in a list of 30 Small Business IT Influencers Worth Following in 2022]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want a career in developer advocacy? Alexis Roberson's story will inspire you to apply]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-developer-advocacy</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-developer-advocacy"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alexis Roberson started her career in technology because of a challenge from a college professor. Now she's a developer advocate on Elastic’s community team. Read her story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.4.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.4.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.4.2 over the previous patch versions in 8.4.x.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
8.4.2 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rich Kuzsma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want a career in developer advocacy? Alexis Roberson's story will inspire you to apply]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-developer-advocacy</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-developer-advocacy"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Alexis Roberson, Developer Advocate at Elastic, started her career in technology because of a challenge from a college professor. The ask? To major in computer science for a semester and see how she liked it. 
Fast forward to 2019 and Alexis graduated with a computer science degree and started her career as a DevOps engineer—a far cry from the English major she thought she’d graduate with.
Now it’s probably safe to say that her professor’s instincts were right. Alexis completed multiple tech internships across the United States during college, was a teaching assistant at GirlsWhoCode, as well as hosting a sponsored six-week coding camp for middle school girls.
All of this eventually led her to becoming a developer advocate on Elastic’s community team. But first, she took a 12-week produc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.4.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rich Kuzsma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – September 19, 2022]]></title>
        <id>c87835feafb2eecd408bc548fd91e06e13509083</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-september-19-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T19:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are heating up in Seattle, with preparation for AWS re:Invent 2022 well underway. Later this month the entire News Blog team will participate in our now-legendary “speed storming” event. Over the course of three or four days, each of the AWS service teams with a launch in the works for re:Invent will give us […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vagrant 2.3 Introduces Go Runtime]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vagrant-2-3-introduces-go-runtime</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vagrant-2-3-introduces-go-runtime"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vagrant 2.3 introduces a new Vagrant executable written in Golang, tying the Vagrant architecture more closely into the broader HashiCorp ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.0.0-M7 and 5.8.0-M3 are released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/19/spring-security-6-0-0-m7-and-5-8-0-m3-are-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/19/spring-security-6-0-0-m7-and-5-8-0-m3-are-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 6.0.0-M7 and 5.8.0-M3 are available now.



See the 6.0.0-M7 and 5.8.0-M3 release notes for more details.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How network engineers can get more sleep using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform: Your guide to AnsibleFest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-network-engineers-can-get-more-sleep-using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-your-guide-to-ansiblefest-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-network-engineers-can-get-more-sleep-using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-your-guide-to-ansiblefest-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since connectivity is critical to all types of business applications including cloud apps, managing and maintaining the network often falls into the overnight hours. This is great for the business, but it puts a large wrinkle in your work-life balance. Luckily, AnsibleFest is here to help you get more sleep!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cindy Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: Local Storage Capacity Isolation Reaches GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/19/local-storage-capacity-isolation-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/19/local-storage-capacity-isolation-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jing Xu (Google)
Local ephemeral storage capacity isolation was introduced as a alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.7 and it went beta in 1.9. With Kubernetes 1.25 we are excited to announce general availability(GA) of this feature.
Pods use ephemeral local storage for scratch space, caching, and logs. The lifetime of local ephemeral storage does not extend beyond the life of the individual pod. It is exposed to pods using the container’s writable layer, logs directory, and EmptyDir volumes. Before this feature was introduced, there were issues related to the lack of local storage accounting and isolation, such as Pods not knowing how much local storage is available and being unable to request guaranteed local storage. Local storage is a best-effort resource and pods can be evicted due t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at Interspeech 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/google-at-interspeech-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/google-at-interspeech-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T02:00:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cat Armato, Program Manager, Google 
This week, the 23rd Annual Conference of the International Speech Communication Association (INTERSPEECH 2022) is being held in Incheon, South Korea, representing one of the world’s most extensive conferences on research and technology of spoken language understanding and processing. Over 2,000 experts in speech-related research fields gather to take part in oral presentations and poster sessions and to collaborate with streamed events across the globe. 
We are excited to be a Diamond Sponsor of INTERSPEECH 2022, where we will be showcasing nearly 50 research publications and supporting a number of workshops, special sessions and tutorials. We welcome in-person attendees to drop by the Google booth to meet our researchers and participate in Q&…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust Online Allocation with Dual Mirror Descent]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/robust-online-allocation-with-dual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/robust-online-allocation-with-dual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Santiago Balseiro, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research, and Associate Professor at Columbia University, and Vahab Mirrokni, Distinguished Scientist, Google Research 
The emergence of digital technologies has transformed decision making across commercial sectors such as airlines, online retailing, and internet advertising. Today, real-time decisions need to be repeatedly made in highly uncertain and rapidly changing environments. Moreover, organizations usually have limited resources, which need to be efficiently allocated across decisions. Such problems are referred to as online allocation problems with resource constraints, and applications abound. Some examples include: 
 
Bidding with Budget Constraints: Advertisers increasingly purchase ad slots using auction-based mark…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Drift Detection Helps Maintain a Secure Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-drift-detection-helps-maintain-a-secure-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-drift-detection-helps-maintain-a-secure-infrastructure"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drift detection is essential to maintaining efficiency while minimizing risk and giving teams confidence in your infrastructure as code (IaC) provisioning workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workflow diagram and pattern examples using BPMN models]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=62079</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/workflow-diagram-and-pattern-examples-using-bpmn-models/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are multiple angles to look at workflows one of which is patterns. The Workflow Patterns initiative differentiates between control, data, and resource perspectives. They are not just focusing on the modeling language as such but have workflow systems in mind too. It’s valuable to have a closer look at those patterns and discuss which parts of it can be shown and even automated in BPMN, and which parts are taken care of in the technical implementation. I have seen BPMN diagrams that try to include every aspect in the diagram itself. This often leads to overloaded BPMN models with a lack of clear transparency of the business flow. Therefore, it is important to focus on all aspects of workflow...
The post Workflow diagram and pattern examples using BPMN models appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nele Uhlemann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2022 preview – A conference for all things process orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=62651</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/camunda-con-2022-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T21:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our annual process orchestration conference, CamundaCon, is back this October 5-6 with a new hybrid format. Join us online from the comfort of your desk or meet us in person in Berlin, Germany. No matter how you CamundaCon, it will be a fun and insightful event! This year’s agenda is jam-packed with an all-star line-up of experts who will share their experience automating, orchestrating, and improving core business processes. You’ll hear real-world use cases and best practices from companies across all industries that have found innovative ways to deliver better customer experiences through orchestration. Here’s a sneak peek at a few of the sessions you won’t want to miss: Navdeep Singh of Walmart will share how they manage customer experiences...
The post CamundaCon 2022 preview – A conference for all things process orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PaLI: Scaling Language-Image Learning in 100+ Languages]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/pali-scaling-language-image-learning-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/pali-scaling-language-image-learning-in.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T19:16:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xi Chen and Xiao Wang, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Advanced language models (e.g., GPT, GLaM, PaLM and T5) have demonstrated diverse capabilities and achieved impressive results across tasks and languages by scaling up their number of parameters. Vision-language (VL) models can benefit from similar scaling to address many tasks, such as image captioning, visual question answering (VQA), object recognition, and in-context optical-character-recognition (OCR). Increasing the success rates for these practical tasks is important for everyday interactions and applications. Furthermore, for a truly universal system, vision-language models should be able to operate in many languages, not just one. 
In “PaLI: A Jointly-Scaled Multilingual Language-Image Model”, we introduce a uni…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.4 Beta Adds Nomad Variables and Updates Service Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-4-adds-nomad-variables-and-updates-service-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-4-adds-nomad-variables-and-updates-service-discovery"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The beta release of HashiCorp Nomad 1.4 enhances native service discovery support with health checks and introduces Nomad Variables, which lets users store configuration values.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 210 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65737</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-210-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T17:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We spent most of sprint 210 focusing on accessibility issues and bug fixes. Here is a list of the items that have been resolved.
Issue
Unable to create a branch from card
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 210 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Tools Explained Using a Minecraft World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-tools-explained-using-a-minecraft-world</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-tools-explained-using-a-minecraft-world"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit our Minecraft world and learn how HashiCorp Vault, Consul, Nomad, and Boundary all work through fun analogies. Join us at HashiConf Global 2022 — in Los Angeles or online Oct. 4-6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase your resilience with new regions in Camunda Platform 8 SaaS]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=62542</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/increase-your-resilience-with-new-regions-in-camunda-platform-8-saas/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce new regions for Camunda Platform 8 SaaS that further strengthen the resilience, performance, and data requirements for our SaaS customers. Enterprise customers can now choose to create their clusters in a number of regions including Europe West, US Central, US East, and the most recent addition, Australia South East. This provides multiple benefits, such as increasing availability, allowing to set up fail-safes, adhering to regulatory requirements for regional data storage, and reduced latency due to closer physical proximity. Resilience and redundancy in technology are important for all modern organizations and are top of mind for many. Across industries, organizations need a solution that scales effectively and is resilient to provide a good base for process orchestration....
The post Increase your resilience with new regions in Camunda Platform 8 SaaS appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annie Talvasto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: Two Features for Apps Rollouts Graduate to Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/15/app-rollout-features-reach-stable/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/15/app-rollout-features-reach-stable/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Ravi Gudimetla (Apple), Filip Křepinský (Red Hat), Maciej Szulik (Red Hat)
This blog describes the two features namely minReadySeconds for StatefulSets and maxSurge for DaemonSets that SIG Apps is happy to graduate to stable in Kubernetes 1.25.
Specifying minReadySeconds slows down a rollout of a StatefulSet, when using a RollingUpdate value in .spec.updateStrategy field, by waiting for each pod for a desired time.
This time can be used for initializing the pod (e.g. warming up the cache) or as a delay before acknowledging the pod.
maxSurge allows a DaemonSet workload to run multiple instances of the same pod on a node during a rollout when using a RollingUpdate value in .spec.updateStrategy field.
This helps to minimize the downtime of the DaemonSet for consumers.
These features …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Direct VPC Routing Between On-Premises Networks and AWS Outposts Rack]]></title>
        <id>6d089016af02ca1b0fdb9d5d59d86f2aae0f62a3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-direct-vpc-routing-between-on-premises-networks-and-aws-outposts-rack/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T22:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we announced direct VPC routing for AWS Outposts rack. This enables you to connect Outposts racks and on-premises networks using simplified IP address management. Direct VPC routing automatically advertises Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) subnet CIDR addresses to on-premises networks. This enables you to use the private IP addresses of resources in your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: PodHasNetwork Condition for Pods]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/14/pod-has-network-condition/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/14/pod-has-network-condition/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author:
Deep Debroy (Apple)
Kubernetes 1.25 introduces Alpha support for a new kubelet-managed pod condition
in the status field of a pod: PodHasNetwork. The kubelet, for a worker node,
will use the PodHasNetwork condition to accurately surface the initialization
state of a pod from the perspective of pod sandbox creation and network
configuration by a container runtime (typically in coordination with CNI
plugins). The kubelet starts to pull container images and start individual
containers (including init containers) after the status of the PodHasNetwork
condition is set to "True". Metrics collection services that report latency of
pod initialization from a cluster infrastructural perspective (i.e. agnostic of
per container characteristics like image size or payload) can utilize the
PodHas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOLNeRF: Learn from One Look]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/lolnerf-learn-from-one-look.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/lolnerf-learn-from-one-look.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T21:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Daniel Rebain, Student Researcher, and Mark Matthews, Senior Software Engineer, Google Research, Perception Team 
An important aspect of human vision is our ability to comprehend 3D shape from the 2D images we observe. Achieving this kind of understanding with computer vision systems has been a fundamental challenge in the field. Many successful approaches rely on multi-view data, where two or more images of the same scene are available from different perspectives, which makes it much easier to infer the 3D shape of objects in the images. 
There are, however, many situations where it would be useful to know 3D structure from a single image, but this problem is generally difficult or impossible to solve. For example, it isn’t necessarily possible to tell the difference between an …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.10 Brings Custom Pipelines and Nomad Plugin Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-10-brings-custom-pipelines-and-nomad-plugin-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-10-brings-custom-pipelines-and-nomad-plugin-updates"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint 0.10 — now generally available — introduces the tech preview of custom pipelines and improvements to the Nomad integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible vs. Terraform Demystified]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-vs.-terraform-demystified</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-vs.-terraform-demystified"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update 
Check out the new article Ansible vs. Terraform, clarified on RedHat.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F5, New Relic, and Sophos Highlight New Consul Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/f5-new-relic-and-sophos-among-new-consul-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/f5-new-relic-and-sophos-among-new-consul-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Consul ecosystem continues its growth with the addition of 15 new self-managed, enterprise, and HCP Consul integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – September 12, 2022]]></title>
        <id>e12120d49afe56b0cb9f9b01c88fc4cb655ae305</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-september-12-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T23:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am working from London, UK, this week to record sessions for the upcoming Innovate EMEA online conference—more about this in a future Week In Review. While I was crossing the channel, I took the time to review what happened on AWS last week. Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my attention: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul-Terraform-Sync 0.7 Adds High Availability and Redundancy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-terraform-sync-0-7-adds-high-availability-and-redundancy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-terraform-sync-0-7-adds-high-availability-and-redundancy"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of HashiCorp Consul-Terraform-Sync 0.7 represents a key step in the maturity of our Network Infrastructure Automation solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drift Detection for Terraform Cloud is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/drift-detection-for-terraform-cloud-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/drift-detection-for-terraform-cloud-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drift Detection for Terraform Cloud continuously checks infrastructure state to detect and notify operators of any changes, minimizing risk, downtime, and costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The anatomy of automation execution environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-anatomy-of-automation-execution-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-anatomy-of-automation-execution-environments"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 introduced  major architectural changes, like automation mesh and automation execution environments, that help extend Ansible automation across your organization in a flexible manner, providing a single solution to all your organizational and hybrid cloud automation needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Announcing the Auto-refreshing Official Kubernetes CVE Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/12/k8s-cve-feed-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/12/k8s-cve-feed-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Pushkar Joglekar (VMware)
A long-standing request from the Kubernetes community has been to have a
programmatic way for end users to keep track of Kubernetes security issues
(also called "CVEs", after the database that tracks public security issues across
different products and vendors). Accompanying the release of Kubernetes v1.25,
we are excited to announce availability of such
a feed as an alpha
feature. This blog will cover the background and scope of this new service.
Motivation
With the growing number of eyes on Kubernetes, the number of CVEs related to
Kubernetes have increased. Although most CVEs that directly, indirectly, or
transitively impact Kubernetes are regularly fixed, there is no single place for
the end users of Kubernetes to programmatically subscribe or pull the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Walk in the Wild from Terrain Semantics]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/learning-to-walk-in-wild-from-terrain.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/learning-to-walk-in-wild-from-terrain.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yuxiang Yang, Student Researcher, Robotics at Google 
An important promise for quadrupedal robots is their potential to operate in complex outdoor environments that are difficult or inaccessible for humans. Whether it’s to find natural resources deep in the mountains, or to search for life signals in heavily-damaged earthquake sites, a robust and versatile quadrupedal robot could be very helpful. To achieve that, a robot needs to perceive the environment, understand its locomotion challenges, and adapt its locomotion skill accordingly. While recent advances in perceptive locomotion have greatly enhanced the capability of quadrupedal robots, most works focus on indoor or urban environments, thus they cannot effectively handle the complexity of off-road terrains. In these environme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Make Interns a Dynamic Part of Your Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-make-interns-a-dynamic-part-of-your-team</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-make-interns-a-dynamic-part-of-your-team"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figuring out where interns fit into larger team goals can be tough. One HashiCorp manager shares three essential tips to encourage success for everyone involved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: KMS V2 Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/09/kms-v2-improvements/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/09/kms-v2-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Anish Ramasekar, Rita Zhang, Mo Khan, and Xander Grzywinski (Microsoft)
With Kubernetes v1.25, SIG Auth is introducing a new v2alpha1 version of the Key Management Service (KMS) API. There are a lot of improvements in the works, and we're excited to be able to start down the path of a new and improved KMS!
What is KMS?
One of the first things to consider when securing a Kubernetes cluster is encrypting persisted API data at rest. KMS provides an interface for a provider to utilize a key stored in an external key service to perform this encryption.
Encryption at rest using KMS v1 has been a feature of Kubernetes since version v1.10, and is currently in beta as of version v1.12.
What’s new in v2alpha1?
While the original v1 implementation has been successful in helping Kubernetes us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Multi-Axis Approach for Vision Transformer and MLP Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/a-multi-axis-approach-for-vision.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/a-multi-axis-approach-for-vision.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T17:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zhengzhong Tu and Yinxiao Li, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Convolutional neural networks have been the dominant machine learning architecture for computer vision since the introduction of AlexNet in 2012. Recently, inspired by the evolution of Transformers in natural language processing, attention mechanisms have been prominently incorporated into vision models. These attention methods boost some parts of the input data while minimizing other parts so that the network can focus on small but important parts of the data. The Vision Transformer (ViT) has created a new landscape of model designs for computer vision that is completely free of convolution. ViT regards image patches as a sequence of words, and applies a Transformer encoder on top. When trained on sufficiently la…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changes to the Terraform Partner Integration Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-partner-integration-program-changes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-partner-integration-program-changes"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are making some changes to the way that we tag modules and providers in the Terraform Registry for better consistency, clarity, and scalability in the Registry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Automation Experience: AnsibleFest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-automation-experience-ansiblefest-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-automation-experience-ansiblefest-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is almost time for our favorite event of the year! AnsibleFest is back as an in-person event, and it’s the only place to feel the full power of automation. Join us October 18 and 19 in Chicago, and immerse yourself in the movement that’s made Ansible an industry-leading automation technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Global Preview: Evolving Your Cloud Operating Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-preview-evolving-your-cloud-operating-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-preview-evolving-your-cloud-operating-model"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Find out about the 13 most interesting HashiConf Global sessions for enterprise cloud platform teams. Join us October 4 - 6, 2022 in Los Angeles and virtual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes’s IPTables Chains Are Not API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/07/iptables-chains-not-api/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/07/iptables-chains-not-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Dan Winship (Red Hat)
Some Kubernetes components (such as kubelet and kube-proxy) create
iptables chains and rules as part of their operation. These chains
were never intended to be part of any Kubernetes API/ABI guarantees,
but some external components nonetheless make use of some of them (in
particular, using KUBE-MARK-MASQ to mark packets as needing to be
masqueraded).
As a part of the v1.25 release, SIG Network made this declaration
explicit: that (with one exception), the iptables chains that
Kubernetes creates are intended only for Kubernetes’s own internal
use, and third-party components should not assume that Kubernetes will
create any specific iptables chains, or that those chains will contain
any specific rules if they do exist.
Then, in future releases, as part of KEP-31…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Graph connectors for Microsoft Search]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65671</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-graph-connectors-for-microsoft-search/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T23:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Search is the workplace search solution offered with Microsoft 365. Microsoft Search lets you find the information you need by unlocking knowledge and expertise. It helps you find what you need to complete what you’re working on. Whether you’re searching for people,
The post Azure DevOps Graph connectors for Microsoft Search appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digitizing Smell: Using Molecular Maps to Understand Odor]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/digitizing-smell-using-molecular-maps.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/digitizing-smell-using-molecular-maps.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T17:35:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Richard C. Gerkin, Google Research, and Alexander B. Wiltschko, Google 


Did you ever try to measure a smell? …Until you can measure their likenesses and differences you can have no science of odor. If you are ambitious to found a new science, measure a smell.
  
— Alexander Graham Bell, 1914.

 How can we measure a smell? Smells are produced by molecules that waft through the air, enter our noses, and bind to sensory receptors. Potentially billions of molecules can produce a smell, so figuring out which ones produce which smells is difficult to catalog or predict. Sensory maps can help us solve this problem.  Color vision has the most familiar examples of these maps, from the color wheel we each learn in primary school to more sophisticated variants used to perform color correc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault, Kubernetes, and the Graduation of vault-k8s to Version 1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-kubernetes-and-the-graduation-of-vault-k8s-to-version-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-kubernetes-and-the-graduation-of-vault-k8s-to-version-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of vault-k8s 1.0 marks a great time to learn how HashiCorp Vault has integrated with Kubernetes in the past and what to look forward to in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – September 5, 2022]]></title>
        <id>8f3c0923bae1a075227962f5ea6ebbfc45ae02a5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-september-5-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T18:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! As a new week begins, let’s quickly look back at the most significant AWS news from the previous seven days. Last Week’s Launches Here are the launches that got my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>