<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-07-28T00:21:59.682Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-07-28T00:21:59.682Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon Route 53 Application Recovery Controller]]></title>
        <id>4dd26d69ade9053b95b2204f25c1aed35d499bcf</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/tSAJ8u0H0bg/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T21:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce the availability today of Amazon Route 53 Application Recovery Controller, a Amazon Route 53 set of capabilities that continuously monitors an application’s ability to recover from failures and controls application recovery across multiple AWS Availability Zones, AWS Regions, and on premises environments to help you to build applications that must […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HashiCorp Consul with Kong Ingress Controller for Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-hashicorp-consul-with-kong-ingress-controller-for-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-hashicorp-consul-with-kong-ingress-controller-for-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure Kong Ingress Controller for Kubernetes with transparent proxy on HashiCorp Consul service mesh to manage traffic to and between your Kubernetes services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Current Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11310</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/27/our-current-strategy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=our-current-strategy"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T18:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve been running Software Daily for 6 years.  When we started it back in 2015, the goal was to create a software engineering podcast that was 60% as good as Software Engineering Radio, but aired with 5x the frequency.  5 shows per week, 50 weeks per year, 5 ads per show, means 1,250 advertising spots.
The post Our Current Strategy appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collecting and operationalizing threat data from the Mozi botnet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/collecting-and-operationalizing-threat-data-from-the-mozi-botnet</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/collecting-and-operationalizing-threat-data-from-the-mozi-botnet"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting and preventing malicious activity such as botnet attacks is a critical area of focus for threat intel analysts, security operators, and threat hunters. Taking up the Mozi botnet as a case study, this blog post demonstrates how to use open source tools, analytical processes, and the Elastic Stack to perform analysis and enrichment of collected data irrespective of the campaign. This will allow you to take the lessons and processes outlined below to your organization and apply them to your specific use cases.

The Mozi botnet has been leveraging vulnerable Internet of Things (IoT) devices to launch campaigns that can take advantage of the force multiplication provided by a botnet (Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS), email spam, brute-force, password spraying, etc.). Mozi was firs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending the Internet of Things from hackers and viruses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/defending-the-internet-of-things-from-hackers-and-viruses</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/defending-the-internet-of-things-from-hackers-and-viruses"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leon Gubbels is a Security Business Developer at ENGIE, an Elastic MSP. Remco Sprooten is the Product Owner for the security team. Together they describe how their team expanded their security-as-a-service offer to address operational technology (OT) as well as traditional IT systems. 

The 2010 Stuxnet malicious software attack on a uranium enrichment plant in Iran had all the twists and turns of a spy thriller. The plant was air gapped (not connected to the internet) so it couldn’t be targeted directly by an outsider. Instead, the attackers infected five of the plant’s partner organizations, hoping that an engineer from one of them would unknowingly introduce the malware to the network via a thumb drive. 

That is exactly what happened. Exploiting zero-day flaws, the malware entered the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Gubbels,Remco Sprooten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With BGP Address Family Resource Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-bgp-address-family-resource-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-bgp-address-family-resource-modules"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern enterprise networks have grown a lot in size and complexity, making them more difficult to manage than ever before. Working on these complex networks manually can be tedious, time-consuming, costly, and more prone to error.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2021: Get with the Program]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=25406</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/camundacon-2021-get-with-the-program/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T12:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The countdown has officially begun for CamundaCon 2021. Our agenda is now live, and registration is open for you to reserve your spot and join us September 22–23. 
The post CamundaCon 2021: Get with the Program appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charley Mann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 27th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/27/this-week-in-spring-july-27th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/27/this-week-in-spring-july-27th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, Spring fans, from the beautiful island of Oahu, Hawaii. How’re you doing? We’ve got a ton of stuff to look at so let’s get to it! 


  
In last week’s A Bootiful Podcast, I talk to industry analyst, fascinating person, strategist, and storyteller Michael Coté

  
I love this look at building a first application with RabbitMQ streams

  
I loved this infographic by Dormain Drewitz on modernizing the mainframe

  
Premiering Now: SpringOne Tour - July 2021: Do or Do Not, There is no try{} in Production

  
Spring Boot 2.4.9 is now available

  
Spring Boot 2.5.3 is now available

  
Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1 is now available

  
Spring Data is a 10 years old today the 23rd of July 2021!

  
This Week in Spring - July 20th, 2021

  
Using Java 16 records with Thymeleaf

  
Spring Cloud scales Spring Boot apps to billions of requests per day without the hassle of managing infrastructure. See it in action and hear how Swiss Re is acceleratin

  
Register for @SpringOne today]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an Event-Based HA Architecture with Nomad and Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-an-event-based-ha-architecture-with-nomad-and-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-an-event-based-ha-architecture-with-nomad-and-consul"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how content moderation service Chatsight uses HashiCorp Nomad and Consul to speed deployment and maximize uptime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud is now available on Google Cloud in Asia Pacific Northeast 3 (Seoul)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-available-on-google-cloud-in-asia-pacific-northeast-3-seoul</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-is-now-available-on-google-cloud-in-asia-pacific-northeast-3-seoul"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce you can now run Elastic Cloud on Google Cloud in the Asia Pacific Northeast 3 (Seoul) region.  
  
Elastic Cloud gives you the power of enterprise search, observability, and security in the Asia Pacific Northeast 3 (Seoul) region of Google Cloud. Easily search applications, websites, and workplace content platforms for information. Quickly gain deep insights into your environment by monitoring applications and uptime as well as analyzing centralized logs and metrics. You can also help protect your technology investment by layering endpoint security with security event monitoring (SIEM).  
  
Deploy your own way 
 Elastic Cloud gives you the flexibility to run where and how you want. Deploy in the cloud on Amazon Web Services, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure, or all the above. You can choose between our managed service offering, or manage the service yourself with built-in automation and orchestration tools. 
  
When you log in to the Elastic Cloud console, simply select your preferred region and cloud service provider and choose how you want to optimize your deployment based on the compute, memory, or I/O requirements of your specific use case. Once you click “Create deployment,” your Elastic Cloud workload is provisioned in minutes.  
  
Visit our documentation to learn more. 
  
Elastic Cloud and marketplace integration 
 If you are a Google Cloud customer, you can also subscribe to Elastic Cloud (Elasticsearch managed service) via the Google Cloud Marketplace. You can select between usage plans and integrated billing consolidates your Elastic Cloud usage charges into your existing Google Cloud bill. Your Elastic Cloud spend accrues towards your Google Cloud spending commitments. 
  
Getting started is easy: Log in to the Elastic Cloud console or sign up for a free 14-day trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A faster, more seamless way to engage Elastic Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-faster-more-seamless-way-to-engage-elastic-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-faster-more-seamless-way-to-engage-elastic-support"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of July 25, 2021, we have launched a brand-new Elastic Support Portal. The new portal experience is fully integrated with Elastic Cloud and builds upon our previous update around login and authentication. For existing subscription users, the flow to get help stays the same — you’ll continue to access support.elastic.co with your Elastic Cloud account. This blog post explains some details around the new portal experience and how it will impact our users. 

What is changing?
We’ve built a new Support Portal experience where you can create cases, get updates, and engage with Elastic Support. With the new portal, the ability to create and review cases, download licenses, and check on subscription information all stays the same. We built the new portal with our Source Code in mind and adheri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Support</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controlling Processes in a Smart Factory with the Camunda Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=24939</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/controlling-processes-in-a-smart-factory-with-the-camunda-platform/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T14:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how a novel software stack can reduce the gap between the production shop floor and enterprise-level management systems in Industry 4.0
The post Controlling Processes in a Smart Factory with the Camunda Platform appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charley Mann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pulsar Rerevisted with Enrico Olivelli]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11299</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/26/pulsar-rerevisted-with-enrico-olivelli/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pulsar-rerevisted-with-enrico-olivelli"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T09:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous episode, Pulsar Revisited, we discussed how the company DataStax has added to their product stack Astra Streaming, their cloud-native messaging and event streaming service that’s built on top of Apache Pulsar. We discussed Apache Pulsar and the added features DataStax offers like injecting machine learning into your data streams and viewing real-time
The post Pulsar Rerevisted with Enrico Olivelli appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flawed Data]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2494/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2494/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/flawed_data.png" title="We trained it to produce data that looked convincing, and we have to admit the results look convincing!" alt="We trained it to produce data that looked convincing, and we have to admit the results look convincing!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pulsar Revisited with Jonathan Ellis]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11289</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/23/pulsar-revisited-with-jonathan-ellis/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pulsar-revisited-with-jonathan-ellis"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T23:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Pulsar is a cloud-native, distributed messaging and streaming platform originally created at Yahoo! and now a top-level Apache Software Foundation project (pulsar.apache.org). Pulsar is used by many large companies like Yahoo!, Verizon media, Tencent, and Splunk. The company DataStax, an open, multi-cloud stack for modern data apps, has added to their product stack Astra
The post Pulsar Revisited with Jonathan Ellis appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.23]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62012</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-07-23/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T17:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Friday! With Jay out of the office this week, I’m back with some great community content to keep you going until he’s back.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.23 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Murawski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premiering Now: SpringOne Tour - July 2021: Do or Do Not, There is no try{} in Production]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/23/premiering-now-springone-tour-july-2021-do-or-do-not-there-is-no-try-in-production</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/23/premiering-now-springone-tour-july-2021-do-or-do-not-there-is-no-try-in-production"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this July 2021 installment of SpringOne Tour, Josh Long, Cora Iberkleid, Angie Jones, Madhura Bhave, Bella Bai, Olga Maciaszek-Sharma, Whitney Lee, and Nate Schutta look at the wide and wonderful world of testing, continuous integration, and continuous delivery. 

This event - a mini-conference if you will - is two hours and some change long and features dedicated segments from the industry’s best, so grab a drink, a note pad, and let’s get to it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-6-0-m1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-6-0-m1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 120 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Auto-configuration for Spring Data Envers

  
More metrics support (including task execution and scheduling export and support for the Dynatrace v2 API)

  
Auto-configured Spring Web Service Server Tests

  
Improved Configuration of the Maven Plugin’s Start Goal


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests. Our next set of releases are due August 19, 2021.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dual USB-C]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2493/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2493/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/dual_usb_c.png" title="Small devices use two-prong USB-AC, but there's also a three-prong version with a USB-B plug as the ground." alt="Small devices use two-prong USB-AC, but there's also a three-prong version with a USB-B plug as the ground." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitchell's New Role at HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mitchell-s-new-role-at-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mitchell-s-new-role-at-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mitchell Hashimoto takes on a new individual contributor role at HashiCorp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Orange Business Services is building a better SIEM with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-orange-business-services-is-building-a-better-siem-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-orange-business-services-is-building-a-better-siem-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a security analyst at Orange Business Services in Paris, and one of my current projects for the Orange Group is implementing a new SIEM based on the Elastic Stack. In this blog post, I’ll share why we chose Elastic and how we were able to integrate Elastic into our existing SIEM, resulting in faster investigations and saving our engineers’ time.

So follow along:

Orange Group is a multi-service network operator and digital service provider in 26 countries and serves about 253 million customers with 147,000 employees. Orange Business Services, the unit dedicated to businesses and organizations, focuses on digital services. From connectivity, the Internet of Things (IoT), and the cloud to artificial intelligence (AI), application development, and cybersecurity, Orange Business Services …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jocelyn Renouf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.3 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-5-3-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-5-3-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T14:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.3 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 58 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.4.9 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-4-9-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/spring-boot-2-4-9-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T10:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.4.9 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 35 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stack Overflow for Teams: A Centralized Knowledge Sharing and Collaboration Platform with Tom Limoncelli]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11280</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/22/stack-overflow-for-teams-a-centralized-knowledge-sharing-and-collaboration-platform-with-tom-limoncelli/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=stack-overflow-for-teams-a-centralized-knowledge-sharing-and-collaboration-platform-with-tom-limoncelli"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T09:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever googled a CS or programming question, you likely found an answer (or many) on Stack Overflow. Founded in 2008 and named after a common computing error, Stack Overflow empowers the world to develop technology through collective knowledge. More than 100 million people visit Stack Overflow every month making it one of the
The post Stack Overflow for Teams: A Centralized Knowledge Sharing and Collaboration Platform with Tom Limoncelli appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: industry analyst, fascinating person, strategist, and storyteller Michael Coté]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/a-bootiful-podcast-industry-analyst-fascinating-person-strategist-and-storyteller-michael-cot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/22/a-bootiful-podcast-industry-analyst-fascinating-person-strategist-and-storyteller-michael-cot"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to industry analyst, fascinating person, strategist, and storyteller Michael Coté (@cote).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Duplicate Batch Jobs in HashiCorp Nomad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-duplicate-batch-jobs-in-hashicorp-nomad</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-duplicate-batch-jobs-in-hashicorp-nomad"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two approaches to injecting variability into your Nomad batch job template without having to modify the template in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Contact Center Day – July 2021]]></title>
        <id>00b7c611ad2f6105489605e59f50390273ecc710</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/9-I5Zf71gm0/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T15:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, I ordered from Amazon.fr a box of four toothpaste tubes, but only one was in the box. I called Amazon’s customer center. The agent immediately found my order without me having to share the long order number. She issued a refund and told me I even can keep the one tube I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CockroachDB: Distributed Databases and Containerization with Spencer Kimball]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11275</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/21/cockroachdb-distributed-databases-and-containerization-with-spencer-kimball/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cockroachdb-distributed-databases-and-containerization-with-spencer-kimball"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T09:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2003, Google developed a robust cluster management system called Borg. This enabled them to manage clusters with tens of thousands of machines, moving them away from virtual machines and firmly into container management. Then, in 2014, they open sourced a version of Borg called Kubernetes, or K8s.  Now, in 2021, CockroachDB is a distributed
The post CockroachDB: Distributed Databases and Containerization with Spencer Kimball appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commonly Mispronounced Equations]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2492/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2492/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/commonly_mispronounced_equations.png" title="&quot;Epsihootamoo doopsiquorps&quot; --the Schrödinger equation for the hydrogen atom" alt="&quot;Epsihootamoo doopsiquorps&quot; --the Schrödinger equation for the hydrogen atom" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Herding (Apache) Camels with HashiCorp Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/herding-apache-camels-with-hashicorp-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/herding-apache-camels-with-hashicorp-consul"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how to keep track of your Apache Camel services running throughout a deployment, and enable them to communicate with one another in a multi-cloud or hybrid cloud environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes – @Azure Logic Apps with @ChloeCondon]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61948</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-azure-logic-apps-with-chloecondon/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T16:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes – @Azure Logic Apps with @ChloeCondon appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How versatile is the Elastic Stack? Ask Walmart, NASA, or Airbus.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-versatile-is-the-elastic-stack-ask-walmart-nasa-airbus</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-versatile-is-the-elastic-stack-ask-walmart-nasa-airbus"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do an airline, the world’s largest retailer, the French government, Adobe, and NASA’s JPL have in common? They use the Elastic Stack to empower customers, communities, and, even, interplanetary exploration.  
 With the Elastic Stack’s ability to take data from any source and in any format, and then search, analyze, and visualize it in real time, organizations can act quickly to improve customer experience and power critical systems. The flexibility of Elastic as a platform means that the same underlying technology can serve a broad range of challenges.  
 See how companies across the globe are using Elastic to... 
 
Combat fraud and save consumers millions
 
Walmart’s Global Investigations team has used Elastic to ingest more than 4 billion metadata records over the past 5 years to co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Quintal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.13.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-13-4-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-13-4-released"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.13.4 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Beats, Logstash, Workplace Search, App Search and APM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Goodheart-Smithe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 20th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/20/this-week-in-spring-july-20th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/20/this-week-in-spring-july-20th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T14:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, my friends, from Hawai’i, where I’m currently on vacation! And, because I’m on vacation, I’ll cut to the chase: there’s a lot of great stuff to get to this week (surprise!) 

But first, a friendly turtle I met the other day:


You’re welcome. Now then, where were we? Oh right! 


  
In last week’s installment of A Bootiful Podcast, I talk about visualizing software architecture with the C4 model with architect Simon Brown. Don’t miss this one!

  
Spring Tips: Some cool features possible with Spring Integration 5.5

  
Have you checked out the speakers in this year’s SpringOne, on September 1st to 2nd, 2021? I’ll be there and so will many amazing others!

  
Spring Data 2021.0.3 and 2020.0.11 released

  
Spring Data 2021.1.0-M1 released

  
Spring Framework 5.3.9 and 5.2.16 available now

  
I love this blog looking at Spring GraphQL Milestone One

  
Spring Security 5.6.0-M1 released

  
The State of Spring Survey is back and we want to hear from you!

  
I love to see this, finally, Building applications with RabbitMQ streams

  
Blog: Kubernetes Release Cadence Change: Here’s What You Need To Know]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fun with private Automation Hub - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/fun-with-private-automation-hub-part-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/fun-with-private-automation-hub-part-2"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous blog post, I provided a brief history on Ansible Content Collections and demonstrated how to upload a Collection to a private Automation Hub. We ended the blog by synchronizing content from Ansible Galaxy and Automation Hub. Today, we will configure Ansible Tower to communicate with private Automation Hub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Leroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sust Global: Taking Action Against Climate Change with Josh Gilbert]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11270</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/20/sust-global-taking-action-against-climate-change-with-josh-gilbert/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sust-global-taking-action-against-climate-change-with-josh-gilbert"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T09:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments, consumers, and companies across the world are becoming more aware and attentive to the risks and causes of climate change. From recycling to using solar power, people are looking for ways to reduce their carbon footprint. Markets like the financial sector, governments, and consulting are looking for ways to understand climate data to make
The post Sust Global: Taking Action Against Climate Change with Josh Gilbert appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EBS io2 Block Express Volumes with Amazon EC2 R5b Instances Are Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>4f26815f4609dfa07968fe11baa5223ab8c8533c</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/o7h88XQ3T_Y/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T20:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2020, we previewed Amazon EBS io2 Block Express volumes, the next-generation server storage architecture that delivers the first SAN built for the cloud. Block Express is designed to meet the requirements of the largest, most I/O-intensive, mission-critical deployments of Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle, SAP HANA, and SAS Analytics on AWS. Today, I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imply Infra: Big Data Analysis and Real-World Examples with Jad Naous]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11265</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/19/imply-infra-big-data-analysis-and-real-world-examples-with-jad-naous/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=imply-infra-big-data-analysis-and-real-world-examples-with-jad-naous"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T18:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big data analytics is the process of collecting data, processing and cleaning it, then analyzing it with techniques like data mining, predictive analytics, and deep learning. This process requires a suite of tools to operate efficiently. Data analytics can save companies money, drive product development, and give insight into the market and customers. The company
The post Imply Infra: Big Data Analysis and Real-World Examples with Jad Naous appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.6.0-M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/19/spring-security-5-6-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/19/spring-security-5-6-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I’m pleased to announce the release of Spring Security 5.6.0-M1!



In addition to dependency upgrades, bug fixes, and minor enhancements, the milestone contains a few noteworthy changes:





An AuthorizationManager for method security



Support for any data type in Access Token Response



A separate repository for Spring Security samples





You can find the complete details in the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immune Factory]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2491/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2491/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/immune_factory.png" title="In the final vote, the doubters were won over by the strength of the name IMMUNION." alt="In the final vote, the doubters were won over by the strength of the name IMMUNION." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convince Ashmeet Sidana to Invest in Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11262</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/18/how-to-convince-ashmeet-sidana-to-invest-in-your-business/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-convince-ashmeet-sidana-to-invest-in-your-business"/>
        <updated>2021-07-18T17:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ashmeet Sidana is the founder of Engineering Capital.
The post How to Convince Ashmeet Sidana to Invest in Your Business appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HashiCorp Does Developer Advocacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-does-developer-advocacy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-does-developer-advocacy"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about our approach to developer advocacy, from choosing Developer Advocates to represent and engage our community, to how we approach the work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.0.3 and 2020.0.11 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/16/spring-data-2021-0-3-and-2020-0-11-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/16/spring-data-2021-0-3-and-2020-0-11-released"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data2021.0.2 and 2020.0.10 service releases.

Both releases are built on top of Spring Framework 5.3.9. For your convenience, you can consume these releases through Spring Boot 2.5.3 and 2.4.9, respectively. Our teammates on the Boot team will release those in about a week.

The service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.

To round things off, here are the links to the artifacts, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.0.3


  
Spring Data Commons 2.5.3 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.2.3 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.5.3 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data KeyValue 2.5.3 -…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.1.0-M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/16/spring-data-2021-1-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/16/spring-data-2021-1-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data 2021.1.0-M1 milestone release.

Both releases are built on top of Spring Framework 5.3.9. For your convenience, you can consume this release through Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1, which our team mates on the Boot team will release in about a week.

The 2021.1 release train ships a set of features and dependency upgrades.
The most important changes are:


  
Upgrade to Querydsl 5.

  
Support for a wide range of Redis 6.2 commands.

  
Support for dialect-dependent custom conversions in Spring Data JDBC. This was used to improve the support of java.time types across multiple databases.

  
Support for streaming large result sets in Spring Data JDBC.

  
Support for AggregateReference in query derivation.

  
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design for the future: Improving the Camunda Optimize Report builder experience]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=21705</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/06/design-for-the-future-improving-the-camunda-optimize-report-builder-experience/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T10:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize is maturing. New features and a better understanding of user needs required a refinement of the tool's UI and provided Camunda’s design team with an opportunity to improve the user experience.
The post Design for the future: Improving the Camunda Optimize Report builder experience appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.16]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61978</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-07-16/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T08:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.07.16 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.16 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid Threat Protection with Sumo Logic Cloud SIEM Powered by AWS]]></title>
        <id>372e69aca051cae4f4c1b6a43259e8a84c0f5a51</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/aTcqLe6p0cY/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT security teams need to have a real-time understanding of what’s happening with their infrastructure and applications. They need to be able to find and correlate data in this continuous flood of information to identify unexpected behaviors or patterns that can lead to a security breach. To simplify and automate this process, many solutions have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Stack: A New DevOps Experience with Juraj Masar]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11238</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/15/better-stack-a-new-devops-experience-with-juraj-masar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=better-stack-a-new-devops-experience-with-juraj-masar"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T21:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps has shortened the development life cycle for countless applications and is embraced by companies around the world. But managing and monitoring multiple environments is still a major pain point, particularly when companies need to mix cloud and legacy systems. Knowing when services go down and quickly pinpointing the cause is essential for continuous development. 
The post Better Stack: A New DevOps Experience with Juraj Masar appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Visualizing software architecture with the C4 model with architect Simon Brown]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/15/a-bootiful-podcast-visualizing-software-architecture-with-the-c4-model-with-architect-simon-brown</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/15/a-bootiful-podcast-visualizing-software-architecture-with-the-c4-model-with-architect-simon-brown"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, I talk to author, prolific public speaker, an architect’s architect, and one of the most interesting people I get to bump into, and learn from, in this wacky, wild, and wonderful ecosystem of ours: Simon Brown (@simonbrown).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of Spring Survey is back!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/15/state-of-spring-survey-is-back</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/15/state-of-spring-survey-is-back"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR - head over to spring.io/survey to take the State of Spring 2021 survey! You can also RT this tweet and help spread the word! Thank you <3


We ran the State of Spring survey last year, and it was a huge success. Spring community members across the globe, like you, shared their views and experiences, and it all made for fantastic reading.

The survey is back this year, and we want to hear from you! How can Spring help you build new apps and experiences this year? What would you like us to change? This year, we have new sections on Spring Native, building & sharing APIs internally/externally, and a deeper dive on Data.

In exchange for 15 minutes of your time taking the survey, you’ll be among the first to receive our report and the insights included in it. 

Sounds good? Head over to spring.io/survey now! The survey will close at the end of July. 

Do consider helping us share the survey by retweeting this post on Spring Central twitter, and thank you for sharing your thoughts and experiences with us! 

The Spring Team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing customers the best Elastic experience on Alibaba Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-customers-the-best-elastic-experience-on-alibaba-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-customers-the-best-elastic-experience-on-alibaba-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership between Elastic and Alibaba Cloud has expanded our community of users and developers into thousands of commercial users. 
	

This partnership is a leading example of Elastic’s commitment to partnering with companies that users trust with their cloud infrastructure and developing a cloud-native, flexible platform. Other partners include Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud, and AWS.
	

Now, we are thrilled to be the recipient of Alibaba Cloud’s Walking Together Award. Here, Pankaj Khushani, Sr. Director of Partners at Elastic, explains how Elastic and Alibaba Cloud have overcome market and global challenges to drive growth. 

What is unique about the partnership?
One of the most unique things about our partnership is that Alibaba Elasticsearch is one of Alibaba’s self-developed sol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Quintal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Your Summer Spotify Playlist with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/build-your-summer-spotify-playlist-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/build-your-summer-spotify-playlist-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow our new tutorial to build your summer playlist with Terraform using a community-authored Spotify provider. Hear from the author and share your playlist for a chance to win a free HashiCorp T-shirt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does search solve data problems?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-does-search-solve-data-problems</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-does-search-solve-data-problems"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is enterprise data a benefit or a burden?

Think about all of the data your organization generates and consumes in the digital age — from security event logs to application error messages, energy consumption to vendor contracts. There is so much, and all of it is usually stored in silos, making the data difficult to synthesize to provide better services, identify signals proactively, or make stronger business decisions. How do organizations overcome the challenges of understanding their data so that they can finally derive value from it, allowing organizations to truly put their data to work? 

The answer is to shift your organization’s thinking away from the complexity of consolidating data to how to better find the answers within it. More data can mean more insights, and those benefits h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Quintal,Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paging Doctor Cloud! Amazon HealthLake Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>57587dfa2c2661bbc68cad661a38c942328e95e6</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/DuRcp2g2t04/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2020, we previewed Amazon HealthLake, a fully managed, HIPAA-eligible service that allows healthcare and life sciences customers to aggregate their health information from different silos and formats into a structured, centralized AWS data lake, and extract insights from that data with analytics and machine learning (ML). Today, I’m very happy to announce […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Some cool features possible with Spring Integration 5.5]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/14/spring-tips-some-cool-features-possible-with-spring-integration-5-5</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/14/spring-tips-some-cool-features-possible-with-spring-integration-5-5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, I look at some key features made possible by the new Spring Integration 5.5 release, including the new Spring .zip archive support and the new Spring Native hints supporting GraalVM native images]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free training fundamentals courses from Elastic Enterprise Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/free-training-fundamentals-courses-elastic-enterprise-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/free-training-fundamentals-courses-elastic-enterprise-search"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently released new free on-demand Elastic training courses for the products in the Elastic Enterprise Search solution: Elastic Workplace Search and Elastic App Search. 

Our on-demand courses provide the same immersive learning experience found in the classroom, but delivered in a convenient, remote environment. These self-paced courses include expertly designed materials, engaging demos, and hands-on lab exercises. They provide everything you need to start creating powerful search experiences for your workplace, websites, and apps.
 
Elastic Workplace Search and Elastic App Search are built on the Elastic Stack, so you can enjoy its speed, scale, and relevance without the heavy development and maintenance requirements of building your own search solution.
 
App Search Fundamentals
E…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamara Rosini,Darren Meiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation Savings Planner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-savings-planner</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-savings-planner"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-plan your automation savings with Red Hat Insights for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Science on AWS: Implementing AI and ML Pipelines on AWS with Chris Fregly]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11236</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/14/data-science-on-aws-implementing-ai-and-ml-pipelines-on-aws-with-chris-fregly/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-science-on-aws-implementing-ai-and-ml-pipelines-on-aws-with-chris-fregly"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T09:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data science is an interdisciplinary field that combines strong technical skills with industry knowledge to perform a large range of jobs. Data scientists solve business questions with hands-on work cleaning and analyzing data, building machine learning models and applying algorithms, and generating dynamic visuals and tools to understand the world from the data it generates.
The post Data Science on AWS: Implementing AI and ML Pipelines on AWS with Chris Fregly appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.9 and 5.2.16 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/14/spring-framework-5-3-9-and-5-2-16-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/14/spring-framework-5-3-9-and-5-2-16-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T08:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.9 and 5.2.16 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.9 includes 45 fixes and improvements. Spring Framework 5.2.16 includes 12 selected fixes and improvements.

Stay tuned for follow-up Spring Boot releases next week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 13th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/13/this-week-in-spring-july-13th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/13/this-week-in-spring-july-13th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How’re you doing? I’m heads-down, hurriedly making final preparations for tomorrow’s SpringOne Tour episode installment. This is going to be SO MUCH FUN. Do NOT miss this show tomorrow morning, 10AM California time. I’ll be there, along with my friends Madhura Bhave, Olga Maciaszek-Sharma, Bella Bai, Whitney Lee, Core Iberkleid, Nate Schutta, and special guest star Angie Jones. 

We look forward to seeing you there and we’ll explore the wide and wonderful world of continuous delivery, testing and more together. 


  
JOOQ 3.15.0 Release  is out, and includes support for R2DBC (and much more)

  
Neat! The JRE will be UTF-8 by default instead of dangerously assuming the host operating system’s default: openjdk/jdk

  
A Bootiful Podcast: Matt Raible Last week, I talked to Matt Raible, and you can too! I love that guy. So happy he was able to join the show again.

  
Spring Tips: Spring Cloud Square

  
This is neat: you can run TestNG tests with JUnit 5 now

  
Piotr Mińkowski on Twitter: JPAstreamer is a library for expressing JPA/Hibernate queries as Java streams. It can be also integrated with Spring. 

  
Apress’ R2DBC Revealed book is available for order

  
Scaling Spring Boot Microservices

  
Have you seen the lineup for our annual tentpole conference, SpringOne, this  Sep 1–2, 2021? I’ll be there and so will a ton of other amazing people.

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.1.2 available now

  
Spring Cloud Hoxton.SR12 has been released

  
Check out this cool Spring GraphQL demo project]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.1 RC now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61967</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2020-1-1-rc-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T17:51:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we released Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.1 RC. This is our planned prerelease before our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.1. You can upgrade from Azure DevOps Server 2020.1 or previous versions of TFS and Azure DevOps. You can find the full details in our release notes.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.1 RC now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Move Fast with Jeff Meyerson]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11231</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/13/move-fast-with-jeff-meyerson/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=move-fast-with-jeff-meyerson"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T16:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode we discuss the new Move Fast book, as well as many aspects of the current state of software engineering. Daliana Liu interviews Jeff Meyerson, host of Software Daily and author of Move Fast. This interview was also recorded as a video podcast. Check out the video on the Software Daily YouTube channel.
The post Move Fast with Jeff Meyerson appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 46 – OpenShift on @Azure with @jjasghar]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61890</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-46-openshift-on-azure-with-jjasghar/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T14:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 46 – OpenShift on @Azure with @jjasghar appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS) – 15 Years and Still Queueing!]]></title>
        <id>2c8d960c80b46e817beea8943dac6c1c391c0232</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/yQjvDBuBwoA/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time sure does fly! I wrote about the production launch of Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS) back in 2006, with no inkling that I would still be blogging fifteen years later, or that this service would still be growing rapidly while remaining fundamental to the architecture of so many different types of web-scale applications. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.1.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=24420</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/camunda-cloud-110-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T10:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.1.0, the next version of our innovative process automation SaaS offering, is here. 
The post Camunda Cloud 1.1.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Mueller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16.0-alpha3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=23929</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/camunda-platform-runtime-7160-alpha3-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T07:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16.0-alpha3 is here, featuring support for Java 15 & GraalVM JavaScript, and a new create deployment REST API. 
The post Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16.0-alpha3 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda BPM Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Modeler 4.9 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=23565</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/camunda-modeler-49-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Camunda Modeler 4.9 release ships with support for Camunda Cloud 1.1, improvements to the core editor UI, BPMN and DMN editor enhancements, and bug fixes.
The post Camunda Modeler 4.9 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nico Rehwaldt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.5.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=24143</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/camunda-optimize-350-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T07:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.5.0. which ships with new capabilities including Multi Process Reports and an Elasticsearch headers plugin.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.5.0 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Mueller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cawemo Enterprise (On-Premises) 1.7 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=24133</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/cawemo-enterprise-on-premises-17-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re happy to announce the 1.7 release of Cawemo Enterprise On-Premises, including improvements like copy & paste between diagrams and smarter milestone autosaving.
The post Cawemo Enterprise (On-Premises) 1.7 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Rogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Lineage: Understanding Data Lineage at Scale with Julien Le Dem]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11210</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/12/data-lineage-understanding-data-lineage-at-scale-with-julien-le-dem/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-lineage-understanding-data-lineage-at-scale-with-julien-le-dem"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T18:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big Data has exploded the past decade as cloud computing and more efficient hardware made scaling essentially limitless. Products like Uber revolve entirely around analyzing data to provide rides. According to an EMC/IDC study, there was approximately 5.2TB of data for every person in 2020. That estimate was made before the transition to remote work,
The post Data Lineage: Understanding Data Lineage at Scale with Julien Le Dem appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic named a Leader in The Forrester Wave: Cognitive Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-named-leader-forrester-wave-cognitive-search-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-named-leader-forrester-wave-cognitive-search-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re thrilled to announce that Elastic has been named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Cognitive Search, Q3 2021*, highlighting, in our opinion, our commitment to providing a set of tools that makes it quicker and easier to build great search experiences with Elasticsearch. 

In addition to receiving the highest score possible in the strategy category, Elastic also received the highest scores possible in the operations and market awareness criteria. We believe this underlines the investments and rapid pace of product innovation Elastic has committed to Enterprise Search over the past year. For example, we’ve continued to deepen our integrations, including adding prebuilt connectivity for Slack, Box, and Gmail. 

“[Elastic’s] sweet spot is for enterprises that want fast, friendly, and affo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Riley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(Full Audiobook) Move Fast: How Facebook Builds Software]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11220</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/11/full-audiobook-move-fast-how-facebook-builds-software/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=full-audiobook-move-fast-how-facebook-builds-software"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T11:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is the full audiobook for “Move Fast: How Facebook Builds Software”. Continue listening to the end to hear my most recent album “Simulation”.
The post (Full Audiobook) Move Fast: How Facebook Builds Software appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing HashiTalks: Build, a Developer-Focused Edition of Our Community Event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-hashitalks-build-a-developer-focused-edition-of-our-community-event</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-hashitalks-build-a-developer-focused-edition-of-our-community-event"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what to expect from the first developer-focused edition of HashiTalks — and why you don't want to miss this virtual community event on July 21 and 22, 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.1.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/09/spring-authorization-server-0-1-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/09/spring-authorization-server-0-1-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.1.2.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




compile 'org.springframework.security.experimental:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.1.2'




For additional details on this new project, see the initial announcement and project page.



The main features delivered in this release are:





Ability to configure a custom Authorization Consent page (gh-283)



JDBC implementation of RegisteredClientRepository (gh-265), OAuth2AuthorizationService (gh-245) and OAuth2AuthorizationConsentService (gh-313)



Ability to configure the Authorization Endpoint (gh-342)



Ability to configure the Token Endpoint (gh-319)





See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the sample to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues |  ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.09]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61944</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-07-09/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T13:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.07.09 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.09 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investment Strategy: Defining New Markets with Sarah Guo]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11178</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/09/investment-strategy-defining-new-markets-with-sarah-guo/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=investment-strategy-defining-new-markets-with-sarah-guo"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T09:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We talk to a lot of exciting startups from all over the world about their tech products. Recently we’ve heard from people innovating in the blockchain space, cloud infrastructure, databases, and automation tools. However, in today’s episode, we’re going to talk about how these tech startups get investments to build their great products in the
The post Investment Strategy: Defining New Markets with Sarah Guo appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add search to your iOS app with Elastic App Search: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-add-search-to-your-ios-app-part-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-add-search-to-your-ios-app-part-2"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part one, we went over setting up your Elastic stack and ingesting data. In the second part of this blog series, we will be creating an iOS app that uses Elasticsearch for searching a movie database.

Note: This tutorial is based on Elasticsearch version 7.12.x

Starting a New Xcode Project


	
Open Xcode and create a new project.
In the iOS tab, select App and choose Next
Configure the options for setting up the new app
	
Product name: App-Search
Team: <your team name>
Organization Identifier: <your identifier>
Interface: SwiftUI
Life Cycle: SwiftUI App
Language: Swift
Use core data: No
Include tests: No

	
Select Next
Choose where to save your project, and select Create
 
Building the UI

The UI will be built out in the ContentView.swift file.
The basic structure of the UI will be as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Groves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add search to your iOS app with Elastic App Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-add-search-to-your-ios-app-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-add-search-to-your-ios-app-part-1"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a short and sweet, to-the-point, tutorial series that shows how to add search functionality to an iOS app using Elasticsearch for free! More specifically, in this two-part blog series, we will be creating an iOS app that uses Elastic App Search for searching a movie database. By the end of this tutorial, whether you need to search through a small movie database or through petabytes of cloud metrics, you’ll have the knowledge you need to build an amazing search experience for iOS mobile users.

Note: This tutorial is based on Elasticsearch version 7.12.x

Setup Elastic Cloud trial


	
Navigate to https://www.elastic.co/cloud/.
Choose Start free trial.
Sign up and login.
Choose Start your free trial.
Select the Enterprise Search option.
Choose to Expand the settings.
Choose version 7…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Groves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynatrace for DevOps and SRE with Aloïs Reitbauer]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11209</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/08/dynatrace-for-devops-and-sre-with-alois-reitbauer/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dynatrace-for-devops-and-sre-with-alois-reitbauer"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T17:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company Dynatrace provides intelligent observability, continuous automation, and causation-based AI to help Cloud Ops, DevOps, and SRE teams transform faster, innovate more, and deliver better business outcomes. They offer application performance monitoring, infrastructure monitoring, cloud automation, application security, and much more. While being an industry leader in simplifying complex cloud applications, Dynatrace is continuously
The post Dynatrace for DevOps and SRE with Aloïs Reitbauer appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping SAML attributes to Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform organizations and teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/mapping-saml-attributes-to-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-organizations-and-teams</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/mapping-saml-attributes-to-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-organizations-and-teams"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two-Factor Authentication (2FA) is an additional layer of security that can be used to help protect enterprise applications from unauthorized access. While OAuth, and even some LDAP configs are viable options to enable 2FA in Ansible Automation Platform, users prefer to leverage Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) for this purpose, as described in Using two-factor SAML with Red Hat Ansible Tower. On the other hand, 2FA to managed machines is discouraged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Leiva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical CPU time performance tuning for security software: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/practical-cpu-time-performance-tuning-for-security-software-part-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/practical-cpu-time-performance-tuning-for-security-software-part-2"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous blog, we discussed how to monitor, troubleshoot, and fix high %CPU issues. We also revealed a system API that could have an unexpected impact on CPU consumption. In this episode, we’ll discuss another time-related performance aspect that is unique to security software: application startup time. You don’t need to be a developer to benefit from this article. As long as you are curious to find out how the applications in your environment perform and why sometimes they seem to be very slow and want to improve that, you might find this blog post helpful.
 
What is application startup time?

Security software usually sits along the critical path an application takes when it is about to launch or execute. The software makes the decision either to block or allow the launching/executi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yamin Tian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Matt Raible]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/08/a-bootiful-podcast-matt-raible</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/08/a-bootiful-podcast-matt-raible"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Matt Raible! I love talking to Matt Raible, and I’ll bet you would too. He’s one of the good ones, people. One of the legends of the Java and JavaScript communities. One of the greats. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily Manage Security Group Rules with the New Security Group Rule ID]]></title>
        <id>275d63fb9a5b17d9475df998629b499d6de358c8</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/p1HdsCm42h0/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS, we tirelessly innovate to allow you to focus on your business, not its underlying IT infrastructure. Sometimes we launch a new service or a major capability. Sometimes we focus on details that make your professional life easier. Today, I’m happy to announce one of these small details that makes a difference: VPC security […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.13.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-13-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-13-3-released"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.13.3 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Beats, Logstash, Workplace Search, App Search and APM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Duarte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security prevents 100% of REvil ransomware samples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-prevents-100-percent-of-revil-ransomware-samples</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-prevents-100-percent-of-revil-ransomware-samples"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users of Elastic Security are protected through numerous layers of protections against the REvil ransomware that affected Kaseya VSA and its customers. Elastic Security’s layered protections prevented 100% of the REvil ransomware samples tested before damage and loss could occur to the business.

We believe that detections and preventions must be layered, as no single protection works 100% of the time. There are times where detection in the SIEM/central analytics layer is the most effective, especially when you need to take signals from multiple places or correlate the activity to determine it is malicious. However, the most effective way to stop an attack is at the host. 

Prevention is paramount when it comes to ransomware. Teams cannot wait to be notified of an issue after their data is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 6.8.17 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-6-8-17-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-6-8-17-released"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 6.8.17 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Kibana, Elasticsearch, Beats, Logstash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Duarte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AIX Patch Management with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/aix-patch-management-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/aix-patch-management-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading enterprises today use Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform to provision, configure, manage, secure and orchestrate hybrid IT environments. A common misconception is that Ansible is just used to manage the Linux operating system. This is a false belief. Ansible supports Linux, Windows, AIX, IBM i and IBM z/OS environments. This blog will help AIX system administrators get started with Ansible on AIX, and introduce a patching use case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Talor Holloway</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Hoxton.SR12 has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/07/spring-cloud-hoxton-sr12-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/07/spring-cloud-hoxton-sr12-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T16:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Service Release 12 (SR12) of the Spring Cloud Hoxton Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the Hoxton release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the Hoxton Release Train

See all issues included in this release here.

This was primarily a bug fix and documentation release. Hoxton.SR12 is compatible with Spring Boot 2.3.x and 2.2.x.

NOTE: This will be the last regularly scheduled release of the Hoxton Release Train. It now enters a special maintenance period for security fixes and critical bugs until the end of Feb 2022 (which follows the lifecycle of Spring Boot 2.3.x). See the wiki for more information.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Added TaskSchedulerWrappe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing SSH Access at Scale with HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-ssh-access-at-scale-with-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-ssh-access-at-scale-with-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build scalable, role-based SSH access with SSH certificates and HashiCorp Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changes to support for ciphers used to connect to Elasticsearch Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/notice-cipher-changes-ess</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/notice-cipher-changes-ess"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Elastic Cloud we are committed to offering our customers the most secure way to run their workloads in the cloud. With the goal of being “secure by default,” we are deprecating ciphers that are considered weak and insecure. Going forward, we will only support ciphers that are included in the Mozilla intermediate list. These changes will take effect after January 30, 2022. We will communicate a precise date closer to the change.

What are the changes?
We are updating the list of ciphers supported for clients connecting to their Elasticsearch clusters, Kibana, or other components on Elasticsearch Service. The changes are basically on two fronts:

 
	
We will deprecate certain ciphers that are considered weak by modern encryption standards. The ciphers we are going to stop supporting in al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubha Anjur Tupil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Career Karma with Ruben Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11203</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/07/career-karma-with-ruben-harris/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=career-karma-with-ruben-harris"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T09:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode we discuss coding bootcamps, fear, fitness, and more with Ruben Harris, CEO of Career Karma. This interview was also recorded as a video podcast. Check out the video on the Software Daily YouTube channel. Sponsorship inquiries: sponsor@softwareengineeringdaily.com
The post Career Karma with Ruben Harris appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Spring Cloud Square]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/07/spring-tips-spring-cloud-square</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/07/spring-tips-spring-cloud-square"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long (@starbuxman) looks at how to build smarter HTTP clients for your Spring Boot microservices with Spring Cloud Square, Retrofit, and OKHTTP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 6th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/06/this-week-in-spring-july-6th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/06/this-week-in-spring-july-6th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T01:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We’re in July already! That blows my mind - we’re closer to 2022 than 2020 at this point. I don’t wanna jinx it, but this year seems markedly better than last year, and I hope it stays that way. Anyway, friends, let’s get on with the roundup!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Benjamin Wilms, founder of the Chaos Monkey for Spring Boot and Steadybit, a company to help you build more robust software

  
BlockHound: how it works

  
Getting Started with Apache Camel and Spring Boot

  
GraalVM on Twitter

  
Hello, Spring GraphQL

  
Introducing Spring GraphQL

  
Maciej Walkowiak on Twitter

  
Spring Tips: Spring Retrosocket

  
Use New Relic to effortlessly monitor applications and dependencies in Azure Spring Cloud

  
Detect, Diagnose and Resolve Issues Faster in Spring Boot applications using @NewRelic across your Azure Spring Cloud instances. 

  
Register for @SpringOne today. https://t.co/2Imy31RPwz https://t.co/nVXiILvyOH http://bit.ly/SpringOne21TW VMwareTanzu SpringOne

  
This project - mhewedy/spring-data-jpa-mongodb-expressions - adds MongoDB query expressions to Spring Data JPA. This’ll be a win for so many JavaScript clients that like to build queries using MongoDB expressions!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security Recognized in the 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for SIEM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-recognized-in-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-siem</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-recognized-in-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-siem"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to share that Elastic Security has been recognized in the 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Security Information and Event Management (SIEM). Elastic Security is the latest Elastic solution to be recognized in a 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant report, following the 2021 Magic Quadrant for Insight Engines and 2021 Magic Quadrant for Application Performance Monitoring. 

Download the complimentary report to see Gartner’s market evaluation, and read on to understand why we think that momentum is continuing to build for Elastic Security.


The 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Security Information and Event Management (SIEM)1

 

SIEM for the modern SOC
The Elastic Stack has enabled security teams at organizations like Uber and the Indiana University OmniSOC revamp how they operate since…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols,Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your deployments on Elastic Cloud with Azure Private Link]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-your-deployments-on-elastic-cloud-with-azure-private-link</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-your-deployments-on-elastic-cloud-with-azure-private-link"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the general availability of the Azure Private Link integration with Elastic Cloud. Azure Private Link provides private connectivity between your VNET (Virtual Network) and other Azure resources. Private Link simplifies your cloud network architecture and eliminates data exposure to the public internet by routing your data to private Azure service endpoints.  
 The use of Azure Private Link with Elastic Cloud provides an additional layer of security to help you meet your security policy and compliance requirements. You can take advantage of Azure Private Link across all subscription tiers on Elastic Cloud. In this blog we’ll show you how easy it is to get started. We’ll walk you through the steps to configure Private Link access between your VNET and Elastic Cloud…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubha Anjur Tupil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 37 – Microsoft Power Apps with @98codes]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61886</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-37-microsoft-power-apps-with-98codes/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 37 – Microsoft Power Apps with @98codes appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta: Maintaining Security Standards with Christina Cacioppo]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11197</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/06/vanta-maintaining-security-standards-with-christina-cacioppo/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=vanta-maintaining-security-standards-with-christina-cacioppo"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T09:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOC 2 is a security audit to prove that SaaS companies have secured their company and customer data. It’s often considered the minimum audit necessary to sell software. HIPAA is a federal law regulating how sensitive medical information about patients must be handled. ISO 27001 is the global benchmark for demonstrating your information security management
The post Vanta: Maintaining Security Standards with Christina Cacioppo appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Zalando Orchestrates its Sales Order Process with Camunda]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=23247</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/how-zalando-orchestrates-its-sales-order-process-with-camunda/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T08:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Europe's leading online fashion retailer serves 42 million active customers in 20 markets, leveraging Camunda for back-end logistics.
The post How Zalando Orchestrates its Sales Order Process with Camunda appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charley Mann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Your Own Amazon]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11193</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/04/build-your-own-amazon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=build-your-own-amazon"/>
        <updated>2021-07-04T11:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I worked as an engineer at Amazon, I would arrive at the office every day before 6:30am. Amazon’s enormous campus is in downtown Seattle. The company expands across the city like a massive, growing organism composed of towering buildings and ecospheres. The constant wet mist of Seattle always seems lighter within Amazon campus, perhaps
The post Build Your Own Amazon appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Text Blaze: Text Shortcuts with Scott Fortmann-Roe]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11177</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/03/text-blaze-text-shortcuts-with-scott-fortmann-roe/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=text-blaze-text-shortcuts-with-scott-fortmann-roe"/>
        <updated>2021-07-03T16:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are over 4 billion people using email. Many people using email for business communicate quick questions to colleagues, send repetitive, template-based information to potential customers and freshly hired employees, and repeat a lot of the same phrases. We actually repeat phrases in a lot of written formats. How often do you copy and paste
The post Text Blaze: Text Shortcuts with Scott Fortmann-Roe appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.02]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61927</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-07-02/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.07.02 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.07.02 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LayerCI with Colin Chartier]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11158</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/01/layerci-with-colin-chartier/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=layerci-with-colin-chartier"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T05:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous integration is a coding practice where engineers deliver incremental and frequent code changes to create higher quality software and collaborate more. Teams attempting to continuously integrate new code need a consistent and automated pipeline for reviewing, testing, and deploying the changes. Otherwise change requests pile up in the queue and nothing gets integrated efficiently. 
The post LayerCI with Colin Chartier appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transparent Proxy on Consul Service Mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/transparent-proxy-on-consul-service-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/transparent-proxy-on-consul-service-mesh"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.10 can transparently intercept and redirect traffic to sidecar proxies in the service mesh to allow applications to be deployed without modification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Boundary 0.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-boundary-0-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-boundary-0-4"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.4.0 and Boundary Desktop 1.2.0 includes features supporting brokering of HashiCorp Vault secrets for Boundary targets to end-users, enhanced session cleanup, and foundational features for event logging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault Achieves Red Hat OpenShift Helm Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-achieves-red-hat-openshift-helm-certification</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-achieves-red-hat-openshift-helm-certification"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Vault Helm chart has achieved Red Hat OpenShift Certification to help OpenShift users more readily deploy secrets management on Kubernetes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meltano: ELT for DataOps with Douwe Maan]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11176</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/30/meltano-elt-for-dataops-with-douwe-maan/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=meltano-elt-for-dataops-with-douwe-maan"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T02:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ELT is a process for copying data from a source system into a target system. It stands for “Extract, Load, Transform” and starts with extracting a copy of data from the source location. It’s loaded into the target system like a data warehouse, and then it’s ready to be transformed into a usable format for
The post Meltano: ELT for DataOps with Douwe Maan appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Day 2021 – Two Chart-Topping Days]]></title>
        <id>0989c2f1a859a1e69d4d900252cc47ca4e779558</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/dZ110navB2M/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T16:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In what has now become an annual tradition (check out my 2016, 2017, 2019, and 2020 posts for a look back), I am happy to share some of the metrics from this year’s Prime Day and to tell you how AWS helped to make it happen. This year I bought all sorts of useful goodies […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onboarding Applications to Vault Using Terraform: A Practical Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/onboarding-applications-to-vault-using-terraform-a-practical-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/onboarding-applications-to-vault-using-terraform-a-practical-guide"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build an automated HashiCorp Vault onboarding system with Terraform using sensible naming standards, ACL policy templates, pre-created application entities, and workflows driven by VCS and CI/CD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 45 – Observing @Azure with @DatadogHQ, with guest @ryan_maclean]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61881</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-45-observing-azure-with-datadoghq-with-guest-ryan_maclean/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T14:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 45 – Observing @Azure with @DatadogHQ, with guest @ryan_maclean appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic with Sean Li]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11159</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/29/magic-with-sean-li/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=magic-with-sean-li"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T09:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode we discuss plug and play auth, password management, and crypto with Sean Li, co-founder and CEO of Magic. This interview was also recorded as a video podcast. Check out the video on the Software Daily YouTube channel. Sponsorship inquiries: sponsor@softwareengineeringdaily.com
The post Magic with Sean Li appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planetary-Scale Computing – 9.95 PFLOPS & Position 40 on the TOP500 List]]></title>
        <id>c5a5694ebc6350153549c534be9a573abb574e54</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/NjovUW5A61A/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T20:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weather forecasting, genome sequencing, geoanalytics, computational fluid dynamics (CFD), and other types of high-performance computing (HPC) workloads can take advantage of massive amounts of compute power. These workloads are often spikey and massively parallel, and are used in situations where time to results is critical. Old Way Governments, well-funded research organizations, and Fortune 500 companies […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timescale: Time Series Databases with Mike Freedman]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11170</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/06/28/timescale-time-series-databases-with-mike-freedman/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=timescale-time-series-databases-with-mike-freedman"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T19:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some data problems, you may be more concerned with the state of data at a particular point. A ticket is booked, or it’s not. How many poetry submissions were made to the contest? This is relational data. For other problems, you’re concerned with the change in data over time. Solar energy consumption, for example,
The post Timescale: Time Series Databases with Mike Freedman appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>