<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-17T01:49:27.497Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-17T01:49:27.497Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to measure innersource across your organization]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-16-how-to-measure-innersource-across-your-organization/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-16-how-to-measure-innersource-across-your-organization/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T22:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The innersource contribution percentage is the rate of contributions from people outside the team that originally authored the software. Let’s dive into what it can look like for your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – May 16, 2022]]></title>
        <id>188f6fbb789cd4b216b2e97a6340bddf3499db79</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-16-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T19:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I had been on the road for the last five weeks and attended many of the AWS Summits in Europe. It was great to talk to so many of you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we’re using projects to build projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-16-how-were-using-projects-to-build-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-16-how-were-using-projects-to-build-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At GitHub we use GitHub to build our own products, and the new projects experience is no different. Check out how our team uses projects to build powerful project planning for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Achieves ISO/IEC 27001:2013 Certification!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-16-github-achieves-iso-iec-270012013-certification/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-16-github-achieves-iso-iec-270012013-certification/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub’s Information Security Management System (ISMS) has been certified against ISO 27001:2013, an internationally recognized standard for security program best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask me Anything Recap - April]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ask-me-anything-recap-april</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ask-me-anything-recap-april"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For this webinar, we had an awesome group of individuals with a diverse talent range across multiple skill sets from Product Management, Technical Marketing and Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newbies welcome]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42020</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696281996/0/sethsblog~Newbies-welcome/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T08:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The paradox of most tightly-knit communities is that they have an internal culture. And that culture often makes it difficult for a new person to join. It’s hard to have insiders if you don’t have outsiders. This is true for guilds of copy editors, fans of anime or branches of science. The key transition point […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity is a data challenge, and better search technology is key to improving visibility and action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/cybersecurity-is-a-data-challenge,-and-better-search-technology-is-key-to-improving-visibility-and-action</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/cybersecurity-is-a-data-challenge,-and-better-search-technology-is-key-to-improving-visibility-and-action"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T07:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From customer-facing search boxes to database search crawlers, enterprise search technology can strengthen cybersecurity threat and risk management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity is a data challenge, and better search technology is key to improving visibility and action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/cybersecurity-is-a-data-challenge,-and-better-search-technology-is-key-to-improving-visibility-and-action</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/cybersecurity-is-a-data-challenge,-and-better-search-technology-is-key-to-improving-visibility-and-action"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T07:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Data security is increasingly under threat inside the enterprise amid three converging forces: the proliferation of cloud tools and platforms; the many different types of data that they generate, and the need to correlate all of it for analytics.

While cloud platforms are the critical infrastructure for how technology teams scale and operate today, many companies still don’t have a clear or complete view of all their digital assets in this emerging environment. Advanced enterprise search capabilities, however, can eliminate blind spots and add an important layer of cybersecurity. 

“Today, enterprises need to be able to query their environment, and they need to be able to query their data,” says Katie Teitler, senior product marketer at Axonius, a cybersecurity asset management company,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-22976: BCrypt skips salt rounds for work factor of 31]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/15/cve-2022-22976-bcrypt-skips-salt-rounds-for-work-factor-of-31</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/15/cve-2022-22976-bcrypt-skips-salt-rounds-for-work-factor-of-31"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T05:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Severity



Medium - 5.3





Vendor



Spring by VMWare





Affected VMWare Products and Versions





Spring Security 5.5.x prior to 5.5.7



Spring Security 5.6.x prior to 5.6.4



Earlier unsupported versions







Description



Spring Security versions 5.5.x prior to 5.5.7, 5.6.x prior to 5.6.4, and earlier unsupported versions contain an integer overflow vulnerability. When using the BCrypt class with the maximum work factor (31), the encoder does not perform any salt rounds, due to an integer overflow error.



The default settings are not affected by this CVE.



Only in circumstances where the BCryptPasswordEncoder has been configured with the maximum work factor are affected. Due to current limitations in computer hardware, the use of such a high work factor is computationally impractical.



You need to be using BCrypt with a work factor of 31 to be impacted. You can check whether or not your passwords are impacted by using the following mitigation tool.





Mitigation



Prior to updating to the latest, please update your BCryptPasswordEncoder to use a lower number of rounds. At the time of this writing, OWASP recommends a value of 10.



Then, use the above-referenced mitigation tool to update your password hashes.



Once your password hashes are updated, you should update your version according to the following table:





5.5.x users should upgrade to 5.5.7



5.6.x users should upgrade to 5.6.4



Or users should upgrade to 5.7.0





After upgrading your Spring Security dependency, you should advise affected users to change their password.



A mitigation FAQ can also be found in the mitigation tool.





Credit



This issue was identified and responsibly reported by Eyal Kaspi.





References





Password Encoder documentation.







History



2021-04-10: Initial vulnerability report published.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2022-22975: Authorization Bypass in RegexRequestMatcher]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/15/cve-2022-22975-authorization-bypass-in-regexrequestmatcher</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/15/cve-2022-22975-authorization-bypass-in-regexrequestmatcher"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T05:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Severity



High





Vendor



Spring by VMware





Description



In Spring Security versions 5.5.6 and 5.5.7 and older unsupported versions, RegexRequestMatcher can easily be misconfigured to be bypassed on some servlet containers.



Applications using RegexRequestMatcher with . in the regular expression are possibly vulnerable to an authorization bypass.





Affected VMware Products and Versions



Applications using RegexRequestMatcher with a regular expression that contains . are likely vulnerable to an authorization bypass for versions:





Spring Security 5.5.x prior to 5.5.7



Spring Security 5.6.x prior to 5.6.4



Earlier unsupported versions







Mitigation



Users should update to a version that includes fixes. Releases that have fixed this issue include Spring Security:



5.5.x users should upgrade to 5.5.7 or greater
5.6.x users should upgrade to 5.6.4 or greater





Credit



This vulnerability was discovered and responsibly reported by:





Hiroki Nishino (LINE Corporation)



Toshiki Sasazaki (LINE Corporation)



Yoshinori Hayashi (LINE Corporation)



Jonghwan Kim (LINE Corporation)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Health Data]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2620/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2620/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/health_data.png" title="Donate now to help us find a cure for causality. No one should have to suffer through events because of other events." alt="Donate now to help us find a cure for causality. No one should have to suffer through events because of other events." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.0, 5.6.4, 5.5.7 Released - Fixes CVE-2022-22975 & CVE-2022-22976]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/15/spring-security-5-7-0-5-6-4-5-5-7-released-fixes-cve-2022-22975-cve-2022-22976</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/15/spring-security-5-7-0-5-6-4-5-5-7-released-fixes-cve-2022-22975-cve-2022-22976"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.0  (release notes), 5.6.4  (release notes), 5.5.7 (release notes) have been released which fix





CVE-2022-22975



CVE-2022-22976.





Please update as soon as possible.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone else is]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42013</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696132578/0/sethsblog~Everyone-else-is/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T08:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, not everyone. Just most people. When you do something that everyone else is doing, you’re likely to get what everyone else is getting. But in almost every population, “everyone” leaves out the people who go first, who change things, who are weird and who challenge the status quo. That’s an option, even when it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data, information and decisions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42924</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/695972622/0/sethsblog~Data-information-and-decisions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T08:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is everywhere, but turning it into information isn’t free. It takes focus, effort, consultation and time. More information is only useful if it helps you make a decision. Knowing the temperature on Saturn isn’t useful. Knowing it to even more accuracy is less useful. That’s because we’re not making any decisions that involve the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2022.1.1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=246027</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2022/05/2022-1-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With DataSpell 2022.1.1, we have worked hard to improve the overall DataSpell user experience. You can download the build from the website, update via the Toolbox App, apply a patch (go to DataSpell | Check for Updates), or use a snap package (for Ubuntu). For Jupyter notebooks, we concentrated on multiple issues involving the display […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1.1 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=245447</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/05/webstorm-2022-1-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1.1, the first bug-fix update for WebStorm 2022.1, is now available! It’s packed with fixes and improvements, including long-awaited support for Vite and a fix for the bug affecting the running and debugging of npm scripts. You can update to v2022.1.1 by using the Toolbox App, installing it right from the IDE, or downloading […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.1.1 is released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=245963</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/05/phpstorm-2022-1-1-is-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first minor update for PhpStorm 2022.1 is now available. You can update to it using the Toolbox App or right from inside the IDE. You can also download PhpStorm 2022.1.1 from the website. This release mainly brings a bunch of bug fixes and quality-of-life improvements. Let’s take a look! Improved blade formatting (WI-37087) The @case and @break […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.1.1 Is Out With Syntax Highlighting and Navigation for go.work, Generics-Related Inspections, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=245845</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/05/13/goland-2022-1-1-is-out-with-syntax-highlighting-and-navigation-for-go-work-generics-related-inspections-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T13:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GoLand 2022.1.1 update is out! You can download the build from the website, update via the Toolbox App, apply a patch (go to GoLand | Check for Updates), or use a snap package (for Ubuntu). In this update, we’ve added some new features for Go workspaces, generics, and more. Download Syntax highlighting and navigation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 13.05.2022]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64029</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-06-13-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T12:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back this week for another top stories from the #AzureDevOps #Community!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 13.05.2022 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.2 and 2022.0 M4 released.]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/13/spring-data-2021-2-and-2022-0-m4-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/13/spring-data-2021-2-and-2022-0-m4-released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the Data Team and everyone who contributed, I’m pleased to announce the GA release of the 2021.2 release train as well as the 4th Milestone of the 2022.0 one.

Already working on the 2022.0 train, based on Spring Framework 6, Java17 and Jakarta EE 9, the 2021.2 release ships bug fixes and selected back ported features.

Other than dependency upgrades, these are some of the major changes:


  
Infrastructure to introspect a projection type.

  
Common infrastructure for property-specific value converters.

  
Improved support for IdClass handling in data-jpa.

  
Declarative Update methods in data-mongodb.

  
Reindexing support in data-elasticsearch.

  
Direct projections for data-cassandra.

  
ACL support for Redis Sentinels.

  
Lock and Null precedence support …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five beats]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42921</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/695799348/0/sethsblog~Five-beats/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T08:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we’re close to an answer, there are two easy paths–name it, right now, and move on. Or avoid the answer and the responsibility that comes with it and stall. The best path is the third one. Wait for five beats. Kneejerk is not an admirable trait. A few breaths before we rip into someone. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the new PHP client for Elasticsearch 8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-the-new-php-client-for-elasticsearch-8</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-the-new-php-client-for-elasticsearch-8"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We released a new PHP client for Elasticsearch 8 using the PSR-7 and PSR-18 standards. This release offers a new pluggable architecture and a better developer experience, avoiding BC breaks at the same time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enrico Zimuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the new PHP client for Elasticsearch 8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-the-new-php-client-for-elasticsearch-8</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-the-new-php-client-for-elasticsearch-8"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The new PHP client for Elasticsearch 8 has been rewritten from scratch. Along with adopting the PSR standards, we’ve also redesigned the architecture and moved the HTTP transport layer outside. A pluggable system is also now available, thanks to the HTTPlug library.

Read on to explore:

The new architecture and features of the PHP client
How to consume the endpoints and manage errors using the PSR-7 standard for HTTP messages
How to interact with Elasticsearch using an asynchronous approach

The old client
The elasticsearch-php library is the official client for programming Elasticsearch with PHP. This library exposes all the 400+ endpoints of Elasticsearch using a main Client class. In version 7 of this library, all the endpoints are exposed using functions — for example, the index API…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enrico Zimuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crêpe]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2619/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2619/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/crepe.png" title="A medicine that makes you put two dots over your letters more often is a diäretic." alt="A medicine that makes you put two dots over your letters more often is a diäretic." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode Bug-Fix Update 2022.1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=245729</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/05/appcode-bug-fix-update-2022-1-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T23:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode 2022.1 was released just a few weeks ago and was focused on quality improvements and enhancements. Today we are publishing the AppCode 2022.1.1 bug-fix update. If you haven’t yet upgraded to the new v2022.1, now is a good time to do so! Build 221.5591.52 is available from our website, from the Toolbox App, or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion Bug-Fix Update 2022.1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=245727</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/05/clion-bug-fix-update-2022-1-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T23:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.1 was released in mid-April and was focused on quality improvements and enhancements for existing features and workflows. While the team has already started working on 2022.2, the scope for which we announced recently, there are still bug fixes and enhancements we want to deliver in v2022.1. That’s why today we are publishing the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenges in Multi-objective Optimization for Automatic Wireless Network Planning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/challenges-in-multi-objective.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/challenges-in-multi-objective.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Ahmadian and Matthew Fahrbach, Research Scientists, Google Research, Large-Scale Optimization Team 
Economics, combinatorics, physics, and signal processing conspire to make it difficult to design, build, and operate high-quality, cost-effective wireless networks. The radio transceivers that communicate with our mobile phones, the equipment that supports them (such as power and wired networking), and the physical space they occupy are all expensive, so it’s important to be judicious in choosing sites for new transceivers. Even when the set of available sites is limited, there are exponentially many possible networks that can be built. For example, given only 50 sites, there are 250 (over a million billion) possibilities!  
Further complicating things, for every location wher…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.0-M4 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/12/spring-framework-6-0-0-m4-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/12/spring-framework-6-0-0-m4-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.0-M4 is available now.

Spring Framework 6.0.0-M4 ships with all the fixes from 5.3.20 released yesterday, and also includes 39 fixes and improvements specific to the 6.0 branch.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.1.4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=245660</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/05/12/datagrip-2022-1-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new DataGrip 2022.1.4 bug-fix update is now available. DBE-15552: We’ve fixed a bug that was causing the names and icons of DDL data sources to be missing from the Database Explorer. Thanks! DataGrip team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2022.1.1 Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=245676</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/05/2022-1-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first minor update to PyCharm 2022.1 is here. You can update to this version from inside the IDE, using the Toolbox App, or using snaps if you are an Ubuntu user. You can also download it from our website. PEP 617: The syntax for Python 3.9’s parenthesized context managers is now fully supported. [PY-42200] […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qodana 2022.1 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=qodana&amp;p=244853</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/qodana/2022/05/qodana-2022-1-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are continuously adding new functionality and improving Qodana, our code quality platform. To keep you updated about what’s new, we’re starting a series of regular release blog posts with the major release of Qodana 2022.1. License audit has been an extra linter that had to be configured separately from the main linters. It now […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The post-industrial collision]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42000</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/695648564/0/sethsblog~The-postindustrial-collision/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many knowledge-economy employees say that the main cause of dissatisfaction at work is lack of agency. Lack of control over our time and our decisions and our output is demeaning. It turns people into cogs. As the nature of work changes, innovation and small groups are adding far more value than the race to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: EasyMock contributor, Java Champion, and Java luminary Henri Tremblay]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/12/a-bootiful-podcast-easymock-contributor-java-champion-and-java-luminary-henri-tremblay</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/12/a-bootiful-podcast-easymock-contributor-java-champion-and-java-luminary-henri-tremblay"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow Java Champion, EasyMock engineer, and Java luminary, JUG leader, and legend Henri Tremblay (@henri_tremblay)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing SPAs and Blazor Applications using the BFF Pattern – Recording]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=245598</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/05/12/securing-spas-and-blazor-applications-using-the-bff-pattern-recording/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T05:53:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recording for our webinar, Using the BFF pattern to secure SPA and Blazor Applications with Duende Software co-founder Dominick Baier, is now available. Subscribe to our community newsletter to receive notifications about future webinars. Modern web development means that more and more application code is running in the browser. Traditionally this has been JavaScript […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get visibility into AWS Lambda serverless functions with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of Elastic Observability’s new capabilities around monitoring AWS Lambda functions in your cloud-native environment. Get detailed insights into your distributed, microservices architecture and applications through our APM capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akhilesh Pokhariyal,Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make time for your mental health this May, here’s how]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-mental-health-awareness</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-mental-health-awareness"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the pandemic continues to evolve, mental health is very much in the spotlight. To support our Elasticians, we offer a variety of benefits related to mental health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get visibility into AWS Lambda serverless functions with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-apm-aws-lambda-serverless-functions"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Adoption of AWS Lambda functions in cloud-native applications has increased exponentially over the past few years. Serverless functions, such as the AWS Lambda service, provide a high level of abstraction from the underlying infrastructure and orchestration, given these tasks are managed by the cloud provider. Software development teams can then focus on the implementation of business and application logic. 
Some additional benefits include billing for serverless functions based on the actual compute and memory resources consumed, along with automatic on-demand scaling. One difficulty in using serverless functions, however, is making them observable in the wider end-to-end microservices architecture context. 
,Elastic APM for AWS Lambda: The architecture
In a previous blog post, we showe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akhilesh Pokhariyal,Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make time for your mental health this May, here’s how]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-mental-health-awareness</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-mental-health-awareness"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
May is Mental Health Awareness Month in the United States, and as we continue into the third year of the COVID-19 pandemic and start to see some aspects of life return to ‘normal’, our collective mental health deserves to be continually looked after. 
While the switch to primarily working from home wasn’t a huge departure from pre-pandemic life for our distributed team, other aspects of life moving into the home caused a huge shift for many—especially parents. With kids learning from home, parents working from home, and no option for outside help, the situation was ripe for anxiety, stress, and ultimately burnout. 
One study reports that 63% of moms, “feel like they’ve worked a full day after handling their family’s needs in the morning”, and 48% of those women feel like burnout is keepi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Tines partner to detect security threats and reduce mean time to respond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-tines-partner-to-detect-security-threats-and-reduce-mean-time-to-respond</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-tines-partner-to-detect-security-threats-and-reduce-mean-time-to-respond"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Tines are partnering to help our joint users detect security threats and reduce mean time to respond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Spiteri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Tines partner to detect security threats and reduce mean time to respond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-tines-partner-to-detect-security-threats-and-reduce-mean-time-to-respond</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-tines-partner-to-detect-security-threats-and-reduce-mean-time-to-respond"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today, we’re happy to announce that Elastic and Tines are partnering to help our joint users detect security threats and reduce mean time to respond. 

Many of the world’s best security teams rely on the power of Elastic’s high-speed, cloud-scale detection, prevention, and response capabilities to investigate and contain potential security threats within their environments. Many of these same teams trust Tines’ no-code automation platform to optimize their mission-critical workflows, respond to attacks at speed and scale, reduce toil on analysts, and remove the friction associated with integrations.

By combining Elastic and Tines, security teams are able to dramatically reduce dwell times, mean time to respond, and false-positive rates while also strengthening their agility and impact.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Spiteri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 Adds Native Service Discovery and Edge Workload Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 includes built-in service discovery, improved edge compute support, Container Storage Interface (CSI) general availability, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1.1 Is Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=245570</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/05/intellij-idea-2022-1-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T18:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released the first minor update for IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1.  You can update to this version from inside the IDE, using the Toolbox App, or using snaps if you are an Ubuntu user. You can also download it from our website. Here is the list of the most important fixes that you’ll find in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graduation is here! Celebrate the Class of 2022, and join GitHub on June 11 🎓]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-11-graduation-is-here-celebrate-the-class-of-2022-and-join-github-on-june-11/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-11-graduation-is-here-celebrate-the-class-of-2022-and-join-github-on-june-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, thousands of students from around the world came together and redefined the world we live in, how we learn, and how we move forward. We are honored to be part of the experience and eager to celebrate this milestone. So on June 11 we celebrate the Class of 2022 and welcome them to [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Language Models Perform Reasoning via Chain of Thought]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/language-models-perform-reasoning-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/language-models-perform-reasoning-via.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jason Wei and Denny Zhou, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain team 
In recent years, scaling up the size of language models has been shown to be a reliable way to improve performance on a range of natural language processing (NLP) tasks. Today’s language models at the scale of 100B or more parameters achieve strong performance on tasks like sentiment analysis and machine translation, even with little or no training examples. Even the largest language models, however, can still struggle with certain multi-step reasoning tasks, such as math word problems and commonsense reasoning. How might we enable language models to perform such reasoning tasks? 
In “Chain of Thought Prompting Elicits Reasoning in Large Language Models,” we explore a prompting method for improving the re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Zero-Resource Machine Translation to Support New Languages in Google Translate]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/24-new-languages-google-translate.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/24-new-languages-google-translate.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:07:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Isaac Caswell and Ankur Bapna, Research Scientists, Google Translate  
Machine translation (MT) technology has made significant advances in recent years, as deep learning has been integrated with natural language processing (NLP). Performance on research benchmarks like WMT have soared, and translation services have improved in quality and expanded to include new languages. Nevertheless, while existing translation services cover languages spoken by the majority of people world wide, they only include around 100 languages in total, just over 1% of those actively spoken globally. Moreover, the languages that are currently represented are overwhelmingly European, largely overlooking regions of high linguistic diversity, like Africa and the Americas. 
 There are two key bottlenecks t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 Now Supports NitroTPM and UEFI Secure Boot]]></title>
        <id>43dd6308bbff890b8b4acc020ae36428fe8fba36</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-now-supports-nitrotpm-and-uefi-secure-boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In computing, Trusted Platform Module (TPM) technology is designed to provide hardware-based, security-related functions. A TPM chip is a secure crypto-processor that is designed to carry out cryptographic operations. There are three key advantages of using TPM technology. First, you can generate, store, and control access to encryption keys outside of the operating system. Second, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Monthly &#8211; May 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-11-open-source-monthly-may-2022-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-11-open-source-monthly-may-2022-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Open Sauced, GitHub&#8217;s Explore page, Hacktoberfest, and First Timers Only help folks discover open source projects. This monthly series–Open Source Monthly—will add to these efforts by helping: First-time contributors find the right project to contribute to Corporations and individuals find a new project to sponsor Open source maintainers gain more consistent contributors and sponsors [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第209話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270296674344129439</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270296674344129439"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structure and Organize .NET Projects with Rider]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=241707</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/05/11/structure-and-organize-net-projects-with-rider/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T12:51:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’re starting out with a new project or refactoring a mature codebase, good folder and file organization makes your life less stressful. Having a good structure for your project creates an atmosphere that enables reading comprehension and fluid navigation. In this blog post, we’ll look at some ways to organize and streamline your .NET […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Cool Features of Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=53306</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/10-cool-features-of-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T12:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how these features support better IT and business collaboration, more efficient process execution, and instant troubleshooting. 
The post 10 Cool Features of Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe Is Back: Join Us in Amsterdam or Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years as a fully digital event, HashiConf Europe will once again return to Amsterdam on 20-22 June 2022. Here’s what you can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.20 and 5.2.22 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/11/spring-framework-5-3-20-and-5-2-22-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/11/spring-framework-5-3-20-and-5-2-22-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T08:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.20 and 5.2.22 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.20 includes 14 fixes and improvements.
Spring Framework 5.2.22 includes 2 backports.

In addition, these releases include fixes for 2 vulnerabilities:


  

  
CVE-2022-22970
 “Spring Framework DoS via Data Binding to MultipartFile or Servlet Part”
 Denial of Service (DoS) attack in Spring MVC or Spring WebFlux applications that handle file uploads and rely on data binding to set a MultipartFile or javax.servlet.Part to a field in a model object.
 Severity: Medium

  

  
CVE-2022-22971
 “Spring Framework DoS with STOMP over WebSocket”
 Denial of service (DoS) attack by authenticated users in Spring applications with a STOMP over WebSocket endpoint.
 Severity: Medium


These new versions are recommended upgrades for all Spring production scenarios.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“…somebody else will.”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41984</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/695479513/0/sethsblog~somebody-else-will/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a great excuse for racing to the bottom. Corporations with power go ahead and take advantage of customers. “Well, if we don’t do it, a competitor will.” The public markets don’t require companies to throw out their principles to succeed. In fact, they reward companies that do the opposite. People exploit vulnerabilities in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Living-off-the-land attacks with new Elastic Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-living-off-the-land-attacks-with-new-elastic-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-living-off-the-land-attacks-with-new-elastic-integration"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an earlier blog post, we talked about how to use the detection rules repository command line interface (CLI), set up up the ProblemChild framework and get it up and running in your environment. We have now added a Living off the land (LotL) detection package to the Integrations app in Kibana. In a single click, you can install and start using the ProblemChild model and associated assets including anomaly detection configurations and detection rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Alvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leadership @ Elastic | Carolyn Herzog on why company culture matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-leadership-at-elastic-carolyn-herzog-on-why-company-culture-matters</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-leadership-at-elastic-carolyn-herzog-on-why-company-culture-matters"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our Leadership @ Elastic blog series, we hear from our Chief Legal Officer, Carolyn Herzog, on the importance of an inclusive culture and diversity of thought and how Elastic brings it to life everyday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Expands Strategic Partnership with Microsoft to Benefit Customers in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-expands-strategic-partnership-with-microsoft-to-benefit-customers-in-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-expands-strategic-partnership-with-microsoft-to-benefit-customers-in-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic expanded its strategic partnership with Microsoft to help you accelerate results and reduce operational costs with native integrations, consolidated account management in Azure Marketplace, and deployment of Elastic Cloud in 16 Azure regions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurent Mechain,Adrienne Cohen,Dusty Jackson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Living-off-the-land attacks with new Elastic Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-living-off-the-land-attacks-with-new-elastic-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-living-off-the-land-attacks-with-new-elastic-integration"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
It is becoming more common that adversary attacks consist of more than a standalone executable or script. Advanced attacker techniques, like “living off the land” (LotL) that appear normal in isolation become more suspicious when observed in a parent-child context. If you are running Windows in your environment, it is important to have a system for detecting these types of attacks.  Traditional heuristic-based detections, though effective in detecting a single event, often fail to generalize across a multi-step attack.  At Elastic we have trained a Living off the Land classifier, anomaly detection jobs and security detection rules to help our security professionals discover LotL attacks.

With the advent of Integration packages in the Elastic stack we can now deliver the full, customizab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Alvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leadership @ Elastic | Carolyn Herzog on why company culture matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-leadership-at-elastic-carolyn-herzog-on-why-company-culture-matters</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-leadership-at-elastic-carolyn-herzog-on-why-company-culture-matters"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Welcome Chief Legal Officer Carolyn Herzog
Elastic’s new Chief Legal Officer, Carolyn Herzog, values organizations that don’t just talk about company culture and diversity of thought, but live it every day. It’s one of the many reasons she joined the Elastic team. Carolyn believes in doing well and doing good and is an advocate for “technology for good”. This is evidenced in her various writings and public presentations, both discussing the human experience in companies and the purpose that the company provides in the communities that it serves.   

“I feel like Elastic is a very special place,” said Carolyn. “I’ve had a great career and worked with wonderful people; I wanted to join a company that treats their employees with dignity and respect and authentically recognizes that includin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Expands Strategic Partnership with Microsoft to Benefit Customers in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-expands-strategic-partnership-with-microsoft-to-benefit-customers-in-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-expands-strategic-partnership-with-microsoft-to-benefit-customers-in-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re pleased to share exciting news regarding a new multi-year partnership agreement between Elastic and Microsoft. Today’s announcement builds on our history of collaboration and will help you more easily search, observe and protect your applications, data, and infrastructure with Elastic Cloud on Azure. Our joint investments make it easier than ever for you to accelerate the results that matter.
,Deploy and manage Elastic Cloud on Azure
Our partnership is focused on helping you get more out of both your data and your infrastructure. Elastic and Azure put the data you need to fuel your business at your fingertips, making it easy to find what you are looking for quickly and adapt to achieve your business objectives.

By combining the power of search and a future-ready cloud, it’s easier…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurent Mechain,Adrienne Cohen,Dusty Jackson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Selection Bias]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2618/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2618/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/selection_bias.png" title="We carefully sampled the general population and found that most people are familiar with acquiescence bias." alt="We carefully sampled the general population and found that most people are familiar with acquiescence bias." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced 2FA experience for your npm account]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-10-enhanced-2fa-experience-for-your-npm-account/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-10-enhanced-2fa-experience-for-your-npm-account/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T16:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Late last year, in response to an unprecedented series of account takeovers resulting from the compromise of developer accounts without 2FA enabled, we committed to a variety of enhancements to the npm registry to make two-factor authentication (2FA) adoption easier for developers. Today, we are launching a public beta for a significantly improved 2FA experience [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a brand new way to automate your Azure cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-a-brand-new-way-to-automate-your-azure-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-a-brand-new-way-to-automate-your-azure-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T13:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December of 2021, Red Hat and Microsoft announced Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hicham Mourad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 10th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/10/this-week-in-spring-may-10th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/10/this-week-in-spring-may-10th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! I’m writing this from - I can’t believe I get to say this - abroad! I’m in London, UK! Now, this is not particularly noteworthy for those millions who already live here. But I don’t live here. I’m a visitor! I live in San Francisco. I had to fly here! On a plane! With other people! ACROSS THE OCEAN. This is my first international flight since March of 2020, and I couldn’t be more excited to be here for Devoxx UK and also just to catch up with old friends I haven’t seen in nearly three years. If you know me, and how I used to travel, you’ll appreciate how odd it is for me to be this excited to have crossed a border. It’s been sooo long! I’ve missed the process. I’ve missed seeing people. I’ve missed all of it. 

One thing I haven’t missed is a lot of this week’s new and noteworthy, which I recap in this week’s This Week in Spring roundup. Let’s goooo! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Java Champion and Spring Katas legend Chandra Guntur

  
Apr 28 - What’s New in Spring Cloud Gateway Commercial?

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.24: Volume Expansion Now A Stable Feature

  
Blog: Storage Capacity Tracking reaches GA in Kubernetes 1.24

  
Build a Goodreads Clone with Spring Boot and Astra DB — Part 1

  
How to enable mutual TLS in a Spring Boot Application | by Salar Ahmadi | Mar, 2022 | Medium

  
Schedule a task in Spring Boot. Spring Boot is the most popular… | by Aleksandar Grujic | Mar, 2022 | Medium

  
RSocket Broker HTTP Bridge 0.3.0 has been released. Check out this SpringOne presentation and an updated sample

  
they updated the tutorial showing how to create your first application in IntellIJ IDEA  and it’s even nicer!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[But where are the secret recipes?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42890</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/695331500/0/sethsblog~But-where-are-the-secret-recipes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, I’ve been sharing recipes as pages here on the blog, but never posting about them… you only got the link if I sent it to you. Well, your wait is over. For those seeking non-obvious but delicious and light-on-their-feet recipes, here you go:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=53158</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1. Check out the latest improvements and bug fixes with this release.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52734</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-automation-platform-7-18-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're pleased to announce the first alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0. Learn about the improvements made in this release. 
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How top global CISOs protect their organizations amid rising threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-top-global-cisos-protect-their-organizations-amid-rising-threats</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-top-global-cisos-protect-their-organizations-amid-rising-threats"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research highlights where organizations need to accelerate process and technology changes to improve the effectiveness of cybersecurity strategies — or risk falling behind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajiv Raghunarayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How top global CISOs protect their organizations amid rising threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-top-global-cisos-protect-their-organizations-amid-rising-threats</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-top-global-cisos-protect-their-organizations-amid-rising-threats"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
New data shows a leading group of cybersecurity executives are investing in an emerging set of capabilities — think, next-generation security information and event management (SIEM), endpoint detection and response (EDR), and extended detection and response (XDR) — and have practices in place that are far ahead of most organizations’, highlighting a growing resilience gap.  
The study co-sponsored by Elastic, “Cybersecurity Solutions for a Riskier World,” reveals how 1,200 organizations across 16 countries and 14 industries, with a combined cybersecurity spend of $125.2 billion, are investing in their defenses in response to the mounting threat landscape. It is an urgent call to action by research firm ThoughtLab, who identified a small set of leading organizations. However, the majority…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajiv Raghunarayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the HashiCorp Releases API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hashicorp-releases-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hashicorp-releases-api"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Releases API is now available. This API is your one-stop shop for finding and viewing extended metadata about HashiCorp product releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – May 9, 2022]]></title>
        <id>8339454c5a5172e1abc7a324ae07df48c5db2a14</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-9-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Another week starts, and here’s a collection of the most significant AWS news from the previous seven days. This week is also the one-year anniversary of CloudFront Functions. It’s exciting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supercharging GitHub Actions with Job Summaries]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-09-supercharging-github-actions-with-job-summaries/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-09-supercharging-github-actions-with-job-summaries/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now output and group custom Markdown content on the Actions run summary page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Applications at the Edge with HashiCorp Nomad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-applications-at-the-edge-with-hashicorp-nomad</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-applications-at-the-edge-with-hashicorp-nomad"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Nomad users in the gaming, farming, and biotech industries are orchestrating applications and devices at the edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting You Around the Globe]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52992</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/supporting-you-around-the-globe/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We now offer follow-the-sun support. Pick your preferred time zone and get expert help to resolve any issue.
The post Supporting You Around the Globe appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for next semester with GitHub Global Campus and Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-09-prepare-for-next-semester-with-github-global-campus-and-codespaces/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-09-prepare-for-next-semester-with-github-global-campus-and-codespaces/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teachers, it is now your turn to join GitHub Global Campus with our student community! Get access to exclusive benefits, programs, and the Power of Codespaces at no cost in GitHub Classroom!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous Detection and Mitigation (CDM)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/continuous-detection-and-mitigation-cdm</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/continuous-detection-and-mitigation-cdm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>achenamp@redhat.com (Ajay Chenampara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ones who didn’t help]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42870</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/695152748/0/sethsblog~The-ones-who-didnt-help/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If 2% of a population takes coordinated action, it makes a difference. If 5% do, it can change everything. This simple math also means that most people rarely do anything. Perhaps they don’t care. Perhaps they’re afraid to speak up and commit. And perhaps it’s simply easier to go along for a free ride. Of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticians honored for outstanding achievement in cloud-partner marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticians-honored-for-outstanding-achievement-in-cloud-partner-marketing</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticians-honored-for-outstanding-achievement-in-cloud-partner-marketing"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A with Adrienne Cohen and Isabelle Li, who were just named to 2022 CRN Women of the Channel list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trish Sammer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticians honored for outstanding achievement in cloud-partner marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticians-honored-for-outstanding-achievement-in-cloud-partner-marketing</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticians-honored-for-outstanding-achievement-in-cloud-partner-marketing"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Adrienne Cohen and Isabelle Li lead cloud-partner marketing efforts for Microsoft and Google

We’re so proud that two Elasticians have been named to the 2022 CRN Women of the Channel list. Adrienne Cohen and Isabelle Li are both Director of Partner Marketing at Elastic, leading efforts with Microsoft and Google, respectively.

We spoke with Adrienne and Isabelle to get their insights on why building productive channel relationships with cloud partners is so important for our customers. 
Making things as easy as possible for the customer

How does Elastic’s focus on cloud partners benefit customers? Do you have some examples that are particularly meaningful to you?

Adrienne: Giving customers quick and easy access to Elastic Cloud on Microsoft’s Azure Marketplace has been so cool and rewa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trish Sammer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maps]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2617/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2617/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/maps.png" title="OpenStreetMap was always pretty good but is also now *really* good? And Apple Maps's new zoomed-in design in certain cities like NYC and London is just gorgeous. It's cool how there are all these good maps now!" alt="OpenStreetMap was always pretty good but is also now *really* good? And Apple Maps's new zoomed-in design in certain cities like NYC and London is just gorgeous. It's cool how there are all these good maps now!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resilient markets]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42859</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/694949232/0/sethsblog~Resilient-markets/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T08:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “free market” is a bit of a myth. Other than some board games, it doesn’t exist in real life. We eagerly regulate things like dangerous goods, fraud, insider trading, the warranty of merchantability, trademarks, dumping poison in the water supply, selling heroin to kids, etc. All of these boundaries are designed to create more […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defining the enemy]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=39809</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/694726016/0/sethsblog~Defining-the-enemy/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-07T08:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some situations seem to call for an opponent. It might be our personality, the structure of the engagement or the way we’ve been taught to behave, but having an enemy seems to focus individuals and groups. For fifty years, America decided that the USSR was the enemy, and spent a great deal of time and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Observability with OpenTelemetry and Consul Service Mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/improve-observability-with-opentelemetry-and-consul-service-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/improve-observability-with-opentelemetry-and-consul-service-mesh"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Add OpenTelemetry to your Java or .NET applications on Kubernetes and combine them with Consul service mesh metrics and traces for use with Prometheus and Jaeger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s most common security vulnerabilities explained]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-06-todays-most-common-security-vulnerabilities-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-06-todays-most-common-security-vulnerabilities-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're taking a look at some of the most common security vulnerabilities and detailing how developers can best protect themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.06.05]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63983</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-06-05/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.06.05 are here!
I am April Edwards and every week I try to bring you the latest updates from around the DevOps on Azure community.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.06.05 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 Highlights from  #CamundaSummit]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52738</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-platform-8-highlights-from-camundasummit/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 only just arrived, and there’s already a lot of excitement around this new release. Early adopters share their highlights.
The post Camunda Platform 8 Highlights from  #CamundaSummit appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dorothy Tso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Java Champion and Spring Katas legend Chandra Guntur]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/05/a-bootiful-podcast-java-champion-and-spring-katas-legend-chandra-guntur</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/05/a-bootiful-podcast-java-champion-and-spring-katas-legend-chandra-guntur"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow Java Champion and Java ecosystem luminary Chandra Guntur (@cguntur) about Java, Spring, and the Spring Katas, among other things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 of our favorite games + source code from Ludum Dare 50]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-05-ludum-dare-50/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-05-ludum-dare-50/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T20:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[20 of our favorite games plus source code from the latest Ludum Dare competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Locomotion Skills Safely in the Real World]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/learning-locomotion-skills-safely-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/learning-locomotion-skills-safely-in.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:05:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jimmy (Tsung-Yen) Yang, Student Researcher, Robotics at Google 
The promise of deep reinforcement learning (RL) in solving complex, high-dimensional problems autonomously has attracted much interest in areas such as robotics, game playing, and self-driving cars. However, effectively training an RL policy requires exploring a large set of robot states and actions, including many that are not safe for the robot. This is a considerable risk, for example, when training a legged robot. Because such robots are inherently unstable, there is a high likelihood of the robot falling during learning, which could cause damage. 
The risk of damage can be mitigated to some extent by learning the control policy in computer simulation and then deploying it in the real world. However, this approac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable Self-Service AWS EKS Deployments with CDK for Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/enable-self-service-aws-eks-deployments-with-cdk-for-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/enable-self-service-aws-eks-deployments-with-cdk-for-terraform"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how platform and developer teams can collaborate effectively using CDK for Terraform, Terraform Cloud, and Sentinel to safely deploy EKS workloads to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphWorld: Advances in Graph Benchmarking]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/graphworld-advances-in-graph.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/graphworld-advances-in-graph.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T21:24:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Palowitch and Anton Tsitsulin, Research Scientists, Google Research, Graph Mining team 
Graphs are very common representations of natural systems that have connected relational components, such as social networks, traffic infrastructure, molecules, and the internet. Graph neural networks (GNNs) are powerful machine learning (ML) models for graphs that leverage their inherent connections to incorporate context into predictions about items within the graph or the graph as a whole. GNNs have been effectively used to discover new drugs, help mathematicians prove theorems, detect misinformation, and improve the accuracy of arrival time predictions in Google Maps. 
A surge of interest in GNNs during the last decade has produced thousands of GNN variants, with hundreds introduced each year. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Run Tasks are Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-are-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-are-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate security, compliance, and cost management into the Terraform Cloud workflow using Run Tasks. Now generally available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Camunda Platform 8’s GraphQL API]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52506</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/getting-started-with-camunda-platform-8s-graphql-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting familiar with Camunda Platform 8? Learn why GraphQL is replacing REST API as the interface technology and how it works.
The post Getting Started with Camunda Platform 8’s GraphQL API appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpa: Automated Model-Parallel Deep Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/alpa-automated-model-parallel-deep.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/alpa-automated-model-parallel-deep.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T21:30:00.058Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zhuohan Li, Student Researcher, Google Research, and Yu Emma Wang, Senior Software Engineer, Google Core  
  Update — 2022/05/06: This post has been updated to provide additional details about the collaboration with external research partners in the development of Alpa.     
  
Over the last several years, the rapidly growing size of deep learning models has quickly exceeded the memory capacity of single accelerators. Earlier models like BERT (with a parameter size of < 1GB) can efficiently scale across accelerators by leveraging data parallelism in which model weights are duplicated across accelerators while only partitioning and distributing the training data. However, recent large models like GPT-3 (with a parameter size of 175GB) can only scale using model parallel training, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 3rd, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/03/this-week-in-spring-may-3rd-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/03/this-week-in-spring-may-3rd-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you doin’? 

I’m excited! This week I’m speaking at the ArabJUG, and I’ll be speaking at Microsoft’s huuuge JDConf event. Both of these are virtual. Then, next Monday, I’m on a plane bound for London, UK, where I’ll be speaking at Devoxx UK 2022. Then, not even two weeks later, I’ll be speaking at Spring IO, in Barcelona, Spain! Then a week later, I’ll be speaking at JNation, in Lisbon, Portugal. To say that I am excited would be an understatement, my friends. 

And all of that ignores the great stuff since last week. Let’s dive right into it! 


  
Last week I talked to fellow Java Champion, Sun veteran, and industry legend Simon Ritter on A Bootiful Podcast: Simon Ritter, Java Champion, and deputy CTO at …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Applications and Servers at the Edge with Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-applications-and-servers-at-the-edge-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-applications-and-servers-at-the-edge-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous blog, Why 2022 will be the year for edge automation, we discussed the objective of edge solutions to bring resources closer to the end user or data source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wanted to rewrite a query in Spring Data JPA?]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/02/ever-wanted-to-rewrite-a-query-in-spring-data-jpa</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/02/ever-wanted-to-rewrite-a-query-in-spring-data-jpa"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T00:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, no matter how many features you try to apply, it seems impossible to get Spring Data JPA to apply every thing
you’d like to a query before it is sent to the EntityManager.



With 3.0.0-SNAPSHOT (and targeted for the next milestone release train of Spring Data), you now have the ability to get your hands on the query, right before it’s sent to the EntityManager and "rewrite" it. That is, you can make any alterations at the last moment.



Check it out below:



Example 1. Declare a QueryRewriter using @Query




public interface MyRepository extends JpaRepository<User, Long> {

    @Query(value = "select original_user_alias.* from SD_USER original_user_alias",
                    nativeQuery = true, queryRewriter = MyQueryRewriter.class) // (1)
    List<User> f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – May 2, 2022]]></title>
        <id>650b6b46711677bb46ba175a4d35a12387ae3f6a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-2-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Wow, May already! Here in the Pacific Northwest, spring is in full bloom and nature has emerged completely from her winter slumbers. It feels that way here at AWS, too, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Benchmark Your Camunda Platform 8 Cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52174</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/how-to-benchmark-your-camunda-platform-8-cluster/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about our interesting journey with benchmarking and how to run a benchmark to figure out what your Zeebe cluster can do.
The post How to Benchmark Your Camunda Platform 8 Cluster appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extracting Skill-Centric State Abstractions from Value Functions]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/extracting-skill-centric-state.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/extracting-skill-centric-state.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T17:02:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dhruv Shah, Intern, and Brian Ichter, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google 
Advances in reinforcement learning (RL) for robotics have enabled robotic agents to perform increasingly complex tasks in challenging environments. Recent results show that robots can learn to fold clothes, dexterously manipulate a rubik’s cube, sort objects by color, navigate complex environments and walk on difficult, uneven terrain. But "short-horizon" tasks such as these, which require very little long-term planning and provide immediate failure feedback, are relatively easy to train compared to many tasks that may confront a robot in a real-world setting. Unfortunately, scaling such short-horizon skills to the abstract, long horizons of real-world tasks is difficult. For example, how would one trai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Simon Ritter, Java Champion and deputy CTO at Azul]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/28/a-bootiful-podcast-simon-ritter-java-champion-and-deputy-cto-at-azul</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/28/a-bootiful-podcast-simon-ritter-java-champion-and-deputy-cto-at-azul"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Azul Deputy CTO and Java’s own mad scientist and luminary Simon Ritter (@speakjava)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon MSK Serverless Now Generally Available–No More Capacity Planning for Your Managed Kafka Clusters]]></title>
        <id>305f11c2d5084adabac03bcf0422320fe63911fe</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-msk-serverless-now-generally-available-no-more-capacity-planning-for-your-managed-kafka-clusters/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T18:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are making Amazon MSK Serverless generally available to help you reduce even more the operational overhead of managing an Apache Kafka cluster by offloading the capacity planning and scaling to AWS. In May 2019, we launched Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka to help our customers stream data using Apache Kafka. Apache Kafka […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Storage-Optimized Amazon EC2 Instances (I4i) Powered by Intel Xeon Scalable (Ice Lake) Processors]]></title>
        <id>6d11b906558df90e167a43676ae4febc00ab2a71</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-storage-optimized-amazon-ec2-instances-i4i-powered-by-intel-xeon-scalable-ice-lake-processors/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years we have released multiple generations of storage-optimized Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances including the HS1 (2012) , D2 (2015), I2 (2013) , I3 (2017), I3en (2019), D3/D3en (2020), and Im4gn/Is4gen (2021). These instances are used to host high-performance real-time relational databases, distributed file systems, data warehouses, key-value stores, and more. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.2 Brings New Cross-Namespace Controls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-2-brings-new-cross-namespace-controls</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-2-brings-new-cross-namespace-controls"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.2, now generally available, enhances the gateway’s traffic management capabilities by adding cross-namespace reference policy enforcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2022 HashiCorp SI & Reseller Partner Network Award Winners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2022-hashicorp-si-reseller-partner-network-award-winners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2022-hashicorp-si-reseller-partner-network-award-winners"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 HashiCorp Partner Network Awards for Systems Integrators and Resellers have been announced. Find out who the winners are in our five categories this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第208話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496898209741</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496898209741"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Conversations: Uwe Koch, HDI Insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51911</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/community-conversations-uwe-koch-hdi-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the first installment of our Community Conversations blog series with Uwe Koch, a Camunda Champion and enterprise architect.
The post Community Conversations: Uwe Koch, HDI Insurance appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 26th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/this-week-in-spring-april-26th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/this-week-in-spring-april-26th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! This week I was hoping to be in glorious Chicago, Illinois for the first in-person SpringOne Tour installment since the pandemic. But, alas, I couldn’t go because - out of an abundance of caution, and since I was exposed to COVID19 in Atlanta, GA - it was thought to be safer to keep some folks home and virtual. Sigh. This policy makes perfect sense and it’s what I wanted. But it’s still a smidge disappointing to not be there. I miss y’all! It was fun at least doing a remote presentation. 

Anyway, without further ado, let’s get into today’s roundup! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud legend Glenn Renfro about batch processing, tasks, stream processing, data flow, and t-shirts

  
Add Prefix to All Spring Boot Controllers

  
CVE report published for Spring Security OAuth

  
JobRunr 5.0 is out now and it supports Spring Native!

  
GraalVM 22.1: Developer experience improvements, Apple Silicon builds, and more

  
I love Spring GraphQL, but its not the only option out there. GraphQL Using Netflix’s DGS Framework & Spring-Boot (Schema-First Approach)

  
Kafka With Java, Spring, and Docker — Asynchronous Communication Between Microservices

  
Mayunk Jain on Twitter

  
Serverless with Spring. 1. Introduction:  In this article, we… | by Apurv Sheth | Mar, 2022 | Medium

  
Spring Boot 2.5.13 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.6.7 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.7.0-RC1 is now available

  
Spring Boot Tutorial - Nice & Easy

  
Spring Session 2021.2.0-RC1, 2021.1.3 and 2021.0.6 released

  
Spring Tools 4.14.1 released

  
Spring for GraphQL 1.0 RC1 Released]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.2 Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/spring-cloud-2021-0-2-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/spring-cloud-2021-0-2-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T22:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Service Release 2 of the Spring Cloud 2021.0 Release Train is available today. This was primarily a bug fix release. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2021.0.2 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0.2 Release Train

See the project page for all issues included in the release.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Pass request data context in blocking LoadBalancer client (1090)

  
Support custom HTTP status code in LoadBalancer lifecycle (1066)

  
Support URI without port for default ServiceInstance ([1054]https://github.com/spring-cloud/spring-cloud-commons/pull/1054))

  
Improved calculating Round Robin LoadBalancer position ([1078]https://github.com/spring-cloud/spring-clo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolution of ML Fact Store]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5941d3231762</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/evolution-of-ml-fact-store-5941d3231762?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T20:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Vivek Kaushal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.14.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/spring-tools-4-14-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/26/spring-tools-4-14-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.14.1 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: use startupSnapshot instead of startup timer call to avoid wiping out the underlying data

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: When vscode opens a Java project for about 2 hours, the suggestion function will fail (#750)

  
(VSCode) enhancement: live hovers are now automatically show up when you launch a Spring Boot application in VSCode. Additional JVM args for the Spring Boot app to enable JMX are added to the launch automatically. More details can be found in the user guide section about Live Application Information.

  
(VSCode) enhancement: add extension APIs to get live data (#751) - contributed by @Eskibear


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog/#2022-04-27-4141-release-incl-language-servers-version-1330

Spring Tools 4.15.0 is scheduled to be released in mid June 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Wavelength Zone in Toronto – The First in Canada]]></title>
        <id>0536fdf5007395f77dfe25feb6e76bd15622ea6a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-wavelength-zone-in-toronto-the-first-in-canada/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T15:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless communication has put us closer to each other. 5G networks increase the reach of what we can achieve to new use cases that need end-to-end low latency. With AWS Wavelength, you can deploy AWS compute and storage services within telecommunications providers’ data centers at the edge of the 5G networks. Your applications can then […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ICLR 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/google-at-iclr-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/google-at-iclr-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T19:46:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cat Armato and Callan Hajosy, Program Managers 
The 10th International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR 2022) kicks off this week, bringing together researchers, entrepreneurs, engineers and students alike to discuss and explore the rapidly advancing field of deep learning. Entirely virtual this year, ICLR 2022 offers conference and workshop tracks that present some of the latest research in deep learning and its applications to areas ranging from computer vision, speech recognition and text understanding to robotics, computational biology, and more. 
 As a Platinum Sponsor of ICLR 2022 and Champion DEI Action Fund contributor, Google will have a robust presence with nearly 100 accepted publications and extensive participation on organizing committees and in workshops…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 25, 2022]]></title>
        <id>0fb329a009aafc65690dcbba4bb516553ed47289</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-25-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! The first in this year’s series of AWS Summits took place in San Francisco this past week and we had a bunch of great announcements. Let’s take a closer look… […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Tips for Making the Most of Camunda Community Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51741</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/4-tips-for-making-the-most-of-camunda-community-summit/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Community Summit 2022 features our most varied and engaging agenda to date. Follow these tips to take full advantage of your experience.
The post 4 Tips for Making the Most of Camunda Community Summit appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Thengvall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Cloud Search to Streamline Workspace Search and Switching]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-cloud-search-to-streamline-workspace-search-and-switching</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-cloud-search-to-streamline-workspace-search-and-switching"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new search capability available for all tiers in Terraform Cloud will allow you to easily switch between workspaces and organizations in the UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-driven remediation with systemd and Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-remediation-with-systemd-and-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-remediation-with-systemd-and-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform can assist you here with not only keeping your infrastructure in check, but also giving your teams the peace of mind that systems are running as they should.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.22.04]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63912</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-22-04/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T02:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back this week for another top stories from the #AzureDevOps #Community!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.22.04 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pix2Seq: A New Language Interface for Object Detection]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pix2seq-new-language-interface-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pix2seq-new-language-interface-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T20:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ting Chen and David Fleet, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Object detection is a long-standing computer vision task that attempts to recognize and localize all objects of interest in an image. The complexity arises when trying to identify or localize all object instances while also avoiding duplication. Existing approaches, like Faster R-CNN and DETR, are carefully designed and highly customized in the choice of architecture and loss function. This specialization of existing systems has created two major barriers: (1) it adds complexity in tuning and training the different parts of the system (e.g., region proposal network, graph matching with GIOU loss, etc.), and (2), it can reduce the ability of a model to generalize, necessitating a redesign of the model for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss Re’s Journey Toward a Cloud-Native Orchestration Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51662</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/swiss-res-journey-toward-a-cloud-native-orchestration-solution/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ready for a digital transformation? Learn why Swiss Re selected Camunda Platform 8 as its cloud-native process orchestration solution.
The post Swiss Re’s Journey Toward a Cloud-Native Orchestration Solution appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.12 Hardens Security on Kubernetes with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-12-hardens-security-on-kubernetes-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-12-hardens-security-on-kubernetes-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This release strengthens zero trust security architecture by leveraging HashiCorp Vault to reduce secrets sprawl and automate server TLS certificate rotation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Cloud legend Glenn Renfro about batch processing, tasks, stream processing, data flow, and t-shirts]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-legend-glenn-renfro-about-batch-processing-tasks-stream-processing-data-flow-and-t-shirts</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-cloud-legend-glenn-renfro-about-batch-processing-tasks-stream-processing-data-flow-and-t-shirts"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of A Bootiful Podcast! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring Cloud luminary and all around lovable guy Glenn Renfro (@cppwfs) about batch processing, tasks, messaging, integration, data flow, and a million other things. Also: t-shirts!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0-RC1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-7-0-rc1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-7-0-rc1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T22:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0-RC1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes more than a 100 bug fixes, enhancements, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Auto-configuration for Kafka Retry Topics

  
Auto-configuration for RSocket support in GraphQL


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden Interfaces for Ambient Computing]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/hidden-interfaces-for-ambient-computing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/hidden-interfaces-for-ambient-computing.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T19:59:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alex Olwal, Research Scientist, Google Augmented Reality and Artem Dementyev, Hardware Engineer, Google Research 
As consumer electronics and internet-connected appliances are becoming more common, homes are beginning to embrace various types of connected devices that offer functionality like music control, voice assistance, and home automation. A graceful integration of devices requires adaptation to existing aesthetics and user styles rather than simply adding screens, which can easily disrupt a visual space, especially when they become monolithic surfaces or black screens when powered down or not actively used. Thus there is an increasing desire to create connected ambient computing devices and appliances that can preserve the aesthetics of everyday materials, while providing …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Serverless Inference – Machine Learning Inference without Worrying about Servers]]></title>
        <id>3f2dde001172ce44e72138f038da17f0191c2c33</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-serverless-inference-machine-learning-inference-without-worrying-about-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T17:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December 2021, we introduced Amazon SageMaker Serverless Inference (in preview) as a new option in Amazon SageMaker to deploy machine learning (ML) models for inference without having to configure or manage the underlying infrastructure. Today, I’m happy to announce that Amazon SageMaker Serverless Inference is now generally available (GA). Different ML inference use cases […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Aurora Serverless v2 is Generally Available: Instant Scaling for Demanding Workloads]]></title>
        <id>94931a6d5038a338992ac375a270cfd3a1a2c213</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-aurora-serverless-v2-is-generally-available-instant-scaling-for-demanding-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are very excited to announce that Amazon Aurora Serverless v2 is generally available for both Aurora PostgreSQL and MySQL. Aurora Serverless is an on-demand, auto-scaling configuration for Amazon Aurora that allows your database to scale capacity up or down based on your application’s needs. Amazon Aurora is a MySQL- and PostgreSQL-compatible relational database […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the General Availability of AWS Amplify Studio]]></title>
        <id>a646396f947ba813c8558c3ba67d16b8e63ee6bd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-general-availability-of-aws-amplify-studio/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amplify Studio is a visual interface that simplifies front- and backend development for web and mobile applications. We released it as a preview during AWS re:Invent 2021, and today, I’m happy to announce that it is now generally available (GA). A key feature of Amplify Studio is integration with Figma, helping designers and front-end developers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IoT TwinMaker Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>0bc74371fc1afc6c01a04e5c726c01a6a266613e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-iot-twinmaker-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year at AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced the preview of AWS IoT TwinMaker, a new AWS IoT service that makes it faster and easier to create digital twins of real-world systems and use them to monitor and optimize industrial operations. A digital twin is a living digital representation of an individual physical system that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Count Downloads in the Public Terraform Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-count-downloads-in-the-public-terraform-registry</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-count-downloads-in-the-public-terraform-registry"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how download metrics are calculated in the HashiCorp Terraform Registry, and how that count has evolved over time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Detect Operational Issues in Lambda Functions with Amazon DevOps Guru for Serverless]]></title>
        <id>8268d306374a02f09df77e136e38f9dbf78c0766</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/automatically-detect-operational-issues-in-lambda-functions-with-amazon-devops-guru-for-serverless/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T15:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing Amazon DevOps Guru for Serverless, a new capability for Amazon DevOps Guru. It allows developers to improve the operational performance and availability of serverless applications. AWS pioneered the serverless computing space with the launch of AWS Lambda in 2014. Today, hundreds of thousands of customers are using AWS Lambda. Lambda allows […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.7 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-6-7-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-6-7-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T11:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.7 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 38 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE report published for Spring Security OAuth]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/cve-report-published-for-spring-security-oauth</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/cve-report-published-for-spring-security-oauth"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Spring Security OAuth 2.5.2 to address the following CVE report.


  
CVE-2022-22969: Denial-of-Service (DoS) in spring-security-oauth2


This vulnerability exposes OAuth 2.0 Client applications only.

Please review the information in the CVE report and upgrade immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.13 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-5-13-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/21/spring-boot-2-5-13-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T08:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.13 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 31 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FormNet: Beyond Sequential Modeling for Form-Based Document Understanding]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/formnet-beyond-sequential-modeling-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/formnet-beyond-sequential-modeling-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T20:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Chen-Yu Lee and Chun-Liang Li, Research Scientists, Google Research, Cloud AI Team 
Form-based document understanding is a growing research topic because of its practical potential for automatically converting unstructured text data into structured information to gain insight about a document’s contents. Recent sequence modeling, which is a self-attention mechanism that directly models relationships between all words in a selection of text, has demonstrated state-of-the-art performance on natural language tasks. A natural approach to handle form document understanding tasks is to first serialize the form documents (usually in a left-to-right, top-to-bottom fashion) and then apply state-of-the-art sequence models to them.  
 However, form documents often have more complex layouts …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp and AWS Make it Easier to Secure Workloads in EKS with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-and-aws-partner-to-enhance-kubernetes-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-and-aws-partner-to-enhance-kubernetes-security"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp has partnered with AWS to enhance security on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service with Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opt-in to Auditing on Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63895</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/opt-in-to-auditing-on-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T17:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Auditing has now been made an opt-in feature on Azure DevOps. In our last blog post about Auditing, we discussed the exciting changes coming to the Auditing feature on Azure DevOps, as we work on bringing the feature to general availability.
The post Opt-in to Auditing on Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Migration Hub Orchestrator – New Migration Orchestration Capability with Customizable Workflow Templates]]></title>
        <id>0f99199a54f5eb036f2cc7d2f96cd7faee3329da</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-migration-hub-orchestrator-new-migration-orchestration-capability-with-customizable-workflow-templates/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T16:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can migrate any workload from an on-premises environment to AWS. The key to a successful migration to AWS is a well-thought-out plan, informative tools, prior migration experience, and a quality implementation. Every step along the way, you can use AWS’s years of experience to build your organizational, operational, and technical capabilities so that you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New reference architecture: Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 1.2 to 2 Migration Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-1.2-to-2-migration-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-1.2-to-2-migration-guide"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[we created a simple reference architecture to help guide you migrate from Ansible Automation Platform 1.2 to Ansible Automation Platform 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Prompt for Continual Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/learning-to-prompt-for-continual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/learning-to-prompt-for-continual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T17:00:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zifeng Wang, Student Researcher, and Zizhao Zhang, Software Engineer, Google Research
Supervised learning is a common approach to machine learning (ML) in which the model is trained using data that is labeled appropriately for the task at hand. Ordinary supervised learning trains on independent and identically distributed (IID) data, where all training examples are sampled from a fixed set of classes, and the model has access to these examples throughout the entire training phase. In contrast, continual learning tackles the problem of training a single model on changing data distributions where different classification tasks are presented sequentially. This is particularly important, for example, to enable autonomous agents to process and interpret continuous streams of informati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kubernetes to Nomad Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-kubernetes-to-nomad-cheat-sheet</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-kubernetes-to-nomad-cheat-sheet"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Kubernetes users looking to learn HashiCorp Nomad concepts and commands  — or vice versa — we’ve designed a cheat sheet for quick reference and a fast onramp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 18, 2022]]></title>
        <id>ef7b946d35336128b5b4045b8988427e735ae9f3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-18-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T18:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Here we are with another roundup of the most significant AWS launches from the previous week. Among the news, we have a new deployment option for Amazon FSx for NetApp […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Partner Network (APN) – 10 Years and Going Strong]]></title>
        <id>8ef86720707ad81177cef1eb9b0d2fe43d2e7cc6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-partner-network-apn-10-years-and-going-strong/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T15:27:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten years ago we launched AWS Partner Network (APN) in beta form for our partners and our customers. In his post for the beta launch, my then-colleague Jinesh Varia noted that: Partners are an integral part of the AWS ecosystem as they enable customers and help them scale their business globally. Some of our greatest […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep dive on Ansible VScode extension]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/deep-dive-on-ansible-vscode-extension</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/deep-dive-on-ansible-vscode-extension"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible as part of the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform continues to grow and mature. Recent enhancements include Ansible Content Collections, automation execution environments, and an increasing list of integrations using plugins and modules. It is more important than ever that both new and experienced content creators have access to tools that help them write better content faster. The newly created Ansible Devtools initiative focuses on developing and enhancing tools like ansible-navigator, Ansible VScode extension, ansible-lint and so on to help ease the Ansible automation content creator experience. In this blog, we will do a deep dive into the Ansible VSCode extension, giving an overview of how it works and the initial setup required to get it working after installation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>