<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-09-11T02:27:50.174Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-11T02:27:50.174Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does it mean to be smart?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43760</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/710398298/0/sethsblog~What-does-it-mean-to-be-smart/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-10T08:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You probably know that Bruce Wayne is actually Batman. That’s a secret identity that most of us are aware of. And if you’re up on pop culture, you know that the best Batman was played by the late actor Adam West. Visit the visual search engine Lexica, though, and you’ll see that it knows that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Walk in the Wild from Terrain Semantics]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/learning-to-walk-in-wild-from-terrain.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/learning-to-walk-in-wild-from-terrain.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yuxiang Yang, Student Researcher, Robotics at Google 
An important promise for quadrupedal robots is their potential to operate in complex outdoor environments that are difficult or inaccessible for humans. Whether it’s to find natural resources deep in the mountains, or to search for life signals in heavily-damaged earthquake sites, a robust and versatile quadrupedal robot could be very helpful. To achieve that, a robot needs to perceive the environment, understand its locomotion challenges, and adapt its locomotion skill accordingly. While recent advances in perceptive locomotion have greatly enhanced the capability of quadrupedal robots, most works focus on indoor or urban environments, thus they cannot effectively handle the complexity of off-road terrains. In these environme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visualizing Geospatial Data in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=275770</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/09/visualizing-geospatial-data-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T16:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are interviewing Adam Symington, author of the PythonMaps project, which is dedicated to using Python to develop beautiful yet very informative geospatial data visualizations. Adam is a geospatial data scientist working as the head of data science at Geollect Ltd, a geospatial intelligence company that aims to better understand the maritime world using […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Make Interns a Dynamic Part of Your Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-make-interns-a-dynamic-part-of-your-team</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-make-interns-a-dynamic-part-of-your-team"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figuring out where interns fit into larger team goals can be tough. One HashiCorp manager shares three essential tips to encourage success for everyone involved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCA vs SAST: what are they and which one is right for you?]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-09-sca-vs-sast-what-are-they-and-which-one-is-right-for-you/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-09-sca-vs-sast-what-are-they-and-which-one-is-right-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T15:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re taking a look at two commonly-used security tools and detailing how they can help secure your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code With Me: A New Way To Boost Your Kotlin Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=276646</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/blog/2022/09/09/code-with-me-kotlin/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T14:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collaborative learning, when learners work together on a shared assignment, makes for a highly-engaged process. Through hearing diverse thoughts, articulating arguments, and brainstorming, learners tend to achieve more complete knowledge and skills as a group than they could individually. Code With Me is a built-in feature of IntelliJ-based IDEs for collaborative programming that enables developers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Kalinina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your process communication with the new Slack Connector]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=61972</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/level-up-your-process-communication-with-the-new-slack-connector/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce an out-of-the-box Slack Connector.
The post Level up your process communication with the new Slack Connector appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake-aceuticals]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43734</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/710290176/0/sethsblog~Fakeaceuticals/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T08:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of course, we’ve always had snake oil salesmen. We’ve always had patent medicines, odd electric probes and copper bracelets. That’s partly because placebos work, and partly because when someone isn’t feeling well, it’s tempting to seek relief and belief. In the last fifty years, peer-reviewed and tested medicine has gotten dramatically more effective at the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic’s Tiffany Witwer Built a Career from Civil Engineering to Customer Success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/power-to-fly-how-elastic-s-tiffany-witwer-built-a-career-from-civil-engineering-to-customer-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/power-to-fly-how-elastic-s-tiffany-witwer-built-a-career-from-civil-engineering-to-customer-success"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With an overall positive outlook on life, Tiffany brings that same energy to her customers at work as the Head of Customer Success for Elastic. Tiffany shares her career journey from civil engineering to customer success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiersten Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic’s Tiffany Witwer Built a Career from Civil Engineering to Customer Success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/power-to-fly-how-elastic-s-tiffany-witwer-built-a-career-from-civil-engineering-to-customer-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/power-to-fly-how-elastic-s-tiffany-witwer-built-a-career-from-civil-engineering-to-customer-success"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
This blog post was originally published on the Power to Fly website.

Tiffany Witwer from Elastic is a proud mom of three.
“I enjoy being a parent because it teaches me patience and it gives me a different perspective,” she shares. “It allows me to be more present, laugh more, and appreciate the small things.”
In between her duties as a mom, she keeps herself mentally and physically healthy by running, biking, swimming, or doing yoga — all activities that help her start the day with gratitude. "It gives me the right perspective and attitude to go into the day,” she says.
With an overall positive outlook on life, Tiffany brings that same energy to her customers at work as the Head of Customer Success for Elastic.
We sat down with Tiffany, who shared with us her career journey from civil e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiersten Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interruption]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2670/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2670/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/interruption.png" title="It's been extra bad ever since my GPS got stuck on Phoebe Judge mode." alt="It's been extra bad ever since my GPS got stuck on Phoebe Judge mode." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: KMS V2 Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/09/kms-v2-improvements/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/09/kms-v2-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Anish Ramasekar, Rita Zhang, Mo Khan, and Xander Grzywinski (Microsoft)
With Kubernetes v1.25, SIG Auth is introducing a new v2alpha1 version of the Key Management Service (KMS) API. There are a lot of improvements in the works, and we're excited to be able to start down the path of a new and improved KMS!
What is KMS?
One of the first things to consider when securing a Kubernetes cluster is encrypting persisted API data at rest. KMS provides an interface for a provider to utilize a key stored in an external key service to perform this encryption.
Encryption at rest using KMS v1 has been a feature of Kubernetes since version v1.10, and is currently in beta as of version v1.12.
What’s new in v2alpha1?
While the original v1 implementation has been successful in helping Kubernetes us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot now available for teachers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-08-github-copilot-now-available-for-teachers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-08-github-copilot-now-available-for-teachers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a year in technical preview, GitHub Copilot, an AI pair programmer, is now free for all teachers verified on GitHub Global Campus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Multi-Axis Approach for Vision Transformer and MLP Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/a-multi-axis-approach-for-vision.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/a-multi-axis-approach-for-vision.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T17:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zhengzhong Tu and Yinxiao Li, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Convolutional neural networks have been the dominant machine learning architecture for computer vision since the introduction of AlexNet in 2012. Recently, inspired by the evolution of Transformers in natural language processing, attention mechanisms have been prominently incorporated into vision models. These attention methods boost some parts of the input data while minimizing other parts so that the network can focus on small but important parts of the data. The Vision Transformer (ViT) has created a new landscape of model designs for computer vision that is completely free of convolution. ViT regards image patches as a sequence of words, and applies a Transformer encoder on top. When trained on sufficiently la…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2.2 Release Candidate]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=277745</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/09/phpstorm-2022-2-2-release-candidate/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T17:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2.2 Release Candidate is now available, and it’s the final build before the stable release. The most notable changes and bug fixes in this build include: Fixed: Incorrect indent for array element with ?? operator (WI-67807)  Fixed: Remote SSH target run fails (IDEA-297442)  Fixed: Autocomplete popup is not shown in Data Editor filter field […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changes to the Terraform Partner Integration Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-partner-integration-program-changes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-partner-integration-program-changes"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are making some changes to the way that we tag modules and providers in the Terraform Registry for better consistency, clarity, and scalability in the Registry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=277644</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/09/08/datagrip-2022-2-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! We’ve released the third bug-fix update for DataGrip 2022.2. Here’s what’s been improved: DBE-6418 We’ve added the Smallest subquery or statement option in Preferences | Query Execution | When inside statement execute. It will run the nested subquery under the cursor or the entire statement if there is no subquery. DBE-16264 Ignore modification of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates About Educational Courses on Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=277926</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/09/08/updates-about-educational-courses-on-marketplace-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to share some news about the educational courses on JetBrains Marketplace! In our previous blog post, we discussed the most significant content updates from March to May 2022. Today we’re going to take a look at the improvements from the past couple of months!  JetBrains Marketplace hosts programming courses, created by both […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sofia Kolchanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the Kotlin Multiplatform Mobile Content Creators]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=277875</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/09/join-the-kotlin-multiplatform-mobile-content-creators/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T10:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kotlin Multiplatform Mobile Beta is approaching, and the technology ecosystem is continuing to grow and mature. We can’t help but mention the community efforts in this area. Developers all over the world are sharing their experience adopting the technology, providing tips and tricks, and creating great educational samples and other pieces of content to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Petrova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[But first, we need to talk about it]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43647</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/710174306/0/sethsblog~But-first-we-need-to-talk-about-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People don’t talk about end-of-life suffering or the cost of healthcare in the last year of life, so it never gets better. Instead, we pretend it isn’t an issue and the problem persists. We don’t talk about the ongoing and escalating costs (human and financial) of our changing climate, so the systems that are making […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm Overview 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=277593</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/09/phpstorm-overview-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T07:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to get to know PhpStorm? Maybe you have a colleague or friend who wants to know why you love this IDE? We’ve made a five-minute video about PhpStorm for you. We’ll highlight some of its core features: a to-the-point summary of why PhpStorm is a great choice for all PHP developers out […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research: open source software in India, Kenya, Egypt, and Mexico]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-08-research-open-source-software-in-india-kenya-egypt-and-mexico/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-08-research-open-source-software-in-india-kenya-egypt-and-mexico/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T07:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read the new GitHub report on OSS in India, Kenya, Egypt, and Mexico. Available now in English, and in Spanish and Arabic later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Hashicorp's Rosemary Wang on securing the intersection of apps and ops with Hashicorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/08/a-bootiful-podcast-hashicorp-s-rosemary-wang-on-securing-the-intersection-of-apps-and-ops-with-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/08/a-bootiful-podcast-hashicorp-s-rosemary-wang-on-securing-the-intersection-of-apps-and-ops-with-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Hashicorp Developer Advocate Rosemary Wang (@joatmon08) about a few Hashicorp technologies and their integrations with Spring Boot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APM correlations in Elastic Observability: Automatically identifying probable causes of slow or failed transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/apm-correlations-elastic-observability-root-cause-transactions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/apm-correlations-elastic-observability-root-cause-transactions"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview on how Elastic Observability and APM correlations can help diagnose and troubleshoot application issues. We will cover a real-life application issue and review some other common scenarios where APM is commonly used by developers, SREs and DevOps teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinay Chandrasekhar,Akhilesh Pokhariyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APM correlations in Elastic Observability: Automatically identifying probable causes of slow or failed transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/apm-correlations-elastic-observability-root-cause-transactions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/apm-correlations-elastic-observability-root-cause-transactions"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As a DevOps engineer or SRE, you are often faced with investigating complex problems — mysterious application performance issues that happen intermittently or to only certain portions of your application traffic — that impact your end users and potentially your company’s financial targets. Sifting through hundreds or even thousands of transactions and spans can be a lot of tedious, manual, and time consuming investigative work. Cloud-native or distributed microservices deployments introduce further complexities, increasing time to root cause determination. 

Wouldn’t it be awesome if you could quickly identify a common pattern that can help explain such a seemingly complex problem, thus demystifying it and paving the way for quicker root cause analysis and remediation? 

The APM correlat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinay Chandrasekhar,Akhilesh Pokhariyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.4 (codename Jubilee) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/07/spring-cloud-2021-0-4-codename-jubilee-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/07/spring-cloud-2021-0-4-codename-jubilee-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T22:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the General Availability (RELEASE) of the Spring Cloud 2021.0.4 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2021.0.4 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0.4 Release Train

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.
Spring Cloud Config


  
Replace JSCH with Apache MINA to resolve a number of SSH issues (#1901)


Spring Cloud Gateway


  
Added native JSON to gRPC filter (#2657)

  
Support ‘use-insecure-trust-manager’ & ‘trustedX509Certificates’ for GRPC Filter (2699)


Spring Cloud Openfeign


  
Allow overriding binary content types list ([#734]https://github.com/spring-cloud/spring-cloud-openfeign/…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: August 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-07-github-availability-report-august-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-07-github-availability-report-august-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T18:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In August, we experienced one incident resulting in significant impact to Codespaces. We’re still investigating that incident and will include it in next month’s report. This report also sheds light into an incident that impacted Codespaces in July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Automation Experience: AnsibleFest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-automation-experience-ansiblefest-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-automation-experience-ansiblefest-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is almost time for our favorite event of the year! AnsibleFest is back as an in-person event, and it’s the only place to feel the full power of automation. Join us October 18 and 19 in Chicago, and immerse yourself in the movement that’s made Ansible an industry-leading automation technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research: quantifying GitHub Copilot’s impact on developer productivity and happiness]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-07-research-quantifying-github-copilots-impact-on-developer-productivity-and-happiness/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-07-research-quantifying-github-copilots-impact-on-developer-productivity-and-happiness/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the GitHub Copilot Technical Preview launched just over one year ago, we wanted to know one thing: Is this tool helping developers? The GitHub Next team conducted research using a combination of surveys and experiments, which led us to expected and unexpected answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Global Preview: Evolving Your Cloud Operating Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-preview-evolving-your-cloud-operating-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-global-preview-evolving-your-cloud-operating-model"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Find out about the 13 most interesting HashiConf Global sessions for enterprise cloud platform teams. Join us October 4 - 6, 2022 in Los Angeles and virtual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Busy Plugin Developers Newsletter – Summer 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=277627</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2022/09/busy-plugin-developers-newsletter-summer-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T10:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marketplace updates: ⭐️ Introducing Space apps in JetBrains Marketplace and the Space Apps Contest JetBrains Space – an all-in-one solution for software projects and teams – can now be extended with applications. A Space application is an external server-side service or client-side application (JavaScript, mobile, or desktop) that can interact with Space modules. For example, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constraints are a gift]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40871</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/710009054/0/sethsblog~Constraints-are-a-gift/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T08:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If only” is a soothing refrain. If only the constraints were lifted, and the things that are scarce were abundant. If only the barriers were lifted and there was more time or fewer obstacles… That’s a trap. If the constraints went away, you’d be playing a totally different game, because your competitors would see their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detection engineering — Maximizing analyst efficiency using Cardinality Threshold rules on your alerts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detection-engineering-maximizing-analyst-efficiency-using-cardinality-threshold-rules-on-your-alerts-</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detection-engineering-maximizing-analyst-efficiency-using-cardinality-threshold-rules-on-your-alerts-"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Threshold rules to create alerts on your alerts is a great way to maximize your analyst effectiveness without sacrificing visibility. By using these rules, security analysts spend less time investigating false positives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Jewitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detection engineering — Maximizing analyst efficiency using Cardinality Threshold rules on your alerts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detection-engineering-maximizing-analyst-efficiency-using-cardinality-threshold-rules-on-your-alerts-</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detection-engineering-maximizing-analyst-efficiency-using-cardinality-threshold-rules-on-your-alerts-"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As the Threat Detection and Response (TDR) team on Elastic’s internal Infosec team, one of our responsibilities is building, tuning, and maintaining the security detections used to find and stop attacks against Elastic systems. This includes the Elastic Cloud environment, which currently spans 50+ cloud regions and four different cloud providers ingesting more than 1.5 petabytes of data per day.
We also work very closely with our Incident Response team and the analysts triaging alerts so we can feel their pain when detections don’t work as intended. Within Elastic, we call ourselves Customer Zero and we always use the newest versions of our products. We meet every week with the development teams that are building Elastic products to provide real-world feedback, bug reports, and feature r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Jewitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why CISOs are the new champions of insurance transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-cisos-are-the-new-champions-of-insurance-transformation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-cisos-are-the-new-champions-of-insurance-transformation"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security will be top of mind for any insurance digital transformation effort. CISOs can therefore set best practices and implement new tools and processes that drive greater comfort for the company, clients, partners, and regulators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why CISOs are the new champions of insurance transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-cisos-are-the-new-champions-of-insurance-transformation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-cisos-are-the-new-champions-of-insurance-transformation"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The insurance industry's business model is rapidly evolving as the latest consumer and business technologies deliver greater quantities of real-time data than ever before. McKinsey predicts that by 2030, processes like underwriting as we know it will cease to exist — machine and deep learning models will automate policies and reduce delivery time to seconds. The rapid adoption of new tools, infrastructure, and talent will certainly influence underwriting, pricing, claims, distribution, and other core components of the insurance industry. The accumulation of system generated data will also help insurers better understand their customers’ preferences, habits, and risks — and thus support a more intelligent level of service and a more holistic product offering.

As with all technology advan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things You Should Not Do]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2669/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2669/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/things_you_should_not_do.png" title="Now I'm tempted to start telling people that I secretly don't actually know how to do any physics calculations, and so all the answers in What If are based on me actually trying to do the thing and then reporting what happened, but phrased as if it's hypothetical." alt="Now I'm tempted to start telling people that I secretly don't actually know how to do any physics calculations, and so all the answers in What If are based on me actually trying to do the thing and then reporting what happened, but phrased as if it's hypothetical." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes’s IPTables Chains Are Not API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/07/iptables-chains-not-api/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/07/iptables-chains-not-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Dan Winship (Red Hat)
Some Kubernetes components (such as kubelet and kube-proxy) create
iptables chains and rules as part of their operation. These chains
were never intended to be part of any Kubernetes API/ABI guarantees,
but some external components nonetheless make use of some of them (in
particular, using KUBE-MARK-MASQ to mark packets as needing to be
masqueraded).
As a part of the v1.25 release, SIG Network made this declaration
explicit: that (with one exception), the iptables chains that
Kubernetes creates are intended only for Kubernetes’s own internal
use, and third-party components should not assume that Kubernetes will
create any specific iptables chains, or that those chains will contain
any specific rules if they do exist.
Then, in future releases, as part of KEP-31…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Graph connectors for Microsoft Search]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65671</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-graph-connectors-for-microsoft-search/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T23:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Search is the workplace search solution offered with Microsoft 365. Microsoft Search lets you find the information you need by unlocking knowledge and expertise. It helps you find what you need to complete what you’re working on. Whether you’re searching for people,
The post Azure DevOps Graph connectors for Microsoft Search appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digitizing Smell: Using Molecular Maps to Understand Odor]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/digitizing-smell-using-molecular-maps.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/digitizing-smell-using-molecular-maps.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T17:35:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Richard C. Gerkin, Google Research, and Alexander B. Wiltschko, Google 


Did you ever try to measure a smell? …Until you can measure their likenesses and differences you can have no science of odor. If you are ambitious to found a new science, measure a smell.
  
— Alexander Graham Bell, 1914.

 How can we measure a smell? Smells are produced by molecules that waft through the air, enter our noses, and bind to sensory receptors. Potentially billions of molecules can produce a smell, so figuring out which ones produce which smells is difficult to catalog or predict. Sensory maps can help us solve this problem.  Color vision has the most familiar examples of these maps, from the color wheel we each learn in primary school to more sophisticated variants used to perform color correc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for OctogatosConf 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-06-join-us-for-octogatosconf-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-06-join-us-for-octogatosconf-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T16:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live on September 15, 2022, with talks by industry experts in Spanish, Portuguese, and English, on topics including software development, security, technical project management, community, open source, professional development and best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault, Kubernetes, and the Graduation of vault-k8s to Version 1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-kubernetes-and-the-graduation-of-vault-k8s-to-version-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-kubernetes-and-the-graduation-of-vault-k8s-to-version-1-0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of vault-k8s 1.0 marks a great time to learn how HashiCorp Vault has integrated with Kubernetes in the past and what to look forward to in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contributing to open source at GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-06-contributing-to-open-source-at-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-06-contributing-to-open-source-at-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T13:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A software engineer’s personal journey to becoming an open source contributor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy: New Projects and Topics in August]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=277340</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/09/06/jetbrains-academy-new-projects-and-topics-in-august-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T11:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The academic season is either close or has already started for most of us. Our content updates will help you get the ball rolling in an interactive environment of JetBrains Academy without getting overwhelmed. This August we released three new projects and 31 new educational topics. Moreover, we introduced our brand new Computer Algorithms and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | September 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=277274</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/09/06/net-annotated-monthly-september-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T10:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? As of 2020, 64.82% of searches on Google ended without clicking to another web property. People stay in the top half of the first page of search results. .NET news Announcing .NET Framework 4.8.1 .NET 6 is now in Ubuntu 22.04 C# 11 preview: generic math, required members, and more Announcing built-in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – September 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=277300</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/09/java-annotated-monthly-september-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T09:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! For the September edition of Java Annotated Monthly, we’ve prepared a lot of resources to help you transition smoothly into the fall season. In addition, we cordially invite you to join our free online IntelliJ IDEA Conf, which takes place September 29–30. Java News JEP 429 – The proposal introduces extent-local variables, which enable […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ida Bzowska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The treatment of bystanders]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43714</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/709842444/0/sethsblog~The-treatment-of-bystanders/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This seems to be cultural, not based on income, caste, race or genetics. Some professions and communities give a greater percentage of their income to charity than others. Some towns have no-kill dog shelters while others have a reputation for abandonment. You might find an online community that welcomes and supports newcomers, and another that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 5th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/06/this-week-in-spring-september-5th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/06/this-week-in-spring-september-5th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How are you? It’s a fantastic Tuesday, the 5th of September, 2022, and I couldn’t be happier. It’s also Labor Day weekend here in the US. It marks the unofficial end of summer, which is a bit sad. But, on the upside, it’s a four-day weekend for me! I’m technically off today. So, you’ll forgive me, but I won’t spend too much time here. Let’s dive right into this week’s roundup!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Dr. Kris De Volder on Spring Tools, VS Code, and so much more

  
Connect to Multiple Databases Using Spring Data Mongodb

  
End-to-end tracing with OpenTelemetry

  
I love this article by Hashicorp’s Rosemary Wang on refreshable secrets for Kubernetes Applications with Vault Agent

  
Microsoft is committed to the success of Java developers

  
Price Reduction - Azure Spring Apps does more, costs less!

  
The Second Best Way to Fetch a Spring Data JPA DTO Projection – Java, SQL and jOOQ.

  
The best way to fetch a Spring Data JPA DTO Projection - Vlad Mihalcea

  
Speaking of JOOQ, did you know there’s good reactive API support included? Check it out: 3.15.0 Release with Support for R2DBC, Nested ROW, ARRAY, and MULTISET types, 5 new SQL dialects, CREATE PROCEDURE, FUNCTION, and TRIGGER support and Much More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – September 5, 2022]]></title>
        <id>8f3c0923bae1a075227962f5ea6ebbfc45ae02a5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-september-5-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T18:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! As a new week begins, let’s quickly look back at the most significant AWS news from the previous seven days. Last Week’s Launches Here are the launches that got my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploratory Data Analysis in Practice]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=276863</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2022/09/05/exploratory-data-analysis-in-practice/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T11:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have a lot of data for training a machine learning model or making a data-driven decision, it can be very difficult to observe it manually or via Excel. That’s where data analysis tools and programming languages, such as Python, can help. Using Datalore can make the process even easier and lead you to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting the hull shape right]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43706</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/709646610/0/sethsblog~Getting-the-hull-shape-right/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s tempting to have your book copyedited and typeset before you have your editor read it. And it feels right to spend time on the company’s website before you have your first customer… But if you don’t have the foundational elements right, the fit and finish don’t matter at all. This summer I designed and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artemis Quote]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2668/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2668/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/artemis_quote.png" title="Another option: &quot;It is an honor to be the first human to set foot on the moon.&quot;" alt="Another option: &quot;It is an honor to be the first human to set foot on the moon.&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The speed of change]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42604</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/709459412/0/sethsblog~The-speed-of-change/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moore’s law talks about the fact that computer chips get faster and cheaper over time. It turns out that the biggest shift to our culture isn’t the changing speed of a computer chip, it’s what happens when we network humans together. Adding more people to the internet has accelerated science, politics and every element of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cultural distress (and consumerism)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43675</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/709325620/0/sethsblog~Cultural-distress-and-consumerism/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-03T08:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For decades, marketers (and politicians) have been working to amplify cultural distress, a hack on our emotions. Not the tragic emotional distress of being unable to care for your kids, find a place to live or deal with trauma, but the invented cultural distress of modern industrialized societies. This is the easily created shame of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · August 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-02-release-radar-aug-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-02-release-radar-aug-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T23:13:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We&#8217;ve been gearing up to launch GitHub Universe 2022 and our community has been launching cool projects left right and center.  These projects include everything from world-changing technology to developer tooling, and weekend hobbies. Here are some of the open source projects that released major version updates this August. Read more about these projects in [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git&#8217;s database internals V: scalability]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-02-gits-database-internals-v-scalability/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-02-gits-database-internals-v-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T13:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fifth and final part of our blog series exploring Git's internals shows several strategies for scaling your Git repositories that match related database sharding techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The last minute]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42639</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/709174952/0/sethsblog~The-last-minute/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you do anything at the last minute that takes more than a minute, you’re not organizing your project properly. The last minute is not a buffer zone, nor is it the moment to double-check your work. The last minute is simply sixty seconds to enjoy and to remind yourself that you successfully planned ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Internet Interaction]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2667/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2667/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/first_internet_interaction.png" title="To that stranger on the KOOL Tree House chat room, I gotta hand it to you: You were, ultimately, not wrong." alt="To that stranger on the KOOL Tree House chat room, I gotta hand it to you: You were, ultimately, not wrong." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing COSI: Object Storage Management using Kubernetes APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/02/cosi-kubernetes-object-storage-management/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/02/cosi-kubernetes-object-storage-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Sidhartha Mani (Minio, Inc)
This article introduces the Container Object Storage Interface (COSI), a standard for provisioning and consuming object storage in Kubernetes. It is an alpha feature in Kubernetes v1.25.
File and block storage are treated as first class citizens in the Kubernetes ecosystem via Container Storage Interface (CSI). Workloads using CSI volumes enjoy the benefits of portability across vendors and across Kubernetes clusters without the need to change application manifests. An equivalent standard does not exist for Object storage.
Object storage has been rising in popularity in recent years as an alternative form of storage to filesystems and block devices. Object storage paradigm promotes disaggregation of compute and storage. This is done by making data avail…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Standardize Cryptography in the Enterprise with HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-standardize-cryptography-in-the-enterprise-with-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-standardize-cryptography-in-the-enterprise-with-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how centralizing encryption tools in a self-service platform for developers lowers the cost of ownership, centralizes best practices, and makes auditing easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: introducing the new, larger GitHub-hosted runners beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-09-01-github-actions-introducing-the-new-larger-github-hosted-runners-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-09-01-github-actions-introducing-the-new-larger-github-hosted-runners-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T16:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now your team can spend less time managing infrastructure and more time writing code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t blame the mouse]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41723</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/709012278/0/sethsblog~Dont-blame-the-mouse/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you leave your cheese out and the mouse eats it, the mouse is simply being a mouse. While it might be nice if the mouse didn’t wreck your dinner, that’s his job. Often, we show up with our cheese and then become indignant when the mouse does what mice do. “Oh, you’re a mouse.” […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Dr. Kris De Volder on Spring Tools, VS Code, and so much more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/01/a-bootiful-podcast-dr-kris-de-volder-on-spring-tools-vs-code-and-so-much-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/01/a-bootiful-podcast-dr-kris-de-volder-on-spring-tools-vs-code-and-so-much-more"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode Josh Long (@starbuxman)  talks to Dr. Kris De Volder, a longtime member of the Spring Tools team, about all the cool stuff he’s worked on and is going to work on. And then we get knee deep into a discussion around building IDE integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud price change to create alignment across purchasing options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-price-change-to-create-alignment-across-purchasing-options</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-price-change-to-create-alignment-across-purchasing-options"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud pricing is changing to simplify and bring parity across Direct and Marketplace prices. Customers will pay the same price for Elastic Cloud whether they purchase from Elastic or their preferred Cloud Service Provider’s marketplace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanda Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud price change to create alignment across purchasing options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-price-change-to-create-alignment-across-purchasing-options</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-cloud-price-change-to-create-alignment-across-purchasing-options"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Effective November 1, 2022 Elastic is making changes to Elastic Cloud pricing to simplify and bring parity across Direct and Marketplace prices. Moving forward, customers will pay the same price for Elastic Cloud whether they purchase directly from Elastic or through their preferred Cloud Service Provider’s marketplace. Thanks to our close partnership with the cloud providers over the last few years, we've significantly reduced the marketplace fees our customers have been paying and are now able to align pricing across all purchasing avenues.

Many customers prefer to use their pre-committed cloud marketplace spend to purchase software as it helps shorten the purchase cycle and accelerate onboarding. With this change, when customers purchase an Elastic subscription using their pre-committed cloud provider marketplace spend, they will pay the same price they would pay Elastic directly.

As a result of this change, some customers will see a small price decrease, while others may see slightly higher prices (up to 4%), but many will see little or no change. Elastic has directly communicated with all impacted customers. The price change for impacted customers will be reflected in the November billing statement made available in December 2022.

In addition, to help customers optimize their Elastic deployment and reduce costs, we’ve added a number of features. These include simple, no-downtime migration capability to help users adopt the most price-performant instance type for their use case, as well as Searchable Snapshots, which enables users to leverage cost-effective cloud-based object storage. Please see our blog post, Top 5 ways to optimize your Elastic Cloud costs. 

We encourage you to reach out to your account team if you have questions. If you are unsure who your account representative is, you can Contact Elastic. For information on Elastic pricing, you can visit our pricing page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanda Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Patent Phrase Similarity Dataset]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/announcing-patent-phrase-similarity.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/announcing-patent-phrase-similarity.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted Grigor Aslanyan, Software Engineer, Google 
Patent documents typically use legal and highly technical language, with context-dependent terms that may have meanings quite different from colloquial usage and even between different documents. The process of using traditional patent search methods (e.g., keyword searching) to search through the corpus of over one hundred million patent documents can be tedious and result in many missed results due to the broad and non-standard language used. For example, a "soccer ball" may be described as a "spherical recreation device", "inflatable sportsball" or "ball for ball game". Additionally, the language used in some patent documents may obfuscate terms to their advantage, so more powerful natural language processing (NLP) and semantic similari…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 209 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65658</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-209-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T16:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We fixed a bunch more issues for New Boards Hub in sprint 209. Here is a list of the items that have been resolved.
Issue
OnBlur instead of onChange
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 209 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation in banking: 6 considerations for digital transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60932</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/automation-in-banking-6-considerations-for-digital-transformation/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation and banking have been two peas in a technological pod since the 1934 introduction of the IBM ® 801 Bank Proof machine, a check sorting machine. Later innovations like the automated teller machine and the debit card continued the banking automation trend of digitizing analog processes. With the advent of the internet, machine learning, and cloud computing, there are still so many automation opportunities to explore.  For instance, using AI for risk assessment, automating the classification of unstructured data, or reducing manual work can help you increase the agility of the overall organization, improve the customer experience, and get new features and products to market much more rapidly. We’re going to explore six concepts to keep in mind for...
The post Automation in banking: 6 considerations for digital transformation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price Reduction - Azure Spring Apps does more, costs less!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/31/price-reduction-azure-spring-apps-does-more-costs-less</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/31/price-reduction-azure-spring-apps-does-more-costs-less"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We believe in providing the most innovative cloud offerings at incredibly competitive prices. As we operate Azure Spring Apps, we continue to build efficiencies and economies of scale. We are passing those efficiencies to you. 

Many customers have asked us to lower the size of the base unit to make it easier to get started and accommodate smaller projects. 
Announcing Price and Base Unit Reduction

Effective September 1st, we are reducing the base unit of Azure Spring Apps Standard and Enterprise to 6 vCPUs and 12 GB of Memory. And reducing the overage prices for vCPU and Memory. 


New Monthly FREE Grants

Furthermore, to help you get started, effective mid-September, we are offering monthly FREE grants – 50 vCPU hours and 100 Memory GB hours. 

Let’s look at a few examples: 

Note…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank BRI mitigates cybercrime and financial risk with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bank-bri-mitigates-cybercrime-and-financial-risk-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bank-bri-mitigates-cybercrime-and-financial-risk-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bank BRI is one of the largest banks in Indonesia and Southeast Asia. As Bank BRI continues to grow its ecosystem, the number of assets it must defend against cybercrime only increases. Learn how the organization set out to find new tools to protect its complex network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank BRI mitigates cybercrime and financial risk with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bank-bri-mitigates-cybercrime-and-financial-risk-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bank-bri-mitigates-cybercrime-and-financial-risk-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Bank BRI is one of the largest banks in Indonesia and Southeast Asia, providing end-to-end financial solutions to more than 130 million customers. As part of its core mission, the bank has a particular focus on empowering microbusinesses and advancing the financial inclusiveness of the countries it serves.

With such a wide range of customers and partners, Bank BRI has created an extensive network across the region. Its long history within the financial sector also means that it has an array of IT assets and tools across the bank, which consist of legacy systems, cutting-edge solutions, and everything in between. In addition, the company’s tremendous size and heterogeneity have created many unique challenges, including difficulty obtaining complete visibility into all of the bank’s syste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: cgroup v2 graduates to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/31/cgroupv2-ga-1-25/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/31/cgroupv2-ga-1-25/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors:: David Porter (Google), Mrunal Patel (Red Hat)
Kubernetes 1.25 brings cgroup v2 to GA (general availability), letting the
kubelet use the latest container resource
management capabilities.
What are cgroups?
Effective resource management is a
critical aspect of Kubernetes. This involves managing the finite resources in
your nodes, such as CPU, memory, and storage.
cgroups are a Linux kernel capability that establish resource management
functionality like limiting CPU usage or setting memory limits for running
processes.
When you use the resource management capabilities in Kubernetes, such as configuring
requests and limits for Pods and containers,
Kubernetes uses cgroups to enforce your resource requests and limits.
The Linux kernel offers two versions of cgroups: cgroup v1 and cgr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and VMware Announce VMware Cloud on AWS integration with Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP]]></title>
        <id>fdb3e5851333d5a35feee69841bc3b0de7ed14eb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-and-vmware-announce-vmware-cloud-on-aws-integration-with-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our customers are looking for cost-effective ways to continue to migrate their applications to the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is a fully managed, jointly engineered service that brings VMware’s enterprise-class, software-defined data center architecture to the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS offers our customers the ability to run applications across operationally consistent VMware vSphere-based […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can a Service Mesh Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-can-a-service-mesh-do</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-can-a-service-mesh-do"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A service mesh is a force multiplier that can do everything from service discovery to zero trust security, load balancing, multi-cloud connectivity, automation, and north-south traffic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is committed to the success of Java developers]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/microsoft-is-committed-to-the-success-of-java-developers</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/microsoft-is-committed-to-the-success-of-java-developers"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! This is a guest post from our friend Julia Liuson, President, Developer Division, Microsoft

As a company, we are committed to making Java developers as efficient and productive as possible. This commitment means empowering you to use any tool, framework, and application server on any operating system. Wherever you are with Java, Microsoft supports your workload with an abundance of choices and with a wide range of developer tools and services. 
Code, Deploy, and Scale Java Your Way

Today, more and more Java developers are looking at how they can bring their existing Java applications to the cloud—or how to build new cloud-native applications. We have been working to make it easier for you to bring your Java applications to the cloud using the tools and frameworks you l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BPMN and DMN Modeler for Atlassian Confluence]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60833</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/bpmn-and-dmn-modeler-for-atlassian-confluence/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Document business processes with the BPMN and DMN Modeler for Confluence - two plugins available for free on the Atlassian Marketplace.
The post BPMN and DMN Modeler for Atlassian Confluence appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 30th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/this-week-in-spring-august-30th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/30/this-week-in-spring-august-30th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How are you? How’re you doin’ this fine tuesday morning? I’m doing well, of course, because this week VMware’s tentpole show - VMware Explore - is happening not even a mile from my home, here in San Francisco! And this is just the first one - there’ll be another show, my favorite show, in December: SpringOne 2022! I sure hope you’ve registered and that we’ll see you there! 

Indeed, I’ve got a lunch to get to, so let’s get this this week’s wrapup done a little more quickly: without further ado….


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert

  
Creating a custom Spring Cloud Gateway Filter

  
Feign Client Exception Handling

  
Kai Tödter has just announced version 1.6.0 of JSON:API for Spring HATEOAS

  
Multitenancy With Spring Data JPA

  
PKCE Support for Secret Clients with Spring Security

  
Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is available now!

  
Swagger: Specify Two Responses with the Same Response Code

  
Are you building Spring Apps? Join us to learn how to build, deploy and operate Spring Apps at scale.

  
So, here is VMware’s stack for building a platform on the platform as kubernetes, the Tanzu Application Platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Open–AWS Region in the United Arab Emirates (UAE)]]></title>
        <id>abade96b96022cbe9580a09867b67fafe3511c48</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-aws-region-in-the-united-arab-emirates-uae/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T06:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Region in the United Arab Emirates is now open. The official name is Middle East (UAE), and the API name is me-central-1. You can start using it today to deploy workloads and store your data in the United Arab Emirates. The AWS Middle East (UAE) Region is the second Region in the Middle […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Elastic Maps to make public datasets observable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-use-elastic-maps-to-make-public-datasets-observable</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-use-elastic-maps-to-make-public-datasets-observable"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a growing trend among many countries to publish their data as open datasets that are available to the public. These curated datasets are an excellent resource for developers looking to create a demo set for their applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing <i>Elastic Insights</i> magazine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-insights-magazine</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-insights-magazine"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Volume 1 of Elastic Insights, a new digital magazine from Elastic that covers the most pressing technology matters facing digital leaders today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.4.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.4.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.4.1 over the previous versions in 8.4.x.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
8.4.1 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Version 8.4.1 fixes a Kibana issue where any 8.3.x cluster, which contains a currently snoozed rule, will fail to upgrade with a saved object migration failure. This does not apply to indefinite snooze or mute, only to on-demand snooze (i.e., snooze for 1 hour).
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Cote</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Elastic Maps to make public datasets observable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-use-elastic-maps-to-make-public-datasets-observable</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-use-elastic-maps-to-make-public-datasets-observable"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
There’s a growing trend among many countries to publish their data (for example, the number and location of bicycles that have been stolen in Berlin) as open datasets that are available to the public. These curated datasets are an excellent resource for developers looking to create a demo set for their applications.

In this post, we’ll take the example of Berlin’s bicycle theft database to walk through how you can use Elastic Maps to make visual dashboards and maps of publicly available data as demos in your applications.
The dataset
First grab yourself a copy of the CSV from Fahrraddiebstahl in Berlin | Offene Daten Berlin. This is irregularly updated. In this blog, I won’t cover how to retrieve this document regularly and send it to Elasticsearch. If you want to do something like that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing <i>Elastic Insights</i> magazine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-insights-magazine</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-elastic-insights-magazine"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Download Volume 1 today!

Elastic today launched Elastic Insights, a new digital magazine for technology leaders about how to better drive results that matter for your organization.  

The theme of this issue is “The Future of Unstructured Data.” This report examines how leaders create growth, resilience, and order from chaos with a set of solutions and processes. We focus on the impact of search-powered technologies to help businesses achieve the outcomes they expect from cloud-driven digital transformation.

“Almost 90% of all the data that matters to any given enterprise is unstructured, according to IDC,” writes Rick Laner, Elastic’s Chief Customer Officer and the guest editor of this debut issue.

“Thinking about the hundreds of technology leaders that I’ve advised, that means that without the right processes and technology, they’d only have a view into 10% of their company,” he writes. “No one can make smart decisions that way.”

Search-powered technologies enable the search of data across multiple sources such as websites, applications, databases, and hybrid cloud environments, according to a study conducted by Forrester Consulting, commissioned by Elastic. 

Contributor and noted tech writer Rusty Weston highlights the impact of search-powered technology in our feature article. Additional articles featuring advice and interviews from our expert contributor network cover digital transformation, customer experience, cybersecurity, and observability challenges that digital business leaders have faced and overcome. 

Elastic Insights will be published quarterly, encompassing the latest research and insights that Elastic’s partners, customers, and Elasticians have to offer. Be sure to download this issue to be informed of future releases.

Get your copy of Elastic Insights today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Smalera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.4.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-4-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Cote</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 29, 2022]]></title>
        <id>d79ee60a7a83272276a7f3bd52c297b82f87c603</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-29-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T19:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve just returned from data and machine learning (ML) conferences in Los Angeles and San Francisco, California. It’s been great to chat with customers and developers about the latest technology trends and use cases. This past week has also been packed with launches at AWS. Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refresh Secrets for Kubernetes Applications with Vault Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/refresh-secrets-for-kubernetes-applications-with-vault-agent</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/refresh-secrets-for-kubernetes-applications-with-vault-agent"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the system signal and live reload methods for updating Kubernetes applications when secrets change. See an example via a Spring Boot application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Red Hat OpenShift - The Easy Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/monitoring-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-red-hat-openshift-the-easy-way</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/monitoring-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-red-hat-openshift-the-easy-way"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform enables teams and organizations to drive their automation from across the cloud and on-premise, keeping Ansible Automation Platform healthy with the ability to monitor key metrics becomes paramount.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability helps monitor your Azure workloads on the new Arm-based VMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/microsoft-azure-arm-virtual-machines-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/microsoft-azure-arm-virtual-machines-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The launch of Azure’s new Arm-based virtual machines (VMs) built on Ampere Altra processors brings more flexibility and choice to Azure customers around the world. You can deploy Elastic Observability (available on Azure Marketplace) to monitor and manage your cloud applications built on these new VMs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugo Sangiorgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability helps monitor your Azure workloads on the new Arm-based VMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/microsoft-azure-arm-virtual-machines-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/microsoft-azure-arm-virtual-machines-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Microsoft Azure’s recently launched new Azure Virtual Machines (VMs) feature the Ampere Altra Arm-based processor. These new VMs are engineered to efficiently run horizontally scalable workloads such as web servers, application servers, and open source databases. They deliver excellent price-performance and represent an important addition to Microsoft Azure's portfolio of instance types.

Elastic Observability can give you a holistic view of your cloud resources as you migrate your workloads to the new Arm architecture. Elastic’s native Azure Integration for Activity Logs, VM and Container Metrics along with Elastic APM allows you to collect logs, metrics, and traces for the Azure platform and applications running on it. Once deployed, you can easily compare the performance between Arm-a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugo Sangiorgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: CSI Inline Volumes have graduated to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/29/csi-inline-volumes-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/29/csi-inline-volumes-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jonathan Dobson (Red Hat)
CSI Inline Volumes were introduced as an alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.15 and have been beta since 1.16. We are happy to announce that this feature has graduated to General Availability (GA) status in Kubernetes 1.25.
CSI Inline Volumes are similar to other ephemeral volume types, such as configMap, downwardAPI and secret. The important difference is that the storage is provided by a CSI driver, which allows the use of ephemeral storage provided by third-party vendors. The volume is defined as part of the pod spec and follows the lifecycle of the pod, meaning the volume is created once the pod is scheduled and destroyed when the pod is destroyed.
What's new in 1.25?
There are a couple of new bug fixes related to this feature in 1.25, and the CSIInlineVolum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a custom Spring Cloud Gateway Filter]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/26/creating-a-custom-spring-cloud-gateway-filter</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/26/creating-a-custom-spring-cloud-gateway-filter"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we look into writing a custom extension for Spring Cloud Gateway. Before we get started, let’s go over how Spring Cloud Gateway works:




  
First, a client makes a network request to the Gateway

  
The Gateway is defined with a number of routes, each with Predicates to match the request to the route. For example, you can match on the path segment of the URL or the HTTP method of the request.

  
Once matched, the Gateway executes pre-request logic on each of the filters applied to the route. For example, you might want to add query parameters to your request

  
A proxy filter routes the request to the proxied service

  
The service executes and returns a response

  
The gateway receives the response and executes post-request logic on each filter before return…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What HashiCorp Interns Learned This Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-hashicorp-interns-learned-this-summer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-hashicorp-interns-learned-this-summer"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10 interns in HashiCorp’s Early Career Program share what they learned during their summer with the company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways to involve your community to improve your programs]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60542</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/3-ways-to-involve-your-community-to-improve-your-programs/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community programs are valuable tools for organizations. But enabling engagement in these programs can be challenging.
The post 3 ways to involve your community to improve your programs appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danielle Andrist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the latest AWS Heroes – August 2022]]></title>
        <id>f94b7ec2837a44f904bb188f134e48c449671094</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-latest-aws-heroes-august-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T18:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global AWS community is filled with passionate builders, eager to learn and explore ways to build better and faster on AWS. Within the AWS community, a select few individuals truly go above and beyond to share their knowledge and inspire others through content creation, event organization, open source contributions, and more. These community leaders […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-Definition Segmentation in Google Meet]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/high-definition-segmentation-in-google.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/high-definition-segmentation-in-google.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tingbo Hou and Juhyun Lee, Software Engineers, Google 
In recent years video conferencing has played an increasingly important role in both work and personal communication for many users. Over the past two years, we have enhanced this experience in Google Meet by introducing privacy-preserving machine learning (ML) powered background features, also known as “virtual green screen”, which allows users to blur their backgrounds or replace them with other images. What is unique about this solution is that it runs directly in the browser without the need to install additional software.  
So far, these ML-powered features have relied on CPU inference made possible by leveraging neural network sparsity, a common solution that works across devices, from entry level computers to high-end …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Fine-Grained Visual Embedding Powered by Amazon QuickSight]]></title>
        <id>a1501b50fea420ead40fcf160e7a0bea82b5b85f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-fine-grained-visual-embedding-powered-by-amazon-quicksight/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T16:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing a new feature, Fine-Grained Visual Embedding Powered by Amazon QuickSight. With this feature, individual visualizations from Amazon QuickSight dashboards can now be embedded in high-traffic webpages and applications. Additionally, this feature enables you to provide rich insights for your end-users where they need them the most, without server or software setup […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-fellow-java-champion-and-timescaledb-developer-advocate-christoph-engelbert</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/25/a-bootiful-podcast-fellow-java-champion-and-timescaledb-developer-advocate-christoph-engelbert"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow Java Champion and TimescaleDB developer advocate Christoph Engelbert (@noctarius2k) about PostgreSQL, Java, time series databases, observability, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Run Tasks Ecosystem Continues to Grow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-run-tasks-ecosystem-continues-to-grow</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-run-tasks-ecosystem-continues-to-grow"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teams can now integrate oak9 and Torq into the Terraform Cloud workflow via run tasks. Plus: A list of integrations now validated to work with Terraform Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.25: Pod Security Admission Controller in Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/25/pod-security-admission-stable/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/25/pod-security-admission-stable/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Tim Allclair (Google), Sam Stoelinga (Google)
The release of Kubernetes v1.25 marks a major milestone for Kubernetes out-of-the-box pod security
controls: Pod Security admission (PSA) graduated to stable, and Pod Security Policy (PSP) has been
removed.
PSP was deprecated in Kubernetes v1.21,
and no longer functions in Kubernetes v1.25 and later.
The Pod Security admission controller replaces PodSecurityPolicy, making it easier to enforce predefined
Pod Security Standards by
simply adding a label to a namespace. The Pod Security Standards are maintained by the K8s
community, which means you automatically get updated security policies whenever new
security-impacting Kubernetes features are introduced.
What’s new since Beta?
Pod Security Admission hasn’t changed much since the Beta i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using ML to Boost Engagement with a Maternal and Child Health Program in India]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/using-ml-to-boost-engagement-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/using-ml-to-boost-engagement-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Aparna Taneja, Software Engineer, and Milind Tambe, Principal Scientist, Google Research, India Research Lab 
The widespread availability of mobile phones has enabled non-profits to deliver critical health information to their beneficiaries in a timely manner. While advanced applications on smartphones allow for richer multimedia content and two-way communication between beneficiaries and health coaches, simpler text and voice messaging services can be effective in disseminating information to large communities, particularly those that are underserved with limited access to information and smartphones. ARMMAN1, one non-profit doing just this, is based in India with the mission of improving maternal and child health outcomes in underserved communities. 
    


Overview of ARMMAN

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning for Budget Constrained Recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6cbc5263a32a</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/reinforcement-learning-for-budget-constrained-recommendations-6cbc5263a32a?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Ehtsham Elahi
with James McInerney, Nathan Kallus, Dario Garcia Garcia and Justin Basilico]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS Support App in Slack to Manage Support Cases]]></title>
        <id>7987abd39e83187889bce5fb0aa7f7f73557375e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-support-app-in-slack-to-manage-support-cases/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatOps speeds up software development and operations by enabling DevOps teams to use chat clients and chatbots to communicate and run tasks. DevOps engineers have increasingly moved their monitoring, system management, continuous integration (CI), and continuous delivery (CD) workflows to chat applications in order to streamline activities in a single place and enable better collaboration […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is available now!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/24/spring-batch-5-0-0-m5-is-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/24/spring-batch-5-0-0-m5-is-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M5 is now available from our milestone repository. The main theme of this milestone is improving testing support in Spring Batch. This post walks through the major changes in this area as well as other changes introduced in this milestone release. For the complete list of changes, see the release notes.
Test utilities configuration updates

Up to version 4.3, the JobLauncherTestUtils used to autowire the job under test with the goal of facilitating the test setup. But what if multiple jobs are defined in the test context? And what if no Job beans are defined at all? So while this autowiring was convenient for most cases, it turned out to cause several issues in the aforementioned situations. In this release, and based on community feedback,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps and CI/CD with automation controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/devops-and-ci/cd-with-automation-controller</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/devops-and-ci/cd-with-automation-controller"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog shares practical examples of using Ansible Automation Platform to accelerate your DevOps journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: PodSecurityPolicy: The Historical Context]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/podsecuritypolicy-the-historical-context/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/podsecuritypolicy-the-historical-context/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mahé Tardy (Quarkslab)
The PodSecurityPolicy (PSP) admission controller has been removed, as of
Kubernetes v1.25. Its deprecation was announced and detailed in the blog post
PodSecurityPolicy Deprecation: Past, Present, and Future,
published for the Kubernetes v1.21 release.
This article aims to provide historical context on the birth and evolution of
PSP, explain why the feature never made it to stable, and show why it was
removed and replaced by Pod Security admission control.
PodSecurityPolicy, like other specialized admission control plugins, provided
fine-grained permissions on specific fields concerning the pod security settings
as a built-in policy API. It acknowledged that cluster administrators and
cluster users are usually not the same people, and that creating workloads …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UVQ: Measuring YouTube's Perceptual Video Quality]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/uvq-measuring-youtubes-perceptual-video.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/uvq-measuring-youtubes-perceptual-video.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T17:02:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yilin Wang, Staff Software Engineer, YouTube and Feng Yang, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research 
Online video sharing platforms, like YouTube, need to understand perceptual video quality (i.e., a user's subjective perception of video quality) in order to better optimize and improve user experience. Video quality assessment (VQA) attempts to build a bridge between video signals and perceptual quality by using objective mathematical models to approximate the subjective opinions of users. Traditional video quality metrics, like peak signal-to-noise ratio (PSNR) and Video Multi-Method Assessment Fusion (VMAF), are reference-based and focus on the relative difference between the target and reference videos. Such metrics, which work best on professionally generated content …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why hyperautomation can help developers grow]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=60513</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/08/why-hyperautomation-can-help-developers-grow/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning skills to harness new technologies increases your employability and gives you a leg up to secure a better job and higher salary.
The post Why hyperautomation can help developers grow appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 23rd, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/23/this-week-in-spring-august-23rd-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/23/this-week-in-spring-august-23rd-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! We’ve got a ton to cover, so let’s dive right into it!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Flowable founder Joram Barrez on a Bootiful Podcast on workflow, business process management, and more

  
Building IoT Applications Using Fauna and Spring

  
Cosmos DB for Spring Developers, Part I: Using Cosmos DB as a SQL Database

  
How to Build Web Servers with Paketo Buildpacks - Paketo Buildpacks

  
Introducing Experimental Spring Support for Apache Pulsar

  
Propagating Exceptions With OpenFeign and Spring

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M1 available now

  
Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M1 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.6.11 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.7.3 available now

  
Spring Boot Actuator

  
Spring Boot Native image builds with 22.2.0 are failing · Issue #176 paketo-buildpacks/native-image - this is in regards to an issue related to Buildpacks that just appeared last week. There’s a workaround that’s been recently deployed.

  
Spring Boot and Spring Security with JWT including Access and Refresh Tokens 🔑

  
Spring JDBC Batch Inserts

  
Spring Security 5.8.0-M2 is released

  
Spring Shell 2.1.1 is now available

  
Spring for GraphQL with Querydsl.

  
Testcontainers and Spring Boot for local development and integration testing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.25: Combiner]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/kubernetes-v1-25-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/kubernetes-v1-25-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes 1.25 Release Team
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.25!
This release includes a total of 40 enhancements. Fifteen of those enhancements are entering Alpha, ten are graduating to Beta, and thirteen are graduating to Stable. We also have two features being deprecated or removed.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes 1.25: Combiner
The theme for Kubernetes v1.25 is Combiner.
The Kubernetes project itself is made up of many, many individual components that, when combined, take the form of the project you see today. It is also built and maintained by many individuals, all of them with different skills, experiences, histories, and interests, who join forces not just as the release team but as the many SIGs that support the project and the community year-round.
With this rel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 22, 2022]]></title>
        <id>cd57561ca684dacfdb5a73e1204fff6a6bfa1214</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-22-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T18:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I’m back from my summer holidays and ready to get up to date with the latest AWS news from last week! Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Cloud Skills Shortage Is Affecting Multi-Cloud Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-a-cloud-skills-shortage-is-affecting-multi-cloud-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-a-cloud-skills-shortage-is-affecting-multi-cloud-adoption"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 State of Cloud Strategy survey reveals that IT organizations are turning to platform teams and automated tools to bridge a growing skills shortage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 10th Anniversary, Amazon S3 Glacier – A Decade of Cold Storage in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>2d8c2df87af9a66f78fc7d7776db8517bedf54f4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-10th-anniversary-amazon-s3-glacier-a-decade-of-cold-storage-in-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T15:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten years ago, on August 20, 2012, AWS announced the general availability of Amazon Glacier, secure, reliable, and extremely low-cost storage designed for data archiving and backup. At the time, I was working as an AWS customer and it felt like an April Fools’ joke, offering long-term, secure, and durable cloud storage that allowed me […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing a VMware Template Lifecycle with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/managing-a-vmware-template-lifecycle-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/managing-a-vmware-template-lifecycle-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we manage a large number of virtual machines (VMs), we want to reduce the differences between them and create a standard template. By using a standard template, it becomes easier to manage and propagate the same operation on the different nodes. When using VMware vSphere, it is a common practice to share a standardized VM template and use it to create new VMs. This template is often called a golden image. Its creation involves a series of steps that can be automated with Ansible. In this blog, we will see how one can create and use a new golden image.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gonéri Le Bouder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad Service Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-service-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-service-discovery"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad’s addition of native service discovery offers a new option for simple service registration, plus integration with Consul for more complex service mesh use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/22/sig-storage-spotlight/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/22/sig-storage-spotlight/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS)
Since the very beginning of Kubernetes, the topic of persistent data and how to address the requirement of stateful applications has been an important topic. Support for stateless deployments was natural, present from the start, and garnered attention, becoming very well-known. Work on better support for stateful applications was also present from early on, with each release increasing the scope of what could be run on Kubernetes.
Message queues, databases, clustered filesystems: these are some examples of the solutions that have different storage requirements and that are, today, increasingly deployed in Kubernetes. Dealing with ephemeral and persistent storage, local or remote, file or block, from many different vendors, while considering how to provide the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/19/spring-shell-2-1-1-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/19/spring-shell-2-1-1-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T13:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release and Maven Central.

Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OptFormer: Towards Universal Hyperparameter Optimization with Transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/optformer-towards-universal.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/optformer-towards-universal.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T19:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yutian Chen, Staff Research Scientist, DeepMind, and Xingyou (Richard) Song, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team 
One of the most important aspects in machine learning is hyperparameter optimization, as finding the right hyperparameters for a machine learning task can make or break a model’s performance. Internally, we regularly use Google Vizier as the default platform for hyperparameter optimization. Throughout its deployment over the last 5 years, Google Vizier has been used more than 10 million times, over a vast class of applications, including machine learning applications from vision, reinforcement learning, and language but also scientific applications such as protein discovery and hardware acceleration. As Google Vizier is able to keep track of use patterns i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.4 Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-4-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-4-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.4 introduces support for the new beta version of the Kubernetes Gateway API and HTTP path rewrites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary 0.10 Expands Credential Management and Admin UI IAM Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-10-expands-credential-management-and-admin-ui-iam-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-10-expands-credential-management-and-admin-ui-iam-workflows"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary 0.10 adds support for credential management of SSH keys and enhanced IAM workflows in the admin UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Flowable founder Joram Barrez on a Bootiful Podcast on workflow, business process management, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/a-bootiful-podcast-flowable-founder-joram-barrez-on-a-bootiful-podcast-on-workflow-business-process-management-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/a-bootiful-podcast-flowable-founder-joram-barrez-on-a-bootiful-podcast-on-workflow-business-process-management-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Flowable founder Joram Barrez (@jbarrez) about workflow, business process management (BPM), decision management, rules, and so much more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/spring-boot-2-7-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/18/spring-boot-2-7-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T07:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.3 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 48 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.11 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-boot-2-6-11-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-boot-2-6-11-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T06:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.11 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 40 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第215話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270375685435178676</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270375685435178676"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Stargazing, solutions and staycations: the Kubernetes 1.24 release interview]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/18/stargazing-solutions-and-staycations-the-kubernetes-1.24-release-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/18/stargazing-solutions-and-staycations-the-kubernetes-1.24-release-interview/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Craig Box (Google)
The Kubernetes project has participants from all around the globe. Some are friends, some are colleagues, and some are strangers. The one thing that unifies them, no matter their differences, are that they all have an interesting story. It is my pleasure to be the documentarian for the stories of the Kubernetes community in the weekly Kubernetes Podcast from Google. With every new Kubernetes release comes an interview with the release team lead, telling the story of that release, but also their own personal story.
With 1.25 around the corner, the tradition continues with a look back at the story of 1.24. That release was led by James Laverack of Jetstack. James was on the podcast in May, and while you can read his story below, if you can, please do listen to it i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrialized Workflows - Using Microsoft CAF Patterns and Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/industrialized-workflows-using-microsoft-caf-patterns-and-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/industrialized-workflows-using-microsoft-caf-patterns-and-terraform"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how even non-technical operators can use HashiCorp Terraform Cloud to deploy Azure resources based on Microsoft's Cloud Adoption Framework (CAF) templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Trusted Advisor – New Priority Capability]]></title>
        <id>b0c7ecebd1612af876be081dc850f50a0a0ebf98</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-trusted-advisor-new-priority-capability/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T17:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Trusted Advisor is a service that continuously analyzes your AWS accounts and provides recommendations to help you to follow AWS best practices and AWS Well-Architected guidelines. Trusted Advisor implements a series of checks. These checks identify ways to optimize your AWS infrastructure, improve security and performance, reduce costs, and monitor service quotas. Today, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Survey Shows Broad Cloud Waste — HashiCorp Terraform Can Help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-survey-shows-broad-cloud-waste-hashicorp-terraform-can-help</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-survey-shows-broad-cloud-waste-hashicorp-terraform-can-help"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to our 2022 State of Cloud Strategy Survey, 94% of organizations have avoidable cloud spending. See where the money’s going and how Terraform can help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating automation execution environments using ansible-builder and Shipwright]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-automation-execution-environments-using-ansible-builder-and-shipwright</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/creating-automation-execution-environments-using-ansible-builder-and-shipwright"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reproducibility and consistency are two key traits that are the driving forces behind the popularity of containers. Consistency is also a principle found within Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. With only a few lines of YAML-formatted manifests, thousands of instances can be set up and configured uniformly. While the management of target instances is simple, it is the control node, or where the Ansible execution is initiated, that can  be the most challenging aspect. As Ansible is written in Python, does the machine have the correct version of Python installed?  Are the necessary Python modules installed? Are there any operating system dependencies needed? The list goes on and on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ablock@redhat.com (Andrew Block)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-1-0-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-1-0-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 1.0.0-M1.



You can download it from repo.spring.io milestone repository by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:1.0.0-M1'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-0-4-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/17/spring-authorization-server-0-4-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0-M1.



You can download it from repo.spring.io milestone repository by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.4.0-M1'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Grillo Built a Low-Cost Earthquake Early Warning System on AWS]]></title>
        <id>13b116ed4d0b61d043f96e454e4cc6a616f9f183</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-grillo-built-a-low-cost-earthquake-early-warning-system-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T18:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is estimated that 50 percent of the injuries caused when a high magnitude earthquake affects an area are because of falls or falling hazards. This means that most of these injuries could have been prevented if the population had a few seconds of warning to take cover. Grillo, a social impact enterprise focused on seismology, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.8.0-M2 is released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/spring-security-5-8-0-m2-is-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/spring-security-5-8-0-m2-is-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.8.0-M2 is available now.



This release includes dependency upgrades, bug fixes, and enhancements. Here are a few noteworthy changes:





Hash-based Content-Security-Policy for SAML post pages



Customization of redirect strategy





See the 5.8.0-M2 release notes for more details.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards Helpful Robots: Grounding Language in Robotic Affordances]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/towards-helpful-robots-grounding.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/08/towards-helpful-robots-grounding.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T14:02:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brian Ichter and Karol Hausman, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Over the last several years, we have seen significant progress in applying machine learning to robotics. However, robotic systems today are capable of executing only very short, hard-coded commands, such as “Pick up an apple,” because they tend to perform best with clear tasks and rewards. They struggle with learning to perform long-horizon tasks and reasoning about abstract goals, such as a user prompt like “I just worked out, can you get me a healthy snack?” 
Meanwhile, recent progress in training language models (LMs) has led to systems that can perform a wide range of language understanding and generation tasks with impressive results. However, these language models are inherently not grounded i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Experimental Spring Support for Apache Pulsar]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/introducing-experimental-spring-support-for-apache-pulsar</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/introducing-experimental-spring-support-for-apache-pulsar"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce that we are incubating a new experimental Spring project for Apache Pulsar. This project aims to provide Spring-friendly APIs, building blocks, and programming models for writing Java applications that interact with Apache Pulsar. 

Apache Pulsar is a popular messaging system with a growing ecosystem of developers in the enterprise messaging and streaming space. Here are some main features and advantages of using Apache Pulsar for messaging-based software applications:


  
Apache Pulsar provides both the traditional queuing semantics of RabbitMQ, ActiveMQ, and others and the log-based structure of Apache Kafka through various subscription models.

  
The broker in Apache Pulsar is stateless, and the storage is not part of the broker. Instead, it uses another A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 16th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/this-week-in-spring-august-16th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/08/16/this-week-in-spring-august-16th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another wonder-filled installment of This Week in Spring! It’s been a week! Sometimes I can scarcely believe it myself. And can you believe it’s August 16th already?? My daughter’s starting school this week! We’re in the northern hemisphere, and Summer break is already over and done with for her. There’s still another month and some change of summer, officially, though. So, I hope you all are doing whatever you can to maximize your enjoyment of it before the darker and colder months arrive. 

Twitter helps me pass the time. I’ve been working on some code and wanted to use Twitter’s OAuth 2 and PKCE support in the application but couldn’t quite make it work. So I pinged my pal (everybody’s pal, really!) and Spring Security lead Rob Winch (@rob_winch) for some cl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Decade of Ever-Increasing Provisioned IOPS for Amazon EBS]]></title>
        <id>62b434c84905bf2a24ca8943b82a7e2149abf628</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/a-decade-of-ever-increasing-provisioned-iops-for-amazon-ebs/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T22:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress is often best appreciated in retrospect. It is often the case that a steady stream of incremental improvements over a long period of time ultimately adds up to a significant level of change. Today, ten years after we first launched the Provisioned IOPS feature for Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS), I strongly believe that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – HTTP/3 Support for Amazon CloudFront]]></title>
        <id>a4970c24e76d5efa333710d9e50da964387520ea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-http-3-support-for-amazon-cloudfront/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T22:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudFront is a content delivery network (CDN) service, a network of interconnected servers that is geographically closer to the users and reaches their computers much faster. Amazon CloudFront reduces latency by delivering data through 410+ globally dispersed Points of Presence (PoPs) with automated network mapping and intelligent routing. With Amazon CloudFront, content, API requests […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – August 15, 2022]]></title>
        <id>ec58e447970e428041f23a062ac4b1e7cf8bc433</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-august-15-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love the AWS Twitch channel for watching interesting online live shows such as AWS On Air, Containers from the Couch, and Serverless Office Hours. Last week, AWS Storage Day 2022 was hosted virtually on the AWS Twitch channel and covered recent announcements and insights that address customers’ needs to reduce and optimize storage costs and build data resiliency […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.13 Introduces Cluster Peering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-introduces-cluster-peering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-introduces-cluster-peering"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This release enhances a number of features in Consul while adding such new features as a Consul on Kubernetes CNI plugin and a beta version of cluster peering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Meet Our Contributors - APAC (China region)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/15/meet-our-contributors-china-ep-03/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/15/meet-our-contributors-china-ep-03/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors & Interviewers: Avinesh Tripathi, Debabrata Panigrahi, Jayesh Srivastava, Priyanka Saggu, Purneswar Prasad, Vedant Kakde
Hello, everyone 👋
Welcome back to the third edition of the "Meet Our Contributors" blog post series for APAC.
This post features four outstanding contributors from China, who have played diverse leadership and community roles in the upstream Kubernetes project.
So, without further ado, let's get straight to the article.
Andy Zhang
Andy Zhang currently works for Microsoft China at the Shanghai site. His main focus is on Kubernetes storage drivers. Andy started contributing to Kubernetes about 5 years ago.
He states that as he is working in Azure Kubernetes Service team and spends most of his time contributing to the Kubernetes community project. Now he is the mai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>