<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-03-29T01:38:59.185Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-03-29T01:38:59.185Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“New Boards Hub” Public Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63721</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T19:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December we posted about the “New Boards Hub” being available for everyone as an opt-in experience. We got a lot of feedback from our users. You let us know the experience was far from ready. As a result, we buckled down and spent the last 3 months fixing bugs (over 300) and tightening it up.
The post “New Boards Hub” Public Preview appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 28, 2022]]></title>
        <id>36fca099d51da2eb5217d3b6cd96385675ea994c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-28-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T19:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Welcome to another round up of the most significant AWS launches from the previous week. Among the most relevant news, we have improvements done in AWS Lambda, a new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to secure your end-to-end supply chain on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-28-how-to-secure-your-end-to-end-supply-chain-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-28-how-to-secure-your-end-to-end-supply-chain-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securing your projects is no easy task, but end-to-end supply chain security is more top of mind than ever. We&#8217;ve seen bad actors expand their focus to taking over user accounts, commonly used dependencies, and also build systems. Defending against these attacks is hard, because there&#8217;s no one thing you can do to protect your [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the newest features in the Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for ServiceNow ITSM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-the-newest-features-in-the-red-hat-ansible-certified-content-collection-for-servicenow-itsm</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-the-newest-features-in-the-red-hat-ansible-certified-content-collection-for-servicenow-itsm"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for ServiceNow helps you create automated workflows targeting IT service management (ITSM) tasks faster while establishing and maintaining a single source of truth in the ServiceNow configuration management database (CMDB). In this blog, I’ll share the latest features we’ve added to the Collection, and you can find additional resources about existing features at the end of this blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java 18 Features Support]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=236318</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/03/java-18-features-support/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T15:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java 18 has now been released, and starting from version 2022.1, IntelliJ IDEA offers support for it. Support for code snippets The @snippet tag for JavaDoc’s Standard Doclet was introduced in JDK 18 to simplify the inclusion of example source code in API documentation. Even without an explicit wrapper, the snippet fragment is still recognized […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Klisho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HashiCorp Women Leaders Got Into Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-women-leaders-got-into-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-women-leaders-got-into-tech"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four women leaders at HashiCorp talk about their journey to a career in tech and offer lessons, inspiration, and advice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.1 EAP #7]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=236247</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/03/phpstorm-2022-1-eap-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T14:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.1 EAP build #7 is now available. To catch up on all the new features coming to PhpStorm 2022.1, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the latest EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. You can also manually […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An update on Java 17+ adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/28/an-update-on-java-17-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/28/an-update-on-java-17-adoption"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T14:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a follow-up to my blog post from last year’s SpringOne, it is time for an update on our Java 17+ baseline efforts!

We established the new baseline on our main branches, with a few milestones out already. The feedback has been very positive, not only in terms of framework improvements but also in terms of the motivation for a Java upgrade at the application level. Of course, it does not end with JDK 17 LTS: JDK 18 is an immediate option already, JDK 19 will be the current release when we go final later this year, with JDK 20 to be in early access by then - and JDK 21 LTS on the horizon already…

On a related note, the recent JRebel 2022 Java Developer Productivity Report included some interesting numbers on JDK 17: 62% of the participants indicated a plan for a JDK 17 upgrade within t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Domain Name for Camunda Artifactory]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=46342</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/a-new-domain-name-for-camunda-artifactory/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make sure to switch to the new domain between April 1 - Sept. 30, 2022, before the old URLs will be shut down. 
The post A New Domain Name for Camunda Artifactory appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaima Mansouri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Essentials with Rider]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=234306</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/03/28/github-essentials-with-rider/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T12:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub is an online hosting service for the Git version control system. It surfaces many features of Git, plus many of its own, including some social coding features. In this blog post, we’ll take a look at the essentials of using GitHub in Rider. Get to know GitHub Before we continue, it’s important to know […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-calibrating]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41688</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687915014/0/sethsblog~Recalibrating/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T08:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When an entrepreneur gets funded, it’s often difficult for them to start spending money on assets–the old limits fade slowly. What used to be smart is now dumb. What used to too risky is now the safe thing to do. When someone gets older or is injured, one of the dangers is that they’ll fail […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE report published for Spring Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/28/cve-report-published-for-spring-framework</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/28/cve-report-published-for-spring-framework"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Spring Framework 5.3.17 to address the following CVE report.


  
CVE-2022-22950: Spring Expression DoS Vulnerability


Please review the information in the CVE report and upgrade immediately.

Spring Boot users should upgrade to 2.5.11 or 2.6.5.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 best practices for using and troubleshooting the Reindex API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-best-practices-for-using-and-troubleshooting-the-reindex-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-best-practices-for-using-and-troubleshooting-the-reindex-api"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post you you will learn about the power of Reindex API  and how to use those to run it confidently. We will review potential errors and give you best practice tips and tricks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camilo Sierra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 best practices for using and troubleshooting the Reindex API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-best-practices-for-using-and-troubleshooting-the-reindex-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-best-practices-for-using-and-troubleshooting-the-reindex-api"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
When using Elasticsearch you may want to move data from one index to another, or even from one Elasticsearch cluster to another Elasticsearch cluster. There are multiple variations and features that could be used, and the Reindex API is one of them.
In this blog post, I will be discussing the reindex API, how to know if the API works, what can cause potential failures, and how to troubleshoot.
By the end of this blog post, you will understand the options the Reindex API has and how to run it confidently.
The reindex API is one of the most useful APIs across multiple use cases:

Transferring data between clusters (Reindex from a remote cluster)
Re-define, change, and/or update mappings
Process and index through ingestion pipelines
Clearing deleted documents to reclaim storage space
Split …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camilo Sierra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spacecraft Debris Odds Ratio]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2599/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2599/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/spacecraft_debris_odds_ratio.png" title="You say this daily walk will reduce my risk of death from cardiovascular disease by 30%, but also increase my risk of death by bear attack by 300%? That's a 280% increased! I'm not a sucker; I'm staying inside." alt="You say this daily walk will reduce my risk of death from cardiovascular disease by 30%, but also increase my risk of death by bear attack by 300%? That's a 280% increased! I'm not a sucker; I'm staying inside." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speeding up for the red light]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41683</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687775406/0/sethsblog~Speeding-up-for-the-red-light/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-27T08:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad drivers do this often, everywhere I’ve ever been in the world. Instead of gracefully and safely slowing for a light they know will be red by the time they get there, or even a stop sign, they hit the gas and then slam the brakes. One big reason is that the certainty of on-then-off […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expertise vs Attitude]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40748</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687666300/0/sethsblog~Expertise-vs-Attitude/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-26T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The typical online job site lists millions of jobs. And just about every one of them is a cry for expertise. From the title to the requirements, companies hire for expertise. Logic helps us understand that only one out of ten people are in the top 10% when it comes to expertise. And that means […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock all the GitHub secrets within .Tech Domains newest experience: Break The Code 2!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-25-unlock-github-secrets-next-techs-break-the-code-2/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-25-unlock-github-secrets-next-techs-break-the-code-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T18:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Education is fired up for the return of .Tech Domains developer community competition: Break The Code 2. We've hacked in some new enigmas, cheat codes, and easter eggs for digital sleuths to uncover!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: The One Where You Completely Delete a Process Definition]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=46316</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/qa-the-one-where-you-completely-delete-a-process-definition/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a process definition cluttering up your deployment? Learn how to delete it once you no longer want to run it anymore. 
The post Q&A: The One Where You Completely Delete a Process Definition appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1 Beta Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=235809</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/03/webstorm-2022-1-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T12:51:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1 has reached the Beta milestone! You can upgrade to the latest build using the Toolbox App or our website. To catch up on what has already been implemented, check out our previous EAP blog posts. DOWNLOAD WEBSTORM 2022.1 BETA We’d like to thank everyone who has tried the EAP builds and shared their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Ryabukha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where do symbols live?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42540</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687550494/0/sethsblog~Where-do-symbols-live/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T09:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the original Nike swoosh, on a sheet of paper in a filing cabinet somewhere, disappeared, what would happen to the value of Nike? Or to the way you feel about your sneakers? If the negative of a famous photo is burned in a fire, or a painting is stolen from a museum, what happens […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Event streaming guru Jan Svoboda on Apache Kafka Design Patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/a-bootiful-podcast-event-streaming-guru-jan-svoboda-on-apache-kafka-design-patterns</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/a-bootiful-podcast-event-streaming-guru-jan-svoboda-on-apache-kafka-design-patterns"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to event streaming guru at Confluent, the company behind Apache Kafka, Jan Svoboda about Apache Kafka design patterns. 


  
Kafka summit in London Europe end of April 2022 Kafka Summit London 2022 | April 25-26 | London, UK

  
the Confluent Developer Education Portal: Your Apache Kafka® Journey begins here

  
check out the upcoming Kafka Summit London event April 25-26, 2022]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-3-0-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-3-0-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-M2 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 50 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Reinstated Support for EhCache 3

  
Reinstated Support for H2 Console

  
Improved @ConstructorBinding Detection


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0-M3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-7-0-m3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-7-0-m3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0-M3 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes over 90 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Support for generating Docker images with Podman

  
Improved SanitizingFunction support

  
Spring GraphQL 1.0.0-M6 support, including the new GraphQL client


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graphic Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2598/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2598/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/graphic_designers.png" title="They might make it past that first line of defense. For the second, you'll need some picture frames, a level, and a protractor that can do increments of less than a degree." alt="They might make it past that first line of defense. For the second, you'll need some picture frames, a level, and a protractor that can do increments of less than a degree." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.1 EAP6: CMake Presets, Improved CMake Scripts Formatting, and Other Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=235750</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/03/clion-2022-1-eap6-cmake-presets-and-formatting/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T22:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CLion 2022.1 EAP build, 221.5080.52, is now available from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package (if you are using Ubuntu). Please note that if you are on macOS, there is a separate build for Apple Silicon (M1 chip). Those of you already using the EAP5 build can apply […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda Now Supports Up to 10 GB Ephemeral Storage]]></title>
        <id>57c25c20e6d01488a25def63e79d1c56dd2638df</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-lambda-now-supports-up-to-10-gb-ephemeral-storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T20:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless applications are event-driven, using ephemeral compute functions ranging from web APIs, mobile backends, and streaming analytics to data processing stages in machine learning (ML) and high-performance applications. While AWS Lambda includes a 512 MB temporary file system (/tmp) for your code, this is an ephemeral scratch resource not intended for durable storage such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Signs of Disease from External Images of the Eye]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/detecting-signs-of-disease-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/detecting-signs-of-disease-from.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Boris Babenko, Software Engineer and Naama Hammel, Clinical Research Scientist, Google Health 
Three years ago we wrote about our work on predicting a number of cardiovascular risk factors from fundus photos (i.e., photos of the back of the eye)1 using deep learning. That such risk factors could be extracted from fundus photos was a novel discovery and thus a surprising outcome to clinicians and laypersons alike. Since then, we and other researchers have discovered additional novel biomarkers from fundus photos, such as markers for chronic kidney disease and diabetes, and hemoglobin levels to detect anemia.  
A unifying goal of work like this is to develop new disease detection or monitoring approaches that are less invasive, more accurate, cheaper and more readily available. How…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Plugin for WebStorm – Tutorial for JavaScript Developers, Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=232390</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/03/building-a-plugin-for-webstorm-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 and Part 2 of this series, we discussed some of the basics of WebStorm plugin development. This time we’ll see how you can create a more complex integration for a web framework. Let’s build an advanced integration for Stimulus! This part of the tutorial will focus more on explaining the key concepts […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrey Starovoyt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AzureRM 3.0 Brings Enhanced Azure Function Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-azurerm-3-0-brings-enhanced-azure-function-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-azurerm-3-0-brings-enhanced-azure-function-support"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureRM 3.0 brings significant parity between the Azure provider for Terraform and Azure services currently available. Review the breaking changes as you prepare to upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-6-5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-6-5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T15:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.5 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 66 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.1 Goes Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=235203</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/03/24/goland-2022-1-goes-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T14:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.1 has now reached Beta. We’ve stopped adding new features and are concentrating on fixing bugs and getting GoLand ready for the major release in the middle of April. This is the last build in our EAP cycle that doesn’t require a license.  You can get the Beta build via the Toolbox App, download […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.11 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-5-11-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-5-11-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T13:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.11 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 56 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 Goes Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=235006</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/03/intellij-idea-2022-1-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T13:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Beta version of IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 is now available. You can download the latest build from our website, from the free Toolbox App, or by using snaps for Ubuntu. IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 Beta includes features and improvements that were covered in our recent blog posts under the IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 tag. Here are some […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.2.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-authorization-server-0-2-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-authorization-server-0-2-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.2.3.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




compile 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.2.3'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the sample to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues |  ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Aren’t There Legacy App Stores?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=46225</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/why-arent-there-legacy-app-stores/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover what we're doing to provide more options for enterprises to connect their legacy apps to other components of their modern IT stack.
The post Why Aren’t There Legacy App Stores? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The power of TK]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41663</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687408064/0/sethsblog~The-power-of-TK/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T09:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The origin of the editor’s mark “TK” is murky. It’s what you write when there’s a fact or addition you’re waiting on. Instead of stopping everything, simply type “TK” and you know you can come back and fix it later. The modern purpose of TK is that there are few words in English that contain […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benefits and best practices for migrating workloads to Elastic Cloud on AWS, Google Cloud, or Microsoft Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/benefits-and-best-practices-for-migrating-workloads-to-elastic-cloud-on-aws-google-cloud-or-microsoft-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/benefits-and-best-practices-for-migrating-workloads-to-elastic-cloud-on-aws-google-cloud-or-microsoft-azure"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choose a migration path to smoothly transition your existing Elastic workloads to Elastic Cloud to realize a faster time to value and lower your TCO. Get started quickly with the cloud provider of your choice and leverage migration resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicole Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Tanisha L. Turner on breaking the bias for women in tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-someone-like-me-tanisha-l-turner-on-breaking-the-bias-for-women-in-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-someone-like-me-tanisha-l-turner-on-breaking-the-bias-for-women-in-tech"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tanisha L. Turner is a black woman in tech, cybersecurity to be exact, and it’s her goal to break the bias and encourage other women and girls to consider a career in the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benefits and best practices for migrating workloads to Elastic Cloud on AWS, Google Cloud, or Microsoft Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/benefits-and-best-practices-for-migrating-workloads-to-elastic-cloud-on-aws-google-cloud-or-microsoft-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/benefits-and-best-practices-for-migrating-workloads-to-elastic-cloud-on-aws-google-cloud-or-microsoft-azure"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Migrating to Elastic Cloud gives organizations the chance to focus on core business priorities to accelerate results that matter — while maintenance and upkeep is managed for you.
Take advantage of the scalability and cost savings features of Elastic Cloud with simplified options for the migration of your Elastic self-managed workloads to the provider of your choice — Amazon Web Services (AWS), Google Cloud, or Microsoft Azure. Realize a faster time to value by leveraging the latest integrations so you can quickly capture, store, search, and analyze your data. Let’s review the benefits of Elastic Cloud, how to spin up your Elastic Cloud deployment, and determine your best migration path. 
Lower your TCO and save time while keeping your data secure
Reduce operational overhead, automatical…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicole Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Tanisha L. Turner on breaking the bias for women in tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-someone-like-me-tanisha-l-turner-on-breaking-the-bias-for-women-in-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-someone-like-me-tanisha-l-turner-on-breaking-the-bias-for-women-in-tech"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Tanisha L. Turner didn’t set out to create a career in technology, or more specifically, cybersecurity. She wanted to go to medical school to become a cardiologist and was computer programming as a hobby. With support from her then boyfriend, now husband, she turned her hobby into an exceptional career.

“I just thought it was fun,” Turner, now a Senior QA Engineer at Elastic, says. 

She eagerly completed a few computer science courses and then went a step further and pursued cybersecurity. She was already encrypting data in Linux in her spare time, she says.

Turner has since been in the cybersecurity world for more than 10 years, and with Elastic for four. And recently, she was featured among a global list of women in cybersecurity you need to know.

When she is not busy helping to pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0 M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/spring-batch-5-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/spring-batch-5-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T22:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M2 is now available from our milestone repository.

This second milestone comes with two major features:


  
Introduction of the new Observation API from Micrometer 2.0 which gives you both metrics and tracing for your batch jobs!

  
Addition of SAP HANA as a supported database for the job repository


Moreover, this release comes with a number of enhancements and dependencies updates. For more details about all the changes, please check the change log.

I would like to thank all contributors who had a role in this release! As we continue our work on Spring Batch 5, we look forward to your feedback on this second milestone!

Spring Batch Home|Source on Github|Reference documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An update on recent service disruptions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-23-an-update-on-recent-service-disruptions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-23-an-update-on-recent-service-disruptions/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T20:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few weeks, we have experienced multiple incidents due to the health of our database. We wanted to share what we know about these incidents while our team continues to address them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-generated Summaries in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/auto-generated-summaries-in-google-docs.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/auto-generated-summaries-in-google-docs.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mohammad Saleh, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team and Anjuli Kannan, Software Engineer, Google Docs  
For many of us, it can be challenging to keep up with the volume of documents that arrive in our inboxes every day: reports, reviews, briefs, policies and the list goes on. When a new document is received, readers often wish it included a brief summary of the main points in order to effectively prioritize it. However, composing a document summary can be cognitively challenging and time-consuming, especially when a document writer is starting from scratch. 
 To help with this, we recently announced that Google Docs now automatically generates suggestions to aid document writers in creating content summaries, when they are available. Today we describe how this was enab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Native Images with GraalVM and Spring Native on Apple's M1 Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/building-native-images-with-graalvm-and-spring-native-on-apple-s-m1-architecture</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/building-native-images-with-graalvm-and-spring-native-on-apple-s-m1-architecture"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It finally happened! They did it! They did it just in time for me to get on the road and start building applications on the road with my shiny new laptop, too! JOY!! Oracle and the GraalVM team released GraalVM and the GraalVM native image capability for Apple M1! I’ve been waiting for this day for so, so, so long! I bought the first Apple M1 the day of the announcement way back in 2020 (does anybody remember that far back? That was, meteorologically speaking, the early pandemic period). 

Apple’s M1 devices are insanely fast, energy-efficient beasts of machines that run circles around all but the beefiest and latest-and-greatest Intel/NVidia configurations while also consuming a pittance of the power that other configuration does. In short, I’m a big fan. But the move to this new archite…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: secure self-hosted runners by limiting them to specific workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-23-github-actions-secure-self-hosted-runners-specific-workflows/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-23-github-actions-secure-self-hosted-runners-specific-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T16:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now enforce consistent usage of self-hosted runner groups across your organization and enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.10 Adds Login MFA, PKI to Use HSMs, Usage Metrics, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-10</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-10"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.10 improves Vault’s core workflows and makes key features production-ready to better serve your use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第206話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496829058927</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496829058927"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.1 EAP 3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=235156</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/03/23/datagrip-2022-1-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T13:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! A new EAP build for DataGrip 2022.1 is now available. Let’s see what’s new: New version of Modify Table We are slightly reworking the Modify Table window. The new version will have a fully generated UI based on introspective properties, which will allow it to have a variety of database-specific parameters. For now we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maksim Sobolevskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Level Set at the Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/lets-level-set-at-the-edge</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/lets-level-set-at-the-edge"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
 
Typically when people hear the word edge, everyone gets a little apprehensive of what that means. So Josh, Andy, Martin and Chad got together to collaborate on what that means from their collective experiences across multiple industries. In this blog we will cover what the difference is between the near edge and far edge, as well as give some examples of what we have seen in these environments across multiple industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chad Ferman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Microsoft Azure: Optimize performance and cost with new virtual machine types on Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-microsoft-azure:-optimize-performance-and-cost-with-new-virtual-machine-types-on-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-microsoft-azure:-optimize-performance-and-cost-with-new-virtual-machine-types-on-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take advantage of expanded support for Microsoft Azure Virtual Machine types on Elastic Cloud. Optimize performance and cost based on your custom use cases with these additional combinations of compute, memory, and disk configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuvraj Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Microsoft Azure: Optimize performance and cost with new virtual machine types on Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-microsoft-azure:-optimize-performance-and-cost-with-new-virtual-machine-types-on-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-microsoft-azure:-optimize-performance-and-cost-with-new-virtual-machine-types-on-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,Many organizations are looking for ways to improve price-performance across their use cases. That is why we are excited to announce expanded support for Microsoft Azure Virtual Machine (VM) types on Elastic Cloud. You can now select new hardware profiles backed by Edsv4, Ddv4 and Fsv2 VM series for deployments in Azure. These additional combinations of compute, memory, and disk configurations allow you to utilize hardware that best fits your custom use cases — to optimize performance and cost. https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt0c678915dd2d16c8/622f46b7638e1304348432da/azure-launch-video_(1).gif,azure-launch-video_(1).gif,
Let’s go over how you can get started with these new VMs by logging into Elastic Cloud and creating a new deployment or migrating an existin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuvraj Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The cake mix insight]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41661</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687256818/0/sethsblog~The-cake-mix-insight/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Betty Crocker (not her real name) first started selling cake mixes, all you had to do was add water. They failed. But when they changed the recipe and required users to add oil and an egg, sales went up. Because people like to feel as though they’re cooking. It made the mix an activity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Multitenant JDBC]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/spring-tips-multitenant-jdbc</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/spring-tips-multitenant-jdbc"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment we look at how to use Spring’s AbstractRoutingDataSource to build multi-tenant JDBC database code. 

code: https://github.com/spring-tips/multitenant-jdbc
speaker: Josh Long (@starbuxman)

</iframe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How auto instrumentation with the next iteration of the Elastic APM .NET Agent works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrumentation-elastic-apm-net-agent</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrumentation-elastic-apm-net-agent"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T00:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we will look at the next iteration of the Elastic APM .NET Agent and its new auto instrumentation capabilities. We will also discuss what a profiler-based agent is, and what the profiler-based version of the Elastic .NET APM Agent is capable of.
APM .NET agent profiler auto instrumentation
We're pleased to announce the first public beta release of Profiler-based auto instrumentation for our .NET APM agent. With this approach, the agent can automatically instrument .NET Framework, .NET Core and .NET applications, without requiring code changes or recompilation. A profiler-based approach uses the CLR Profiling APIs to rewrite methods of interest at runtime. This powerful capability allows the .NET APM agent to instrument and trace code that would otherwise be unfeasible. W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russ Cam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How auto instrumentation with the next iteration of the Elastic APM .NET Agent works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrumentation-elastic-apm-net-agent</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/auto-instrumentation-elastic-apm-net-agent"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T00:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This powerful capability allows the .NET APM agent to instrument and trace code that would otherwise be unfeasible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russ Cam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salary Negotiation]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2597/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2597/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/salary_negotiation.png" title="&quot;We can do 0.33 or 0.34, but our payroll software doesn't allow us to--&quot; &quot;NO DEAL.&quot;" alt="&quot;We can do 0.33 or 0.34, but our payroll software doesn't allow us to--&quot; &quot;NO DEAL.&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving your GitHub feed]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-22-improving-your-github-feed/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-22-improving-your-github-feed/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T23:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are rolling out a new beta version of GitHub’s home feed, making it easier to discover projects, developers and more across GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - March 22nd, 2022 (Java 18 Edition!)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/22/this-week-in-spring-march-22nd-2022-java-18-edition</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/22/this-week-in-spring-march-22nd-2022-java-18-edition"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! Spring time is here! Astrologically and meteorlogically, speaking, of course. I love this season. Longer days, greener grass, bluer skies, and more. Next week, my family and I are headed to Hawaii for some much-needed R&R while my daughter has a week off from school. (It’s hard to believe she might be going to college in another state in 18 short months! We need all the family vacations we can get together! T_T) 

As always, we’ve got a lot to look at today, so let’s dive right into it! 


  
First thing: Java 18 was released today! There are a ton new features, including UTF-8 by default, a simple HTTP server, a reimplementation of core reflection to use method handles, an SPI for internet resolution, an easier Jav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.0.0-M3 and 5.7.0-M3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/22/spring-security-6-0-0-m3-and-5-7-0-m3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/22/spring-security-6-0-0-m3-and-5-7-0-m3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 6.0.0-M3 and 5.7.0-M3 are available now.



This third 6.0 milestone covers build and release enhancements as well as the deprecation of WebSecurityConfigurerAdapter that was already released with 5.7.0-M2. The third 5.7 milestone covers several enhancements to SAML 2.0 and OAuth 2.0 support as well as a change to use UTF-8 by default for HTTP Basic credentials in Spring WebFlux.



For the release changes, please refer to the releases page.



Project Site | Reference | Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0 Milestone 6 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/22/spring-for-graphql-1-0-milestone-6-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/22/spring-for-graphql-1-0-milestone-6-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T18:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of everyone involved, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the sixth and final milestone of Spring for GraphQL on the way to 1.0. Our next stop is RC1 in 4 weeks, followed by the GA on May 17.
GraphQL Client

A GraphQL client is something we identified as a goal quite early on. It’s issue number 10 from 336 at present in the issue tracker, but we viewed testing support as higher priority and so the GraphQL Tester came first and has been available from the start.

The Tester did prove valuable and popular, but we knew we had to fully explore the client before 1.0 as the two are closely related but have slightly different perspectives, and we wanted to make sure they’re aligned with each other.

A second point is that the Tester has supported testing subscriptions on the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the GHES repository cache]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-22-introducing-the-ghes-repository-cache/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-22-introducing-the-ghes-repository-cache/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T17:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a GHES customer with heavy read traffic on your monorepo, check out the repository cache, especially if you have CI workloads distributed around the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elegant Cert Governance with Vault Identity and Sentinel Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/elegant-cert-governance-with-vault-identity-and-sentinel-policy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/elegant-cert-governance-with-vault-identity-and-sentinel-policy"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how using policy as code to enforce governance for certificate creation inside HashiCorp Vault reduces cost of ownership and lowers risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Goldman Sachs Built a Brand New Platform on Camunda Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=46053</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/why-goldman-sachs-built-a-brand-new-platform-on-camunda-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get the details behind Goldman Sachs' new platform to provide microservice orchestration across all of its teams and meet client demands.
The post Why Goldman Sachs Built a Brand New Platform on Camunda Cloud appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.1 EAP #6]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=234950</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/03/phpstorm-2022-1-eap-6/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T12:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.1 EAP build #6 is now available. To catch up on all the new features, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the latest EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. Or you can manually download the EAP builds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2022.1 EAP 2: What’s New?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=235041</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2022/03/dataspell-2022-1-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2022.1 EAP 2 is now available, and you can try the newly added features right away. Get the latest version using the ToolBox App by clicking Update – this will update your existing installation. You can also download the new EAP as a standalone version using this button: DOWNLOAD DATASPELL 2022.1 EAP 2 New […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nadia Antonova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Initial AOT support in Spring Framework 6.0.0-M3]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/22/initial-aot-support-in-spring-framework-6-0-0-m3</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/22/initial-aot-support-in-spring-framework-6-0-0-m3"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T12:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those of you who know the Spring Native experimental project are aware that the Spring team has been working on native image support for Spring applications since 2019. After a first beta in March 2021, we shipped an extensive revision of our Spring Native efforts in December 2021.

We’ve also announced at SpringOne last year that we intend to promote this work to Spring Framework 6.0 proper in the course of 2022. Following the release of our third milestone, this blog post walks you through what has been included already and what is coming next.
Ahead-Of-Time Processing

Processing the application context ahead of time opens many doors for optimizations. Depending on the context, we can reduce the amount of infrastructure that we ship, pre-compute certain features that you’ve declared o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okta and LAPSUS$: What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/okta-and-lapsus-what-you-need-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/okta-and-lapsus-what-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat hunt for the recent LAPSUS$ breach targeting Okta users using these simple steps with Elastic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okta and LAPSUS$: What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/okta-and-lapsus-what-you-need-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/okta-and-lapsus-what-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The LAPSUS$ group

Financially motivated adversary groups executing ransomware attacks have rightfully gotten our attention in recent years. Similar to Lulzec, there’s a new group catching attention with different motivations, targeting larger organizations. 

The LAPSUS$ group emerged onto the scene a number of months ago, targeting high-profile organizations such as Nvidia, Samsung, and Ubisoft — making various demands that in some cases, resulted in either data dumps or screenshots of internal systems shared via the group’s Telegram account. These were sometimes determined by user-voted polls within the group, suggesting that this is only the beginning of a series of attacks the group is undertaking more frequently as they gain press coverage.

Groups of this nature focus on data thef…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The lurkers]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42512</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687098102/0/sethsblog~The-lurkers/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T08:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s frustrating for anyone who leads. If everyone who says that they’re a contributor/member/supporter/fan/long-term customer showed up, huge things would happen. So we spend a lot of time hustling to get the lurkers to take action. Post again! Create more incentives! Dumb it down! Most of all, focus on creating urgency. This isn’t how progress […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Women of Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have employee resource groups aligned with a variety of shared identities that allow Elasticians to build a sense of community and belonging at work. Here, we meet Women of Elastic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​Elastic Stack 8.1.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.1.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Neirynck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Women of Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-women-of-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Employee resource groups, or as we like to call them, Elastician resource groups, have been an informal part of Elastic’s culture since 2016. They started as Slack channels that any Elastician could join.

These ERGs were formalized in 2021 to ensure that the members would have structure, budget, and ultimately, a voice based on any dimension of diversity, allyship, and advocacy. This was an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy.

Our ERGs are aligned to shared identities, interests, affinities, or allyships. The goal is to create a community of people with something in common and to encourage sharing, learning, and networking. Each has visions and goals they are working towards besides building a sense of community and belonging.
Our Core ERGs
We have se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​Elastic Stack 8.1.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 8.1.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
The 8.1.1 patch contains fixes and small enhancements for the stack. 
For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
Elastic Stack

Kibana
Elasticsearch
Beats
Logstash

Elastic Enterprise Search

Enterprise Search

Elastic Enterprise Search

APM

Elastic Security

Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Neirynck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2022.0.0-M3, 2021.2.0-M4, 2021.1.3, and 2021.0.10 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/21/spring-data-2022-0-0-m3-2021-2-0-m4-2021-1-3-and-2021-0-10-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/21/spring-data-2022-0-0-m3-2021-2-0-m4-2021-1-3-and-2021-0-10-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T23:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce Spring Data service releases 2021.1.3 and 2021.0.10.
Both releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot 2.6.5 respective 2.5.11 are going to pick up these releases in the upcoming days.

Along with the service releases, we released the next milestone 2021.2.0-M4 of the 2021.2 release train. Spring Boot 2.7.0-M3 will pick up this release soon. We have summarized the new and noteworthy changes in our 2021.2 release notes.

We have also released the next milestone 2022.0.0-M3 of the 2022.0 release train. Spring Boot 3.0.0-M2 will pick up this release. We have summarized the new and noteworthy changes in our 2022.0 release notes.

To round things off, here are the links to the individual modules,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start working on GitHub Issues faster]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-21-start-working-on-github-issues-faster/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-21-start-working-on-github-issues-faster/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T21:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now create a branch to work on an issue directly from the issue page so that it's easier to get started right away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 21, 2022]]></title>
        <id>55b35723d9259f39ac1ad27522fdece23d9b4c0f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-21-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Another week, another round up of the most significant AWS launches from the previous seven days! Among the news, we have new AWS Heroes and a cost reduction. Also, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Validate all the things: improve your security with input validation!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-21-validate-all-things-input-validation/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-21-validate-all-things-input-validation/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T17:41:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there's one habit that can make software more secure, it's probably input validation. Here's how to apply OWASP Proactive Control C5 (Validate All Inputs) to your code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in the Ansible Content Collection for Kubernetes 2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-the-ansible-content-collection-for-kubernetes-2.3</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-the-ansible-content-collection-for-kubernetes-2.3"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With increased adoption of container automation, IT organizations continue to expand their requirements when it comes to deploying and managing their Kubernetes clusters. As such, we at Red Hat continue to add new features and capabilities to meet those demands by announcing the availability of kubernetes.core version 2.3, our Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for Kubernetes and Helm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1 EAP #6]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=234760</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/03/webstorm-2022-1-eap-6/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T12:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1 EAP build #6 is now available. To catch up on all the new features, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. You can also manually download the EAP builds from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Aganezova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peak customer service and the hospitality mindset]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42499</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687001330/0/sethsblog~Peak-customer-service-and-the-hospitality-mindset/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T08:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is cheaper better? Is profit the only thing to be maximized? For its first decade, Federal Express embraced customer service as a marketing tool. They were competing with the postal service, but more than that, they were trying hard to create a habit that turned 25 cent deliveries into $20 deliveries, particularly among businesses. They […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security Research Roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-research-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-research-roundup"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security Intelligence and Analytics researches and investigates threat actors, malware, campaigns or a specific intrusion. We’ll highlight recent research about Log4j, BLISTER, Cobalt Strike, and Operation Bleeding Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security Research Roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-research-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-security-research-roundup"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The job of researching the latest vulnerabilities, campaigns, attack patterns, and threat actors is never complete. The Elastic Security Intelligence and Analytics team’s charter is to democratize access to knowledge and capabilities. We believe doing so is the key to changing the threat landscape and we publish this information to educate Elastic customers and the larger security community. 

Our security team researches and publishes information about malware, threat actors, campaigns, attack patterns, and specific vulnerabilities. Here’s a roundup of our latest findings and how to protect your organization.
Log4j vulnerability research
Quickly after the Log4j vulnerability was released, Elastic provided guidance on how to find the Log4Shell vulnerability using the Elastic Security and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxies]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2596/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2596/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/galaxies.png" title="I know it seems overwhelming, but don't worry; I'm sure most of them have only a few stars, and probably no planets." alt="I know it seems overwhelming, but don't worry; I'm sure most of them have only a few stars, and probably no planets." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The things you can’t see]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40735</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/686901838/0/sethsblog~The-things-you-cant-see/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-20T08:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you remember all the elements you didn’t used to notice? It might be the way you see typography now, or the tuning of an orchestra. Or the alignment in the mouldings of a house you’re inspecting or the way an engine sounds… (or whether you put a ‘u’ in moulding) Expertise is about learning […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Question authority]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=32256</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/686802770/0/sethsblog~Question-authority/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-19T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lock-in persists. That’s why it’s so valued by monopolists, tyrants and cults. The ability to speak up always creates inefficiency. It’s easier to just shut up and drive. Or be driven. But the ability to speak up is a self-cleaning algorithm. Our freedom to move on, to criticize and to suggest creates the conditions for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · February 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-17-release-radar-feb-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-17-release-radar-feb-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T23:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our community has shipped lots of open source project updates in the last month. Here's a few of our staff picks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Elastic's Felix Barnsteiner on APM for Spring Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/17/a-bootiful-podcast-elastic-s-felix-barnsteiner-on-apm-for-spring-developers</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/17/a-bootiful-podcast-elastic-s-felix-barnsteiner-on-apm-for-spring-developers"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Elastic’s Felix Barnsteiner about APM for Spring developers. 


  
make log onboarding easier. Start here.

  
use this to make slow methods show up in traces]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Artifacts feed continues to make product accessible to everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63598</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-artifacts-feed-continues-to-make-product-accessible-to-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T18:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Azure Artifacts continues to be a central place where thousands of developers host, consume, manage packages and share build artifacts, it remains imperative that our user interfaces are accessible.
The post Azure Artifacts feed continues to make product accessible to everyone appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Omokoh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offline Optimization for Architecting Hardware Accelerators]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/offline-optimization-for-architecting.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/offline-optimization-for-architecting.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T18:04:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Amir Yazdanbakhsh, Research Scientist and Aviral Kumar, Student Researcher, Google Research 
Advances in machine learning (ML) often come with advances in hardware and computing systems. For example, the growth of ML-based approaches in solving various problems in vision and language has led to the development of application-specific hardware accelerators (e.g., Google TPUs and Edge TPUs). While promising, standard procedures for designing accelerators customized towards a target application require manual effort to devise a reasonably accurate simulator of hardware, followed by performing many time-intensive simulations to optimize the desired objective (e.g., optimizing for low power usage or latency when running a particular application). This involves identifying the right ba…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Artifacts now provides native support to use packages from more repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63606</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-artifacts-now-provides-native-support-to-use-packages-from-more-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T17:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously, Azure Artifacts customers were only able to natively consume packages from Maven Central as an upstream source, which has been a blocker for customers who want to fully leverage our services as they depend on other vital repos for DevOps.
The post Azure Artifacts now provides native support to use packages from more repositories appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Omokoh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: The One Where You’re Retrieving Process Variables from an External Task Worker]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/qa-the-one-where-youre-retrieving-process-variables-from-an-external-task-worker/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you go about retrieving a variable in your process instance that you’re not sure what or where it is? Let us show you.
The post Q&A: The One Where You’re Retrieving Process Variables from an External Task Worker appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.0-M3 and 5.3.17 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/17/spring-framework-6-0-0-m3-and-5-3-17-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/17/spring-framework-6-0-0-m3-and-5-3-17-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T11:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.0-M3 and 5.3.17 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.17 includes 17 fixes and improvements as well as a fix for CVE-2022-22950: Spring Expression DoS Vulnerability and is a recommended upgrade for all Spring production scenarios.

Spring Framework 6.0.0-M3 includes 33 additional fixes and improvements specific to the 6.0 branch.

This milestone brings a first batch of migration of our AOT (Ahead Of Time) efforts from Spring Native, paving the way for Native support in the wider Spring ecosystem. See the follow-up blog post detailing these and what’s next to come.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New and Updated AWS Well-Architected Lenses]]></title>
        <id>34ce16af41c5307d25c3a7835f037d791ed25f0d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-and-updated-aws-well-architected-lenses/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T22:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since 2015, the AWS Well-Architected Framework has been helping AWS customers and partners improve their cloud architectures. The framework consists of design principles, questions, and best practices across multiple pillars: Operational Excellence, Security, Reliability, Performance Efficiency, and Cost Optimization. At AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced a new Sustainability Pillar to help organizations learn, measure, and improve their workloads using environmental best practices […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know the first AWS Heroes of 2022!]]></title>
        <id>b69882dff9b6088e2fe49ea33224aa377fd9b88f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/get-to-know-the-first-aws-heroes-of-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T21:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Heroes program is a worldwide initiative which acknowledges individuals who have truly gone above and beyond to share knowledge in technical communities. AWS Heroes share knowledge by hosting events, Meetups, workshops, and study groups, or by authoring blogs, creating videos, speaking at conferences, or contributing to open source projects. You can see some […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.14.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/16/spring-tools-4-14-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/16/spring-tools-4-14-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T17:54:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.14.0 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
updated to Eclipse 2022-03 release (new and noteworthy)


fixes and improvements


  
(VSCode) fixed: VSCode Spring boot tools 1.30.0 error trying to find JVM (#726)

  
(VSCode) fixed: vscode “Problems” diagnostic entries lack “source” field (#725)

  
(VSCode) fixed: orphan vscode extension processes left running (#704)

  
(VSCode) fixed: deadlock in language server process avoids process to be shutdown (#741)

  
(VSCode) fixed: Outline View is broken again on Windows (#742)

  
(VSCode) fixed: boot-java.live-information.automatic-tracking.on is not working on vscode (#733)

  
(VSCode) fixed: Java 17 is mis-identified as Java 8 (#713)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Deadlock with Spring LSP in Eclipse 4.23 with STS 4.23 nightlies (#729)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-03-16-4140-release-incl-language-servers-version-1320

Spring Tools 4.14.1 is scheduled to be released in late April 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid Quantum Algorithms for Quantum Monte Carlo]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/hybrid-quantum-algorithms-for-quantum.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/hybrid-quantum-algorithms-for-quantum.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T16:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by William J. Huggins, Research Scientist, Google Quantum AI 
The intersection between the computational difficulty and practical importance of quantum chemistry challenges run on quantum computers has long been a focus for Google Quantum AI. We’ve experimentally simulated simple models of chemical bonding, high-temperature superconductivity, nanowires, and even exotic phases of matter such as time crystals on our Sycamore quantum processors. We’ve also developed algorithms suitable for the error-corrected quantum computers we aim to build, including the world’s most efficient algorithm for large-scale quantum computations of chemistry (in the usual way of formulating the problem) and a pioneering approach that allows for us to solve the same problem at an extremely high spatial res…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women’s History Month: Stories of Making a Difference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/women-s-history-month-stories-of-making-a-difference</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/women-s-history-month-stories-of-making-a-difference"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In honor of Women’s History Month, five women at HashiCorp share stories on how they work to make a difference in their communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save time with partial re-runs in GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-16-save-time-partial-re-runs-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-16-save-time-partial-re-runs-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T14:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is now possible to re-run only failed jobs or a single job in GitHub Actions workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Spring Shell and Spring Native]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/16/spring-tips-spring-shell-and-spring-native</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/16/spring-tips-spring-shell-and-spring-native"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode Josh Long (@starbuxman) looks at the joy of writing fast, native CLI applications with Spring Boot, Spring Shell, GraalVM, and Spring Native]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multimodal Bottleneck Transformer (MBT): A New Model for Modality Fusion]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/multimodal-bottleneck-transformer-mbt.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/multimodal-bottleneck-transformer-mbt.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T20:47:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Arsha Nagrani and Chen Sun, Research Scientists, Google Research, Perception Team 
People interact with the world through multiple sensory streams (e.g., we see objects, hear sounds, read words, feel textures and taste flavors), combining information and forming associations between senses. As real-world data consists of various signals that co-occur, such as video frames and audio tracks, web images and their captions and instructional videos and speech transcripts, it is natural to apply a similar logic when building and designing multimodal machine learning (ML) models.  
 Effective multimodal models have wide applications — such as multilingual image retrieval, future action prediction, and vision-language navigation — and are important for several reasons; robustness, which …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecating weak cryptographic standards (TLS 1.0 and 1.1) in Azure DevOps Services]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63575</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deprecating-weak-cryptographic-standards-tls-1-0-and-1-1-in-azure-devops-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T11:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps team needed to partially rollback the previous release of TLS 1.0/1.1 deprecation that was run on Jan 31st, 2022. This was due to unexpected issues caused by the change. Here’s a link to the previous blog post related to that release.
The post Deprecating weak cryptographic standards (TLS 1.0 and 1.1) in Azure DevOps Services appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Camunda Cloud in a (Nut)shell]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45665</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/managing-camunda-cloud-in-a-nutshell/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how the CLI allows you to troubleshoot and get information from your Camunda Cloud cluster, deploy processes, and run job workers. 
The post Managing Camunda Cloud in a (Nut)shell appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nele Uhlemann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 14, 2022]]></title>
        <id>1400c50e1d58b518d15c77730287ed5e1c6705e4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-14-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T23:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Welcome to the March 14 AWS Week in Review post, and Happy Pi Day! I hope you managed to catch some of our livestreamed Pi day celebration of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to AWS Pi Day 2022]]></title>
        <id>9ff88e5b6aa3475bbb879efe35f7c2d66532ccfe</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/welcome-to-aws-pi-day-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T16:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) sixteen years ago today! As I often told my audiences in the early days, I wanted them to think big thoughts and dream big dreams! Looking back, I think it is safe to say that the launch of S3 empowered them to do just that, and initiated […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform, Packer, and CI/CD Videos from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-packer-and-ci-cd-videos-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-packer-and-ci-cd-videos-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several of this year’s HashiTalks speakers presented useful Terraform, Packer, and CI/CD tips and tricks. Learn from this list of highlights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Simple Ways Automation Can Save You Money on Your AWS Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/two-simple-ways-automation-can-save-money-on-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/two-simple-ways-automation-can-save-money-on-aws"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform is an excellent automation and orchestration tool for public clouds. For this post, I am going to walk through two common scenarios where Ansible Automation Platform can help out. I want to look outside the common public cloud use-case of provisioning and deprovisioning resources and instead look at automating common operational tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault, Boundary, and Zero Trust Videos from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-boundary-and-zero-trust-videos-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-boundary-and-zero-trust-videos-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several of this year’s HashiTalks showcased useful strategies and use cases for HashiCorp Vault and Boundary. Watch the videos here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 X2idn and X2iedn Instances for Memory-Intensive Workloads with Higher Network Bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>f702f965974bf29a23cdde80bb0f3dacddcfcbc5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-x2idn-and-x2iedn-instances-for-memory-intensive-workloads-with-higher-network-bandwidth/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T21:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2016, we launched Amazon EC2 X1 instances designed for large-scale and in-memory applications in the cloud. The price per GiB of RAM for X1 instances is among the lowest. X1 instances are ideal for high performance computing (HPC) applications and running in-memory databases like SAP HANA and big data processing engines such as Apache […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul and Chaos Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-and-chaos-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-and-chaos-engineering"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn more about how HashiCorp Consul can help improve application resiliency, and how to test whether it’s working with chaos engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Community Summit 2022: Dedicated to Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45372</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/camunda-community-summit-2022-dedicated-to-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Expert Sessions agenda is now live for you to preview. Join us on April 26 - 28 for our virtual, interactive conference.
The post Camunda Community Summit 2022: Dedicated to Developers appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Thengvall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Airline Tail Assignments for Cleaner Skies]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/optimizing-airline-tail-assignments-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/optimizing-airline-tail-assignments-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T18:52:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Emily Masten, Software Engineer, Google Research, Operations Research Team  
Airlines around the world are exploring several tactics to meet aggressive CO2 commitments set by the International Civil Aviation Organization (ICAO). This effort has been emphasized in Europe, where aviation accounts for 13.9% of the transportation industry’s carbon emissions. The largest push comes from the European Green Deal, which aims to decrease carbon emissions from transportation by 90% by 2051. The Lufthansa Group has gone even further, committing to a 50% reduction in emissions compared to 2019 by the year 2030 and to reach net-zero emissions by 2050.  
 One unexpected approach that airlines can use to lower carbon emissions is through optimizing their tail assignment, i.e., how to assign air…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[User Story Videos from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/user-story-videos-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/user-story-videos-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insightful case-study sessions were plentiful at this year’s HashiTalks. Check them out in these user-story video highlights from the virtual conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第205話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496802660149</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496802660149"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible cookie: Magic in the middle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-ansible-cookie-magic-in-the-middle</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-ansible-cookie-magic-in-the-middle"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Ansible Automation Platform was compared to the crunchy goodness of a cookie, private automation hub would be the sweet center bringing it all together and making your mouth water!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust Graph Neural Networks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/robust-graph-neural-networks.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/robust-graph-neural-networks.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T19:44:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bryan Perozzi, Research Scientist and Qi Zhu, Research Intern, Google Research 
Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) are powerful tools for leveraging graph-structured data in machine learning. Graphs are flexible data structures that can model many different kinds of relationships and have been used in diverse applications like traffic prediction, rumor and fake news detection, modeling disease spread, and understanding why molecules smell. 
 

Graphs can model the relationships between many different types of data, including web pages (left), social connections (center), or molecules (right).

        
As is standard in machine learning (ML), GNNs assume that training samples are selected uniformly at random (i.e., are an independent and identically distributed or “IID” sample). This i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 70 – Intro to @Azure Stream Analytics with @fleid_bi]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63507</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-70-intro-to-azure-stream-analytics-with-fleid_bi/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T16:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 70 – Intro to @Azure Stream Analytics with @fleid_bi appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the Bias – Women at AWS Developer Relations]]></title>
        <id>660bac839b3d1f53837ae0f822bfc533a449a9fc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/breaking-the-bias-women-at-aws-developer-relations/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T15:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today for International Women’s Day we’re joined by a special guest writer, Rashmi Nambiar. She’s here to share her conversations with a few other members of the AWS Developer Relations team, talking about their work and experience as women in tech. Enjoy! – The AWS News Blog Team When I was contemplating joining AWS, many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rashmi Nambiar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International Women's Day: HashiCorp Leaders Share Their Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/international-women-s-day-hashicorp-leaders-share-their-stories</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/international-women-s-day-hashicorp-leaders-share-their-stories"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In honor of International Women’s Day, three HashiCorp leaders talk about their inspirations, their challenges, and their hopes for the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0-alpha5 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=44937</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/camunda-automation-platform-7-17-0-alpha5-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0. Check out the improvements featured in this release.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0-alpha5 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.8.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45305</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/camunda-optimize-3-8-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the new features we're introducing to expand on our existing functionality and make the interface more user-friendly.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.8.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.4.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45445</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/camunda-cloud-1-4-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Cloud 1.4.0-alpha2. You can sign up for a free trial now to get started right away.
The post Camunda Cloud 1.4.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 7, 2022]]></title>
        <id>333419a96f3de40ad13a5947d1445b7bfe0a3156</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-7-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T21:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Hello Again The AWS Week in Review is back! Many years ago, I tried to write a weekly post that captured the most significant AWS activity. This was easy […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer provides automation, collaboration, and security for managing images across multiple clouds. It includes image security and compliance workflows with Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning from Weakly-Labeled Videos via Sub-Concepts]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/learning-from-weakly-labeled-videos-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/learning-from-weakly-labeled-videos-via.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T18:08:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zizhao Zhang and Guanhang Wu, Software Engineers, Google Research, Cloud AI Team  
Video recognition is a core task in computer vision with applications from video content analysis to action recognition. However, training models for video recognition often requires untrimmed videos to be manually annotated, which can be prohibitively time consuming. In order to reduce the effort of collecting videos with annotations, learning visual knowledge from videos with weak labels, i.e., where the annotation is auto-generated without manual intervention, has attracted growing research interest, thanks to the large volume of easily accessible video data. Untrimmed videos, for example, are often acquired by querying with keywords for classes that the video recognition model aims to classify.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate your Ansible Playbooks to Support AWS boto3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-migrate-your-ansible-playbooks-to-support-aws-boto3</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-migrate-your-ansible-playbooks-to-support-aws-boto3"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform is known for automating Linux, Windows and networking infrastructure. While both the community version of Ansible and our enterprise offering, Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, are prominently known for configuration management, this is just a small piece of what you can really achieve with Ansible’s automation. There are many other use-cases that Ansible Automation Platform is great at automating, such as your AWS, Azure or Google public cloud]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Tencent Cloud Secrets Engine and Authentication Method in HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-tencent-cloud-secrets-engine-authentication-method-in-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-tencent-cloud-secrets-engine-authentication-method-in-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T05:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tencent Cloud has announced new HashiCorp Vault integrations. See how they are implemented in this guest post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRILLsson: Small, Universal Speech Representations for Paralinguistic Tasks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/trillsson-small-universal-speech.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/trillsson-small-universal-speech.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T20:39:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Joel Shor, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research   
In recent years, we have seen dramatic improvements on lexical tasks such as automatic speech recognition (ASR). However, machine systems still struggle to understand paralinguistic aspects — such as tone, emotion, whether a speaker is wearing a mask, etc. Understanding these aspects represents one of the remaining difficult problems in machine hearing. In addition, state-of-the-art results often come from ultra-large models trained on private data, making them impractical to run on mobile devices or to release publicly.  
 In “Universal Paralinguistic Speech Representations Using Self-Supervised Conformers”, to appear in ICASSP 2022, we introduce CAP12— the 12th layer of a 600M parameter model trained on the YT-U training da…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s New Vault Operations Pro Certification Is Lab-Based]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-s-new-vault-operations-pro-certification-is-lab-based</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-s-new-vault-operations-pro-certification-is-lab-based"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s first lab-based certification exam lets Vault professionals vet their knowledge of configuring, managing, and monitoring a production Vault environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon RDS for MySQL & PostgreSQL Multi-AZ Deployment Option: Improved Write Performance & Faster Failover]]></title>
        <id>1c237e54f743e5cabb1a58c19142452eba8836da</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-rds-multi-az-db-cluster/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T22:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing a new Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS) Multi-AZ deployment option with up to 2x faster transaction commit latency, automated failovers typically under 35 seconds, and readable standby instances. Amazon RDS offers two replication options to enhance availability and performance: Multi-AZ deployments gives high availability and automatic failover. Amazon RDS creates a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Deep Learning to Annotate the Protein Universe]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/using-deep-learning-to-annotate-protein.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/using-deep-learning-to-annotate-protein.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T20:16:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Maxwell Bileschi, Staff Software Engineer and Lucy Colwell, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team  
Proteins are essential molecules found in all living things. They play a central role in our bodies’ structure and function, and they are also featured in many products that we encounter every day, from medications to household items like laundry detergent. Each protein is a chain of amino acid building blocks, and just as an image may include multiple objects, like a dog and a cat, a protein may also have multiple components, which are called protein domains. Understanding the relationship between a protein’s amino acid sequence — for example, its domains — and its structure or function are long-standing challenges with far-reaching scientific implications. 

  
An examp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forecasting and tracking the ROI of automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/forecast-track-measure-roi-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/forecast-track-measure-roi-automation"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great ideas start with coffee, but business innovation starts with automation. Just like that morning jolt of warm friendly caffeine, Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform has the ability to enhance, optimize and make your technology stack flow like the beloved beverage most of the world consumes on a daily basis.
 
It is easy to discuss all the technical benefits that Ansible Automation Platform can bring to organizations, but what about the business benefits? How can you observe the state of your automation and return on investment (ROI)? How can you explain the financial impact of automation to key stakeholders? The answer to all of these questions is Red Hat Insights for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform.
 
Red Hat Insights is an analytics platform to help you understand your automation efforts. It lets your data work for you by proactively identifying and correcting issues. Included as a hosted service offering with Ansible Automation Platform, Insights provides a visual dashboard to indicate automation performance, health notifications, organizational statistics, and more.
 
The most relevant features within Insights for IT business leaders and decision makers  who want to validate their automation strategy are Reports, Savings Planner and Automation Calculator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Video Highlights from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-video-highlights-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-video-highlights-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were many popular Kubernetes sessions at this year’s HashiTalks. Watch the highlights from the virtual conference here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Co-training Transformer with Videos and Images Improves Action Recognition]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/co-training-transformer-with-videos-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/co-training-transformer-with-videos-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bowen Zhang, Student Researcher and Jiahui Yu, Senior Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team   
Action recognition has become a major focus area for the research community because many applications can benefit from improved modeling, such as video retrieval, video captioning, video question-answering, etc. Transformer-based approaches have recently demonstrated state-of-the-art performance on several benchmarks. While Transformer models require data to learn better visual priors compared to ConvNets, action recognition datasets are relatively small in scale. Large Transformer models are typically first trained on image datasets and later fine-tuned on a target action recognition dataset. 
 While the current pre-training and fine-tuning action recognition paradigm is stra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 69 – What’s New In @AzureStaticApps with @simona_cotin and @nthonyChu]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63503</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-69-whats-new-in-azurestaticapps-with-simona_cotin-and-nthonychu/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T16:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 69 – What’s New In @AzureStaticApps with @simona_cotin and @nthonyChu appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Customer Carbon Footprint Tool]]></title>
        <id>d83dde763cc072586117e0edc83562050f1ab1a2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-customer-carbon-footprint-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T08:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carbon is the fourth-most abundant element in the universe, and is also a primary component of all known life on Earth. When combined with oxygen it creates carbon dioxide (CO2). Many industrial activities, including the burning of fossil fuels such as coal and oil, release CO2 into the atmosphere and cause climate change. As part […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Developers and Operators, All Paths Lead to Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/for-developers-and-operators-all-paths-lead-to-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/for-developers-and-operators-all-paths-lead-to-consul"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how Consul can help you achieve the right DevOps workflow whether you’re a developer or an operator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federated Learning with Formal Differential Privacy Guarantees]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/federated-learning-with-formal.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/federated-learning-with-formal.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T21:55:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brendan McMahan and Abhradeep Thakurta, Research Scientists, Google Research 
In 2017, Google introduced federated learning (FL), an approach that enables mobile devices to collaboratively train machine learning (ML) models while keeping the raw training data on each user's device, decoupling the ability to do ML from the need to store the data in the cloud. Since its introduction, Google has continued to actively engage in FL research and deployed FL to power many features in Gboard, including next word prediction, emoji suggestion and out-of-vocabulary word discovery. Federated learning is improving the “Hey Google” detection models in Assistant, suggesting replies in Google Messages, predicting text selections, and more. 
While FL allows ML without raw data collection, differe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let Your IPv6-only Workloads Connect to IPv4 Services]]></title>
        <id>e1b359af295167726a228a6bd6d6b6af7809afec</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/let-your-ipv6-only-workloads-connect-to-ipv4-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T21:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing two new capabilities for Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) NAT gateway and Amazon Route 53, allowing your IPv6-only workloads to transparently communicate with IPV4-only services. Curious? Read on; I have details for you. Some of you are running very large workloads involving tens of thousands of virtual machines, containers, or micro-services. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constrained Reweighting for Training Deep Neural Nets with Noisy Labels]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/constrained-reweighting-for-training.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/02/constrained-reweighting-for-training.html"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Abhishek Kumar and Ehsan Amid, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Over the past several years, deep neural networks (DNNs) have been quite successful in driving impressive performance gains in several real-world applications, from image recognition to genomics. However, modern DNNs often have far more trainable model parameters than the number of training examples and the resulting overparameterized networks can easily overfit to noisy or corrupted labels (i.e., examples that are assigned a wrong class label). As a consequence, training with noisy labels often leads to degradation in accuracy of the trained model on clean test data. Unfortunately, noisy labels can appear in several real-world scenarios due to multiple factors, such as errors and inconsistencies in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Improvements in Automation Controller 4.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/performance-improvements-in-automation-controller-4.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/performance-improvements-in-automation-controller-4.1"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 is the next generation automation platform from Red Hat’s trusted enterprise technology experts. With the release of Ansible Automation Platform 2.1, users now have access to the latest control plane – automation controller 4.1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observability, CTS & Nomad Video Highlights from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/observability-cts-nomad-video-highlights-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/observability-cts-nomad-video-highlights-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Observability, Consul-Terraform-Sync use cases, and deep-level Nomad explorations were popular at this year’s HashiTalks. Watch our highlighted videos from the virtual event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>