<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-06-17T01:53:37.531Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-17T01:53:37.531Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · May 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-16-release-radar-may-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-16-release-radar-may-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T22:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each month, we highlight open source projects that have shipped major updates. These projects can include everything from world-changing technology to developer tooling, and weekend hobbies. We cover what the project is and some of their breaking changes. Read about the project, and browse their repositories. Without further ado, here are our top staff picks [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Android kernel mitigations obstacle race]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-16-the-android-kernel-mitigations-obstacle-race/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-16-the-android-kernel-mitigations-obstacle-race/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T16:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post I’ll exploit CVE-2022-22057, a use-after-free in the Qualcomm gpu kernel driver, to gain root and disable SELinux from the untrusted app sandbox on a Samsung Z flip 3. I’ll look at various mitigations that are implemented on modern Android devices and how they affect the exploit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Service Mesh Support for AWS Lambda Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul support for AWS Lambda is now available in public beta enabling services in the mesh to invoke AWS Lambda functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​HashiCorp Recognized as a Best Workplace in the Bay Area]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-recognized-as-a-best-workplace-in-the-bay-area</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-recognized-as-a-best-workplace-in-the-bay-area"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp was ranked 28 on the 2022 Great Place to Work and Fortune magazine Best Workplaces in the Bay Area list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Can’t I Delete a Process Definition in Camunda Platform 8?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57095</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/why-cant-i-delete-a-process-definition-in-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deleting process definitions in Camunda Platform 8 requires complex behavior across multiple components in the system.
The post Why Can’t I Delete a Process Definition in Camunda Platform 8? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carrying costs]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42197</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699402318/0/sethsblog~Carrying-costs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T08:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much does a puppy cost? At the shelter, maybe you need to put up a hundred dollar fee or donation. But that’s tiny compared to food, vet bills, time spent walking, chew toys, yak bones, bully sticks, groomers and those ridiculous dog costumes… perhaps $20,000 if you add it all up. Yet we tend […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bootiful Podcast: Spring Framework contributor Sébastien Deleuze on GraalVM, AOT, project Leyden, and WebAssembly]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/16/bootiful-podcast-spring-framework-contributor-s-bastien-deleuze-on-graalvm-aot-project-leyden-and-webassembly</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/16/bootiful-podcast-spring-framework-contributor-s-bastien-deleuze-on-graalvm-aot-project-leyden-and-webassembly"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring Framework contributor Sébastien Deleuze (@sdeleuze) on GraalVM, AOT, project Leyden, and WebAssembly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Merge 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-15-git-merge-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-15-git-merge-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git Merge, the conference dedicated to bringing the Git community together returns on September 14-15 in Chicago, Illinois.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE report published for Spring Cloud Function]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/cve-report-published-for-spring-cloud-function</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/cve-report-published-for-spring-cloud-function"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Spring Cloud Function 3.2.6 to address the following CVE report.


  
CVE-2202-22979: Spring Cloud Function Dos Vulnerability 


Please review the information in the CVE report and upgrade immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect domain generation algorithm (DGA) activity with new Kibana integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-domain-generation-algorithm-activity-with-new-Kibana-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-domain-generation-algorithm-activity-with-new-Kibana-integration"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have added a DGA detection package to the Integrations app in Kibana. In a single click, you can install and start using the DGA model and associated assets, including ingest pipeline configurations, anomaly detection jobs, and detection rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Alvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect domain generation algorithm (DGA) activity with new Kibana integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-domain-generation-algorithm-activity-with-new-Kibana-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-domain-generation-algorithm-activity-with-new-Kibana-integration"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Searching for a way to help protect your network from potential domain generation algorithm (DGA) attacks? Look no further — a DGA detection package is now available in the Integrations app in Kibana. 

In a single click, users can install and start using the DGA model and associated assets, including ingest pipeline configurations, anomaly detection jobs, and detection rules. Read on for step-by-step instructions on installing and fully enabling the DGA package.

[Related article: Automating the Security Protections rapid response to malware]
What is a DGA?
A DGA is a technique employed by many malware authors to ensure that infection of a client machine evades defensive measures. The goal of this technique is to hide the communication between an infected client machine and the command …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Alvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.15.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-tools-4-15-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-tools-4-15-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.15.0 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
updated to Eclipse 2022-06 release (new and noteworthy)


fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: vscode-sts: an edge case of workspace symbol for @PutMapping (#781)

  
(VSCode) fixed: Failed to refresh live data from process 12704 - com.xxxx.xx.xxx.BillingServiceApp after retries: 10 (#748)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: The Spring Boot Language Server is not immediately shutdown after closing the last open editor to avoid the need to restart the server when you open the next file (related to #568)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: When opening symbols, open the compilation unit from the relevant project (#769)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: The issue with the internal web browser not being able to open HTTP URLs on macOS got fixed. If you prefer to use the internal browser instead of an external one, you can make that switch in the preferences.

  
(Concourse) fixed: Update Concourse registry-image schema (#777)

  
(Concourse) fixed: Add registry_mirror & across as a known properties (#752)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-06-15-4150-release-incl-language-servers-version-1340

Spring Tools 4.15.1 is scheduled to be released in early August 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prebuilding codespaces is generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-15-prebuilding-codespaces-is-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-15-prebuilding-codespaces-is-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teams and GHEC customers can now create blazing fast codespaces, even for your largest and most complex projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​Terraform Cloud Run Tasks with Styra DAS Provides OPA Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-with-styra-das-provides-opa-validation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-with-styra-das-provides-opa-validation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration of HashiCorp Terraform with OPA-founder Styra allows users to validate Terraform infrastructure as code with Open Policy Agent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Netflix Content Engineering makes a federated graph searchable (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/49348511c06c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/how-netflix-content-engineering-makes-a-federated-graph-searchable-part-2-49348511c06c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Alex Hutter, Falguni Jhaveri, and Senthil Sayeebaba]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub now publishes malware advisories in the GitHub Advisory Database]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-15-github-now-publishes-malware-advisories-in-the-github-advisory-database/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-15-github-now-publishes-malware-advisories-in-the-github-advisory-database/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To combat the prevalence of malware in the open source ecosystem, GitHub now publishes malware occurrences in the GitHub Advisory Database. These advisories power Dependabot alerts and remain forever free and usable by the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure - Network Access - blog #2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you to Hicham Mourad and Scott Harwell for co-authoring this blog.
 
Introduction
 
In this blog series, we will continue discussing the deployment of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Harwell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.21 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-framework-5-3-21-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-framework-5-3-21-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T09:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.21 is available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.21 includes 22 fixes and improvements.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some questions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43165</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699261769/0/sethsblog~Some-questions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s it for? What’s it for? What change do you seek to make? What’s the hard part? If you could learn one skill that would help your project, what would it be? How can you tell if it’s working? Would it be easier if you had help? Would it be easier to make an impact […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transition to native Git in TeamCity 2022.04]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=256283</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2022/06/transition-to-native-git-in-teamcity-2022-04/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting from version 2022.04, TeamCity switched to native Git on the server side for Git VCS connections. The switch should positively impact both performance and overall experience of working with Git repositories on the TeamCity server side. In this blog post, we’ll talk about the reasons for the switch and our own experience with this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yegor Naumov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe Is Back: Join Us in Amsterdam or Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years as a fully digital event, HashiConf Europe will once again return to Amsterdam on 20-22 June 2022. Here’s what you can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harness the power of the cloud to build scalable search solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/harness-the-power-of-the-cloud-to-build-scalable-search-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/harness-the-power-of-the-cloud-to-build-scalable-search-solutions"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Cloud is the best way to build highly scalable and performant search solutions using Elastic’s products across any cloud provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Anthem leverages big healthcare data to improve consumers’ lives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-anthem-leverages-big-healthcare-data-to-improve-consumers-lives</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-anthem-leverages-big-healthcare-data-to-improve-consumers-lives"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here we will share our Ansible-based automated deployment solution for ELK, which powers real-time internal search capabilities at Anthem, Inc. and helps the organization improve consumers’ health and wellbeing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miroslav Mihaylov, Ph.D., Anthem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harness the power of the cloud to build scalable search solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/harness-the-power-of-the-cloud-to-build-scalable-search-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/harness-the-power-of-the-cloud-to-build-scalable-search-solutions"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
There are many ways developers can host search applications built with Elastic, ranging from plugging into existing Kubernetes orchestrations to downloading and running the solutions in their own infrastructure. Ultimately, the choice is yours on how you want to manage these solutions. So, how can you ensure you choose the right hosting method? 

Across the board, the best — and easiest — decision is to go with the cloud. Elastic Cloud’s fully managed experience is the optimal way to build highly scalable and performant search solutions using Elastic’s products across any cloud provider. With Elastic Cloud, you can rapidly deploy in your favorite public cloud, or in multiple clouds, and extend the value of Elastic with cloud-native features.

Still not sure? Read on to learn about a few …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Anthem leverages big healthcare data to improve consumers’ lives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-anthem-leverages-big-healthcare-data-to-improve-consumers-lives</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-anthem-leverages-big-healthcare-data-to-improve-consumers-lives"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Challenges with healthcare data  
Healthcare data makes up a third of the world’s data and is projected to grow, in the next few years, at a faster pace than traditional data-rich industries like financial services and manufacturing.* The staggering data volumes in healthcare, in addition to its heterogeneity and fragmentation, represent substantial challenges to extracting data insights for improving healthcare outcomes of individuals and communities. 

At Anthem, Inc., we have undertaken various initiatives to address these challenges — most notably full-text search of healthcare claims.

In this post, we share with you our automated deployment solution for ELK stack. This deployment pattern is in use internally at Anthem to power real-time search capabilities on top of Anthem’s health…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miroslav Mihaylov, Ph.D., Anthem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer Hotline]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2633/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2633/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/astronomer_hotline.png" title="Employment statistics have to correct for the fact that the Weird Bug Hotline hires on a bunch of extra temporary staff every 17 years." alt="Employment statistics have to correct for the fact that the Weird Bug Hotline hires on a bunch of extra temporary staff every 17 years." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating GitHub theme creation with color tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-14-accelerating-github-theme-creation-with-color-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-14-accelerating-github-theme-creation-with-color-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why the GitHub Design Infrastructure team built a dedicated color tool and how they use it to create new color palettes for GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scanned Objects by Google Research: A Dataset of 3D-Scanned Common Household Items]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/scanned-objects-by-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/scanned-objects-by-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:06:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Laura Downs and Anthony Francis, Software Engineers, Robotics at Google  
Many recent advances in computer vision and robotics rely on deep learning, but training deep learning models requires a wide variety of data to generalize to new scenarios. Historically, deep learning for computer vision has relied on datasets with millions of items that were gathered by web scraping, examples of which include ImageNet, Open Images, YouTube-8M, and COCO. However, the process of creating these datasets can be labor-intensive, and can still exhibit labeling errors that can distort the perception of progress. Furthermore, this strategy does not readily generalize to arbitrary three-dimensional shapes or real-world robotic data.  
 

Real-world robotic data collection is very useful, but diffi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can the United States build its Open Source Software policy?]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-14-how-can-the-united-states-build-its-open-source-software-policy/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-14-how-can-the-united-states-build-its-open-source-software-policy/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We share a recap of a recent roundtable event about what a federal open source software policy could look like in the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Access to C++Now 2022 Videos]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=256224</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/06/early-access-to-c-now-2022-videos/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C++Now is one of the most academic events in the C++ calendar. Up in the mountains for a week in Aspen, Colorado, attendees dive into all kinds of profound C++ topics, from new language features and proposals to libraries and tools. C++ chats start at breakfast and continue until late at night in the bar. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Symbol Servers and Other Enhancements for Unreal Engine Development in Rider]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=256185</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/06/14/symbol-servers-and-other-enhancements-for-unreal-engine-development-in-rider/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T13:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Rider 2022.2 EAP build brings some useful enhancements for Unreal Engine developers. If you’ve never used Rider for Unreal Engine projects, give it a try and experience first-class support for the Unreal Engine reflection mechanism, integration with Blueprints, and other benefits available on Windows, Linux, and macOS. Learn more on our website. With […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Schedule a Jupyter Notebook]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=255893</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2022/06/14/how-to-schedule-a-jupyter-notebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T10:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the number of analytics projects grows, you might start getting a lot of requests to rerun or update certain Jupyter notebook results. Some projects, such as web scraping apps or dashboards built on notebook results, might even require hourly updates. In these cases, you might want to automate Jupyter notebooks, rather than rerunning them […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problems now (problems later)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41268</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699167198/0/sethsblog~Problems-now-problems-later/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People always address now problems before they work on later problems. Every time. On one night in 2004, you might have had two choices. You could go out for a fancy dinner with friends, or you could buy one share of Google at their IPO. A couple of decades later, your dinner is forgotten but […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet Below Deck, Part III — State Management]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=fleet&amp;p=254072</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/fleet/2022/06/fleet-below-deck-part-iii-state-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T09:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a multipart series on building Fleet, a next-generation IDE by JetBrains. Part I – Architecture Overview Part II – Breaking Down the Editor Part III – State Management In previous parts of this series, we looked at an overview of the Fleet architecture and discussed the algorithms and data structures that are used […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vitaly Bragilevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: “Idiomatic Pandas: 5 tips for better Pandas”, With Matt Harrison and Jodie Burchell]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=255879</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/06/webinar-idiomatic-pandas-5-tips-for-better-pandas-with-matt-harrison-and-jodie-burchell/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been a long-time Pandas user, relying on it heavily since the start of my data science career. However, up until the last couple of years, I struggled with certain issues, such as not being able to work with very large DataFrames or efficiently run heavy data processing tasks. I’d also often find my Jupyter […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jodie Burchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57164</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1. Check out the latest improvements including the Management Dashboard, new reports, and Spring Boot migration. 
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (parts 5 and 6 of an ongoing series)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-5-and-6-of-an-ongoing-series</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-5-and-6-of-an-ongoing-series"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In thi^^^ these installments, we continue our series introducing the Spring for GraphQL project. This series features Spring for GraphQL lead Rossen Stoyanchev (@rstoya05) - whose work you may know from basically everything in the wide and wonderful world of Springdom having to do with the web (HTTP, RSocket, WebSockets, GraphQL, JSF, MVC, etc) - and GraphQL Java engine founder and lead Andi Marek (@andimarek) and of course yours truly, Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long (@starbuxman). It provides an in-depth look at all things Spring for GraphQL.

This week I’m publishing two new installments. 

The first of this week’s installments, part five of the series, looks at using GraphQL subscriptions to stream data in a way that is agnostic of the supported transport protoco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye Spring IDE - Welcome Spring Tools 4]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/goodbye-spring-ide-welcome-spring-tools-4</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/goodbye-spring-ide-welcome-spring-tools-4"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 31 of 2004, only a few months after version 1.0 of the Spring Framework itself got released, Torsten Jürgeleit created a repository and made the initial commits to a project that became the tooling support for Spring in Eclipse, the Spring IDE project (while the roots of that work are probably going back further in time, as the comment of the first commit to the repository reads like there was a CVS repository even before that time.). Shortly after, Christian Dupuis joined, led the project for many years and initiated the Spring Tool Suite on top of Spring IDE.

It’s been a long time since then.

On December 4 of 2017, a new chapter for the Spring tooling began with the introduction of the all-new Spring Tools 4 and its first public beta release, followed by the first GA releas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 14th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/this-week-in-spring-june-14th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/14/this-week-in-spring-june-14th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’ve just arrived in beautiful Berlin, Germany, for the forthcoming We Are Developers show with more than five thousand attendees. I was in Toronto, Canada, for the epic SpringOne Tour installment there. I’ve also had the privilege of taking these last two trips with my daughter, Kimly. She’s on summer break from school. It’s made the long miserable hours in economy bearable, and something for which I couldn’t be more grateful. I’m also looking forward to being at the upcoming SpringOne Tour installment in New York City, later this month. Don’t miss it! 

In the meantime, we’ve got a ton of good stuff to get to this week so let’s dive right in! 


  
Java architect Brian Goetz foreshadows an interesting new feature …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How technology leaders are overcoming challenges to cloud migration across financial, public, and telecom sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/technology-leaders-challenges-cloud-migration-financial-public-telecom</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/technology-leaders-challenges-cloud-migration-financial-public-telecom"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leaders across industries share how they are adopting cloud to drive speed and impact]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Rabinowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How technology leaders are overcoming challenges to cloud migration across financial, public, and telecom sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/technology-leaders-challenges-cloud-migration-financial-public-telecom</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/technology-leaders-challenges-cloud-migration-financial-public-telecom"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The value of an organization’s data is magnified in the cloud — enabling agility and new sources of revenue — but leaders must first overcome critical challenges. 
We interviewed executives in three economic sectors — financial services, public sector, and telecommunications — for their insights on the unique challenges and opportunities they face, and how they’re leading their organization to deliver stronger results in the cloud. Below are edited excerpts from the conversations.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltec70c92aca2e350c/62a92556c4d59b57e0c25686/roundtable.jpg,roundtable.jpgFinancial services: Cloud is a matter of trust,
Milind Nagnur, chief technology officer, Early Warning Services, parent company of the Zelle payment network

Financial institutio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Rabinowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56809</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/camunda-automation-platform-7180-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the second alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7.18. See what's new and learn how you can contribute. 
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 ways financial services leaders can stay ahead of the cybersecurity risk curve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-stay-ahead-of-the-cybersecurity-risk-curve</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-stay-ahead-of-the-cybersecurity-risk-curve"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting the assets of the financial institution and its clients is becoming harder. According to our recent co-sponsored study with ThoughtLab, there are still many steps that must be taken to ensure security in an emerging risk landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.2.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8.2.3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8.2.3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.2.3 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.2.3 over the previous patch versions in 8.2.x.
The 8.2.3 patch contains fixes and small enhancements for the stack. For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
8.2.3 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Landis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 ways financial services leaders can stay ahead of the cybersecurity risk curve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-stay-ahead-of-the-cybersecurity-risk-curve</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/financial-services-stay-ahead-of-the-cybersecurity-risk-curve"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As financial institutions migrate to modern infrastructure and cloud services, bad actors have extended their skills and capabilities to achieve their missions. This is compounded by the fact that financial and payment vehicles continue to go virtual. Even the slightest breach can result in fines and reputational harm. 

Many financial institutions are successfully taking a risk-based approach to cybersecurity, according to our recent co-sponsored study with ThoughtLab. Cybersecurity Solutions for a Riskier World reports that 91% of financial services companies are either “mid-implementation” or “advanced” in maturity against the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) framework. 

While this is undoubtedly a positive sign for the industry, many steps still need to be taken…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.2.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8.2.3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8.2.3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Landis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Monthly: June 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-13-open-source-monthly-june-2022-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-13-open-source-monthly-june-2022-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T20:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June's Open Source Monthly features Modos–a community-focused company building software and hardware that designs digital devices with respect for users' time, attention, and well-being.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – June 13, 2022]]></title>
        <id>f62346f0e4c3f5f23df31341fcd4572e7dafb8ca</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-13-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T19:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Last Week’s Launches I made a short trip to Austin, Texas last week in order to visit and learn from some customers. As is always the case, the days when […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure - Network Access - blog #1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you to Hicham Mourad and Scott Harwell for co-authoring this blog.
 
Introduction
 
In this blog series we will discuss the deployment of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure, specifically focusing on the deployment access types and what that means for accessing Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Azure after deployment completion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Harwell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.2 EAP4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=255106</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2022/06/rubymine-2022-2-eap4/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T12:14:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine 2022.2 EAP4 is here! Catch up on all the new features by checking out the previous EAP blog posts. Below you can find the most notable improvements. Support for YARD macros We’re continuing to improve our YARD support. Now RubyMine recognizes YARD macro extensions and provides general coding assistance for them. Use the Go […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Zykova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2 EAP #3: Creating Enums]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=254852</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/06/phpstorm-2022-2-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T12:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to the 2022.2 EAP series! If you’re new or unsure what our Early Access Program is, make sure to read the first post in this series. With that said, let’s take a look at what’s new in this week’s version! Download PhpStorm 2022.2 EAP Create Enums using the New PHP Class dialog We’ve […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handmade, original and significant]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43153</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699095656/0/sethsblog~Handmade-original-and-significant/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are still pockets of our culture where a single individual can create and share a body of work that’s resonant and unique. I’ve become hooked on a podcast called A History of Rock Music in 500 Songs. I’m now a backer on Patreon. The show is at https://500songs.com/ [My suggestion is that you start with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized as a Visionary in the 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for APM and Observability for the second consecutive year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-critical-capabilities-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-critical-capabilities-apm"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that Elastic has been recognized as a Visionary in the 2022 Gartner APM and Observability Magic Quadrant for the second year in a row. The Elastic Observability solution scored among the Top 3 vendors in five out of six use cases in the 2022 Gartner Critical Capabilities for APM and Observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized as a Visionary in the 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for APM and Observability for the second consecutive year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-critical-capabilities-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-critical-capabilities-apm"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are excited to announce that Elastic has been recognized as a Visionary in the 2022 Gartner Magic Quadrant for APM and Observability for the second year in a row. In addition, the Elastic solution scored among the Top 3 vendors in five out of six use cases in the 2022 Gartner Critical Capabilities for APM and Observability.
Elastic recognized for its completeness of vision and ability to execute
We believe Elastic's recognition in this report, based on our “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision”, provides validation to our efforts to deliver new and innovative full-stack observability capabilities on a single platform.
We are grateful to our customers who continue to adopt Elastic Observability to ingest business and operational data, break down silos, and enable end-to-end …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greatest Scientist]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2632/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2632/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/greatest_scientist.png" title="&quot;Ow! One of the petri dishes I left on the tower railing fell and hit me on the head! Hey, that gives me an idea...&quot;" alt="&quot;Ow! One of the petri dishes I left on the tower railing fell and hit me on the head! Hey, that gives me an idea...&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Push vs. pull]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=31588</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/699032686/0/sethsblog~Push-vs-pull/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-12T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The non-networked world was driven by push. The merchant stocked goods and waited for you to come buy them. The manufacturer made things in advance and advertised so you’d go buy them. The cab waited by the corner hoping you’d come out and hail it. The door-to-door salesperson went door to door… But the web […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The coyote’s anguish]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43146</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698957390/0/sethsblog~The-coyotes-anguish/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-11T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s one of the best metaphors for life, marketing, achievement, community and possibility in all of TV cartooning. The coyote is always looking for a quick win. Because he doesn’t persist with a plan that builds over time, all of his outlandish stunts add up to nothing but frustration. The coyote is obsessed with gaining […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing a robust digital identity]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-10-implementing-a-robust-digital-identity/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-10-implementing-a-robust-digital-identity/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T19:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you robustly assert and identify a user’s identity?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we think about browsers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-10-how-we-think-about-browsers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-10-how-we-think-about-browsers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T18:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how GitHub thinks about browser support, look at usage patterns, and learn about the tools we use to make sure our customers are getting the best experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 EAP #4: Built-In Remote Development Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=254970</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/06/webstorm-2022-2-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T16:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 EAP build #4 is now available! To catch up on all the new features, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up-to-date. You can also manually download the EAP builds from our website. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (parts 3 and 4 of an ongoing series)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/10/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-3-and-4-of-an-ongoing-series</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/10/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-3-and-4-of-an-ongoing-series"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In thi^^^ these installments, we continue our series introducing the Spring for GraphQL project. This series features Spring for GraphQL lead Rossen Stoyanchev (@rstoya05) - whose work you may know from basically everything in the wide and wonderful world of Springdom having to do with the web (HTTP, RSocket, WebSockets, GraphQL, JSF, MVC, etc) - and GraphQL Java engine founder and lead Andi Marek (@andimarek) and of course yours truly, Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long (@starbuxman). It provides an in-depth look at all things Spring for GraphQL.

This week I’m publishing two new installments. 

In this week’s first installment, episode three of a series, looks at batching requests with Spring for GraphQL’s @BatchMapping support. This mechanism in turn builds on Facebook’s DataLoader facility. 


Then, in this week’s second installment, episode four of a series, we look at how to make a change with mutations. This is one of my favorite parts about GraphQL - it’s plain, pragmatic, and - most importantly - obvious! 


This continues the series we started last week, with episodes one and two, which I recap here: 

In this first installment, we look at the basics of using the GraphQL Java engine that underpins Spring for GraphQL. 


In this second installment, we look at using the Spring for GraphQL component model by writing queries. 


I know it’s been more than a month since we last published a video, so I’m going to be releasing every episode of this series very quickly, over the next week or two. I’ve already recorded and mostly finished producing eight episodes. I’m working on producing a ninth, and that’ll be that! A complete introduction to all things Spring for GraphQL. These are of course part of the usual Spring Tips playlist on YouTube, but also part of the Learn Spring for GraphQL with Josh Long playlist. Follow that one to be notified of any new episodes!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Process and Task Events with Camunda Platform, AWS Kinesis, and Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56867</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/integrating-process-and-task-events-with-camunda-platform-aws-kinesis-and-elasticsearch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Camunda Community Summit 2022, Fidelity Investments Director of Architecture Harish Malavade shared a behind-the-scenes look at Fidelity’s digital automation platform that uses Camunda as its core workflow engine. Here are the technical details. 
The post Integrating Process and Task Events with Camunda Platform, AWS Kinesis, and Elasticsearch appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harish Malavade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Live Stream: WebStorm’s Power User Manual: Angular Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=255353</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/06/webstorms-power-user-manual-angular-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T14:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us Thursday, June 30, 5 pm – 6 pm (CEST) / 11 am – 12 pm (EDT), for our free live stream WebStorm’s Power User Manual: Angular Edition. We’ve invited long-time WebStorm user and Angular guru, Chau Tran, to teach you his tricks for working with this very popular framework. Our Power User live […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Aganezova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.2 EAP #4 Is Out With Support for Fuzz Testing and New Documentation Features]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=254968</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/06/10/goland-2022-2-eap-4-is-out-with-support-for-fuzz-testing-and-new-documentation-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T12:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth build of our current Early Access Program is now available! You can get the EAP build via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package (for Ubuntu), or from inside GoLand select Check IDE updates for Early Access Program in Preferences / Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 EAP 4: Improved Inspections and Code Completion for Java]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=254466</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/06/intellij-idea-2022-2-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T10:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 EAP 4 is now out! This EAP build features Java-related updates that provide improved code completion and better code analysis via new inspections and quick-fixes. Throughout the Early Access Program, we encourage you to test out all of the new features and share your thoughts and suggestions with us. You can download […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marketing vs. promotion]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43144</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698881068/0/sethsblog~Marketing-vs-promotion/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People often use the words to mean the same thing, but they’re different. If an exterminator puts signs and banners in front of a fancy house when they’re inside killing rats, that’s promotion. But it’s not good marketing. Marketing is creating the conditions for a story to spread so you can help people get to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 key strategies for the retail industry to fend off rising cybersecurity risks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/4-key-strategies-for-the-retail-industry-to-fend-off-rising-cybersecurity-risks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/4-key-strategies-for-the-retail-industry-to-fend-off-rising-cybersecurity-risks"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The role of the retail CISO is expanding. With physical and digital shopping experiences melding, e-commerce technology advancing, and cyberattacks, malware, ransomware, and credit card fraud multiplying, CISOs must take on a broader remit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 key strategies for the retail industry to fend off rising cybersecurity risks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/4-key-strategies-for-the-retail-industry-to-fend-off-rising-cybersecurity-risks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/4-key-strategies-for-the-retail-industry-to-fend-off-rising-cybersecurity-risks"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Retailers are facing a more challenging cybersecurity environment than ever, according to a new study, Cybersecurity solutions for a riskier world. With physical and digital worlds colliding, greater levels of regulation, and more savvy cybercriminals, executives agree that we have entered a new era of cyber risk. 

In fact, 30% of retailers say they are not prepared for the threats ahead.

In response to these changes, the role of the retail CISO is expanding. With physical and digital shopping experiences melding, POS systems and e-commerce technology advancing, and cyberattacks, malware, ransomware, and credit card fraud multiplying, CISOs must take on a broader remit that spans functions across the enterprise. 

Here are four tactics successful CISOs and other security professionals …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exercise Progression]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2631/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2631/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/exercise_progression.png" title="They said after I got into a routine, I'd enjoy getting progressively stronger and stop whining so much about how hard exercise was. Well, they were half right!" alt="They said after I got into a routine, I'd enjoy getting progressively stronger and stop whining so much about how hard exercise was. Well, they were half right!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 R6id Instances with NVMe Local Instance Storage of up to 7.6 TB]]></title>
        <id>a84adda0652b06fccf7c94df6d0eeed2bdeb3602</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-r6id-instances/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T21:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2021, we launched the memory-optimized Amazon EC2 R6i instances, our sixth-generation x86-based offering powered by 3rd Generation Intel Xeon Scalable processors (code named Ice Lake). Today I am excited to announce a disk variant of the R6i instance: the Amazon EC2 R6id instances with non-volatile memory express (NVMe) SSD local instance storage. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LIMoE: Learning Multiple Modalities with One Sparse Mixture-of-Experts Model]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/limoe-learning-multiple-modalities-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/limoe-learning-multiple-modalities-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:49:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Basil Mustafa, Research Software Engineer and Carlos Riquelme, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain team 
Sparse models stand out among the most promising approaches for the future of deep learning. Instead of every part of a model processing every input (“dense” modeling), sparse models employing conditional computation learn to route individual inputs to different “experts” in a potentially huge network. This has many benefits. First, model size can increase while keeping computational cost constant — an effective and environmentally friendlier way to scale models, which is often key to high performance. Sparsity also naturally compartmentalizes neural networks. Dense models that learn many different tasks simultaneously (multitask) or sequentially (continual learning) of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Kubernetes legend and friend Cora Iberkleid on Tanzu, Cartographer, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/09/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-legend-and-friend-cora-iberkleid-on-tanzu-cartographer-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/09/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-legend-and-friend-cora-iberkleid-on-tanzu-cartographer-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Kubernetes legend and fellow Tanzu Developer Advocate Cora Iberkleid (@ciberkleid) about Kubernetes and Cartographer supply chains]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copy a work item type using Azure DevOps API’s]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64424</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/copy-a-work-item-type-using-azure-devops-apis-undocumented/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, we all love how we can manage engagements in Azure DevOps (ADO). We can create Epics, Features, User Stories and track our progress on Kanban boards. You can customize work item types to suit the needs of your business and project with ease.
The post Copy a work item type using Azure DevOps API’s appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Art Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pump-Up your ITIL with Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/pump-up-your-itil-with-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/pump-up-your-itil-with-automation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of automation and agility, it seems that Information Technology Infrastructure Library (ITIL) doesn’t have a role to play anymore, being marked as an “old school” framework. Can it be the end of the methodology after it served numerous IT organizations for so long as a guideline and blueprint for their processes?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Lavarde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.0-M5 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/09/spring-shell-2-1-0-m5-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/09/spring-shell-2-1-0-m5-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T10:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.0-M5 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you smart?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42208</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698810146/0/sethsblog~Are-you-smart/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart is no longer memorization. It’s not worth much. Smart is no longer access to information. Everyone has that. Smart is: • Situational awareness • Filtering information • Troubleshooting • Clarity of goals • Good taste • Empathy and compassion for others • The ability to make decisions that further your goals The good news […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating the Security Protections rapid response to malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/automating-security-protections-rapid-response-to-malware</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/automating-security-protections-rapid-response-to-malware"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how we’ve been improving the processes that allow us to make updates quickly in response to new information and propagate those protections to our users, with the help of machine learning models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samantha Zeitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating the Security Protections rapid response to malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/automating-security-protections-rapid-response-to-malware</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/automating-security-protections-rapid-response-to-malware"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Cyber attacks on corporate networks were up 50% in 2021, and it’s expected that 2022 will see more of the same. Elastic Endpoint Security includes a variety of protection layers to ensure maximum coverage against different types of malware. There have been a few examples recently of the need for fast, accurate updates of user environments in order to protect against the latest malware. Here at Elastic, we’ve been improving the processes that allow us to make updates quickly in response to new information and propagate those protections to our users. 

As part of our security solution, we use a machine learning model to help us detect malware based on known characteristics. Since machine learning is never perfect, we deploy supplemental artifacts, including lists of known file hashes that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samantha Zeitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernize Your Mainframe Applications & Deploy Them In The Cloud]]></title>
        <id>6b1b29b8416988254d5bb4b9eb7bf37cc88ab414</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/modernize-your-mainframe-applications-deploy-them-in-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are launching AWS Mainframe Modernization service to help you modernize your mainframe applications and deploy them to AWS fully-managed runtime environments. This new service also provides tools and resources to help you plan and implement migration and modernization. Since the introduction of System/360 on April 7 1964, mainframe computers have enabled many industries […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at Cisco Live: Demos, Presentations, Experts, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-cisco-live-demos-presentations-experts-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-cisco-live-demos-presentations-experts-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re at Cisco Live, June 12-16. Find out more details in our pre-event blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo – OKRs (Objectives and Key Results)]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64394</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-okrs-objectives-and-key-results/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is vision?
The post DevOps Dojo – OKRs (Objectives and Key Results) appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Desktop App with React and Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56716</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/building-a-desktop-app-with-react-and-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow along as Principal Developer Advocate David Simmons uses Camunda Platform 8 and React to build an app that requests, fetches, and saves data.
The post Building a Desktop App with React and Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS MGN Update – Configure DR, Convert CentOS Linux to Rocky Linux, and Convert SUSE Linux Subscription]]></title>
        <id>5d64e7849cb97cd88b049a203409a40516c031fb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-mgn-update-configure-dr-convert-centos-linux-to-rocky-linux-and-convert-suse-linux-subscription/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just about a year ago, Channy showed you How to Use the New AWS Application Migration Server for Lift-and-Shift Migrations. In his post, he introduced AWS Application Migration Service (AWS MGN) and said: With AWS MGN, you can minimize time-intensive, error-prone manual processes by automatically replicating entire servers and converting your source servers from physical, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第210話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270296674398611831</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270296674398611831"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 private automation hub features about automation execution environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/8-private-automation-hub-features-about-automation-execution-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/8-private-automation-hub-features-about-automation-execution-environments"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1 introduced automation execution environments, which is a new way to package automation into a container runtime environment. In addition, private automation hub also joined the party by adding significant support for execution environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scale vs. Speed: Why organizations slow down]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42137</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698746098/0/sethsblog~Scale-vs-Speed-Why-organizations-slow-down/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T08:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you compare a Starbucks of ten years ago to a current one, they’re virtually the same. Compare this to the originals in Seattle, and the difference is startling. The same goes for the design of a typical McDonald’s. Apple launched the Mac with about a dozen full-time people working on its development. Today, they […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regression testing your Java Agent Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/regression-testing-your-java-agent-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/regression-testing-your-java-agent-plugin"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to easily perform regression testing on your Java agent plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Shirazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regression testing your Java Agent Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/regression-testing-your-java-agent-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/regression-testing-your-java-agent-plugin"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For developers who’ve created their own instrumentation with the Java Agent plugin, the next phase of the process is regression testing. By performing regression testing, you can ensure that your plugin functions the way it’s supposed to after you’ve made code changes or updates. 

You’ll have your own plugin, but to illustrate regression testing in this article, I’ll use the plugin in our example repo.

The normal sequence of activity with a plugin
First, let’s understand the normal sequence of activity when the application is started with the Elastic APM (application performance monitoring) Java Agent and the plugin, using the -javaagent option on the command line (There are several ways to attach the agent. For this sequence, let’s assume the recommended -javaagent option.)

The Java …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Shirazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shuttle Skeleton]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2630/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2630/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/shuttle_skeleton.png" title="It's believed to be related to the Stellar Sea Cow." alt="It's believed to be related to the Stellar Sea Cow." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End-to-end Generative Pre-training for Multimodal Video Captioning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/end-to-end-generative-pre-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/end-to-end-generative-pre-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Paul Hongsuck Seo and Arsha Nagrani, Research Scientists, Google Research, Perception Team  
Multimodal video captioning systems utilize both the video frames and speech to generate natural language descriptions (captions) of videos. Such systems are stepping stones towards the longstanding goal of building multimodal conversational systems that effortlessly communicate with users while perceiving environments through multimodal input streams.  
 Unlike video understanding tasks (e.g., video classification and retrieval) where the key challenge lies in processing and understanding multimodal input videos, the task of multimodal video captioning includes the additional challenge of generating grounded captions. The most widely adopted approach for this task is to train an encoder-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Azure is Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Microsoft Azure is now available in public beta. Get started today with a secure, resilient service mesh for connecting applications running in Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 7th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/07/this-week-in-spring-june-7th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/07/this-week-in-spring-june-7th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’ve just landed in tantalizing Toronto, Canada, for the SpringOne Tour Toronto show. I’m so excited to be here, at long last, after so long away from one of my favorite countries. I’ll be doing two talks - my usual, Kubernetes Native Java, and a talk on building Kubernetes Controllers (a.k.a. “Operators”) using the official Kubernetes Java client, Spring Boot, and Spring Native with my amazing friend and teammate Tiffany Jernigan, who you may recall was on the podcast not too long ago. 

After Toronto, I’m off to beautiful Berlin, Germany, for the We Are Developers show. 

If you’re at either show, don’t hesitate to say hi! 


  
Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (parts 1 and 2 of an ongoing series) Hi Spring …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.10 Achieves FIPS 140-2 Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-1-10-achieves-fips-140-2-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-1-10-achieves-fips-140-2-compliance"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault Enterprise 1.10 has been evaluated as conformant with the Federal Information Processing Standard (FIPS) 140-2 standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64349</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-lean-product-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T09:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 and Part 2 of the DevOps Dojo – Lean Product series, we covered the why, what, and how of the product-centric model and lean product model as outlined in the White & Orange Belts of the DevOps Dojo.
The post DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 3 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paying extra]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40085</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/698681446/0/sethsblog~Paying-extra/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T08:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For six years, if you wanted an electric car, you’d need to pay extra. It cost more than the regular kind. Of course, if you decided to buy one, you weren’t paying extra. You were buying sustainability, community awareness, cachet, status, safety, quiet and the feeling of being an early adopter. People never pay extra. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – June 6, 2022]]></title>
        <id>809e92b4a5a28eebe9aaedaedb0238c8547ff419</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-6-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I’ve just come back from a long (extended) holiday weekend here in the US and I’m still catching up on all the AWS launches that happened this past week. I’m […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Appsec at Netflix (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c9e0f1488bc5</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/scaling-appsec-at-netflix-part-2-c9e0f1488bc5?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Astha Singhal, Lakshmi Sudheer, Julia Knecht]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Ansible Automation Platform's Automation Services Catalog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-ansible-automation-platforms-automation-services-catalog</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-ansible-automation-platforms-automation-services-catalog"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.2 introduces a technical preview of automation services catalog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 04.06.2022]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64335</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-04-06-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-04T07:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Don’t Accept the Defaults’ -Abel Wang
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 04.06.2022 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring I/O founder, Spring trainer and community legend Sergi Almar]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-i-o-founder-spring-trainer-and-community-legend-sergi-almar</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-i-o-founder-spring-trainer-and-community-legend-sergi-almar"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! At long last, against all odds, Josh Long (@starbuxman) finally gets to talk to Spring I/O founder and more-than-a-decade-long friend Sergi Almar (@sergialmar) about an edition of Spring I/O after 2019!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the newest AWS Heroes – June 2022]]></title>
        <id>c02650163773177062a3b118f232c97abe7eb4ae</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-newest-aws-heroes-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Heroes are some of the worlds most active and vocal leaders in AWS communities, recognized for their unwavering focus on sharing insights and technical knowledge with others. Heroes have a variety of contributions to community learning: they host events, meetups, and workshops, author blogs, contribute to open source projects, speak at conferences, and more. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022 Deprecation of Reporting Services]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64299</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-deprecation-of-reporting-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the Azure DevOps Server 2022 release, we wanted to reiterate the deprecation of the existing data warehouse reporting services. We previously announced this in the Azure DevOps Server 2020 release notes. The warehouse reporting service has been part of TFS and Azure DevOps for over a decade.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022 Deprecation of Reporting Services appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (parts 1 and 2 of an ongoing series)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-1-and-2-of-an-ongoing-series</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-parts-1-and-2-of-an-ongoing-series"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In thi^^^ these installments, we begin a new series introducing the Spring for GraphQL project. 

In this first installment, GraphQL Java lead Andi Marek (@andimarek) and  I (@starbuxman) look at the basics of using the GraphQL Java engine that underpins Spring for GraphQL. 


In this second installment, Andi and I are joined by Spring for GraphQL lead Rossen Stoyanchev (@rstoya05) as we look at using the Spring for GraphQL component model by writing queries. 


I know it’s been more than a month since we last published a video, so I’m going to be releasing every episode of this series very quickly, over the next week or two. I’ve already recorded and mostly finished producing eight episodes. I’m working on producing a ninth, and that’ll be that! A complete introduction to all things Spring for GraphQL. These are of course part of the usual Spring Tips playlist on YouTube, but also part of the Learn Spring for GraphQL with Josh Long playlist. Follow that one to be notified of any new episodes!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Stream Applications 2021.1.2 GA Release now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/spring-cloud-stream-applications-2021-1-2-ga-release-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/02/spring-cloud-stream-applications-2021-1-2-ga-release-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Cloud Stream Applications 2021.1.2 has been released.

This release is based on Spring Boot 2.6.8 and Spring Cloud 2021.0.3 and contains many improvements and bug fixes - check out the release notes for more information.
Future plans


  
Switch apps to use Spring Boot 3.x

  
Move Spring Cloud Stream App Maven plugins to stream-application repository.

  
Align versioning of Stream Functions and Apps.


Stay in touch…

Please continue to engage with us by creating bug reports and feature requests on Github and asking questions on StackOverflow using the spring-cloud-stream or spring-cloud-dataflow tags.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB Field Level Encryption with HashiCorp Vault KMIP Secrets Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mongodb-field-level-encryption-with-hashicorp-vault-kmip-secrets-engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/mongodb-field-level-encryption-with-hashicorp-vault-kmip-secrets-engine"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how MongoDB’s field-level encryption capability pairs with Vault’s KMIP secrets engine to help organizations deliver strong privacy and security controls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Conversations: Jean Robert Alves, Agi]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56009</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/community-conversations-jean-robert-alves-agibank/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the latest installment of Community Conversations, we sat down with Jean Robert Alves, a Camunda Champion and software architect expert at Agi.
The post Community Conversations: Jean Robert Alves, Agi appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Work Item Revision Limits]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64125</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/work-item-revision-limits/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time a work item is updated, it creates an entry in the work item history. This is a great feature for users to track all the individual changes made to work items. However, we have seen organizations with automated tools that will generate tens of thousands of work item revisions.
The post Work Item Revision Limits appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EMR Serverless Now Generally Available – Run Big Data Applications without Managing Servers]]></title>
        <id>230544885a857a26188de08fe94fb293329b5ed7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-emr-serverless-now-generally-available-run-big-data-applications-without-managing-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced three new serverless options for our data analytics services – Amazon EMR Serverless, Amazon Redshift Serverless, and Amazon MSK Serverless – that make it easier to analyze data at any scale without having to configure, scale, or manage the underlying infrastructure. Today we announce the general availability of Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security OAuth reaches End-of-Life]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/01/spring-security-oauth-reaches-end-of-life</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/01/spring-security-oauth-reaches-end-of-life"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spring Security OAuth and Spring Security OAuth Boot 2 auto-configuration projects have reached end of life.



The Spring Security OAuth project has been replaced by the Client and Resource Server support provided by Spring Security and the Authorization Server support provided by Spring Authorization Server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Support After Our Artifactory Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55942</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/improved-support-after-our-artifactory-migration/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently migrated our 10-year-old artifact storage to a new cloud-based setup. Here's a behind-the-scenes look at the migration and how you can help us continue to improve access and support. 
The post Improved Support After Our Artifactory Migration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Lange</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Released: Automation content navigator 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/released-automation-content-navigator-2.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/released-automation-content-navigator-2.0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation content navigator releases with Ansible Automation Platform 2.2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 31st, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/31/this-week-in-spring-may-31st-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/31/this-week-in-spring-may-31st-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! And welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’ve just returned from three wonderful weeks overseas and now, I’m pleased as punch to convey, that I’m home! And hopefully, COVID-19 free! Who knows what sort of nonsense I caught on the flight home, anyway. Some things, I’ve always said, shouldn’t be open source! But knowledge isn’t one of them and I had a lot of fun with this week’s roundup, so let’s dive right into it! 


  
@RequestMapping Value in Properties File

  
A Bootiful Podcast: the good Dr. David Syer on the new and novel in Spring and Kubernetes

  
A Guide to Docker Logs

  
this is something I learned about at the recent Spring IO show: an open source ticket management system - Alf.io

  
Blog: Contextual Logging in Kubernetes 1.24

  
Blog: Kubernetes 1.24: Maximum Unavailable Replicas for StatefulSet

  
Difference Between docker stop and docker kill Commands

  
Docker Registry API – Listing Images and Tags

  
Introduction to Spring Cloud Sidecar

  
Java HttpClient Timeout

  
Java Weekly, Issue 439

  
Setting Request Headers Using Feign

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.3.0 available now

  
Spring Boot and Liquibase

  
Spring Boot — Reactive Web

  
Spring Native 0.12.0 available now

  
Spring Shell 2.1.0-M4 is now available

  
Spring Vault 2.4.0-M1 and 3.0.0-M1 available

  
Spring Web Service Integration Tests with @WebServiceServerTest

  
Visual Page Design with Spring Boot - YouTube

  
JVM Parameters

  
Azure Spring Apps Enterprise is generally available. Ship faster. Leverage Spring experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating multi-vendor network prefix-lists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-multi-vendor-network-prefix-lists</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-multi-vendor-network-prefix-lists"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To keep the networks healthy, cause connectivity matters
 
I love being a network engineer, even though I struggled to explain to non-networking people about the utmost relevance of network administration. However, during the last two years of the COVID-19 pandemic, the world could see the relevance of having connectivity. Networks are the highways of information. Data, applications, entertainment, and factories need the network connectivity roads to make the world run. It’s interesting that even network models to estimate traffic behavior use algorithms that are similar to the ones to estimate transportation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Native 0.12.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/31/spring-native-0-12-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/31/spring-native-0-12-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Native 0.12.0 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release.

This release includes 12 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades to GraalVM 22.1, Spring Boot 2.7.0 and Spring Cloud 2021.0.3. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.0-M4 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/30/spring-shell-2-1-0-m4-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/30/spring-shell-2-1-0-m4-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T06:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.0-M4 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

Notable changes include:


  
Project has been updated to Boot 2.7.0

  
Command sub-system has been rewritten

  
Support registering commands dynamically

  
Execution target can now also be Function or Consumer

  
Build-in help command is rendered via a template


Please see the release notes for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – May 30, 2022]]></title>
        <id>11f85bc4066ba75d8f5b71875bdaee4c76ef9d1a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-30-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T14:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the US observes Memorial Day. South Korea also has a national Memorial Day, celebrated next week on June 6. In both countries, the day is set aside to remember those who sacrificed in service to their country. This time provides an opportunity to recognize and show our appreciation for the armed services and the important […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Camunda in a Low-code Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55577</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/integrating-camunda-in-a-low-code-platform/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Apex Process Consultants integrated Camunda Platform 7 with their low-code platform to make it easier to build processes. 
The post Integrating Camunda in a Low-code Platform appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Vault 2.4.0-M1 and 3.0.0-M1 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-vault-2-4-0-m1-and-3-0-0-m1-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-vault-2-4-0-m1-and-3-0-0-m1-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T14:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Vault 2.4.0-M1 and 3.0.0-M1 milestones have been released and are now available from repo.spring.io.



Notable new features include:





Support for PEM-encoded certificates and private keys including Elliptic Curve ("EC")



Support for Vault Repositories using versioned Key/Value secrets engines



Support for Vault-based RevisionRepository using versioned Key/Value secrets engines





Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.



Additionally, Spring Vault 3.0.0-M1 ships with:





Upgrade to Java 17 baseline, Spring Framework 6



Upgrade to AWS SDK v2





Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.



Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.



How can you help?


If you’re interested in helping out, check out the "ideal for contribution" tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-vault tag.



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Release 2.4.0-M1 on GitHub | Documentation for 2.4.0-M1 | Release 3.0.0-M1 on GitHub | Documentation for 3.0.0-M1 | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.3 is available. Compatible with Spring Boot 2.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-cloud-2021-0-3-is-available-compatible-with-spring-boot-2-7-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/05/27/spring-cloud-2021-0-3-is-available-compatible-with-spring-boot-2-7-0"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce the Spring Cloud 2021.0.3 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2021.0.3 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0.3 Release Train

This release is primarily for compatibility with Spring Boot 2.7.0 along with Spring Boot 2.6.x.

To see all the issues and pull requests in this release, please see here.
Spring Cloud Sleuth


  
Bug fixes and minor enhancements


Spring Cloud Contract


  
Bug fixes and JsonAssert upgrade


Spring Cloud Gateway


  
Bug fixes and path variable support for PrefixPath filter.


The following modules were updated as part of 2021.0.3:


  
    

      Module 
      Version 
      Issues
    

  
  
    
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M6id and C6id Instances with Up to 7.6 TB Local NVMe Storage]]></title>
        <id>dabb34f9d25282db77234ee28cb2826f74cfe7b3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-m6id-and-c6id-instances-with-up-to-7-6-tb-local-nvme-storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T21:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, we launched the Amazon EC2 M6i instances and C6i instances, our sixth-generation offerings that include 3rd generation Intel Xeon Scalable processors. Today we are expanding Amazon EC2 M6id and C6id instances, backed by NVMe-based SSD block-level instance storage physically connected to the host server. These instances are powered by the Intel Xeon Scalable […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTS 0.6 Adds New Terraform Cloud Agent and HCP Consul Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cts-0-6-new-terraform-cloud-agent-hcp-consul-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cts-0-6-new-terraform-cloud-agent-hcp-consul-support"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of HashiCorp Consul-Terraform-Sync (CTS) 0.6 represents a key step in the maturity of our Network Infrastructure Automation (NIA) solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2.2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible product team at Red Hat is thrilled to announce the general availability of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.2, which includes numerous features and bug fixes that further solidify Ansible Automation Platform as the de facto enterprise IT automation solution for developers to operations teams in data centers, clouds, and at the edge. A few of the most noteworthy features in this release include:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andriusb@redhat.com (Andrius Benokraitis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 Webinar Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55344</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-platform-8-webinar-recap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out these answers to the questions we didn't get to answer during our recent Camunda Platform 8 Release Webinar.
The post Camunda Platform 8 Webinar Recap appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning with Label Differential Privacy]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/deep-learning-with-label-differential.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/deep-learning-with-label-differential.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T20:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by  Pasin Manurangsi and Chiyuan Zhang, Research Scientists, Google Research  
Over the last several years, there has been an increased focus on developing differential privacy (DP) machine learning (ML) algorithms. DP has been the basis of several practical deployments in industry — and has even been employed by the U.S. Census — because it enables the understanding of system and algorithm privacy guarantees. The underlying assumption of DP is that changing a single user’s contribution to an algorithm should not significantly change its output distribution. 
 In the standard supervised learning setting, a model is trained to make a prediction of the label for each input given a training set of example pairs {[input1,label1], …, [inputn, labeln]}. In the case of deep learning, previ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.11 Introduces New Provider Command and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-terraform-0-11-introduces-new-provider-command</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-terraform-0-11-introduces-new-provider-command"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform (CDKTF) 0.11 introduces an easier way to add providers to your application and improvements to the debugging process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to do When You Can’t Quickly Migrate to Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=55237</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/what-to-do-when-you-cant-quickly-migrate-to-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not ready to migrate to Camunda Platform 8 yet? Learn the alternative approaches you can take now to prepare for migrating later.
The post What to do When You Can’t Quickly Migrate to Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring New Possibilities with the AWS Cloud Control Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/exploring-new-possibilities-with-the-aws-cloud-control-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/exploring-new-possibilities-with-the-aws-cloud-control-collection"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently made available an experimental alpha Collection of generated modules using the AWS Cloud Control API for interacting with AWS Services. This content is not intended for production in its current state. We are making this work available because we thought it was important to share our research and get your feedback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for AWS DataSync – Move Data Between AWS and Other Public Locations]]></title>
        <id>905a367112dd04b244491567bac3a7266994c9f7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-aws-datasync-move-data-between-aws-and-google-cloud-storage-or-aws-and-microsoft-azure-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moving data to and from AWS Storage services can be automated and accelerated with AWS DataSync. For example, you can use DataSync to migrate data to AWS, replicate data for business continuity, and move data for analysis and processing in the cloud. You can use DataSync to transfer data to and from AWS Storage services, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image-Text Pre-training with Contrastive Captioners]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/image-text-pre-training-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/image-text-pre-training-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zirui Wang and Jiahui Yu, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Oftentimes, machine learning (ML) model developers begin their design using a generic backbone model that is trained at scale and with capabilities transferable to a wide range of downstream tasks. In natural language processing, a number of popular backbone models, including BERT, T5, GPT-3 (sometimes also referred to as “foundation models”), are pre-trained on web-scale data and have demonstrated generic multi-tasking capabilities through zero-shot, few-shot or transfer learning. Compared with training over-specialized individual models, pre-training backbone models for a large number of downstream tasks can amortize the training costs, allowing one to overcome resource limitations when building large s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 C7g Instances, Powered by AWS Graviton3 Processors]]></title>
        <id>85274dcdcd66e71abf62466cd5e084f9aca8df04</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c7g-instances-powered-by-aws-graviton3-processors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T21:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am excited to announce that Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) C7g instances powered by the latest AWS Graviton3 processors that have been available in preview since re:Invent last year are now available for all. Let’s decompose the name C7g: the “C” instance family is designed for compute-intensive workloads. This is the 7th generation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review – May 23, 2022]]></title>
        <id>75cfd7cc41f56e72a28e830102fd6d20f55dbfb1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-27-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T19:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! This is the right place to quickly learn about recent AWS news from last week, in just about five minutes or less. This week, I have collected a couple of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the HCL Extension for Visual Studio Code 0.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcl-extension-for-visual-studio-code-0-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcl-extension-for-visual-studio-code-0-1"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp adopts the community-created HCL Extension for Visual Studio Code and adds HCL 2.0 support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uplevel your automation skills with Red Hat training for Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/uplevel-your-automation-skills-with-red-hat-training-for-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/uplevel-your-automation-skills-with-red-hat-training-for-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 includes major features that allow customers to onboard more easily with even more flexible automation architectures and use cases. Ansible Automation Platform enables IT professionals to automate at enterprise scale more easily and flexibly. This means that everything you know and love about writing Ansible Playbooks is largely unchanged, but what is evolving is the underlying implementation of how automation is developed, managed, and operated in large complex environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Bonneville</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Survey of Causal Inference Applications at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b62d25175e6f</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/a-survey-of-causal-inference-applications-at-netflix-b62d25175e6f?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T15:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Netflix, we want to entertain the world through creating engaging content and helping members discover the titles they will love. Key to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auth0, Fortinet, and Vercel Among New Verified Terraform Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/auth0-fortinet-and-vercel-among-new-verified-terraform-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/auth0-fortinet-and-vercel-among-new-verified-terraform-providers"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the addition of 18 new verified providers to the growing HashiCorp Terraform ecosystem we hit a milestone with 200 verified Terraform providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Java Applications to Azure using Continuous Delivery]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64092</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploying-java-applications-to-azure-using-continuous-delivery/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T10:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 3 in our series DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions and continuous delivery!
April: [00:00:00] Tune in into this week’s episode of the DevOps lab,
The post Deploying Java Applications to Azure using Continuous Delivery appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a Java Application to Azure using Continuous Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64087</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-a-java-application-to-azure-using-continuous-integration/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T07:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 2 in our series for DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions and continuous integration.
April: We’re back this week with the dev ops lab and we’re continuing our series DevOps for Java shops.
The post Deploy a Java Application to Azure using Continuous Integration appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Do Accessible Design and Engineering at HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-do-accessible-design-and-engineering-at-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-do-accessible-design-and-engineering-at-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two HashiCorp engineers discuss accessible design and engineering at HashiCorp, from overall principles to the tools we use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to Azure Pipelines Runtime Variables Settings [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63937</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/updates-to-azure-pipelines-runtime-variables-settings/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have gotten a lot of feedback on this change and after internal deliberation, we are now rolling back this change ASAP.
We have now fully rolled back the change that caused the issue.
The post Updates to Azure Pipelines Runtime Variables Settings [Updated] appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.8 Expands Health and Events Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-8-expands-health-and-events-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-8-expands-health-and-events-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.8 adds key observability features and improvements to identity-based secure remote access for dynamic infrastructure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64084</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-a-java-application-to-azure-app-service-using-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T07:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 1 in our series for DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions. Brian also covers off feature flags!
April: Welcome to this week’s episode of the dev ops lab.
The post Deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.2 Improves Exception Handling and Updates to the CLI-driven Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-2-improves-exception-handling-and-updates-to-the-cli-driven-workflow</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-2-improves-exception-handling-and-updates-to-the-cli-driven-workflow"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now generally available, HashiCorp Terraform 1.2 introduces exception handling with pre- and post-conditions, support for non-interactive Terraform Cloud operations in a CI/CD pipeline, and CLI support for Run Tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Backup Now Supports Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP]]></title>
        <id>4a4714ab05fe013a182547e67a8696dc9531dab4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-backup-now-supports-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T20:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a long-time reader of this blog, you know that I categorize some posts as “chocolate and peanut butter” in homage to an ancient (1970 or so) series of TV commercials for Reese’s Peanut Butter Cups. Today, I am happy to bring you the latest such post, combining AWS Backup and Amazon FSx […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector-Quantized Image Modeling with Improved VQGAN]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/vector-quantized-image-modeling-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/vector-quantized-image-modeling-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jiahui Yu, Senior Research Scientist, and Jing Yu Koh, Research Software Engineer, Google Research 
In recent years, natural language processing models have dramatically improved their ability to learn general-purpose representations, which has resulted in significant performance gains for a wide range of natural language generation and natural language understanding tasks. In large part, this has been accomplished through pre-training language models on extensive unlabeled text corpora.  
This pre-training formulation does not make assumptions about input signal modality, which can be language, vision, or audio, among others. Several recent papers have exploited this formulation to dramatically improve image generation results through pre-quantizing images into discrete integer …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>