<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-08-23T00:20:28.808Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-08-23T00:20:28.808Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audible dot con]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11475</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/22/audible-dot-con/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=audible-dot-con"/>
        <updated>2021-08-22T15:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Audible is a non-functional product and I’m taking their market with a new kind of audio product.
The post Audible dot con appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Process Automation Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=27320</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/08/how-to-choose-a-process-automation-tool/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T19:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All automation tools are not created equal. It’s important that you choose the right tool for the job.
The post How to Choose a Process Automation Tool appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Planning Options: -refresh=false, -refresh-only, -replace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-planning-options-refresh-false-refresh-only-replace</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-planning-options-refresh-false-refresh-only-replace"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make changes to your infrastructure in Terraform Cloud and Terraform Enterprise faster with the new -refresh=false, -refresh-only, and replace planning options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pragma: Video Games with Eden Chen]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11472</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/20/pragma-video-games-with-eden-chen/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pragma-video-games-with-eden-chen"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T09:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“In October 1958, Physicist William Higinbotham created what is thought to be the first video game. It was a very simple tennis game, similar to the classic 1970s video game Pong, and it was quite a hit at a Brookhaven National Laboratory open house” (aps.org). 63 years have passed, and video games are prolific. The
The post Pragma: Video Games with Eden Chen appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[News Story Reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2505/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2505/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/news_story_reaction.png" title="Unless the next line is, &quot;After we broke up, she blamed the painting and spent years planning her revenge, so my sorrow is mixed with relief that the dogs at least denied her that triumph.&quot;" alt="Unless the next line is, &quot;After we broke up, she blamed the painting and spent years planning her revenge, so my sorrow is mixed with relief that the dogs at least denied her that triumph.&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.0-M2 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/19/spring-boot-2-6-0-m2-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/19/spring-boot-2-6-0-m2-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T18:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.0-M2 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes more than a 100 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon MemoryDB for Redis – A Redis-Compatible, Durable, In-Memory Database Service]]></title>
        <id>c0f4c867c6984fe656087db346b578b038cd1735</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/ubxMIL1QGYc/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T17:42:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive applications need to process requests and respond very quickly, and this requirement extends to all the components of their architecture. That is even more important when you adopt microservices and your architecture is composed of many small independent services that communicate with each other. For this reason, database performance is critical to the success […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InfluxData: Time-Series Data with Russ Savage]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11450</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/19/influxdata-time-series-data-with-russ-savage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=influxdata-time-series-data-with-russ-savage"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T17:09:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time series data are simply measurements or events that are tracked, monitored, downsampled, and aggregated over time. This could be server metrics, application performance monitoring, network data, sensor data, events, clicks, trades in a market, and many other types of analytics data (influxdata.com). The platform InfluxData is designed for building and operating time series applications.
The post InfluxData: Time-Series Data with Russ Savage appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Workspace Tags for Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-workspace-tags-for-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-workspace-tags-for-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud gives you a quick and easy new way to search and filter workspaces based on tags.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.4 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/19/spring-boot-2-5-4-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/19/spring-boot-2-5-4-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T13:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.4 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 35 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft Azure engineering manager Rome Li on his work supporting Microsoft Azure in IntelliJ, Visual Studio, Maven, Eclipse, and Visual Studio Code]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/19/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-azure-engineering-manager-rome-li-on-his-work-supporting-microsoft-azure-in-intellij-visual-studio-maven-eclipse-and-visual-studio-code</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/19/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-azure-engineering-manager-rome-li-on-his-work-supporting-microsoft-azure-in-intellij-visual-studio-maven-eclipse-and-visual-studio-code"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Microsoft’s Rome Li (@akalirong) on his work supporting Microsoft Azure from IntelliJ, Visual Studio, Maven, Eclipse, and Visual Studio Code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.4.10 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/19/spring-boot-2-4-10-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/19/spring-boot-2-4-10-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T11:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.4.10 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 29 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server goes to production !]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/19/spring-authorization-server-goes-to-production</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/19/spring-authorization-server-goes-to-production"/>
        <updated>2021-08-19T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my great pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.2.0.



This release is the first officially supported production-ready version backed by our new support policy.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




compile 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.2.0'




See the release notes for complete details.



For additional details on this project, see the latest and initial announcement and the project page.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the sample to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues |  ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 common questions answered with formulas and time travel in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/kibana-10-common-questions-formulas-time-series-maps</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/kibana-10-common-questions-formulas-time-series-maps"/>
        <updated>2021-08-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kibana creates easy ways to do powerful things with all of your data — to ask and answer questions and follow the flow of analysis. Many times the answer to your question requires calculations based on queried data. Formulas allow you to author your own metrics by combining multiple aggregated fields using math operations.

In addition, moving through and replaying your data in time and space are powerful ways to gain historical context and understand additional insight about the present.

In the below sections you’ll find 10 examples of questions you can answer with dashboard data and map visualizations in Kibana via formulas, time shifts, and moving through data in time. Try following along with your own data or using Kibana’s sample datasets. Have a question? Head on over to our discuss…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Hudgins,Adeline Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Survey Finds Both Offensive, Defensive Drivers for Multi-Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-offensive-defensive-drivers-multi-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-offensive-defensive-drivers-multi-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-08-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on the HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey, we take a deep dive into the business and technology factors driving — and blocking — multi-cloud adoption, including a look at the pandemic's complex effects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Google Cloud instance types on Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-new-google-cloud-instance-types-on-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-new-google-cloud-instance-types-on-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-08-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce support for Google Compute Engine (GCE) N2 general purpose virtual machine (VM) types, and additional hardware configuration options powered by N2 custom machine types. 

N2 VMs leverage Intel 2nd Generation Xeon Scalable processors and provide a balance of compute, memory, and storage. N2 machine types also offer more than a 20% improvement in price-performance over the first-generation N1 machines.



When you provision an Elastic deployment on Google Cloud you will automatically leverage N2 VM types. You can select the default configuration, or choose one of four custom configurations. This optionality allows you to select a combination of vCPU, RAM, and storage to deliver optimal performance for your specific use case. For example, you may select a configurat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Derazon,Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.11.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/18/spring-tools-4-11-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/18/spring-tools-4-11-1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-08-18T11:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.11.1 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
Fixes in this release


  
(VS Code, Spring Boot) fixed: [codespaces] spring boot extension starting up multiple times in Codespaces setting (#669)

  
(VS Code, Spring Boot) fixed: [codespaces] spring boot extension doesn’t find the right JDK when connecting to a codespace (#670)

  
(VS Code, Spring Boot) fixed: JAVA_Home should be right but still shows “Note Java 8 can still be used in your own projects” (#664)

  
(Eclipse) improvement: progress view shows many AsyncLiveExpression refresh messages and doesn’t respond anymore (#653)

  
(Eclipse) improvement: latest CI builds do not show port of running app anymore (#659)

  
(Concourse) improvement: Property ‘commit_message’ not recognized for semver resources (#655)

  
(Concourse) improvement: GitResource schema, add missing properties (#671)

  
(Concourse) improvement: Unknown property ‘fetch_tags’ for type ‘GitSource’(YamlSchemaProblem) (#668)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Spring Tools 4.12.0 is scheduled to be released in late September 2021.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unstoppable Domains: Blockchain Domains with Matthew Gould]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11449</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/18/unstoppable-domains-blockchain-domains-with-matthew-gould/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=unstoppable-domains-blockchain-domains-with-matthew-gould"/>
        <updated>2021-08-18T09:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Domain names are the address of your website that people type into the browser URL bar. Once purchased, a domain name is stored on your behalf by custodians like Google domains. Blockchain domains, on the other hand, are similar to regular domain names except they are stored and controlled in your cryptocurrency wallet. The company
The post Unstoppable Domains: Blockchain Domains with Matthew Gould appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fissile Raspberry Isotopes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2504/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2504/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/fissile_raspberry_isotopes.png" title="Grandma's shelf-stable blackberry pie meson recipe was a huge seller until her farm was shut down by a joint FDA/NRC investigation." alt="Grandma's shelf-stable blackberry pie meson recipe was a huge seller until her farm was shut down by a joint FDA/NRC investigation." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full-cycle observability with the Elastic Stack and Lightrun]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/full-cycle-observability-with-the-elastic-stack-and-lightrun</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/full-cycle-observability-with-the-elastic-stack-and-lightrun"/>
        <updated>2021-08-17T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post was written in collaboration with the team at Lightrun: Itai Tieger, Roy Chen, and Tom Granot. Itai is an R&D team leader specializing in cybersecurity, with over 10 years of experience in the industry. Roy is a software engineer with over 6 years of diverse experience in multiple disciplines. Tom is a solution engineer and a former site reliability engineer.

An application running in production is a difficult beast to tame.

Most experienced developers–ones who spent enough late nights or Saturday mornings trying to break apart a nasty production bug–will try and create the clearest possible picture for their later selves while writing their code, so that they could understand what’s actually going on in the system during an incident. 

To make life easier, developers can …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daliya Spasova,Philipp Krenn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.1 RTW now available]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62215</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2020-1-1-rtw-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-17T18:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we released Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.1 RTW. This is our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.1. You can directly install Azure DevOps Server 2020 Update 1.1 or upgrade from Azure DevOps Server 2020 or Team Foundation Server 2013 or newer.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.1 RTW now available appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 51 – Deploy With ARM Templates with @shankuehn]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62081</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-51-deploy-with-arm-templates-with-shankuehn/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-17T14:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 51 – Deploy With ARM Templates with @shankuehn appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 17th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/17/this-week-in-spring-august-17th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/17/this-week-in-spring-august-17th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-08-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How’re you doing? I’m alright. I’ve been recuperating from a COVID-19 infection. Today was the first day in a while that I woke up and wasn’t short of breath. Most days, I’ve woken up, hacked a few wads of phlegm into the toilet, and then my breathing was fine. But today I woke up and wasn’t short of breath in the first place. (I still hacked a few wads of phlegm). Thank goodness for vaccines, or I expect my experience of this virus would’ve been much worse as a lifelong asthmatic. Things are looking up! 

And then, as if my fortunes couldn’t get any better, I got to compiling this week’s roundup and there’s a ton of great stuff in it so let’s dive right in!


  
Get started with Spring Boot and the CQRS framework Axon

  
In last week’s installment of A Bootiful Podcast: Neo4J CEO and Spring Data cofounder Emil Eifrem on graphs, Neo4J, and more

  
Alexa Request Validation with Spring Cloud Gateway

  
Free Java & OpenJDK Info for Daily Java Usage

  
Spring Authorization Server officially moves to spring-projects

  
Spring Data 2021.0.4 and 2020.0.12 released

  
Spring Data 2021.1.0-M2 released

  
Spring WebClient with Feign

  
Get hands-on with Azure Spring Cloud in 90 minutes.

  
Did you see Cora Iberkleid’s power session on Spring Cloud Gateway? It was awesome!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server officially moves to spring-projects]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/17/spring-authorization-server-officially-moves-to-spring-projects</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/17/spring-authorization-server-officially-moves-to-spring-projects"/>
        <updated>2021-08-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are very excited to announce that Spring Authorization Server has officially moved out of experimental status and into the Spring project’s portfolio!



This move coincides with this week’s 0.2.0 release, which is the first officially supported production-ready version backed by our new support policy.



Since announcing the Spring Authorization Server in April 2020, the implemented features provide support for a large portion of the OAuth 2.1 Authorization Framework and modest support for OpenID Connect 1.0. However, as we move onto the next phase of development, our focus changes to advancing the support for OpenID Connect 1.0.



On behalf of the team, I would like to thank everyone who has contributed and helped grow this project in this short time frame. We are confident in the base that we have built so far and are excited for the next phase of the project. We look forward to continuing this work together and ultimately making Spring Authorization Server the de facto framework for OAuth 2 Authorization Server support on the Java platform.



Let’s get moving onto the next phase!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[getoctane.io: Pay-As-You-Go Pricing with Akash Khanolkar]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11448</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/17/octane-io-pay-as-you-go-pricing-with-akash-khanolkar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=octane-io-pay-as-you-go-pricing-with-akash-khanolkar"/>
        <updated>2021-08-17T09:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pay-as-you-go pricing has become a strong selling point for modern SaaS companies as well as cloud-based companies. Public cloud providers, for example, typically only charge you for only what you use. But implementing this option is challenging because it requires advanced platform analytics. The company Octane is a drop-in metered billing system that gives you
The post getoctane.io: Pay-As-You-Go Pricing with Akash Khanolkar appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 M6i Instances Powered by the Latest-Generation Intel Xeon Scalable Processors]]></title>
        <id>f37eb47e4e2a70fab81aae10293c94725350cb8a</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/LSIPPm7qjYU/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-16T21:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, we introduced the sixth generation of EC2 instances powered by AWS-designed Graviton2 processors. We’re now expanding our sixth-generation offerings to include x86-based instances, delivering price/performance benefits for workloads that rely on x86 instructions. Today, I am happy to announce the availability of the new general purpose Amazon EC2 M6i instances, which offer up to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Vault Tutorials: Vault 1.8 Release Highlights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-vault-tutorials-vault-1-8-release-highlights</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-vault-tutorials-vault-1-8-release-highlights"/>
        <updated>2021-08-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try out the new and enhanced features introduced in Vault 1.8 with step-by-step tutorials on HashiCorp Learn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: What Camunda Platform Architecture Are You?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=26096</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/08/podcast-what-camunda-platform-architecture-are-you/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-16T14:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the Camunda Nation podcast is live. Join us on a journey through the BPMN Diagram to find your ideal Camunda Platform architecture. 
The post Podcast: What Camunda Platform Architecture Are You? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Druid: Event-Driven Data with Eric Tschetter]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11447</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/16/druid-event-driven-data-with-eric-tschetter/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=druid-event-driven-data-with-eric-tschetter"/>
        <updated>2021-08-16T09:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether sending messages, shopping in an app, or watching videos, modern consumers expect information and responsiveness to be near-instant in their apps and devices. From a developer’s perspective, this means clean code and a fast database.  Apache Druid is a database built to power real-time analytic workloads for event-driven data, like user-facing applications, streaming, and
The post Druid: Event-Driven Data with Eric Tschetter appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memo Spike Connector]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2503/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2503/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/memo_spike_connector.png" title="Backward-compatible with many existing cables, and can connect directly to phones or tablets if you press them down hard enough." alt="Backward-compatible with many existing cables, and can connect directly to phones or tablets if you press them down hard enough." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Facebook Works: Comparing its Engineering Process to Google, Microsoft, and Amazon]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11445</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/14/how-facebook-works-comparing-its-engineering-process-to-google-microsoft-and-amazon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-facebook-works-comparing-its-engineering-process-to-google-microsoft-and-amazon"/>
        <updated>2021-08-14T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This episode was published on the GeekWire podcast. Subscribe to GeekWire for more great content. Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg told employees recently that the company’s long-term goal is to “bring the metaverse to life” — helping to create an interconnected world of physical, virtual and augmented reality spaces that will reshape the way we work, interact with
The post How Facebook Works: Comparing its Engineering Process to Google, Microsoft, and Amazon appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Account Data Sharing for Amazon Redshift]]></title>
        <id>903ccd8fce8570d9ea1622cb7649dffac71ba65f</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/6auMmTu8udw/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-13T16:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be successful in today’s fast-moving world, businesses need to analyze data quickly and take meaningful action. Many of our customers embrace this concept to become data-driven organizations. Data-driven organizations treat data as an asset and use it to improve their insights and make better decisions. They unleash the power of data by using secure […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Beeby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Releasing Camunda Platform Community Helm Chart]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=26961</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/08/releasing-camunda-platform-community-helm-chart/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-13T13:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Kubernetes being pretty ubiquitous today, we decided it was time to help you deploy Camunda Platform on Kubernetes in a snap, so we created the Community Helm Chart.
The post Releasing Camunda Platform Community Helm Chart appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.08.13]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62194</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-08-13/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-13T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.08.13 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.08.13 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DaaS with Auren Hoffman]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11436</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/13/daas-with-auren-hoffman/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=daas-with-auren-hoffman"/>
        <updated>2021-08-13T09:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Auren Hoffman is the CEO of SafeGraph. In this episode we discuss data as a service and more. This interview was also recorded as a video podcast. Check out the video on the Software Daily YouTube channel. Sponsorship inquiries: sponsor@softwareengineeringdaily.com
The post DaaS with Auren Hoffman appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Data Table]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2502/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2502/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/every_data_table.png" title="I'm hoping 2022 is relatively normal because I don't know what symbol comes after the asterisk and the dagger." alt="I'm hoping 2022 is relatively normal because I don't know what symbol comes after the asterisk and the dagger." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Waypoint 0.5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-waypoint-0-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-waypoint-0-5"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Waypoint 0.5 focuses on visibility around your application deployments and introduces governance for teams to enable better traceability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.1.0-M2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/12/spring-data-2021-1-0-m2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/12/spring-data-2021-1-0-m2-released"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T18:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data 2021.1.0-M2 milestone release.

The release is built on top of Spring Framework 5.3.9.
For your convenience, you can consume this release through Spring Boot 2.6.0-M2, which our team mates on the Boot team will release in about a week.

To round things off, here are the links to the artifacts, changelogs, and documentation:


  
Spring Data Commons 2.6 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.3 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.6 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data for Apache Cassandra 3.3 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data KeyValue 2.6 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data Neo4j 6.2 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data MongoDB 3.3 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data for Apache Geode 2.6 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data R2DBC 1.4 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data LDAP 2.6 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data Envers 2.6 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data REST 3.6 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data Redis 2.6 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data Elasticsearch 4.3 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data Couchbase 4.3 M2 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.0.4 and 2020.0.12 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/12/spring-data-2021-0-4-and-2020-0-12-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/12/spring-data-2021-0-4-and-2020-0-12-released"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T18:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data2021.0.4 and 2020.0.12 service releases.

Both releases are built on top of Spring Framework 5.3.9. For your convenience, you can consume these releases through Spring Boot 2.5.4 and 2.4.10, respectively. Our teammates on the Boot team will release those in about a week.

The service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.

To round things off, here are the links to the artifacts, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.0.4


  
Spring Data Commons 2.5.4 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.2.4 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.5.4 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data for Apache Cass…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Establish robust threat intelligence with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/establish-robust-threat-intelligence-with-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/establish-robust-threat-intelligence-with-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a powerful search engine, Elasticsearch provides various ways to collect and enrich data with threat intel feeds, while the Elastic Security detection engine helps security analysts to detect alerts with threat indicator matching. In this blog post, we’ll provide an introduction to threat intelligence and demonstrate how Elastic Security can help organizations establish robust cyber threat intelligence (CTI) capabilities.

CTI is contextual information obtained through research and analysis of emerging threats and the application of defensive countermeasures to enhance the protective posture of contested environments. It helps organizations to better understand past, current, and future threats. 

Threat feeds that can be obtained from various open source and commercial platforms become…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haran Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2021 Keynotes Revealed: Angie Jones & Hannah Fry]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=26973</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/08/camundacon-2021-keynotes-revealedangie-jones-hannah-fry/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to share two new keynote speakers who we just added to our CamundaCon 2021 agenda, each of whom will be leading important discussions related to process automation. 
The post CamundaCon 2021 Keynotes Revealed: Angie Jones & Hannah Fry appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gottfried Sehringer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Neo4J CEO and Spring Data cofounder Emil Eifrem on graphs, Neo4J, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/12/a-bootiful-podcast-neo4j-ceo-and-spring-data-cofounder-emil-eifrem-on-graphs-neo4j-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/12/a-bootiful-podcast-neo4j-ceo-and-spring-data-cofounder-emil-eifrem-on-graphs-neo4j-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Neo4j CEO and Spring Data cofounder Emil Eifrem (@emileifrem) .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Run: Serverless Applications with Steren Giannini]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11403</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/12/cloud-run-serverless-applications-with-steren-giannini/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cloud-run-serverless-applications-with-steren-giannini"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T09:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless computing is a cloud computing solution that lets developers deploy applications to containers without managing the servers themselves. Servers and resources are provisioned automatically, pay only for what you use, and experience little to no errors or downtime (ionos). Google Cloud Run is a managed compute platform that enables you to run containers that
The post Cloud Run: Serverless Applications with Steren Giannini appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey: Welcome to the Multi-Cloud Era]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-welcome-to-the-multi-cloud-era</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-welcome-to-the-multi-cloud-era"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our inaugural cloud strategy survey reveals that multi-cloud is now the new normal, driven by digital transformation, with skill shortages, security, and COVID having complex impacts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Best Practices – Structuring Your Repository for Static Web Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62165</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/developer-best-practices-structuring-your-repository-for-static-web-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T15:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Best Practices – YAML Exposure in your pipeline
The post Developer Best Practices – Structuring Your Repository for Static Web Apps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Read active log files more quickly and easily with the new filestream input in Filebeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/read-active-log-files-more-quickly-and-easily-with-the-new-filestream-input-in-filebeat</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/read-active-log-files-more-quickly-and-easily-with-the-new-filestream-input-in-filebeat"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Elastic 7.14, the filestream input, the successor of log input, is now generally available in Filebeat. This new, superior input provides better support for reading active log files, with faster reaction time when there is backpressure in the system, quicker registry updates, better cooperation with external log rotation tools, and more. 
 
Improved registry performance
 
Previously, when a registry file (the file used for saving the progress of publishing events) contained many entries, state updates became slower, even if Filebeat was only collecting a few files. The main problem was that the complete registry was serialized after every ACK from the outputs. That required an expensive fsync call per registry write. Now offset updates are written to the file in an append-only manner.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noémi Ványi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argos Security: Cloud Configuration Security with David O’Brien]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11405</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/11/argos-security-cloud-configuration-security-with-david-obrien/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=argos-security-cloud-configuration-security-with-david-obrien"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T09:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Fugue’s new State of Cloud Security 2020 report, cloud misconfiguration remains the top cause of data breaches in the cloud, and millions of database servers are currently exposed across cloud providers. Some of the leading reasons are a lack of adequate oversight and too many APIs and interfaces to govern. (securityaffairs.co).  Argos Security
The post Argos Security: Cloud Configuration Security with David O’Brien appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Vulnerability with Eric Simons]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11425</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/10/react-vulnerability-with-eric-simons/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=react-vulnerability-with-eric-simons"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T22:50:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stackblitz CEO Eric Simons and Jeff Meyerson discuss a serious vulnerability in React.   Also available on Dropbox, please download this. https://www.dropbox.com/s/9u0m52xj04vqggc/React%20Vulnerability%20with%20Eric%20Simons.mp3?dl=0
The post React Vulnerability with Eric Simons appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fly.io: Geographic App Deployment with Kurt Mackey]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11404</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/10/fly-io-geographic-app-deployment-with-kurt-mackey/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fly-io-geographic-app-deployment-with-kurt-mackey"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T20:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Latency is the time it takes to get from point A to point B. In programming, this might be the time from a user selecting their photos library to the pictures reaching their computer screen from the database.  Fly.io is a simple platform for running full-stack apps and databases close to your users. Some available
The post Fly.io: Geographic App Deployment with Kurt Mackey appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[August patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62180</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/august-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T20:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the August patches, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Fix build definition UI error.
Changed browsing history to display files instead of the root repository.
Fix issue with email delivery jobs for some work item types.
The post August patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Kubernetes User's Guide to HashiCorp Nomad Secret Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-kubernetes-user-s-guide-to-hashicorp-nomad-secret-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-kubernetes-user-s-guide-to-hashicorp-nomad-secret-management"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how secrets management in Kubernetes compares to HashiCorp Nomad, and see why HashiCorp Vault is a powerful solution for both.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Boundary 0.5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-boundary-0-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-boundary-0-5"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.5 and Boundary Desktop 1.2.1 include a new event logging system along with enhancements to the admin console and sessions cleanup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.0.0-alpha1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-0-0-alpha1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-0-0-alpha1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the 7.x minors keep delivering feature after feature, we are thrilled to announce the first public alpha of 8.0.0.

Before we continue with this exciting news, we want to remind you that this is an alpha version. We recommend that you keep it an arm's length from production. There is no guarantee that 8.0.0-alpha1 will be compatible with other preview releases or with 8.0.0 general availability (GA).

Also, 8.0.0-alpha1 will not be available on Elastic Cloud. But, we expect to make a preview version available in the coming months.

The Elastic Pioneer Program
We are also excited to bring back the Elastic Pioneer Program for 8.0. The Pioneer Program debuted in version 5.0 to recognize community participation and feedback. It has been a source of invaluable feedback during the preview …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Krenn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 50 – Intro to @BicepLang with @adotfrank]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62077</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-50-intro-to-biceplang-with-adotfrank/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 50 – Intro to @BicepLang with @adotfrank appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16.0-alpha4 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=26270</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/08/camunda-platform-runtime-7160-alpha4-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T08:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the fourth alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16. This release features improvements such as Initial Quarkus 2.0 support, Liquibase support and 8 bug fixes.
The post Camunda Platform Runtime 7.16.0-alpha4 Release appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda BPM Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.6.0-alpha1 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=26530</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/08/camunda-optimize-3-6-0-alpha1-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T08:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.6.0-alpha1. Discover the highlights of the new capabilities introduced in Optimize 3.6.0-alpha1.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.6.0-alpha1 Release appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.2.0-alpha1 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=26526</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/camunda-cloud-120-alpha1-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T07:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Cloud 1.2.0-alpha1, the first alpha release for our next stable minor release in October. 
The post Camunda Cloud 1.2.0-alpha1 Release appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 10th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/10/this-week-in-spring-august-10th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/10/this-week-in-spring-august-10th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! How’re you doing? I hope you’re doing well. You know, I’ve been thinking a lot about how to retain that zen-like peace that comes with a vacation spent on the beach. I got back from Hawaii eight days ago and I found it to be so very beautiful. Nature really sold it for me; the fresh air is everything. If you don’t have ready access to nature - if you, like me, are in a giant city with the ongoing sound of car horns (“klaxons”), fire engines, traffic, and everything else that accompanies any big city - then may I invite you to breathe with me? 

Just sit still for 30 seconds. Focus on these words. Inhale. Take a big, deep breath, and then hold it in for a few seconds. Then exhale. When was the last time you did that? I don’t do that nearly enough. If I spend 30 or 60 secon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DTC: Content Creation with Daniel Snow]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11402</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/09/dtc-content-creation-with-daniel-snow/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dtc-content-creation-with-daniel-snow"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T19:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Direct-to-Consumer companies sell their products without going through a traditional middleman like an outlet store or wholesaler. By posting content on platforms like TikTok, Facebook, and YouTube, companies can reach millions of users.TikTok, for example, has an estimated 1 billion monthly active users (wallaroomedia). The company Kindred Studios helps direct-to-consumer companies create consistent, beautiful content
The post DTC: Content Creation with Daniel Snow appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第151話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496438639193</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496438639193"/>
        <updated>2021-08-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.08.06]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62155</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-08-06/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T13:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday, and every Friday we try to bring you the latest and greatest in content about DevOps. This week we dedicate this list of community posts to our lost friend, Abel Wang. Abel was always about elevating the community and helping others do their best.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.08.06 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Material Security with Ryan Noon]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11347</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/06/material-security-with-ryan-noon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=material-security-with-ryan-noon"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T09:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Noon is the CEO of Material Security.   This interview was also recorded as a video podcast. Check out the video on the Software Daily YouTube channel.   Sponsorship inquiries: sponsor@softwareengineeringdaily.com
The post Material Security with Ryan Noon appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wasp-Lang: Boilerplate Code with Matija Sosic]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11340</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/05/wasp-lang-boilerplate-code-with-matija-sosic/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wasp-lang-boilerplate-code-with-matija-sosic"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T19:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “boilerplate code” refers to code sections that are repeated across many projects with little to no variation. Every developer is familiar with boilerplate code, whether it be pom.xml files in Java or setting up React.js applications, tweaking boilerplate code for every project is inevitable. Actually, the company Wasp believes writing boilerplate code doesn’t
The post Wasp-Lang: Boilerplate Code with Matija Sosic appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft's Sean Li on Azure, Spring Boot, Azure Spring Cloud, Spring integrations and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/05/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-sean-li-on-azure-spring-boot-azure-spring-cloud-spring-integrations-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/05/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-sean-li-on-azure-spring-boot-azure-spring-cloud-spring-integrations-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long talks to Microsoft’s Sean Li on Azure, Spring Boot, Azure Spring Cloud, Spring integrations and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application Observability with HCP Consul and Datadog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/application-observability-with-hcp-consul-and-datadog</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/application-observability-with-hcp-consul-and-datadog"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spend more time improving observability rather than maintaining infrastructure with HCP Consul and Datadog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Presents: Migrating Your Data – Migrate your MongoDB data to Cosmos DB]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=61981</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-presents-migrating-your-data-migrate-your-mongodb-data-to-cosmos-db/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T15:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last time, I showed you how to create a Cosmos DB account for your MongoDB data using an ARM template. This time, we’ll use the Azure Database Migration Service (DBMS) to migrate my data I have on a Virtual Machine into Cosmos DB.
The post AzureFunBytes Presents: Migrating Your Data – Migrate your MongoDB data to Cosmos DB appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four unexpected benefits of working in a distributed engineering org]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-four-unexpected-benefits-of-working-in-a-distributed-engineering-org</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-four-unexpected-benefits-of-working-in-a-distributed-engineering-org"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software engineers cite constant distractions, long commute times, and a lack of flexibility as the biggest challenges of working in an office setting, according to an internal employee survey conducted by the Elastic Culture team. But the survey also revealed that the biggest benefits of a distributed environment could be the new opportunities it opens for employees — for example, the freedom to catch some waves during the workday.

As Elastic offices slowly begin to reopen worldwide in accordance with local guidelines, we asked our Engineering and Product teams why they value being able to work for a company that’s distributed by intention — whether they work in an office, a shared workspace, or from home. 

You can improve your physical and mental health
Of the Elasticians we surveyed, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extract Insights From Customer Conversations with Amazon Transcribe Call Analytics]]></title>
        <id>2e1848a3c16dd182412ffc24ea189f3aa5a05a7c</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/u3VRBOAMpCM/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T18:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2017, we launched Amazon Transcribe, an automatic speech recognition (ASR) service that makes it easy to add speech-to-text capabilities to any application. Today, I’m very happy to announce the availability of Amazon Transcribe Call Analytics, a new feature that lets you easily extract valuable insights from customer conversations with a single API call. Each […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault Secrets in a Browser Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-browser-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-browser-plugin"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to fetch secrets from Vault with a custom Chrome extension in the latest HashiCorp Learn tutorial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Managed Identities with the HashiCorp Stack: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/azure-managed-identities-with-the-hashicorp-stack-part-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/azure-managed-identities-with-the-hashicorp-stack-part-2"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets management with HashiCorp Vault can use Microsoft Azure managed identities to ease the operational burden of Vault cluster availability: Part 2 in a series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized for innovation by Google Cloud and Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-recognized-for-innovation-by-google-cloud-and-microsoft</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-recognized-for-innovation-by-google-cloud-and-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic received honors from two key partners, Microsoft and Google — a recognition of our efforts to ensure that customers can easily find and use Elastic products in the environments that best suit their needs.

Elastic was named the 2021 Microsoft US Partner Award Winner in Business Excellence in the Commercial Marketplace. In addition, for the second year in a row, Elastic was selected by Google Cloud as the 2020 Technology Partner of the Year for Data Management.

We understand that more organizations are procuring software via marketplaces to ease compliance, cost, and operational complexity within their technology landscape. Through our cloud partnerships with Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure, and others, including Amazon Web Services, our customers can gain access to both free and pai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurent Mechain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okteto: Cloud-Native Applications on Kubernetes with Ramiro Berreleza]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11338</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/04/okteto-with-ramiro-berreleza/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=okteto-with-ramiro-berreleza"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T09:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is an open-source container orchestration system. It makes managing container clusters possible as well as deploying code changes to these containers. Microservice architecture is widely used today in large part because of Kubernetes. However, using it can require a large time commitment due to its learning curve. The company Okteto empowers developers to innovate
The post Okteto: Cloud-Native Applications on Kubernetes with Ramiro Berreleza appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Compelling ROI Case for Camunda]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=25892</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/08/a-compelling-roi-case-for-camunda/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T08:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Forrester Consulting spoke to six longtime Camunda Platform users, they learned how they’re delivering process automation projects faster, driving organizational efficiency and better customer service with massive, multi-million dollar impact to the business. Download the Total Economic Impact study commissioned by Camunda. 
The post A Compelling ROI Case for Camunda appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Rogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Better Data-Driven Applications with Spring Boot and Redis]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/04/spring-tips-better-data-driven-applications-with-spring-boot-and-redis</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/04/spring-tips-better-data-driven-applications-with-spring-boot-and-redis"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Redis is the swiss-army knife of databases and it integrates into Spring-based workloads with ease. In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) and special guest star Brian Sam-Bodden (@bsbodden) look at just a few of the bootiful possibilities for Redis and Spring Boot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beta Support for CRDs in the Terraform Provider for Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/beta-support-for-crds-in-the-terraform-provider-for-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/beta-support-for-crds-in-the-terraform-provider-for-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kubernetes_manifest resource has now graduated into the official Kubernetes provider as a beta, bringing support for CRDs and custom resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 7.14.0 introduces the industry’s first free and open Limitless XDR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the general availability (GA) of Elastic 7.14, including our Elastic Enterprise Search, Observability, and Security solutions, which are built into the Elastic Stack — Elasticsearch and Kibana. 

Elastic 7.14 empowers organizations with the first free and open Limitless XDR, which delivers unified SIEM and endpoint security capabilities in one platform. 

The latest release makes it even easier to manage and monitor data from a growing volume of diverse sources. With Elastic Agent, security practitioners benefit from integrated ransomware and malware prevention as well as remediation on all of their hosts. Users of Elastic Observability can get better visibility across their applications and infrastructure, as well as secure centralized agent management, with Ela…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kearns,Angelos Kottas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Security 7.14: Protect your company with Limitless XDR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 7.14 introduces the industry’s first free and open Limitless XDR solution, unifying the capabilities of SIEM and endpoint security. It is made possible by the general availability of Elastic Agent, which helps equip it to prevent, detect, and respond to threats before adversaries can steal sensitive information or sabotage operations. Let’s dig into the best of what it brings.
Quickly quarantine and inspect endpoints
Elastic Security 7.14 accelerates response by enabling analysts to invoke response actions with Elastic Agent. With the first native response action for Elastic Agent, host isolation, analysts can address malicious activity by quarantining a host from a network, containing the attack and preventing lateral movement to other hosts. Try it out with the Endpoint …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Settle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 7.14: Unified telemetry and accelerated application root cause analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 7.14 introduces the general availability of unified telemetry and centralized agent management with Elastic Agent and Fleet, enabling faster and simpler data onboarding, and reduced security risk, in addition to enhanced correlations for accelerated root cause analysis in Elastic APM. 

These new features allow customers to:

Collect all forms of data from anywhere with a single unified agent per host, with just one agent to install, configure, and scale
Deploy endpoint security seamlessly across their infrastructure, bringing DevOps and security teams into greater convergence
Quickly surface factors that have the most significant impact on service performance
Elastic Observability 7.14 is available now on Elastic Cloud — the only hosted Elasticsearch offering to incl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Elastic Enterprise Search 7.14: Kibana integration and precision tuning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 7.14 now lets you manage all your Elastic products from a single management interface, so you can navigate to App Search and Workplace Search from Kibana without losing your way.

We’re also delivering more flexibility and configurability with precision tuning in App Search and content source flexibility and synonym support in Workplace Search. With all these enhancements, you can set up your teams and customers to find what they’re looking for faster than ever:

Generate more search experience insights with Kibana’s powerful visualizations
Gain tighter customization over your search results with adjustable precision and recall
Configure how you want to ingest data with our out-of-the-box content sources
Create synonyms so teams can find information faster
Elastic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Enterprise Search team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Cloud for 7.14: Connect securely to your public cloud environments with Azure Private Link]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-cloud-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-cloud-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest updates to Elastic Cloud make it even easier for our customers to protect their data using Microsoft Azure Private Link, and offer new options for deployment location and hardware configuration in Google Cloud. 
 
Network security enhancements

We’re excited to announce that support for Microsoft Azure Private Link is now generally available. Private Link provides private connectivity from your Azure virtual network to your Elastic Cloud deployments. The traffic between your virtual network and your Elastic Cloud deployment on Azure travels only within the Azure network, utilizing Private Link endpoints and ensuring that your data stays off the Internet. Soon, you will also be able to leverage Google Cloud Private Service Connect to secure the network connection between your Goo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Kibana 7.14: Formulas and time shifts for richer ad hoc analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-kibana-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-kibana-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kibana 7.14 introduces more capabilities for ad hoc analytics to enable users to cut through the noise and discover insights faster and more easily. 

These new features include custom formulas and time-shifted metrics in Kibana Lens and a time slider in Elastic Maps–all without compromising speed. In addition:

Time-shifted metrics and a time slider in Kibana Lens and Elastic Maps allow users to compare data from different time periods at a glance.
Custom formulas in Kibana Lens and edit tools in Elastic Maps give users the creative freedom to author metrics and add to geo indices.
Elastic Agent, a unified agent for collecting data from multiple sources and protecting your data and hosts, is generally available. Users can choose from 100+ out-of-the-box integrations that are pre-loaded wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeline Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 7.14 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-7-14-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-7-14-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce Elasticsearch 7.14.0, based on Apache Lucene 8.9.0. 

Version 7.14 is the latest stable release of Elasticsearch and is now available for deployment via Elasticsearch Service on Elastic Cloud or via download for use in your own environment(s).

Ready to roll up your sleeves and get started? We have the links you need:

Start Elasticsearch on Elastic Cloud 
Download Elasticsearch
Elasticsearch 7.14.0 release notes
Elasticsearch 7.14.0 breaking changes

Swing for the geofences with Elasticsearch 7.14 
When searching data, “where” is a common and important question. Whether you’re trying to identify whether an outage is a local or global issue, locating adversaries attacking your network, or simply tracking where your food delivery is, Elasticsearch and the Elastic S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Consul Plus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-consul-plus</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-consul-plus"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul Plus allows users to federate Consul clusters across multiple regions for improved redundancy and resiliency of applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 6.8.18 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-6-8-18-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-6-8-18-released"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 6.8.18 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Kibana, Elasticsearch, Beats, Logstash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Jaramillo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Limitless XDR defined: Ingest, retain, and analyze security data freely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-limitless-xdr</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introducing-limitless-xdr"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security's newest features define the potential of XDR for cybersecurity teams. Our single platform brings together SIEM and endpoint security, allowing users to ingest and retain large volumes of data from diverse sources, store and search data for longer, and augment threat hunting with detections and machine learning.
Security vendors are using the term “XDR” with increasing frequency, applying varied definitions to suit their respective technologies. The term began as an evolution of EDR (endpoint detection and response), and tried to encapsulate the need for varied data sources in the investigative process by using “X” for “eXtended.” Through all the varying definitions, the core concepts remain:

Visibility: The exponential growth of data makes a security practitioner’s job i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 10% disk space on your logging datasets with match_only_text]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/save-10-percent-disk-space-on-your-logging-datasets-with-match-only-text</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/save-10-percent-disk-space-on-your-logging-datasets-with-match-only-text"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 7.14 introduces match_only_text, a new field type that can be used as a drop-in replacement for the text field type in logging use cases with a much lower disk footprint, leading to lower costs.

Elasticsearch is attractive for log analysis thanks to its ability to index log messages. Want to count how many log messages contain access denied in the last 24 hours? Elasticsearch can give you the answer in milliseconds thanks to its index structures — but index structures take CPU time to build and need disk space. You could save this CPU and disk space by not indexing your message fields, but then you would also lose the ability to query your logging data in an interactive way.

In order to reduce disk space requirements, match_only_text only indexes a subset of the information…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrien Grand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Agent and Fleet make it easier to integrate your systems with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-and-fleet-make-it-easier-to-integrate-your-systems-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-agent-and-fleet-make-it-easier-to-integrate-your-systems-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are happy to announce three major improvements that will make it easier to integrate your systems and applications with the Elastic Stack. First, we are launching the generally available (GA) release of our Elastic Agent, which is a single, unified agent for both observability and security. A unified agent will simplify data onboarding with fewer things to configure and install.

Second, we are launching the GA release of Fleet, a new Kibana app that lets you centrally manage an entire fleet of Elastic Agents at scale. It acts as a control plane, giving you a real-time view into agent status, remotely upgrade agents, execute queries on each host, and contain security threats.

Third, we are launching our new Integrations app in Kibana along with our first set of GA integrations. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Skowronski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 49 – Intro to @Azure SQL with @StevenMurawski]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62072</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-49-intro-to-azure-sql-with-stevenmurawski/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T14:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 49 – Intro to @Azure SQL with @StevenMurawski appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audit your VMware vCenter Server using Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/audit-your-vmware-vcenter-server-using-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/audit-your-vmware-vcenter-server-using-ansible"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How you can use the modules available in Red Hat supported vmware.vmware_rest Ansible Content Collection to audit your vCenter Servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gonéri Le Bouder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera Hashgraph: Proof-of-Stake Public Networks with Leemon Baird]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11339</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/03/hedera-hashgraph-with-leemon-baird/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hedera-hashgraph-with-leemon-baird"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T09:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain protocols like Bitcoin and Ethereum have changed the cyber world dramatically in the last decade. They’ve created communities of like-minded developers, generated new financial markets, and popularized “decentralization” in computer networks. However, they require large resources to operate which makes scaling difficult and transactions expensive. Hedera is a decentralized public network that takes the
The post Hedera Hashgraph: Proof-of-Stake Public Networks with Leemon Baird appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 3rd, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/03/this-week-in-spring-august-3rd-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/03/this-week-in-spring-august-3rd-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! Can you believe it’s already August, 2021! We’re nearly to 2022! And I am, for better or for worse, back from vacation! I am so happy to be back, but I do miss the sunkissed beaches of Hawai’i. Sigh. Anyway, let’s get into it! We’ve got a ton of things to get into, so without further ado…


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft’s Asir V. Selvasingh on Spring Boot, Spring Cloud, Microsoft Azure, and Azure Spring Cloud

  
Blog: Roorkee robots, releases and racing: the Kubernetes 1.21 release interview

  
Join Pure Storage at VMworld 2021

  
Cassandre is an open-source framework that makes it easy to create your crypto trading bot in Java. Our Spring boot starter takes care of exchange connections, accounts, orders, trades, and positions so you can focus 

  
Check out this Spring Security Authorization Server example

  
Join Confluent Developer advocate Viktor Gamov for this look at Spring and Apache Kafka 101

  
Here’s another interesting look at using Spring Boot with Swagger

  
Did y’all see the latest installment of the SpringOne Tour. This was my favorite installment yet!

  
Flight Status: Oracle Cloud VMware Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Vault Starter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-starter</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-starter"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Starter — now generally available on AWS — offers a production-grade 3-node cluster at a reduced price point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Named as a Leader for the 11th Consecutive Year in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud Infrastructure & Platform Services (CIPS)]]></title>
        <id>446271ecb9bf93846c19f7d2d60e450dedd2456a</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/GuZ2U5msR-8/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T15:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my job at AWS I have the privilege of working with many different teams, all focused to help our customers lower costs, become more agile, and innovate faster. It’s greatly rewarding to see these efforts recognized by our customers and by leading analysts. Last year Gartner introduced a new Magic Quadrant for Cloud Infrastructure […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse ETL: Operationalizing Data Warehouses with Tejas Manohar]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11237</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/02/reverse-etl-operationalizing-data-warehouses-with-tejas-manojar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=reverse-etl-operationalizing-data-warehouses-with-tejas-manojar"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T09:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise data warehouses store all company data in a single place to be accessed, queried, and analyzed. They’re essential for business operations because they support managing data from multiple sources, providing context, and have built-in analytics tools. While keeping a single source of truth is important, easily moving data from the warehouse to other applications
The post Reverse ETL: Operationalizing Data Warehouses with Tejas Manohar appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.0-M1 (aka Jubilee) Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/30/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-m1-aka-jubilee-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/30/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-m1-aka-jubilee-is-available"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T06:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Milestone 1 (M1) of the Spring Cloud 2021 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2021 release notes for more information.

This release is compatible with Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1.

The GitHub Project for this release can be found here.
Notable Changes in the 2021 Release Train
Spring Cloud Gateway


  
StripPrefixFilter now defaults to 1 instead of 0 #2033

  
Add new CacheRequestBodyFilter #1943

  
Share Routes across Gateway instances with Redis #1390


Spring Cloud Sleuth


  
Added JDBC support #1930

  
Instruments Tomcat Valve #1329

  
Support for Spring Vault #1952

  
Automatic tag table generation documentation #1950

  
Spring Cloud D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating the New HashiCorp Enterprise License Deployment Process]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/navigating-the-new-hashicorp-enterprise-license-deployment-process</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/navigating-the-new-hashicorp-enterprise-license-deployment-process"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get helpful resources on a recent change to product license deployments and learn how to navigate this change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Azure by using Grafana dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62089</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/monitoring-azure-by-using-grafana-dashboards/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T16:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By using Azure Monitor, Azure Log Analytics and Application Insights, Azure cloud teams have access to a collection of end-to-end monitoring solutions, directly from the Azure Portal, allowing for Azure Services monitoring, as well as hybrid.
The post Monitoring Azure by using Grafana dashboards appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter De Tender</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DMN-Powered Sorting Hat]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=25669</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/the-dmn-powered-sorting-hat/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T12:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was painfully reminded of the Dark Lord’s failure when I discovered Harry Potter (the person, not the books) turns 40 tomorrow. To help get my mind off of it, I built a Sorting Hat.
The post The DMN-Powered Sorting Hat appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preface with Farooq Abbasi]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11285</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/30/preface-with-farooq-abbasi/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=preface-with-farooq-abbasi"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T09:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode we discuss venture capital and more with Preface Ventures Founder and General Partner Farooq Abbasi. This interview was also recorded as a video podcast. Check out the video on the Software Daily YouTube channel. Sponsorship inquiries: sponsor@softwareengineeringdaily.com
The post Preface with Farooq Abbasi appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heads-Up: AWS Support for Internet Explorer 11 is Ending]]></title>
        <id>c04a29ab1caa1aa963ed25c0ec3f0fe14e12ecef</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/k3NiY2L_p9s/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T21:31:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are using Internet Explorer 11 (IE 11) to access the AWS Management Console, web-based services such as Amazon Chime or Amazon Honeycode, or other parts of the AWS web site (AWS Documentation, AWS Marketing, AWS Marketplace, or AWS Support), it is time to upgrade to a more modern & secure browser such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IoT SiteWise Edge Is Now Generally Available for Processing Industrial Equipment Data on Premises]]></title>
        <id>80f41b2ee1153fdf2a0cce514f2564d85b05a2e5</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/Z1B7j0oz-TY/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T18:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2020, we announced the preview of AWS IoT SiteWise Edge, a new feature of AWS IoT SiteWise that provides software that runs on premises at industrial sites and makes it easy to collect, process, and monitor equipment data locally before sending the data to AWS Cloud destinations. AWS IoT SiteWise Edge software […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting unusual network activity with Elastic Security and machine learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-unusual-network-activity-with-elastic-security-and-machine-learning</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-unusual-network-activity-with-elastic-security-and-machine-learning"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we’ve shown in a previous blog, search-based detection rules and Elastic’s machine learning-based anomaly detection can be a powerful way to identify rare and unusual activity in cloud API logs. Now, as of Elastic Security 7.13, we’ve introduced a new set of unsupervised machine learning jobs for network data, and accompanying alert rules, several of which look for geographic anomalies. In this blog post, we’ll explore a case study demonstrating how network data can yield important detections. 

Before the advent of endpoint detection and response (EDR) tools, security teams relied heavily on network instrumentation like firewall logs and intrusion detection (IDS) alerts. Given the lack of process information or user context, in network logs, the false positive rate for network events c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Chamberlain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing CDK for Terraform 0.5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-cdk-for-terraform-0-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-cdk-for-terraform-0-5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CDK for Terraform 0.5 introduces code generation from HCL and a new cdktf watch workflow for serverless workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第150話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496423060167</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496423060167"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shoreline: Fleet Automation with Anurag Gupta]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11302</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/29/shoreline-fleet-automation-with-anurag-gupta/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shoreline-fleet-automation-with-anurag-gupta"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T09:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s containerized world, it’s common to encounter similar issues with known solutions across multiple pods. For most people there are 2 solutions: go pod-by-pod finding and fixing the problem, or do that while also spending months trying to automate that process. This is significant time and manual labor. The company Shoreline orchestrates real-time debugging
The post Shoreline: Fleet Automation with Anurag Gupta appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate any Process on Micronaut]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=24764</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/07/automate-any-process-on-micronaut/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T07:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Camunda can be run as an embedded engine inside a Micronaut application, with the use of our open source integration project.
The post Automate any Process on Micronaut appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Microsoft's Asir V. Selvasingh on Spring Boot, Spring Cloud, Microsoft Azure, and Azure Spring Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/29/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-asir-v-selvasingh-on-spring-boot-spring-cloud-microsoft-azure-and-azure-spring-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/29/a-bootiful-podcast-microsoft-s-asir-v-selvasingh-on-spring-boot-spring-cloud-microsoft-azure-and-azure-spring-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Microsoft’s Asir V. Selvasingh (@asirselvasingh) about Azure Spring Cloud, Spring Boot, Microsoft Azure and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EC2-Classic Networking is Retiring – Here’s How to Prepare]]></title>
        <id>f59bc7fc5b869bffbdb77f894f6c9a89aa5e26b2</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/3IaLs3ny3aU/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T19:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (July 29, 2021) – Added link to the Support Automation Workflow document & clarified link to AWS MGN pricing. Also updated the list of recommended instance types to favor those built on AWS Nitro System, and added “Networking” to the title. Let’s go back to the summer of 2006 and the launch of EC2. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prophecy: Apple of Data Engineering with Raj Bains]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11313</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/28/prophecy-apple-of-data-engineering-with-raj-bains/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=prophecy-apple-of-data-engineering-with-raj-bains"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T16:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prophecy is a complete Low-Code Data Engineering Platform for the Enterprise. Prophecy enables all your teams on Apache Spark with a unique low-code designer. While you visually build your Dataflows – Prophecy generates high-quality Spark code on Git. Then, you can schedule Spark workflows with Prophecy’s low-code Airflow. Not only that, Prophecy provides end-to-end visibility
The post Prophecy: Apple of Data Engineering with Raj Bains appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Vault 1.8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-8</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-8"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.8 offers a new Vault Diagnose command, Key Management secrets engine AWS GA support, updates to Integrated Storage Autopilot, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon Route 53 Application Recovery Controller]]></title>
        <id>4dd26d69ade9053b95b2204f25c1aed35d499bcf</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/tSAJ8u0H0bg/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T21:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce the availability today of Amazon Route 53 Application Recovery Controller, a Amazon Route 53 set of capabilities that continuously monitors an application’s ability to recover from failures and controls application recovery across multiple AWS Availability Zones, AWS Regions, and on premises environments to help you to build applications that must […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HashiCorp Consul with Kong Ingress Controller for Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-hashicorp-consul-with-kong-ingress-controller-for-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-hashicorp-consul-with-kong-ingress-controller-for-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure Kong Ingress Controller for Kubernetes with transparent proxy on HashiCorp Consul service mesh to manage traffic to and between your Kubernetes services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Current Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11310</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/27/our-current-strategy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=our-current-strategy"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T18:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve been running Software Daily for 6 years.  When we started it back in 2015, the goal was to create a software engineering podcast that was 60% as good as Software Engineering Radio, but aired with 5x the frequency.  5 shows per week, 50 weeks per year, 5 ads per show, means 1,250 advertising spots.
The post Our Current Strategy appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With BGP Address Family Resource Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-bgp-address-family-resource-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/getting-started-with-bgp-address-family-resource-modules"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern enterprise networks have grown a lot in size and complexity, making them more difficult to manage than ever before. Working on these complex networks manually can be tedious, time-consuming, costly, and more prone to error.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 27th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/27/this-week-in-spring-july-27th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/07/27/this-week-in-spring-july-27th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, Spring fans, from the beautiful island of Oahu, Hawaii. How’re you doing? We’ve got a ton of stuff to look at so let’s get to it! 


  
In last week’s A Bootiful Podcast, I talk to industry analyst, fascinating person, strategist, and storyteller Michael Coté

  
I love this look at building a first application with RabbitMQ streams

  
I loved this infographic by Dormain Drewitz on modernizing the mainframe

  
Premiering Now: SpringOne Tour - July 2021: Do or Do Not, There is no try{} in Production

  
Spring Boot 2.4.9 is now available

  
Spring Boot 2.5.3 is now available

  
Spring Boot 2.6.0-M1 is now available

  
Spring Data is a 10 years old today the 23rd of July 2021!

  
This Week in Spring - July 20th, 2021

  
Using Java 16 records with Thymeleaf

  
Spring Cloud scales Spring Boot apps to billions of requests per day without the hassle of managing infrastructure. See it in action and hear how Swiss Re is acceleratin

  
Register for @SpringOne today]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an Event-Based HA Architecture with Nomad and Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-an-event-based-ha-architecture-with-nomad-and-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-an-event-based-ha-architecture-with-nomad-and-consul"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how content moderation service Chatsight uses HashiCorp Nomad and Consul to speed deployment and maximize uptime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pulsar Rerevisted with Enrico Olivelli]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11299</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/07/26/pulsar-rerevisted-with-enrico-olivelli/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pulsar-rerevisted-with-enrico-olivelli"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T09:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous episode, Pulsar Revisited, we discussed how the company DataStax has added to their product stack Astra Streaming, their cloud-native messaging and event streaming service that’s built on top of Apache Pulsar. We discussed Apache Pulsar and the added features DataStax offers like injecting machine learning into your data streams and viewing real-time
The post Pulsar Rerevisted with Enrico Olivelli appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>