<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-11T01:19:51.159Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-11T01:19:51.159Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Avoid Collisions Assigning Ports to NodePort Services]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/11/nodeport-dynamic-and-static-allocation/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/11/nodeport-dynamic-and-static-allocation/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Xu Zhenglun (Alibaba)
In Kubernetes, a Service can be used to provide a unified traffic endpoint for
applications running on a set of Pods. Clients can use the virtual IP address (or VIP) provided
by the Service for access, and Kubernetes provides load balancing for traffic accessing
different back-end Pods, but a ClusterIP type of Service is limited to providing access to
nodes within the cluster, while traffic from outside the cluster cannot be routed.
One way to solve this problem is to use a type: NodePort Service, which sets up a mapping
to a specific port of all nodes in the cluster, thus redirecting traffic from the
outside to the inside of the cluster.
How Kubernetes allocates node ports to Services?
When a type: NodePort Service is created, its corresponding port(s) are al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionize your open source workflows: the top 3 reasons why GitHub Codespaces is a must-have for maintainers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-10-revolutionize-your-open-source-workflows-the-top-3-reasons-why-github-codespaces-is-a-must-have-for-maintainers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-10-revolutionize-your-open-source-workflows-the-top-3-reasons-why-github-codespaces-is-a-must-have-for-maintainers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T19:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Codespaces is reliable, accessible, and always-ready. Try it out during Maintainer Month and take your projects to new heights!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell, Marvell, NetApp, and SUSE expand Vault support with new integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dell-marvell-netapp-and-suse-expand-vault-support-with-new-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dell-marvell-netapp-and-suse-expand-vault-support-with-new-integrations"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Vault partner ecosystem continues to show strong growth with the addition of more than a dozen new Vault integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · May 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-10-game-bytes-may-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-10-game-bytes-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building better pangenomes to improve the equity of genomics]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/building-better-pangenomes-to-improve.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/building-better-pangenomes-to-improve.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:03:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Andrew Carroll, Product Lead, and Kishwar Shafin, Research Scientist, Genomics






For decades, researchers worked together to assemble a complete copy of the molecular instructions for a human — a map of the human genome. The first draft was finished in 2000, but with several missing pieces.  Even when a complete reference genome was achieved in 2022, their work was not finished. A single reference genome can’t incorporate known genetic variations, such as the variants for the gene determining whether a person has a blood type A, B, AB or O. Furthermore, the reference genome didn’t represent the vast diversity of human ancestries, making it less useful for detecting disease or finding cures for people from some backgrounds than others. For the past three years, we have been pa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about Event-Driven Ansible at Red Hat Summit and AnsibleFest 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-event-driven-ansible-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/learn-about-event-driven-ansible-at-red-hat-summit-and-ansiblefest-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may have heard, AnsibleFest will be taking place at Red Hat Summit in Boston May 23-25. This change will allow you to harness everything that Red Hat technology has to offer in a single place and give you even more tools to address your automation needs. Join Ansible and automation-focused audiences to hear from Red Hat and Ansible leaders, customers, and partners while getting the latest on future Ansible product updates, community projects, and what’s coming in IT automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing your pacemaker]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44411</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/739805867/0/sethsblog~Choosing-your-pacemaker/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roger Bannister ran a four-minute mile by having a relay race of pace runners next to him. If he could keep up with his pacer, he’d finish the run in record time. If you work in an office where people are regularly shipping breakthrough work, it’s likely your work will ship as well. If you’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 for Spring Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=351236</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/05/2023-1-for-spring-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T08:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 release came packed with updates for Spring. This blog post will highlight the most noticeable changes, including full support for Lombok, a reworked Spring tool window, navigation for Spring Security rules, Spring Security 6 support, and more. Remember that these features are only available in IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate.  Let’s take a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Maryasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Tristan Ma on celebrating his culture, connecting through ElastAsians, and building his sales career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tristan-ma-culture-through-food</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tristan-ma-culture-through-food"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First generation can be interpreted in many ways. For Tristan Ma, Solutions Architect at Elastic, it means being the first generation to be born in the United States. Read about his career journey and how he celebrates his culture through food.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Tristan Ma on celebrating his culture, connecting through ElastAsians, and building his sales career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tristan-ma-culture-through-food</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-tristan-ma-culture-through-food"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
First generation can be interpreted in many ways. For Tristan Ma, Solutions Architect at Elastic, it means being the first generation to be born in the United States.

While his parents have spent the majority of their lives in North America, Tristan and his sister were the first in their family to be born here.

Tristan’s parents immigrated to North America from Vietnam—his dad moved to the Bay Area as a refugee during the Vietnam War at 14 and his mom moved to Toronto, Canada when she was 9. 

Tristan was born and raised in the Bay Area, the same place where his father attended high school. And while the family speaks English at home, Tristan recalls his parents speaking to each other in their mother tongue, one he didn’t understand. 
“You do start to recognize body language,” he says.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taxiing]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2774/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2774/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/taxiing.png" title="I don't understand why anyone would pay full price for a flatbed truck rental when you can buy 'DETOUR' signs online for like $10." alt="I don't understand why anyone would pay full price for a flatbed truck rental when you can buy 'DETOUR' signs online for like $10." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Unified Camunda Platform 8 SDK for Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80952&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80952</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/unified-camunda-8-sdk-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T21:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Camunda Platform 8 SDK for Node.js provides a single high-level API to interact with many components of Camunda Platform 8.
The post A Unified Camunda Platform 8 SDK for Node.js appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Storage-Optimized Amazon EC2 I4g Instances: Graviton Processors and AWS Nitro SSDs]]></title>
        <id>fa9f4d36a6cc0d15999ca03edf1ef668d2028f09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-storage-optimized-amazon-ec2-i4g-instances-graviton-processors-and-aws-nitro-ssds/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T21:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are launching I4g instances powered by AWS Graviton2 processors that deliver up to 15% better compute performance than our other storage-optimized instances. With up to 64 vCPUs, 512 GiB of memory, and 15 TB of NVMe storage, one of the six instance sizes is bound to be a great fit for your storage-intensive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How companies are boosting productivity with generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-09-how-companies-are-boosting-productivity-with-generative-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-09-how-companies-are-boosting-productivity-with-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T19:42:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how generative AI coding tools are changing the way developers and companies build software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66918</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/now-available-azure-devops-server-2022-0-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T17:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we released Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RTW. This is our final release of Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1. You can directly install Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 or upgrade from Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC, Azure DevOps Server 2022, Team Foundation Server 2015 or newer versions of the product.
The post Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to fix a ReDoS]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-09-how-to-fix-a-redos/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-09-how-to-fix-a-redos/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T17:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning detects ReDoS vulnerabilities automatically, but fixing them isn’t always easy. This blog post describes a 4-step strategy for fixing ReDoS bugs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Push protection is generally available, and free for all public repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-09-push-protection-is-generally-available-and-free-for-all-public-repositories/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-09-push-protection-is-generally-available-and-free-for-all-public-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T16:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the general availability of push protection–a feature that proactively prevents secret leaks in your public and private repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.20.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80942&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80942</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/camunda-automation-platform-7-20-0-alpha1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T15:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first alpha release of Camunda Automation Runtime 7.20, you can find a new JUEL module based on Jakarta EL 4.0 and many bug fixes.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.20.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to start using .NET Background Services]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=312064</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/05/09/dotnet-background-services/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T15:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers, running critical tasks in the background can open up a world of problem-solving possibilities. Background services are ideal for many scenarios, especially if your users are willing to wait for results. Some use-case scenarios for background services include updating globally-used caches, processing queued work, and general health monitoring. With .NET’s hosting model, background […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning Maze Solver]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=350661</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/05/09/reinforcement-learning-maze-solver/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T14:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning is an exciting subfield of machine learning that focuses on teaching agents how to make decisions based on rewards and penalties. Reinforcement learning is like training a puppy. Just as a puppy learns by receiving a reward when it behaves well and being scolded when it misbehaves, reinforcement learning algorithms learn in a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasiia Pogorelova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Learning Center Is Now Available in TeamCity Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=349969</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/05/teamcity-cloud-learning-center/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T10:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for easy-to-consume learning materials to help you master TeamCity? These are now available in our new learning center right within TeamCity Cloud. That means you can find answers to your most burning TeamCity-related questions and access video guides without ever having to leave the platform. Here are some of the questions that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What comes after trust?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45952</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/739399478/0/sethsblog~What-comes-after-trust/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walk into a bank with a stocking on your head and you’re probably going to get arrested. Civil society as we know it is dependent on identity and responsibility. A person does something and owns the consequences. This requirement of identity leads to the dynamic of the free market that we call trust. Even companies, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin News: 1.8.20 Release, KotlinConf Keynote, Redesigned Mascot, Kotlin Foundation News, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=348751</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/05/kotlin-news-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T08:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April has been a busy and eventful month with many updates and a lot of exciting news in the world of Kotlin. Catch up on all the highlights in our digest. Kotlin Multiplatform user survey  If you’re a Kotlin developer, we want to hear from you! We are currently conducting a Kotlin Multiplatform survey to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daria Voronina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 9th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/09/this-week-in-spring-may-9th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/09/this-week-in-spring-may-9th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do incremental snapshots work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-do-incremental-snapshots-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-do-incremental-snapshots-work"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During our instructor-led “Elasticsearch Engineer” training, one of the most common questions we get while teaching about snapshots is “what is the incremental nature of snapshots?” This blog post will cover that topic in detail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lutf ur Rehman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do incremental snapshots work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-do-incremental-snapshots-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-do-incremental-snapshots-work"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic offers many instructor-led, in-person and virtual live trainings, as well as on-demand trainings. Our flagship courses are Elasticsearch Engineer, Data Analysis with Kibana, and Elastic Observability Engineer. All of these courses lead to certifications. 

We recently released the latest version of Elasticsearch Engineer training in response to increased demand and new features. This course is designed for both new Elasticsearch users and Elasticsearch professionals. It begins with the basics for getting started with the Elastic Stack, then quickly dives deep into topics ranging from optimizing search performance to building efficient clusters. View the detailed course outline to find out more about what you’ll learn. All lessons include hands-on labs.

During this instructor-led…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lutf ur Rehman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Safer, More Performant Pruning in kubectl apply]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/09/introducing-kubectl-applyset-pruning/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/09/introducing-kubectl-applyset-pruning/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Katrina Verey (independent) and Justin Santa Barbara (Google)
Declarative configuration management with the kubectl apply command is the gold standard approach
to creating or modifying Kubernetes resources. However, one challenge it presents is the deletion
of resources that are no longer needed. In Kubernetes version 1.5, the --prune flag was
introduced to address this issue, allowing kubectl apply to automatically clean up previously
applied resources removed from the current configuration.
Unfortunately, that existing implementation of --prune has design flaws that diminish its
performance and can result in unexpected behaviors. The main issue stems from the lack of explicit
encoding of the previously applied set by the preceding apply operation, necessitating
error-prone dynam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – AWS Notifications, Serverless event, and More – May 8, 2023]]></title>
        <id>4e74355f2ac25e5c1b2a61d6decd0116b526557f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-aws-notifications-serverless-event-and-more-may-8-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T21:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of this week, I’m flying to Seattle to take part in the AWS Serverless Innovation Day. Along with many customers and colleagues from AWS, we are going to be live on May 17 at a virtual free event. During the AWS Serverless Innovation Day we will share best practices related to building […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start a Camunda 8 Process via REST with Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80864&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80864</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/start-camunda-8-process-rest-webhooks/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T19:19:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can use the Camunda Platform 8 REST API to start a process using the latest Connectors.  
The post Start a Camunda 8 Process via REST with Webhooks appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we work: inclusive retrospectives for the GitHub Accessibility leadership team]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-08-how-we-work-inclusive-retrospectives-for-the-github-accessibility-leadership-team/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-08-how-we-work-inclusive-retrospectives-for-the-github-accessibility-leadership-team/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T18:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about tools and processes the GitHub Accessibility leadership team uses for retrospectives that fully engage every team member.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub code search is generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-08-github-code-search-is-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-08-github-code-search-is-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T16:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s code is now at your fingertips.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a culture of innovation in your business with GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-08-building-a-culture-of-innovation-in-your-business-with-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-08-building-a-culture-of-innovation-in-your-business-with-github/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T15:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider the typical software development practices in an organization. Projects are commonly closed, and causes friction across engineering teams. But open source communities work asynchronously, openly, remotely and at global-scale. What if our internal teams could reuse those same practices?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contributors to Kotlin Projects for Google Summer of Code Announced]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=349818</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/05/kotlin-gsoc-contributors-announced/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T12:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce that 5 Kotlin project contributors have been selected for Google Summer of Code 2023! With the guidance of mentors from JetBrains, Google, and Gradle, they will work on 12-week programming projects with the Kotlin Foundation. We were impressed by the number of high-quality proposals we received. After careful review, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ksenia Shneyveys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Livestream: Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Program]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=349795</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/05/08/livestream-computer-science-and-artificial-intelligence-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T12:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us this Sunday, May 14, 9:00 am UTC (12:00 pm EEST), for the free Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Program livestream. You’ll learn about how our new bachelor’s program at Neapolis University Pafos in Cyprus can help you get closer to a future tech career. Students who graduate from bachelor’s and master’s programs developed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The thing about decay]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44405</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/739264325/0/sethsblog~The-thing-about-decay/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One reason we have so much trouble fixing chronic degenerative conditions is that we need to remove elements before we can start building new functions. If we simply put effort on top of a shaky foundation, it’ll all be wasted. The best way forward might be to take a few steps back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.9, 3.0.3 and 3.1.0-RC1 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/08/spring-shell-2-1-9-3-0-3-and-3-1-0-rc1-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/08/spring-shell-2-1-9-3-0-3-and-3-1-0-rc1-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AIOps effectively with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/aiops-automation-analytics-elastic-observability-use-cases</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/aiops-automation-analytics-elastic-observability-use-cases"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of the AIOps capabilities within the Elastic Observability full-stack solution! From noise reduction to anomaly detection and root cause analysis, AIOps helps teams troubleshoot and respond more quickly to application performance issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugo Sangiorgi,Vinay Chandrasekhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AIOps effectively with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/aiops-automation-analytics-elastic-observability-use-cases</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/aiops-automation-analytics-elastic-observability-use-cases"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Over the past several years, one topic that has become of increasing importance for DevOps and site reliability engineering (SRE) teams is AIOps. Artificial intelligence for IT Operations (AIOps) is the application of artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning (ML), and analytics to improve the day-to-day operational work for IT operations teams. With the move toward distributed applications along with the adoption of cloud-native technologies, teams have been dealing with three major changes in the application environments they observe and manage. 

First, the increasing complexity of applications with workloads and services that are connected across on-premises and cloud along with ephemeral components (Kubernetes) means that traditional IT monitoring tools are too limited. More mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugo Sangiorgi,Vinay Chandrasekhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planetary Scientist]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2773/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2773/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/planetary_scientist.png" title="This rumpled fabric at the corner looks like evidence of ongoing tectonic activity." alt="This rumpled fabric at the corner looks like evidence of ongoing tectonic activity." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Introducing An API For Volume Group Snapshots]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/08/kubernetes-1-27-volume-group-snapshot-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/08/kubernetes-1-27-volume-group-snapshot-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Xing Yang (VMware)
Volume group snapshot is introduced as an Alpha feature in Kubernetes v1.27.
This feature introduces a Kubernetes API that allows users to take crash consistent
snapshots for multiple volumes together. It uses a label selector to group multiple
PersistentVolumeClaims for snapshotting.
This new feature is only supported for CSI volume drivers.
An overview of volume group snapshots
Some storage systems provide the ability to create a crash consistent snapshot of
multiple volumes. A group snapshot represents “copies” from multiple volumes that
are taken at the same point-in-time. A group snapshot can be used either to rehydrate
new volumes (pre-populated with the snapshot data) or to restore existing volumes to
a previous state (represented by the snapshots).
Why ad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In search of chatoyancy]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44524</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/739148711/0/sethsblog~In-search-of-chatoyancy/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-07T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cat’s eye is smooth but doesn’t seem to be… there’s a mystery of depth. That illusion is called chatoyancy. The same is true for some sorts of woods (cedar is an exception). The digital age makes it more and more likely we’re experiencing things through a flat screen, and as a result, it’s very […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nihil hic deest]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45985</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/739005392/0/sethsblog~Nihil-hic-deest/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-06T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This page intentionally left blank has a long history. I thought it was an IBM thing from the 1960s, but I was off by a thousand or more years. There are good reasons for a page to be blank. Folding signatures, printing processes, having chapters start on the right or the left… But there are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How is Camunda Platform 8 Professional Edition Helping Companies Accelerate their Projects?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80806&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80806</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/camunda-professional-edition-accelerate-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T20:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've spoken with our early adopters, who shared with us what they like about the pay-as-you-go model and powerful features of our Professional Edition.
The post How is Camunda Platform 8 Professional Edition Helping Companies Accelerate their Projects? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joao Oliveira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a more inclusive GitHub Global Campus]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-05-building-a-more-inclusive-github-global-campus/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-05-building-a-more-inclusive-github-global-campus/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T16:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every student and teacher deserves the same access to GitHub Education offerings. We’ve enlisted GitHub’s Accessibility team to help identify areas for improving inclusivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in IntelliJ Rust for 2023.1 (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rust&amp;p=349103</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rust/2023/05/05/new-in-intellij-rust-for-2023-1-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T14:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of this “What’s New” series, we only saw the tip of the iceberg – various feature bits that the Rust plugin developers managed to implement during the release cycle. Now we’re going to show you the rest of the iceberg. Let’s dig in and look at all the new ways the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Lobeiko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit Rio 2023: Building an app in 18 minutes with GitHub Copilot X]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-05-web-summit-rio-2023-building-an-app-in-18-minutes-with-github-copilot-x/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-05-web-summit-rio-2023-building-an-app-in-18-minutes-with-github-copilot-x/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T14:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub CEO Thomas Dohmke demonstrated the power of GitHub Copilot X live on stage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new way of work]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45912</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/738838367/0/sethsblog~The-new-way-of-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T08:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon is the last one. They are probably the last huge company where hundreds of thousands of people will be surveilled, measured and ordered to follow the rule book. The pandemic didn’t create distributed work, the laptop did. Human interaction is critical, but the office isn’t actually the most effective way to create that. David […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stefan Pölz – How to test C# unit tests with mutation testing – Webinar Recording]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=349053</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/05/05/stefan-polz-how-to-test-csharp-unit-tests-with-mutation-testing-webinar-recording/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T08:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recording for How to test C# unit tests with mutation testing, with Clean C# Coder, Stefan Pölz is now available on JetBrains TV. Executing the very short development cycle of test-driven development requires discipline and practice. However, the .NET ecosystem offers a wide variety of tools to support authoring a high-quality suite of unit […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Data Flow 2.10.3 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/05/spring-cloud-data-flow-2-10-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/05/spring-cloud-data-flow-2-10-3-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corneil du Plessis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.18.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/05/spring-tools-4-18-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/05/spring-tools-4-18-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lippert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.0-RC2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/05/spring-boot-3-1-0-rc2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/05/spring-boot-3-1-0-rc2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Webb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commemorative Plaque]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2772/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2772/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/commemorative_plaque.png" title="[Below] On this site on May 12th, 2023, I finally learned how to use the masonry bit for my drill." alt="[Below] On this site on May 12th, 2023, I finally learned how to use the masonry bit for my drill." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Quality-of-Service for Memory Resources (alpha)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/05/qos-memory-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/05/qos-memory-resources/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Dixita Narang (Google)
Kubernetes v1.27, released in April 2023, introduced changes to
Memory QoS (alpha) to improve memory management capabilites in Linux nodes.
Support for Memory QoS was initially added in Kubernetes v1.22, and later some
limitations
around the formula for calculating memory.high were identified. These limitations are
addressed in Kubernetes v1.27.
Background
Kubernetes allows you to optionally specify how much of each resources a container needs
in the Pod specification. The most common resources to specify are CPU and Memory.
For example, a Pod manifest that defines container resource requirements could look like:
apiVersion: v1
kind: Pod
metadata:
name: example
spec:
containers:
- name: nginx
resources:
requests:
memory: "64Mi"
cpu: "250m"
limits:
memory: "6…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MaMMUT: A simple vision-encoder text-decoder architecture for multimodal tasks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/mammut-simple-vision-encoder-text.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/mammut-simple-vision-encoder-text.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T21:59:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by AJ Piergiovanni and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research




Vision-language foundational models are built on the premise of a single pre-training followed by subsequent adaptation to multiple downstream tasks. Two main and disjoint training scenarios are popular: a CLIP-style contrastive learning and next-token prediction. Contrastive learning trains the model to predict if image-text pairs correctly match, effectively building visual and text representations for the corresponding image and text inputs, whereas next-token prediction predicts the most likely next text token in a sequence, thus learning to generate text, according to the required task. Contrastive learning enables image-text and text-image retrieval tasks, such as finding the image that best match…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating Critical Traffic At Scale with No Downtime — Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ba1c7a1c7835</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/migrating-critical-traffic-at-scale-with-no-downtime-part-1-ba1c7a1c7835?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T21:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KotlinConf 2023: Watch the Recordings]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=348956</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/05/kotlinconf-2023-recordings/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T15:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KotlinConf 2023 session recordings are now available! Whether you missed out on the event or just want to re-watch your favorite talks, you can now easily find all the talks on the KotlinConf website, along with photos from the conference. Slides from some of the sessions can be accessed by clicking on the respective talk […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ksenia Shneyveys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2023.1.1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=345412</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2023/05/2023-1-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T14:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2023.1.1 provides more precise measurement of cell execution time, fixes for missing DataFrame table data, and more.  Download the new version from our website, directly from the IDE, via the free Toolbox App, or use snaps for Ubuntu. Download DataSpell 2023.1.1 Execution time updates Since some Jupyter Notebook cells run for a long time, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ciara Byrne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy’s New Projects and Topics: May Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=348939</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/05/04/jetbrains-academy-s-new-projects-and-topics-may-update-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T14:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we head into summer, we’re excited to announce our May content update which includes nine new projects for Python, Kotlin, Java, Flask, Android, and Bash, ranging from easy to challenging, as well as 55 new topics. 9 projects that were previously in Beta have also now been fully released! At JetBrains Academy, we are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasiia Pogorelova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The price of salt]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45916</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/738657068/0/sethsblog~The-price-of-salt/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salt is essentially free. A bag of salted nuts is the same price (or less) as an unsalted one. But salt used to be expensive. Truly expensive, like gold. We keep seeing the deflation of things we were sure would remain expensive. Computer chips, disk storage and now, content. Once computers start illustrating, writing and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Java Champion Ken Kousen on Gradle, Java, Kotlin, Mockito, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/04/a-bootiful-podcast-java-champion-ken-koussen-on-gradle-java-kotlin-mockito</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/04/a-bootiful-podcast-java-champion-ken-koussen-on-gradle-java-kotlin-mockito"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial control systems security with Elastic Security and Zeek]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/industrial-control-systems-elastic-security-zeek</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/industrial-control-systems-elastic-security-zeek"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog walks through the security challenges associated with ICS and how Elastic Security and Zeek can help address them, in addition to the benefits of having integrated machine learning and threat intelligence within the ICS security program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdelwahhab Satta, Octodet,Samir Bennacer, Octodet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Elasticsearch and Time Series Data Streams for observability metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-time-series-data-streams-observability-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-time-series-data-streams-observability-metrics"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Time Series Data Streams (TSDS), Elasticsearch introduces optimized storage for metrics time series. Check out how we use it for Elastic Observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Ruflin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial control systems security with Elastic Security and Zeek]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/industrial-control-systems-elastic-security-zeek</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/industrial-control-systems-elastic-security-zeek"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Industrial control systems (ICS) have historically been isolated and less interconnected. Isolation was one of the things that kept these systems more secure behind air gaps, at the cost of lost coordination and collaboration. This is rapidly changing with the rise of Industry 4.0 with increased interconnectivity and integration of smart technologies like Industrial IoT (IIoT) and cloud computing in modern industrial processes.

This blog walks through the security challenges associated with ICS and how Elastic Security and Zeek can help address them, in addition to the benefits of having integrated machine learning and threat intelligence within the ICS security program.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt1e29f607dfe021f0/6453c12670a4470c7a8b2282/blog-elastic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdelwahhab Satta, Octodet,Samir Bennacer, Octodet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Elasticsearch and Time Series Data Streams for observability metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-time-series-data-streams-observability-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-time-series-data-streams-observability-metrics"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elasticsearch is used for a wide variety of data types — one of these is metrics. With the introduction of Metricbeat many years ago and later our APM Agents, the metric use case has become more popular. Over the years, Elasticsearch has made many improvements on how to handle things like metrics aggregations and sparse documents. At the same time, TSVB visualizations were introduced to make visualizing metrics easier. One concept that was missing that exists for most other metric solutions is the concept of time series with dimensions. 

Mid 2021, the Elasticsearch team embarked on making Elasticsearch a much better fit for metrics. The team created Time Series Data Streams (TSDS), which were released in 8.7 as generally available (GA). 

This blog post dives into how TSDS works and how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Ruflin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: StatefulSet PVC Auto-Deletion (beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/04/kubernetes-1-27-statefulset-pvc-auto-deletion-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/04/kubernetes-1-27-statefulset-pvc-auto-deletion-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Matthew Cary (Google)
Kubernetes v1.27 graduated to beta a new policy mechanism for
StatefulSets that controls the lifetime of
their PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs). The new PVC
retention policy lets users specify if the PVCs generated from the StatefulSet spec template should
be automatically deleted or retrained when the StatefulSet is deleted or replicas in the StatefulSet
are scaled down.
What problem does this solve?
A StatefulSet spec can include Pod and PVC templates. When a replica is first created, the
Kubernetes control plane creates a PVC for that replica if one does not already exist. The behavior
before the PVC retention policy was that the control plane never cleaned up the PVCs created for
StatefulSets - this was left up to the cluster administrator, or to some add-on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Bob’s Used Books—a New, Real-World, .NET Sample Application]]></title>
        <id>1c00c599af66e56a57ee408b24db5dd4f41dfeec</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-bobs-used-books-a-new-real-world-net-sample-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T20:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to announce that a new open-source sample application, a fictitious used books eCommerce store we call Bob’s Used Books, is available for .NET developers working with AWS. The .NET advocacy and development teams at AWS talk to customers regularly and, during those conversations, often receive requests for more in-depth samples. Customers tell […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Set Up Your AWS Notifications in One Place]]></title>
        <id>01ea65c02e7f25c9e84ec4d664b25ae3dc22c87a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-set-up-your-aws-notifications-in-one-place/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T17:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are launching AWS User Notifications, a single place in the AWS console to set up and view AWS notifications across multiple AWS accounts, Regions, and services. You can centrally set up and view notifications from over 100 AWS services, such as Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) objects events, Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IndoorSim-to-OutdoorReal: Learning to navigate outdoors without any outdoor experience]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/indoorsim-to-outdoorreal-learning-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/indoorsim-to-outdoorreal-learning-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Joanne Truong, Student Researcher, and Wenhao Yu, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google





Teaching mobile robots to navigate in complex outdoor environments is critical to real-world applications, such as delivery or search and rescue. However, this is also a challenging problem as the robot needs to perceive its surroundings, and then explore to identify feasible paths towards the goal. Another common challenge is that the robot needs to overcome uneven terrains, such as stairs, curbs, or rockbed on a trail, while avoiding obstacles and pedestrians. In our prior work, we investigated the second challenge by teaching a quadruped robot to tackle challenging uneven obstacles and various outdoor terrains. 



In “IndoorSim-to-OutdoorReal: Learning to Navigate Outdoors without an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging the gap between technology and FinOps with HashiCorp and Intel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/bridging-the-gap-between-technology-and-finops-with-hashicorp-and-intel</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/bridging-the-gap-between-technology-and-finops-with-hashicorp-and-intel"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Cloud Optimized Modules for Terraform and Sentinel standardize infrastructure deployment and increase performance with purpose-built policy as code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take Ansible validated content to the next level with Event-Driven Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-with-event-driven-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-with-event-driven-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing has become an essential factor in IT transformation and business innovation. The highly dynamic nature of cloud environments, where new resources are constantly being added and removed, poses new challenges. One of the main challenges organizations face is the lack of visibility into the cloud environment. As cloud computing continues to grow in complexity, it can be challenging to keep track of all the different resources and applications that make up the infrastructure. This lack of visibility can make it difficult to maintain security policies and configurations, making the infrastructure vulnerable to attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing Elastic to robotics developers: Integrating with ROS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-elastic-to-robotics-developers-integrating-with-ros</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-elastic-to-robotics-developers-integrating-with-ros"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the robotics industry grows and evolves, the integration of Elastic with ROS will continue to play a crucial role in enabling developers to effectively manage and analyze the vast amounts of data generated by connected devices and sensors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Salgado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing Elastic to robotics developers: Integrating with ROS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-elastic-to-robotics-developers-integrating-with-ros</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-elastic-to-robotics-developers-integrating-with-ros"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The robotics industry has experienced significant growth in recent years, with the global robotics market size expected to reach US$230 billion by 2025. This growth is largely driven by the increasing adoption of automation and robotics in various industries, including manufacturing, healthcare, logistics, and more. The integration of automation and robotics with Industry 4.0 technologies has brought new challenges, including the management and analysis of large amounts of data generated by connected devices and sensors, which is estimated to generate around 4.4 zettabytes of data per year.

The Robot Operating System (ROS) is an open-source framework that provides a standardized way of developing robotic applications. ROS has become an essential component of the robotics industry, as it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Salgado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第229話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361192645271</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361192645271"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The house painter and the architect]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45928</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/738459503/0/sethsblog~The-house-painter-and-the-architect/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T08:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t design a book until after it’s written. Or cast the movie until the screenplay is complete. The house painter has an important job, but it makes no sense to plan for the painting before the house is designed. This makes a lot of sense because some parts of a project have high variability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing an observability solution for public cloud and on-prem implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-public-cloud-on-prem-implementation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-public-cloud-on-prem-implementation"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the different components architects should consider when designing an observability solution for public cloud and on-premise implementations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calizo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing an observability solution for public cloud and on-prem implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-public-cloud-on-prem-implementation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-public-cloud-on-prem-implementation"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In my previous article, I talked about the importance of how a unified observability approach can augment the security posture of an organization. 
In this article, I’ll discuss the different components architects should consider when designing an observability solution for public cloud and on-premise implementations. 
Having a sound observability solution on both cloud and on-prem is essential. This is especially true due to the rise of microservices architecture adoption, which makes visibility, traceability, and correlation of different components a necessity to be at the forefront of what is happening in your environment via almost real-time insights.
These recommendations are based on many considerations and a number of factors to ensure that the solution provides effective monitori…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calizo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[College Knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2771/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2771/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/college_knowledge.png" title="'Your chitin armor is no match for our iron-tipped stingers! Better go hide in your jars!' --common playground taunt" alt="'Your chitin armor is no match for our iron-tipped stingers! Better go hide in your jars!' --common playground taunt" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The list of compromises]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/738237575/0/sethsblog~The-list-of-compromises/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the no-compromise solutions have failed. If there was a way to solve our problem without giving something up, we would have done that already. So, if a persistent problem is important, the question is not: Should we compromise or not? The question is: Which changes are we going to make first?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: HorizontalPodAutoscaler ContainerResource type metric moves to beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/02/hpa-container-resource-metric/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/02/hpa-container-resource-metric/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Kensei Nakada (Mercari)
Kubernetes 1.20 introduced the ContainerResource type metric
in HorizontalPodAutoscaler (HPA).
In Kubernetes 1.27, this feature moves to beta and the corresponding feature gate (HPAContainerMetrics) gets enabled by default.
What is the ContainerResource type metric
The ContainerResource type metric allows us to configure the autoscaling based on resource usage of individual containers.
In the following example, the HPA controller scales the target
so that the average utilization of the cpu in the application container of all the pods is around 60%.
(See the algorithm details
to know how the desired replica number is calculated exactly)
type: ContainerResource
containerResource:
 name: cpu
 container: application
 target:
 type: Utilization
 averageUtilizatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Spring Cloud AWS 3.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/announcing-spring-cloud-aws-3-0-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/announcing-spring-cloud-aws-3-0-0"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Gibb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 0.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/spring-modulith-0-6-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/spring-modulith-0-6-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 2, 20223]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/this-week-in-spring-may-2-20223</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/this-week-in-spring-may-2-20223"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.7.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-7-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-7-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.7.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.7.1 over 8.7.0 and 8.6.x releases.
The 8.7.1 patch release contains fixes for potential security vulnerabilities. Please see our security advisory for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arpad Kiraly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.10 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-10-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-10-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.17.10 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.10 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrés Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.7.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-7-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-7-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arpad Kiraly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.10 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-10-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-10-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrés Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Review – AWS Verified Access, Java 17, Amplify Flutter, Conferences, and More – May 1, 2023]]></title>
        <id>ae3f62fcbec27e6f57598f0de24b8a0e4fcfbe7e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/week-in-review-aws-verified-access-java-17-amplify-flutter-conferences-and-more-may-1-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T22:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conference season has started and I was happy to meet and talk with iOS and Swift developers at the New York Swifty conference last week. I will travel again to Turino (Italy), Amsterdam (Netherlands), Frankfurt (Germany), and London (UK) in the coming weeks. Feel free to stop by and say hi if you are around. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Winning Process Orchestration Plays for Financial Services]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80223&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80223</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/process-orchestration-plays-financial-services/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To improve a business, improve its processes. But how? Here are some proven process orchestration patterns to follow for financial services. 
The post Four Winning Process Orchestration Plays for Financial Services appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason English</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 221]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66868</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-221/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our team remains dedicated to improving New Boards Hub by addressing any issues that may arise. We’re happy to report that the New Boards Hub has been steadily progressing with each sprint. Although it is not quite ready for general availability yet,
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 221 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you should run your platform team like a product team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/why-you-should-run-your-platform-team-like-a-product-team</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/why-you-should-run-your-platform-team-like-a-product-team"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like a product team, a successful platform team must understand the needs of its "customers" and stakeholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On to the next thing]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44372</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/738073769/0/sethsblog~On-to-the-next-thing/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T07:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vitally important, rarely taught, easily messed up. In order to go onto the next thing, which we all do (unless you’re still wearing pajamas with feet and taking ballet lessons), we need to walk away from the last thing. Wrap it up, learn from it, leave it in good hands. And we also need to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ICLR 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-iclr-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-iclr-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T06:37:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Catherine Armato, Program Manager, Google




The Eleventh International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR 2023) is being held this week as a hybrid event in Kigali, Rwanda. We are proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of ICLR 2023, a premier conference on deep learning, where Google researchers contribute at all levels. This year we are presenting over 100 papers and are actively involved in organizing and hosting a number of different events, including workshops and interactive sessions.

 

If you’re registered for ICLR 2023, we hope you’ll visit the Google booth to learn more about the exciting work we’re doing across topics spanning representation and reinforcement learning, theory and optimization, social impact, safety and privacy, and applications from generative AI to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet ElastAsians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Employee resource groups, or Elastician resource groups as we call them, are groups within Elastic that are aligned with shared identities, experiences, interests, affinities, and allyships.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet ElastAsians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Employee resource groups, or Elastician resource groups as we call them, are groups within Elastic that are aligned with shared identities, experiences, and allyships. 

These groups were formalized in 2021, but they’ve been a part of Elastic’s culture since 2016. By formalizing them, we ensure they all have a structure, budget, and voice. This was an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy. 

Each ERG has their own mission and goals, but as a whole they create community and belonging around shared interests and experiences. 
Our Core ERGs
We have seven formal ERGs: The Accessibles, Blasticians, ElastAsians, Elasticians Unidos, Rainbow Stack, Mil-Asticians, and Women of Elastic. We’ll be spotlighting them over the next year as they relate to culture or comm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Athena Provisioned Capacity]]></title>
        <id>17b4867be4eb5a35b07009ae78749bcc1c401801</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-athena-provisioned-capacity/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T19:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we launch the ability to provision capacity to run your Athena queries. Athena is a query service that makes it simple to analyze data in Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) data lakes and 30 different data sources, including on-premises data sources or other cloud systems, using standard SQL queries. Athena is serverless, so […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.7 (aka Jubilee) has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/28/spring-cloud-2021-0-7-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/28/spring-cloud-2021-0-7-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Maciaszek-Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: StatefulSet Start Ordinal Simplifies Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/28/statefulset-start-ordinal/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/28/statefulset-start-ordinal/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Peter Schuurman (Google)
Kubernetes v1.26 introduced a new, alpha-level feature for
StatefulSets that controls
the ordinal numbering of Pod replicas. As of Kubernetes v1.27, this feature is
now beta. Ordinals can start from arbitrary
non-negative numbers. This blog post will discuss how this feature can be
used.
Background
StatefulSets ordinals provide sequential identities for pod replicas. When using
OrderedReady Pod management
Pods are created from ordinal index 0 up to N-1.
With Kubernetes today, orchestrating a StatefulSet migration across clusters is
challenging. Backup and restore solutions exist, but these require the
application to be scaled down to zero replicas prior to migration. In today's
fully connected world, even planned application downtime may not allow you to
me…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Alerting with Atlas Streaming Eval]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e691c60dc61e</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/improved-alerting-with-atlas-streaming-eval-e691c60dc61e?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An ML-based approach to better characterize lung diseases]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/an-ml-based-approach-to-better.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/an-ml-based-approach-to-better.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:24:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Babak Behsaz, Software Engineer, and Andrew Carroll, Product Lead, Genomics




The combination of the environment an individual experiences and their genetic predispositions determines the majority of their risk for various diseases. Large national efforts, such as the UK Biobank, have created large, public resources to better understand the links between environment, genetics, and disease. This has the potential to help individuals better understand how to stay healthy, clinicians to treat illnesses, and scientists to develop new medicines.


One challenge in this process is how we make sense of the vast amount of clinical measurements — the UK Biobank has many petabytes of imaging, metabolic tests, and medical records spanning 500,000 individuals. To best use this data, we nee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CyberGRX cut ML processing time from 8 days to 56 minutes with AWS Step Functions Distributed Map]]></title>
        <id>6ca49d44c0bb9aa0d343f5673699f5a7fe73ca58</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-cybercrx-cut-ml-processing-time-from-8-days-to-56-minutes-with-aws-step-functions-distributed-map/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T19:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last December, Sébastien Stormacq wrote about the availability of a distributed map state for AWS Step Functions, a new feature that allows you to orchestrate large-scale parallel workloads in the cloud. That’s when Charles Burton, a data systems engineer for a company called CyberGRX, found out about it and refactored his workflow, reducing the processing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust and efficient medical imaging with self-supervision]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robust-and-efficient-medical-imaging.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robust-and-efficient-medical-imaging.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T20:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shekoofeh Azizi, Senior Research Scientist, and Laura Culp, Senior Research Engineer, Google Research
  
  
  
Despite recent progress in the field of medical artificial intelligence (AI), most existing models are narrow, single-task systems that require large quantities of labeled data to train. Moreover, these models cannot be easily reused in new clinical contexts as they often require the collection, de-identification and annotation of site-specific data for every new deployment environment, which is both laborious and expensive. This problem of data-efficient generalization (a model’s ability to generalize to new settings using minimal new data) continues to be a key translational challenge for medical machine learning (ML) models and has in turn, prevented their broad uptak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud no-code provisioning is now GA with new features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-no-code-provisioning-is-now-ga-with-new-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-no-code-provisioning-is-now-ga-with-new-features"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No-code provisioning is now GA for Terraform Cloud Business, providing validated self-service infrastructure, additional security through more granular permissions, and ease of use with variable options as dropdowns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to call the Camunda Inbound Webhook from Postman]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=79381&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=79381</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/how-to-call-camunda-inbound-webhook-postman/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to create processes using the Camunda Webhook Connector and to start them via Postman both in unauthenticated and authenticated modes.
The post How to call the Camunda Inbound Webhook from Postman appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Pappas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LayerNAS: Neural architecture search in polynomial complexity]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/layernas-neural-architecture-search-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/layernas-neural-architecture-search-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T17:20:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yicheng Fan and Dana Alon, Software Engineers, Google Research




Every byte and every operation matters when trying to build a faster model, especially if the model is to run on-device. Neural architecture search (NAS) algorithms design sophisticated model architectures by searching through a larger model-space than what is possible manually. Different NAS algorithms, such as MNasNet and TuNAS, have been proposed and have discovered several efficient model architectures, including MobileNetV3, EfficientNet. 

 


Here we present LayerNAS, an approach that reformulates the multi-objective NAS problem within the framework of combinatorial optimization to greatly reduce the complexity, which results in an order of magnitude reduction in the number of model candidates that must be …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sentinel and control groups now available in HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/sentinel-and-control-groups-now-available-in-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/sentinel-and-control-groups-now-available-in-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Plus Clusters add support for Sentinel policies and control groups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Updates to the Auto-refreshing Official CVE Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/25/k8s-cve-feed-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/25/k8s-cve-feed-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Cailyn Edwards (Shopify), Mahé Tardy (Isovalent), Pushkar Joglekar
Since launching the Auto-refreshing Official CVE feed as an alpha
feature in the 1.25 release, we have made significant improvements and updates. We are excited to announce the release of the
beta version of the feed. This blog post will outline the feedback received, the changes made, and talk about how you can help
as we prepare to make this a stable feature in a future Kubernetes Release.
Feedback from end-users
SIG Security received some feedback from end-users:
The JSON CVE Feed did not comply
with the JSON Feed specification as its name would suggest.
The feed could also support RSS
in addition to JSON Feed format.
Some metadata could be added to indicate the freshness of
the feed overall, or specific CVEs. A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 24, 2023: Amazon CodeCatalyst, Amazon S3 on Snowball Edge, and More…]]></title>
        <id>f99637a00ba132ddbd2ab3f3ddf491e8cdcc7989</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-24-2023-amazon-codecatalyst-amazon-s3-on-snowball-edge-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T21:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As always, there’s plenty to share this week: Amazon CodeCatalyst is now generally available, Amazon S3 is now available on Snowball Edge devices, version 1.0.0 of AWS Amplify Flutter is here, and a lot more. Let’s dive in! Last Week’s Launches Here are some of the launches that caught my eye this past week: Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Power Automate to update Azure DevOps queries]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66806</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/use-power-automate-to-update-azure-devops-queries/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T21:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I’ll explain how to set up automation to automatically update Azure DevOps (ADO) queries. Using an automated Power Automate flow, you save time by not having to manually update your queries for each sprint. Everyone using your queries benefits by having data and details that are always current and accurate.
The post Use Power Automate to update Azure DevOps queries appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Reitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choose Korean in AWS Support as Your Preferred Language]]></title>
        <id>3fd49d6f464a65c650e1d14d5e7d7c56e29331bc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/choose-korean-in-aws-support-as-your-preferred-language/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T20:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the general availability of AWS Support in Korean as your preferred language, in addition to English, Japanese, and Chinese. As the number of customers speaking Korean grows, AWS Support is invested in providing the best support experience possible. You can now communicate with AWS Support engineers and agents in Korean when you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds Vault-backed dynamic credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-vault-backed-dynamic-credentials</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-vault-backed-dynamic-credentials"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic provider credentials in HashiCorp Terraform Cloud now supports Vault dynamic secrets engines to consolidate cloud access for Terraform runs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at CHI 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-chi-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-chi-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T02:26:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Malaya Jules, Program Manager, Google




This week, the Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI 2023) is being held in Hamburg, Germany. We are proud to be a Hero Sponsor of CHI 2023, a premier conference on human-computer interaction, where Google researchers contribute at all levels. This year we are presenting over 30 papers and are actively involved in organizing and hosting a number of different events across workshops, courses, and interactive sessions.


 


If you’re registered for CHI 2023, we hope you’ll visit the Google booth to learn more about the exciting work across various topics, including language interactions, causal inference, question answering and more. Take a look below to learn more about the Google research being presented at CHI 2023 (Goog…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Server Side Field Validation and OpenAPI V3 move to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/24/openapi-v3-field-validation-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/24/openapi-v3-field-validation-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jeffrey Ying (Google), Antoine Pelisse (Google)
Before Kubernetes v1.8 (!), typos, mis-indentations or minor errors in
YAMLs could have catastrophic consequences (e.g. a typo like
forgetting the trailing s in replica: 1000 could cause an outage,
because the value would be ignored and missing, forcing a reset of
replicas back to 1). This was solved back then by fetching the OpenAPI
v2 in kubectl and using it to verify that fields were correct and
present before applying. Unfortunately, at that time, Custom Resource
Definitions didn’t exist, and the code was written under that
assumption. When CRDs were later introduced, the lack of flexibility
in the validation code forced some hard decisions in the way CRDs
exposed their schema, leaving us in a cycle of bad validation causing
bad O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Blocks for ML: Accelerating machine learning prototyping with interactive tools]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/visual-blocks-for-ml-accelerating.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/visual-blocks-for-ml-accelerating.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T19:01:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ruofei Du, Interactive Perception & Graphics Lead, Google Augmented Reality, and Na Li, Tech Lead Manager, Google CoreML

  



  Update — 2023/05/08: This post has been updated to include open-source details for the Visual Blocks framework. 
human body segmentation for video and teleconferencing, depth estimation for 3D reconstruction, hand and body tracking for interaction, and audio processing for remote communication.



However, developing and iterating on these ML-based multimedia prototypes can be challenging and costly. It usually involves a cross-functional team of ML practitioners who fine-tune the models, evaluate robustness, characterize strengths and weaknesses, inspect performance in the end-use context, and develop the applications. Moreover, models are frequently …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Query Node Logs Using The Kubelet API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/21/node-log-query-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/21/node-log-query-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aravindh Puthiyaparambil (Red Hat)
Kubernetes 1.27 introduced a new feature called Node log query that allows
viewing logs of services running on the node.
What problem does it solve?
Cluster administrators face issues when debugging malfunctioning services
running on the node. They usually have to SSH or RDP into the node to view the
logs of the service to debug the issue. The Node log query feature helps with
this scenario by allowing the cluster administrator to view the logs using
kubectl. This is especially useful with Windows nodes where you run into the
issue of the node going to the ready state but containers not coming up due to
CNI misconfigurations and other issues that are not easily identifiable by
looking at the Pod status.
How does it work?
The kubelet already has a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep long-horizon forecasting]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/recent-advances-in-deep-long-horizon.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/recent-advances-in-deep-long-horizon.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T20:26:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rajat Sen and Abhimanyu Das, Research Scientists, Google Research




Time-series forecasting is an important research area that is critical to several scientific and industrial applications, like retail supply chain optimization, energy and traffic prediction, and weather forecasting. In retail use cases, for example, it has been observed that improving demand forecasting accuracy can meaningfully reduce inventory costs and increase revenue. 
 

Modern time-series applications can involve forecasting hundreds of thousands of correlated time-series (e.g., demands of different products for a retailer) over long horizons (e.g., a quarter or year away at daily granularity). As such, time-series forecasting models need to satisfy the following key criterias:



Ability to handle auxi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 Compatible Storage on AWS Snowball Edge Compute Optimized Devices Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>3a5f9a4909fe852e7ed6cc8ac314d50e62bf28b1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-compatible-storage-on-aws-snowball-edge-compute-optimized-devices-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T18:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have added a collection of purpose-built services to the AWS Snow Family for customers, such as Snowball Edge in 2016 and Snowcone in 2020. These services run compute intensive workloads and stores data in edge locations with denied, disrupted, intermittent, or limited network connectivity and for transferring large amounts of data from on-premises and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Human Approach to Process Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78911&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78911</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/human-approach-process-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chances of success are significantly higher when you put humans in the center of your orchestration projects.
The post A Human Approach to Process Automation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Single Pod Access Mode for PersistentVolumes Graduates to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/20/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/20/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chris Henzie (Google)
With the release of Kubernetes v1.27 the ReadWriteOncePod feature has graduated
to beta. In this blog post, we'll take a closer look at this feature, what it
does, and how it has evolved in the beta release.
What is ReadWriteOncePod?
ReadWriteOncePod is a new access mode for
PersistentVolumes (PVs)
and PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs)
introduced in Kubernetes v1.22. This access mode enables you to restrict volume
access to a single pod in the cluster, ensuring that only one pod can write to
the volume at a time. This can be particularly useful for stateful workloads
that require single-writer access to storage.
For more context on access modes and how ReadWriteOncePod works read
What are access modes and why are they important?
in the Introducing Single Pod Acces…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Building without Limits at AWS Developer Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>5642e5e26f54b4e2d613344cf7fb6a8727367ef7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/discover-building-without-limits-at-aws-developer-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T18:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We hope you can join us on Wednesday, April 26, for a free-to-attend online event, AWS Developer Innovation Day. AWS will stream the event simultaneously across multiple platforms, including LinkedIn Live, Twitter, YouTube, and Twitch. Developer Innovation Day is a brand-new event designed specifically for developers and development teams. In the event, sessions throughout the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Technology, AI, Society and Culture]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T18:12:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lauren Wilcox, Senior Staff Research Scientist, on behalf of the Technology, AI, Society, and Culture Team




Google sees AI as a foundational and transformational technology, with recent advances in generative AI technologies, such as LaMDA, PaLM, Imagen, Parti, MusicLM, and similar machine learning (ML) models, some of which are now being incorporated into our products. This transformative potential requires us to be responsible not only in how we advance our technology, but also in how we envision which technologies to build, and how we assess the social impact AI and ML-enabled technologies have on the world. This endeavor necessitates fundamental and applied research with an interdisciplinary lens that engages with — and accounts for — the social, cultural, economic, and ot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第228話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361158146336</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361158146336"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differentially private heatmaps]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/differentially-private-heatmaps.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/differentially-private-heatmaps.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T20:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Badih Ghazi, Staff Research Scientist, and Nachiappan Valliappan, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research






Recently, differential privacy (DP) has emerged as a mathematically robust notion of user privacy for data aggregation and machine learning (ML), with practical deployments including the 2022 US Census and in industry. Over the last few years, we have open-sourced libraries for privacy-preserving analytics and ML and have been constantly enhancing their capabilities. Meanwhile, new algorithms have been developed by the research community for several analytic tasks involving private aggregation of data. 
 

One such important data aggregation method is the heatmap. Heatmaps are popular for visualizing aggregated data in two or more dimensions. They are widely used in ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Efficient SELinux volume relabeling (Beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/18/kubernetes-1-27-efficient-selinux-relabeling-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/18/kubernetes-1-27-efficient-selinux-relabeling-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jan Šafránek (Red Hat)
The problem
On Linux with Security-Enhanced Linux (SELinux) enabled, it's traditionally
the container runtime that applies SELinux labels to a Pod and all its volumes.
Kubernetes only passes the SELinux label from a Pod's securityContext fields
to the container runtime.
The container runtime then recursively changes SELinux label on all files that
are visible to the Pod's containers. This can be time-consuming if there are
many files on the volume, especially when the volume is on a remote filesystem.
Note
subPath of a volume, only that subPath of the whole
volume is relabeled. This allows two pods that have two different SELinux labels
to use the same volume, as long as they use different subpaths of it.

If a Pod does not have any SELinux label assigned in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s happening at KubeCon Europe 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-s-happening-at-kubecon-europe-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-s-happening-at-kubecon-europe-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attending KubeCon EU, either in person or online? Check out what HashiCorp is doing and talking about at the event, and learn about recent Kubernetes-related product features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.16 improves automatic HCL conversion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-16-improves-automatic-hcl-conversion</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-16-improves-automatic-hcl-conversion"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform v0.16 improves automatic conversion of configuration code from HCL to supported languages by enabling type coercion and providing better support for iterators and functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate External Systems Effortlessly with Custom Connectors in Camunda Platform – No Java Coding Required!]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78910&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78910</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/create-custom-template-based-on-rest-connector/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, learn how to create a new custom Connector for Camunda Platform in just a few simple steps and start orchestrating faster.
The post Integrate External Systems Effortlessly with Custom Connectors in Camunda Platform – No Java Coding Required! appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bastian Koerber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review: New Service for Generative AI and Amazon EC2 Trn1n, Inf2, and CodeWhisperer now GA – April 17, 2023]]></title>
        <id>1276fde47550c891c0d47e730e2a5344912bf074</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-new-service-for-generative-ai-and-amazon-ec2-trn1n-inf2-and-codewhisperer-now-ga-april-17-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T19:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I could almost title this blog post the “AWS AI/ML Week in Review.” This past week, we announced several new innovations and tools for building with generative AI on AWS. Let’s dive right into it. Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my attention during the previous week: Announcing Amazon Bedrock and Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: More fine-grained pod topology spread policies reached beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/17/fine-grained-pod-topology-spread-features-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/17/fine-grained-pod-topology-spread-features-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Alex Wang (Shopee), Kante Yin (DaoCloud), Kensei Nakada (Mercari)
In Kubernetes v1.19, Pod topology spread constraints
went to general availability (GA).
As time passed, we - SIG Scheduling - received feedback from users,
and, as a result, we're actively working on improving the Topology Spread feature via three KEPs.
All of these features have reached beta in Kubernetes v1.27 and are enabled by default.
This blog post introduces each feature and the use case behind each of them.
KEP-3022: min domains in Pod Topology Spread
Pod Topology Spread has the maxSkew parameter to define the degree to which Pods may be unevenly distributed.
But, there wasn't a way to control the number of domains over which we should spread.
Some users want to force spreading Pods over a minimum number of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond automatic differentiation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/beyond-automatic-differentiation.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/beyond-automatic-differentiation.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Matthew Streeter, Software Engineer, Google Research




Derivatives play a central role in optimization and machine learning. By locally approximating a training loss, derivatives guide an optimizer toward lower values of the loss. Automatic differentiation frameworks such as TensorFlow, PyTorch, and JAX are an essential part of modern machine learning, making it feasible to use gradient-based optimizers to train very complex models.


 


But are derivatives all we need? By themselves, derivatives only tell us how a function behaves on an infinitesimal scale. To use derivatives effectively, we often need to know more than that. For example, to choose a learning rate for gradient descent, we need to know something about how the loss function behaves over a small but finite windo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 220]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66772</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-220/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sprint 220 was again dedicated to fixing bugs. We continue to drive down that bug backlog as quickly as we can.
Issue
Date and time shift between New Boards and old
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 220 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robotic deep RL at scale: Sorting waste and recyclables with a fleet of robots]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robotic-deep-rl-at-scale-sorting-waste.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robotic-deep-rl-at-scale-sorting-waste.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T19:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sergey Levine, Research Scientist, and Alexander Herzog, Staff Research Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team
  
  
Reinforcement learning (RL) can enable robots to learn complex behaviors through trial-and-error interaction, getting better and better over time. Several of our prior works explored how RL can enable intricate robotic skills, such as robotic grasping, multi-task learning, and even playing table tennis. Although robotic RL has come a long way, we still don't see RL-enabled robots in everyday settings. The real world is complex, diverse, and changes over time, presenting a major challenge for robotic systems. However, we believe that RL should offer us an excellent tool for tackling precisely these challenges: by continually practicing, getting better, and l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a secure Azure reference architecture with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-a-secure-azure-reference-architecture-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-a-secure-azure-reference-architecture-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use HashiCorp Terraform to deploy Azure resources using security best practices and policy as code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Service Connection guidance for AKS customers using Kubernetes tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66692</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/service-connection-guidance-for-aks-customers-using-kubernetes-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T13:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes tasks & Service Connections
AzureFunctionOnKubernetes
These tasks can be configured to target a Kubernetes cluster in a number of ways, using the connectionType property:
Connection Type
Azure Resource Manager
The post Service Connection guidance for AKS customers using Kubernetes tasks appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline Your Ansible Module Development with Content Builder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/streamline-your-ansible-module-development-with-content-builder</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/streamline-your-ansible-module-development-with-content-builder"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo byHush Naidoo Jade Photography onUnsplash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gomathi Selvi Srinivasan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 Inf2 Instances for Low-Cost, High-Performance Generative AI Inference are Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>eb18bd7117541f6c4b0788702c73681882dd3cc4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-inf2-instances-for-low-cost-high-performance-generative-ai-inference-are-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T12:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Innovations in deep learning (DL), especially the rapid growth of large language models (LLMs), have taken the industry by storm. DL models have grown from millions to billions of parameters and are demonstrating exciting new capabilities. They are fueling new applications such as generative AI or advanced research in healthcare and life sciences. AWS has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeWhisperer, Free for Individual Use, is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>449ba7d8898cd00282a5d25974f238fd40f0b703</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-codewhisperer-free-for-individual-use-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T12:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon CodeWhisperer, a real-time AI coding companion, is generally available and also includes a CodeWhisperer Individual tier that’s free to use for all developers. Originally launched in preview last year, CodeWhisperer keeps developers in the zone and productive, helping them write code quickly and securely and without needing to break their flow by leaving […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the SQL Connector to Streamline Trade Ops Processes]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78093&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78093</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/using-sql-connector-streamline-trade-ops-processes/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are new Connectors available for SQL databases. Here's how you can get them and a quick example of how you could use them today in financial services.
The post Using the SQL Connector to Streamline Trade Ops Processes appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UniPi: Learning universal policies via text-guided video generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/unipi-learning-universal-policies-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/unipi-learning-universal-policies-via.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sherry Yang, Research Scientist, and Yilun Du, Student Researcher, Google Research, Brain Team
Building models that solve a diverse set of tasks has become a dominant paradigm in the domains of vision and language. In natural language processing, large pre-trained models, such as PaLM, GPT-3 and Gopher, have demonstrated remarkable zero-shot learning of new language tasks. Similarly, in computer vision, models like CLIP and Flamingo have shown robust performance on zero-shot classification and object recognition. A natural next step is to use such tools to construct agents that can complete different decision-making tasks across many environments.



However, training such agents faces the inherent challenge of environmental diversity, since different environments operate with di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BGP Management with Ansible Validated Content using the network.bgp collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/bgp-management-with-ansible-validated-content-using-the-network.bgp-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/bgp-management-with-ansible-validated-content-using-the-network.bgp-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AnsibleFest 2022, we announced a new addition to the content ecosystem offered through the platform which is Ansible validated content. Ansible validated content is use cases-focused automation content that is packaged as Collections that contain Ansible plugins, roles and playbooks that you can use as an automation job through Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps 2023 Q2 Roadmap update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66701</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-2023-q2-roadmap-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T22:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday we published an updated list of features we plan to deliver in Q2. Each title includes a link where you can find details about each feature. We expect that this will help bring visibility into the key investments for the upcoming quarter.
The post Azure DevOps 2023 Q2 Roadmap update  appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing an aging clock using deep learning on retinal images]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/developing-aging-clock-using-deep.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/developing-aging-clock-using-deep.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:22:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Ahadi, Research Fellow, Applied Science, and Andrew Carroll, Product Lead, Genomics




Aging is a process that is characterized by physiological and molecular changes that increase an individual's risk of developing diseases and eventually dying. Being able to measure and estimate the biological signatures of aging can help researchers identify preventive measures to reduce disease risk and impact. Researchers have developed “aging clocks” based on markers such as blood proteins or DNA methylation to measure individuals’ biological age, which is distinct from one’s chronological age. These aging clocks help predict the risk of age-related diseases. But because protein and methylation markers require a blood draw, non-invasive ways to find similar measures could make aging i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66647</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/announcing-azure-devops-server-2022-0-1-rc/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T17:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are releasing Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC. This is a go-live release, meaning it is supported on production instances, and you will be able to upgrade to our final release.
The post Announcing Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Vault integration via Sidecar Agent Injector vs. Vault Secrets Operator vs. CSI provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-vault-integration-via-sidecar-agent-injector-vs-csi-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-vault-integration-via-sidecar-agent-injector-vs-csi-provider"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A detailed comparison of three HashiCorp-supported methods for HashiCorp Vault and Kubernetes integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.10 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78394&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78394</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/camunda-modeler-5-10/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T15:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the latest version of Camunda Desktop Modeler, including FEEL templating, a visual grid for diagrams and more. 
The post Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.10 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beatriz Mendes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>