<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-11-26T01:37:21.096Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-11-26T01:37:21.096Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.3 Release Candidate 2 Is Available!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=300429</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/11/25/goland-2022-3-release-candidate-2-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T15:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.3 Release Candidate 2 is out. Please note that to use GoLand 2022.3 RC, you need to have an active subscription or start a 30-day trial. Download GoLand 2022.3 RC 2 In this build, we have fixed some bugs. There are also a couple of new features. Usages for Code Vision We’ve introduced usages […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A paradox of status and power]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44275</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/720331640/0/sethsblog~A-paradox-of-status-and-power/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T09:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One can refuse to pay bills, bully employees, steal credit, work the refs and look for shortcuts… or pay bills ahead of time, elevate employees, amplify the credit of others and take the long road. While both are modern signifiers of a certain kind of success, only one is a resilient way forward. Ancient emperors […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paper Title]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2703/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2703/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/paper_title.png" title="CONFLICT OF INTEREST STATEMENT: The authors hope these results are correct because we all want to be cool people who are good at science." alt="CONFLICT OF INTEREST STATEMENT: The authors hope these results are correct because we all want to be cool people who are good at science." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 0.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-modulith-0-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-modulith-0-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T21:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hot on the heels of Spring Boot 3.0 GA, it’s my pleasure to announce the availability of Spring Modulith 0.1. The release concludes the integration of the Moduliths project into the Spring ecosystem. I want to especially thank Dmitry Belyaev and Björn Kieling who helped a lot during the migration and contributed significant new features to the project, the event publication repository implementations for JDBC and MongoDB in particular.

For a general introduction into the project, please check out the original announcement and this InfoQ article.

Changelog | Reference documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0 Goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-3-0-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-3-0-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T18:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, it is my very great pleasure to announce that Spring Boot 3.0 is now generally available and 3.0.0 can be found in Maven Central.

This release is the culmination of 12 months work and over 5700 commits by 151 different individuals. A massive thank you to everyone that has contributed, and to all the early adopters that have been providing vital feedback on the milestones.

This is the first major revision of Spring Boot since 2.0 was released 4.5 years ago. It’s also the first GA version of Spring Boot that provides support for Spring Framework 6.0 and GraalVM. 

Highlights of the new release include:


  
A Java 17 baseline

  
Support for generating native images with GraalVM, superseding the experimental Spring Native project

  
Improved observability with Micrometer and Micrometer Tracing

  
Support for Jakarta EE 10 with an EE 9 baseline


There’s far too many features to list them all here in detail, so head over to the release notes page on our wiki to find out more. If you just want to get started, you can easily bootstrap a new project on start.spring.io. If you’d like to try out the GraalVM support, start.spring.io can help with that too.

Over the coming weeks we’ll be publishing blog posts that cover some Spring Boot 3.0 features in detail.

Thanks again to everyone that has contributed to Spring and Spring Boot over the years! Supporting Jakarta EE 9 and 10, the observability enhancements, and GraalVM support has been a huge team effort that has left no corner of the Spring portfolio untouched. A special thank you to the developers of the other projects in the Spring portfolio, without whom this release would not have been possible.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.3 RC2 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=299834</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/11/intellij-idea-2022-3-rc2/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T17:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.3 is on its way, and we’ve published the second Release Candidate build for it. You can download the new version from our website, update directly from the IDE or via the free Toolbox App, or use snaps for Ubuntu. This build requires an active subscription to IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate. Try the RC2 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode 2022.3 EAP: Fixes for Swift Completion and SPM, a New UI]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=300088</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/11/appcode-2022-3-eap-fixes-for-swift-completion-and-spm-a-new-ui/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T15:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, A new AppCode 2022.3 EAP build (223.7571.113) is available for download from our website or via the Toolbox App. You can also update from the previous 2022.3 EAP build via a patch. DOWNLOAD APPCODE EAP Here are the highlights: Swift code completion: We improved init and deinit keyword completion by removing redundant spaces […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-2-7-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-2-7-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T15:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.6 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 44 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-framework-6-0-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-framework-6-0-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T14:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.2 is available now.

Spring Framework 6.0.2 includes 4 fixes and documentation improvements.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.14 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-2-6-14-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-2-6-14-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T14:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.14 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 39 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
End of life

It’s just over a year since the release of Spring Boot 2.6.0 which means that, as per our open source support policy, 2.6.14 is the last release that’s planned in the 2.6.x line. Releases may be made in the future, but only in response to a commercial support request.

As previously announced, Spring Boot 2.7 will be the last minor in the 2.x line. As such, we’ve extended our open source support for 2.7.x release by an additional 6 months until November 2023. In addition, commercial support for Spring Boot 2.7 has also been extended and is available until February 2025.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin News: 1.8.0-Beta, EAP Champions, Developer Survey Results, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=299955</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/11/kotlin-news-oct-nov-22/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T13:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin 1.8.0-Beta Has Been Released Kotlin 1.8.0-Beta brings the following updates: Gradle 7.3 compatibility Recursive Path utility functions in the stdlib Support for Xcode 14 in Kotlin/Native Discontinuation of support for the old JVM backend Try 1.8.0-Beta We Are Looking for EAP Champions Are you working on a large-scale, production-grade Kotlin project? Would you love to be among […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Petrova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.3 Release Candidate]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=300027</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/11/24/datagrip-2022-3-release-candidate/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T13:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the release candidate for 2022.3. Check out these publications for a reminder of what’s new in this version: 2022.3 EAP 12022.3 EAP 2: Redis support2022.3 EAP 3 Try it out and share your feedback with us!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0 Goes GA!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-batch-5-0-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-batch-5-0-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is finally here! Spring Batch 5.0 is now generally available from Maven Central. Spring Batch 5 is the culmination of two years of work, including dozens of improvements, features, and bug fixes by more than 50 contributors! On Behalf of the team, I would like to thank ALL contributors who had a role in this huge release!

This blog post walks through the major highlights of this new generation of the framework. You can find the details of all the changes in the release notes and the upgrade instructions in the migration guide.
What’s new?


  
New Java version baseline

  
Major dependencies upgrade

  
Full GraalVM native support

  
Introduction of the new Observation API from Micrometer

  
Execution context Meta-data improvement

  
New default execution context serializati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An antidote]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44273</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/720256738/0/sethsblog~An-antidote/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T09:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gratitude might be the way forward. So much of what ails us gets a bit better when we say ‘thank you.’ Even when it’s hard. Especially then.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools Plugin 2022.11 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=299846</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/11/24/edutools-plugin-2022-11-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T09:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new version of EduTools is packed with new features for course creators. You can now automate checks for selected tasks, add custom videos for the dark IDE theme, and take advantage of Kotlin DSL files in your course. We’ve also enhanced the overall experience with multiple improvements and bug fixes. To see what’s new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.3 Release Candidate]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=299827</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/11/clion-2022-3-release-candidate/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T23:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.3 is on its way, and the Release Candidate for v2022.3 is now available! To install CLion 2022.3 RC (build 223.7571.113), download it from the website, update via the Toolbox App, or use this snap package (for Ubuntu). You need to have an active subscription or a trial license to use CLion 2022.3 RC. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2.4 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=299832</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/11/intellij-idea-2022-2-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T17:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2.4.  You can download the new version from our website or update it directly from the IDE. You can also update to it via the free Toolbox App or using snaps for Ubuntu.  This version provides general quality improvements along with several valuable fixes for macOS users: Changing the display […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.3 RC]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=299439</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/11/phpstorm-2022-3-rc/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T16:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.3 Release Candidate is now available! Unlike previous EAP builds, this RC requires you to have a valid PhpStorm license. Let’s take a brief look at some of the most interesting improvements coming in v2022.3: PHP 8.2 full support Code Vision for PHP New UI (Preview) Rendered PHPDoc view Improved Quick Documentation Quick-fix preview […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.3 Release Candidate 2 Is Out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=299443</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/11/webstorm-2022-3-rc2/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T14:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year’s third major release of WebStorm is just days away! Try the WebStorm 2022.3 Release Candidate 2 build today and test out what we’ve implemented in WebStorm 2022.3. DOWNLOAD WEBSTORM 2022.3 RC2 Please note that, unlike our previous EAP builds, you must have an active WebStorm license to use it. Otherwise, you’ll need to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Are Looking For EAP Champions!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=299783</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/11/eap-champions/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T13:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kotlin Early Access Preview (EAP) is a program where the Kotlin team ships a few Beta and Release Candidate builds before every release. Any Kotlin developer can participate in the Early Access Preview, try out the latest Kotlin features before they are released, and help the Kotlin team gather the feedback necessary to stabilize […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Petrova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade of .NET agent for Azure Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65991</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/upgrade-of-net-agent-for-azure-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T11:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are upgrading the .NET used by Azure Pipelines agent from current .NET Core 3.1 to .NET 6. This is to support new Apple silicon hardware as well as newer operating systems such as Ubuntu 22.04, or Windows on ARM64. Another reason for the .NET upgrade is the fact the .NET Core 3.1 version is already in maintenance phase and the support ends on December 13th,
The post Upgrade of .NET agent for Azure Pipelines appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bohdan Janousek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-framework-6-0-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-framework-6-0-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T10:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.1 is available now.

Spring Framework 6.0.1 includes 21 fixes and improvements.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.1.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-for-graphql-1-1-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-for-graphql-1-1-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pleased to announce that Spring for GraphQL 1.1.0 is now available on Maven Central. This version will ship with Spring Boot 3.0.0 later this week.

Spring for GraphQL 1.0.0 was released 6 months ago, so why a new minor version now? The team initially planned a 1.1.0 release with one goal in mind: support Spring Framework 6.0 / Spring Boot 3.0 and adapt to the new baseline for that generation:


  
Java 17

  
Jakarta EE 9

  
GraphQL Java 19


In addition, we shipped some new and noteworthy features we think you’ll like:
Observability

Observability is a major theme across the Spring portfolio in this major new Spring Framework 6 generation. Spring projects now have their own, built-in instrumentation for metrics and traces based on the new Observation API from Micrometer. Thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long is “never”?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43291</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/720173242/0/sethsblog~How-long-is-never/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T09:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It changes. It changes as we age, and it changes depending on the situation. A second-grader might think that a boring class is never going to end. A bad cold might feel endless, unless we have the perspective of someone who has experienced a chronic problem. Some things actually deserve “never.” But most of what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Support Python with JetBrains” Campaign Extended]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=299597</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/11/support-python-with-jetbrains-campaign-extended/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good news! The Support Python with JetBrains campaign has been extended for another week and will now last until November 29, 2022. Buy a PyCharm Pro subscription at 30% OFF, have the full amount of your purchase donated to support Python, and get a complimentary one-year subscription for DataSpell as our treat! I want to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roberto Pesce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: the road to Spring Framework 6: the new Ahead-of-Time Compilation Engine and GraalVM]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-tips-the-road-to-spring-framework-6-the-new-ahead-of-time-compilation-engine-and-graalvm</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-tips-the-road-to-spring-framework-6-the-new-ahead-of-time-compilation-engine-and-graalvm"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Spring Boot 3 is here (or will be tomorrow, on the 24th of November, 2022, to be more precise!), bringing a fantastic new Ahead-of-Time (AOT) compilation engine that supports GraalVM native images. Join me, and we’ll dive deep into the engine and its interactions with the Spring component model. 

This video is a detailed masterclass on the new AOT engine. It starts by examining the everyday usecases of an application developer and delves deeper and deeper into the engine, treating concerns that library and framework developers will care about. 

Enjoy! 


Also, Happy thanksgiving (if you celebrate) from us to you!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What If 2 Gift Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2702/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2702/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/what_if_2_gift_guide.png" title="BABIES OR LITERATURE BUT NOT BOTH: Baby shoes" alt="BABIES OR LITERATURE BUT NOT BOTH: Baby shoes" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks 2023: 24-Hours of Virtual Knowledge Sharing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2023-24-hours-of-virtual-knowledge-sharing</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2023-24-hours-of-virtual-knowledge-sharing"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks returns on February 16, 2023. Join our global community for 24 hours of knowledge sharing. The call for speakers is open until December 7, 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting New GitHub Features Powering Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-11-22-exciting-new-github-features-powering-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-11-22-exciting-new-github-features-powering-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T19:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the exciting enhancements in GitHub that empower Machine Learning practitioners to do more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - November 22nd, 2022 - Spring Boot 3 and Thanksgiving edition!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/22/this-week-in-spring-november-22nd-2022-spring-boot-3-and-thanksgiving-edition</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/22/this-week-in-spring-november-22nd-2022-spring-boot-3-and-thanksgiving-edition"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! It’s Tuesday, the 22nd of November, 2022, as I write this, which means we’re two days away from Spring Boot 3 and Thanksgiving. Spring Boot 3, I’ve written about in abundance so I won’t rehash that. If you want to learn more about some of the amazing new features in Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3, perhaps check out my Spring Tips installment introducing them in this episode:


And, of course, a major new feature in Spring Boot 3 is the new ahead-of-time (AOT) engine, about which I speak at great length in tomorrow’s new installment of Spring Tips:


This video is done so that you can watch the first part as an application developer and get a lot out of it. Folks who want to take the concepts further - as a library, or framework, or developer, can carry on ‘till t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and HashiCorp's Journey to 1 Billion Terraform AWS Provider Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-and-hashicorp-s-journey-to-1-billion-terraform-aws-provider-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-and-hashicorp-s-journey-to-1-billion-terraform-aws-provider-downloads"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Terraform AWS provider has surpassed one billion downloads — here’s how we got there, and what to look for next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Importing/Exporting Collections in automation hubs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/importing/exporting-collections-in-automation-hubs</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/importing/exporting-collections-in-automation-hubs"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article discusses how to export and import Collections from one automation hub to another.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.0.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/22/spring-for-graphql-1-0-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/22/spring-for-graphql-1-0-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of everyone involved, I’m pleased to announce that Spring for GraphQL 1.0.3 is now available from Maven Central. This version will be shipped with Spring Boot 2.7.6 due for release later this week.

This release includes a number of enhancements, documentation improvements, dependency upgrades, and a couple of bug fixes. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

We’re also about to release the 1.1.0 release, targeting Spring Boot 3.0.
How can you help?

If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-graphql tag.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 1.0 is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/22/spring-authorization-server-1-0-is-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/22/spring-authorization-server-1-0-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, we are very excited to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 1.0.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:1.0.0'




Spring Authorization Server has come a long way since its initial commit on April 2, 2020, as the APIs have stabilized and matured over this time. A lot of effort and care has been put into this project to ensure a robust foundation for its continued growth. This first major release delivers a full feature set.



Spring Authorization Server 1.0 is based on Spring Security 6.0, which is based on Spring Framework 6.0 and will require a minimum of JDK 17 at runtime. This major release inherits the VMware Tanzu OSS support policy. Commercial support, which offers an extended support period, is also available from VMware.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples, to become familiar with setup and configuration.



On behalf of the team, I would like to thank everyone who has contributed and helped grow this project. We hope to continue to work together and ultimately establish Spring Authorization Server as the de facto framework for OAuth2 Authorization Server support on the Java platform.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/22/spring-authorization-server-0-4-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/22/spring-authorization-server-0-4-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.4.0.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.4.0'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People problems are complicated problems]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43274</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/720092980/0/sethsblog~People-problems-are-complicated-problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Engineering problems are difficult, but they have a right answer. People problems, by their nature, are on a spectrum, a distribution of possible forward paths. But they’re complicated. A situation might not fit a person, and vice versa. Add a second person and now you have two people, and two people interacting exponentially increase the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Web Services 4.0.0 is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/21/spring-web-services-4-0-0-is-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/21/spring-web-services-4-0-0-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings Spring community,



The Spring Web Services team has released 4.0.0 for general availability. This is the version of Spring WS you’ll need if you are building SOAP-based applications with Spring Boot 3.0.



4.0.x is the generation of Spring Web Services that works with Jakarta EE 9+, the version where the enterprise specs (JAX-WS, etc.) migrate from javax. to jakarta. package prefixes. Check out Juergen Holler’s blog post for more details about Spring Framework 6.0.



Being based upon Spring Framework 6.0, this is also the generation of Spring Web Services that is rebased on top of Java 17 (LTS). So check it out!



For more details, check out our official GitHub release. This includes links to all the related tickets as well as the source code.



We have also adopted GitHub releases as our avenue for tracking changes in a given release. All current and prior releases of Spring WS are now captured in the list of releases on GitHub. Feel free to check them out.



The artifacts are hosted on Maven Central so grab 'em while they’re hot!



Project Page | Source Code | Issues]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Open the 30th AWS Region – Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) Region in India]]></title>
        <id>f54162ba169bc134340904b86d7e7433113a6964</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-the-30th-aws-region-asia-pacific-hyderabad-region-in-india/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T02:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2020, Jeff announced the upcoming AWS Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) as the second Region in India. Yes! Today we are announcing the general availability of the 30th AWS Region, Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) Region, with three Availability Zones and the ap-south-2 API name. The Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) Region is located in the state of Telangana. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wait… Elastic Observability monitors metrics for AWS services in just minutes?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-service-metrics-monitor-observability-easy</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-service-metrics-monitor-observability-easy"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get metrics and logs from your AWS deployment and Elastic Observability in just minutes! We’ll show you how to use Elastic integrations to quickly monitor and manage the performance of your applications and AWS services to streamline troubleshooting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.5.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.5.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.5.2 over the previous versions in 8.5.x.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
8.5.2 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Version 8.5.2 fixes a Fleet server issue on Windows.
It also contains an APM server fix for an issue where the server might be running out of memory when Tail based sampling is enabled. With the fix, buffered transactions are discarded if a certain buffer size is reached.
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Godard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to ESQL — A new query language for flexible, iterative analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introduction-to-esql-new-query-language-flexible-iterative-analytics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introduction-to-esql-new-query-language-flexible-iterative-analytics"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline and enrich investigations using Elasticsearch Query Language (ESQL), a new, robust piped query language. Currently in development, ESQL combined with new ES compute capabilities and multi-query UX in Kibana will unlock more insights for analysts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Payne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wait… Elastic Observability monitors metrics for AWS services in just minutes?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-service-metrics-monitor-observability-easy</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-service-metrics-monitor-observability-easy"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The transition to distributed applications is in full swing, driven mainly by our need to be “always-on” as consumers and fast-paced businesses. That need is driving deployments to have more complex requirements along with the ability to be globally diverse and rapidly innovate.



Cloud is becoming the de facto deployment option for today’s applications. Many cloud deployments choose to host their applications on AWS for the globally diverse set of regions it covers and the myriad of services (for faster development and innovation) available, as well as to drive operational and capital costs down. On AWS, development teams are finding additional value in migrating to Kubernetes on Amazon EKS, testing out the latest serverless options, and improving traditional, tiered applications with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.5.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Godard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to ESQL — A new query language for flexible, iterative analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/introduction-to-esql-new-query-language-flexible-iterative-analytics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/introduction-to-esql-new-query-language-flexible-iterative-analytics"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The Elastic Platform has long been well-regarded as an analytical system for search use cases and machine-generated data. Analytics are focused on processing data-as-ingested, where significant thought is put into how to optimally structure data as it is indexed in Elasticsearch. Kibana exposes Elasticsearch aggregations and uses them to create interactive dashboards, visualizations, and alerts.

But as the Elastic Platform is more widely adopted as a search, security, observability, and general analytics platform, analyst users require the ability to take data-as-ingested, transform it to fit their investigative needs post-ingestion, and derive insights from underlying Elasticsearch index data. They need a concise, integrated, and efficient workflow enabled by rich and expressive querie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Payne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – November 21, 2022]]></title>
        <id>2d631199585324d47a4480b138a96f2d7321055c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-november-21-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T19:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! A new week starts, and the News Blog team is getting ready for AWS re:Invent! Many of us will be there next week and it would be great to meet […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Service Mesh Support for AWS Lambda Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul support for AWS Lambda is now generally available, enabling services in the mesh to invoke Lambda serverless functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.8 and 6.0 are now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/21/spring-security-5-8-and-6-0-are-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/21/spring-security-5-8-and-6-0-are-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T18:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, we are very excited to announce the general availability of Spring Security 6.0! In addition, we are pleased to announce the general availability of Spring Security 5.8, which is provided to simplify upgrading to 6.0.



The 5.8 release brings numerous enhancements, such as session handling improvements, expanded support for the AuthorizationManager API, and additional defense in-depth with support for CSRF BREACH. Check out What’s New in Spring Security 5.8 for a list of new features available in the release.



The 6.0 release adds integration with Spring Observability and works with support for AOT processing provided by Spring Framework 6. Check out What’s New in Spring Security 6.0 for a list of new features available in the release.



Spring Security 6.0 is based on Spring Framework 6.0 and will require a minimum of JDK 17 at runtime. In order to prepare your application for this major release, you are recommended to follow the steps outlined in the migration guide for the 5.8 release and the subsequent steps in the migration guide for the 6.0 release.



As always, we look forward to hearing your feedback!



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Major Releases of Spring for Apache Kafka and Spring for RabbitMQ]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/21/new-major-releases-of-spring-for-apache-kafka-and-spring-for-rabbitmq</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/21/new-major-releases-of-spring-for-apache-kafka-and-spring-for-rabbitmq"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T18:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that new major releases (3.0.0) for Spring for Apache Kafka and Spring for RabbitMQ are now available.



Common Changes



The 3.0.x versions of these projects have the following common changes





they depend on Java version 17 or later



they depend on Spring Framework 6.0.x



support for creating native GraalVM applications



support for micrometer observability and tracing



Bill of Materials POMs are now provided to help with dependency management







Spring for Apache Kafka





support for a global single EmbeddedKafkaBroker (across multiple test classes)



several enhancements for @RetryableTopic (non-blocking retries)



KafkaTemplate methods now return CompleteableFuture instead of ListenableFuture, which has been deprecated





For information about all changes in this release, see What’s New.



In addition, 2.9.3 and 2.8.11 maintenance releases are now available.



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow





Spring for RabbitMQ





support for RabbitMQ super streams, with single active consumers, has been added



the previously deprecated remoting support has been removed



the AsyncRabbitTemplate and RabbitStreamTemplate methods now return CompleteableFuture instead of ListenableFuture, which has been deprecated





For information about all changes in this release, see  What’s New.



In addition, the 2.4.8 maintenance release is now available.



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 for .NET developers]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=68193</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/camunda-platform-8-dotnet-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T17:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, learn how you can take advantage of Camunda for powerful process orchestration as a .NET developer.
The post Camunda Platform 8 for .NET developers appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 new Ansible automation hub updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/3-new-ansible-automation-hub-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/3-new-ansible-automation-hub-updates"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond the buzz at AnsibleFest 2022 around event-driven automation, availability of Ansible in  AWS and Azure marketplaces, and Project Wisdom, some important changes were happening within Ansible automation hub, so let's take a closer look at the latest developments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>trmcconn@redhat.com (Tricia McConnell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring REST Docs 3.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/21/spring-rest-docs-3-0-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/21/spring-rest-docs-3-0-0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T12:25:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce that Spring REST Docs 3.0.0 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This new major version of Spring REST Docs builds on Spring Framework 6.0 and requires Java 17. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

To learn more about Spring REST Docs 3.0, please refer to the release notes.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring REST Docs 2.0.7.RELEASE]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/21/spring-rest-docs-2-0-7-release</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/21/spring-rest-docs-2-0-7-release"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T11:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring REST Docs 2.0.7.RELEASE has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 4 bug fixes and documentation improvements. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contracts and power]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44254</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/720014524/0/sethsblog~Contracts-and-power/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A written contract benefits the party with the least power. Power might be in the form of money, access to plenty of lawyers or simply a willingness to burn it all down to the ground. In the moment before a contract is signed, the lower-powered party momentarily has more power. That’s because the other entity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build scoped search suggestions and search query corrections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-scoped-search-suggestions-and-search-query-corrections</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-scoped-search-suggestions-and-search-query-corrections"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Set up your ecommerce search experiences with scoped suggestions — narrowing results to specific categories or brands — and query corrections, also known as “Did you mean?” to help customers find products faster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lionel Palacin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making deployment health on Elastic Cloud better, one error at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/making-deployment-health-on-elastic-cloud-better-one-error-at-a-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/making-deployment-health-on-elastic-cloud-better-one-error-at-a-time"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improved deployment health experience on Elastic Cloud, including impact areas and troubleshooting steps for errors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubha Anjur Tupil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing intuitive Kibana dashboards as a non-designer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/designing-intuitive-kibana-dashboards-as-a-non-designer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/designing-intuitive-kibana-dashboards-as-a-non-designer"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re not a frontend developer or designer, building dashboards that all can understand and consume can be scary. Check out our tips on structuring Kibana dashboards and picking suitable charts to connect people with your data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond,Marco Vettorello,Giovanni Magni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build scoped search suggestions and search query corrections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-scoped-search-suggestions-and-search-query-corrections</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-scoped-search-suggestions-and-search-query-corrections"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
You get one shot to keep shoppers on your ecommerce website with relevant search results. According to Harris Poll, 76% of online shoppers abandon a retail website after an unsuccessful search.


Therefore, it’s critical to optimize your search experience so buyers can find what they need fast. That’s the theory behind a modern search experience: Nowadays it’s not enough to simply provide a search bar that returns matching products. Your ecommerce site must include a complete set of search tools that personally guide users to the products they want.

In this blog, you’ll learn how to start improving ecommerce search by adding two common features: scoped suggestions and query corrections, also known as “Did you mean?”

Note the following examples have been tested using Elastic 8.5. 
Scope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lionel Palacin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making deployment health on Elastic Cloud better, one error at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/making-deployment-health-on-elastic-cloud-better-one-error-at-a-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/making-deployment-health-on-elastic-cloud-better-one-error-at-a-time"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Maintaining a healthy deployment is critical for a successful Elastic Cloud experience. We want to make it easy for Elastic Cloud users to run healthy deployments, and with our new health reporting capability, this is exactly what we enable. 

If you have been using Elastic Cloud for a while, you are probably used to seeing an error banner when your deployment is unhealthy; this includes issues with Elasticsearch, Kibana, Integration server, or Enterprise Search instances.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blteb26f0b677828fd8/6377b409caf46f1070a5ceaa/blog-elastic-deploymenthealth-1.png,blog-elastic-deploymenthealth-1.png,
While the banner tells you something is wrong, it has limited information about the impact you might see and what you should do to resolve the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubha Anjur Tupil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing intuitive Kibana dashboards as a non-designer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/designing-intuitive-kibana-dashboards-as-a-non-designer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/designing-intuitive-kibana-dashboards-as-a-non-designer"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Developers, SRE engineers, and talented technologists often need to build quick dashboards to showcase important information on the state of their applications that can be consumed by mixed audiences. If you’re not a frontend developer or designer, it can feel scary building intuitive dashboards that all can understand and consume without being overloaded with information. Especially if you don’t feel you possess the artistic design flair of your colleagues, it can feel like you’re missing that key set of rules that they implicitly hold in their heads.

As a frontend engineer, I’ve been fortunate to work with designers and users alike and learn tips on how to build intuitive experiences without bamboozling users into information overload and to access the important information they need …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond,Marco Vettorello,Giovanni Magni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change in Slope]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2701/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2701/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/change_in_slope.png" title="Squinting at a graph is fine for getting a rough idea of the answer, but if you want to pretend to know it exactly, you need statistics." alt="Squinting at a graph is fine for getting a rough idea of the answer, but if you want to pretend to know it exactly, you need statistics." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No competition]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43258</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/719948408/0/sethsblog~No-competition/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no competition for cookbooks on making food out of soccer balls and hockey pucks. There’s no competition for software that charges you to find out the temperature on Mars. There’s no competition for a service that counts how many pairs of shoes you own. In fact, in every market that’s worth entering, there’s competition. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Micropayments for content]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44246</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/719872494/0/sethsblog~Micropayments-for-content/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T09:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a problem that comes up every year or two, but no one has implemented a useful solution yet. Advertising is a surprisingly bad way for a culture to pay for content, because the kind of content that gets rewarded is often dumbed down for a large audience or is optimized for a small […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation Summaries in Google Chat]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/conversation-summaries-in-google-chat.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/conversation-summaries-in-google-chat.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T20:23:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mohammad Saleh, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team, and Yinan Wang, Software Engineer, Google Workspace   
Information overload is a significant challenge for many organizations and individuals today. It can be overwhelming to keep up with incoming chat messages and documents that arrive at our inbox everyday. This has been exacerbated by the increase in virtual work and remains a challenge as many teams transition to a hybrid work environment with a mix of those working both virtually and in an office. One solution that can address information overload is summarization — for example, to help users improve their productivity and better manage so much information, we recently introduced auto-generated summaries in Google Docs.  

Today, we are excited to introduce conv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.14 GA: Announcing Simplified Service Mesh Deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-14-ga-announcing-simplified-service-mesh-deployments</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-14-ga-announcing-simplified-service-mesh-deployments"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul 1.14 introduces the Consul dataplane, service mesh traffic management across cluster peers, and service failover enhancements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some thoughts on Mastodon]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44249</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/719815244/0/sethsblog~Some-thoughts-on-Mastodon/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is, by far, the fastest-growing social network in history, growing more than 20% in about a week. And yet it didn’t stutter much. How can this be? It’s a network in the real internet sense of the word. It’s not just a network of users, it’s a network of servers as well. No one […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2022.0 goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/18/spring-data-2022-0-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/18/spring-data-2022-0-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T14:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the Spring Data engineering team and everyone who contributed to this release, I am pleased to announce the general availability of Spring Data 2022.0 (Codename: Turing) from Maven Central! It is the third major revision since Spring Data’s inception in 2009 to serve you as your framework for modern-day data applications.

Spring Data 2022.0 builds on top of the just-released Spring Framework 6.0 with a Java 17+ baseline. Modules leveraging Jakarta EE technologies, such as Spring Data JPA and Spring Data REST, have been upgraded to Jakarta EE 9+, moving to the jakarta namespace, with a focus on the recently released Jakarta EE 10 APIs, such as Servlet 6.0 and JPA 3.1.

This release lays an initial foundation for Ahead-of-Time compilation arrangements to improve your experien…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.2.6 and 2021.1.10 available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/18/spring-data-2021-2-6-and-2021-1-10-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/18/spring-data-2021-2-6-and-2021-1-10-available"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T14:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of Spring Data 2021.2.6 and 2021.1.10 releases. The service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades. 

For your convenience, the next Spring Boot releases are going to pick up 2021.2.6 and 2021.1.10 in the upcoming days. To round things off, here are the links to the individual modules, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.2.6


  
Spring Data Commons 2.7.6 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.4.6 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.7.6 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data Neo4j 6.3.6 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data MongoDB 3.4.6 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation -…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry/thanks]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42325</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/719788140/0/sethsblog~Sorrythanks/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T08:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you often find yourself saying “sorry” in a way that doesn’t advance the conversation, it might be interesting to substitute “thank you” instead. So, “I’m sorry this came out of the kitchen after your other dishes,” becomes, “thank you for waiting so patiently.” And, “I’m sorry we got disconnected,” becomes, “thank you for calling […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the scenes: The making of a Global Threat Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/behind-the-scenes-global-threat-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/behind-the-scenes-global-threat-report"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What was our approach and process for creating a global threat report?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Dufresne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba Cloud Granting Significant Contribution Partner Award to Elastic at Apsara 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/alibaba-cloud-significant-contribution-partner-award-apsara-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/alibaba-cloud-significant-contribution-partner-award-apsara-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2022 Alibaba Cloud Apsara Summit, Elastic won the Alibaba Cloud Product Ecosystem Partner Significant Contribution Award.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Ge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the scenes: The making of a Global Threat Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/behind-the-scenes-global-threat-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/behind-the-scenes-global-threat-report"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The first Elastic Global Threat Report was published earlier this week. In it, you will learn about trends observed by our threat researchers, our predictions for what’s coming next, and some of our recommendations to operate securely in the face of today’s and tomorrow’s threats. If you haven’t read it yet, go check it out.



As a technical leader in Elastic Security, I'd like to reveal a small amount about what goes into reports like this one and why it’s significant.
Why did we do it? 
If you didn’t already know this, you know it now: Elastic is a security company. We are also different — we’re open and transparent. We share exactly how our detections and preventions work in the protections-artifacts and detection-rules repos. We’ve launched Elastic Security Labs and regularly publis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Dufresne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba Cloud Granting Significant Contribution Partner Award to Elastic at Apsara 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/alibaba-cloud-significant-contribution-partner-award-apsara-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/alibaba-cloud-significant-contribution-partner-award-apsara-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
On November 5, 2022, at the 2022 Alibaba Cloud Apsara Summit, Elastic won the Alibaba Cloud Product Ecosystem Partner Significant Contribution Award. This award commends and thanks the Partner of Alibaba Cloud for maintaining rapid growth despite the double test of the pandemic and the economy, to promote high-quality development themes of Alibaba cloud. Elastic is the only international partner that has won this honor.

2022 is the new beginning of the second five-year strategic cooperation between Elastic and Alibaba Cloud. The two companies will continue to deepen cooperation in products, services, communities, and ecology to achieve a new leap in high quality.
,At this conference, the two parties jointly launched the latest Alibaba Cloud Elasticsearch serverless version, providing end-to-end data access, data management, data application, and visualization module component capabilities around the Elastic Stack ecological components, as well as scenario-based upper-layer application capabilities. The launch of this version can avoid the complexity of large-scale cluster operation and maintenance, and the cloud native service can achieve second-level elastic scaling without planning and managing cluster resource configuration. By optimizing the cost of computing and storage resources, it can reduce the user's usage cost by 70% on average. This version can efficiently manage and analyze massive data, by decoupling of storage and computing, effectively improve read and write efficiency, and greatly reduce database operation and maintenance management costs.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt84a8ebe85ebdcf28/63764e6371c75510a0c9fcca/blog-elastic-alibaba-apsara.png,blog-elastic-alibaba-apsara.png,
The strategic cooperation between Elastic and Alibaba Cloud began in 2017. Currently, the Alibaba Elasticsearch service is available in Alibaba Cloud's service areas in 17 countries and regions, serving thousands of thousands of customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Ge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Account Problems]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2700/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2700/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/account_problems.png" title="My password is just every Unicode codepoint concatenated into a single UTF-8 string." alt="My password is just every Unicode codepoint concatenated into a single UTF-8 string." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Removals, Deprecations, and Major Changes in 1.26]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/11/18/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-1-26/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/11/18/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-1-26/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS)
Change is an integral part of the Kubernetes life-cycle: as Kubernetes grows and matures, features may be deprecated, removed, or replaced with improvements for the health of the project. For Kubernetes v1.26 there are several planned: this article identifies and describes some of them, based on the information available at this mid-cycle point in the v1.26 release process, which is still ongoing and can introduce additional changes.
The Kubernetes API Removal and Deprecation process
The Kubernetes project has a well-documented deprecation policy for features. This policy states that stable APIs may only be deprecated when a newer, stable version of that same API is available and that APIs have a minimum lifetime for each stability level. A deprecated API is o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For your eyes only: improving Netflix video quality with neural networks]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5b8d032da09c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/for-your-eyes-only-improving-netflix-video-quality-with-neural-networks-5b8d032da09c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T21:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Christos G. Bampis, Li-Heng Chen and Zhi Li]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS AppSync GraphQL APIs Supports JavaScript Resolvers]]></title>
        <id>d8e241bd655bf02ea49a61c382181ae10e6846d8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-appsync-graphql-apis-supports-javascript-resolvers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T20:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, AWS AppSync supports JavaScript resolvers and provides a resolver evaluation engine to test them before publishing them to the cloud. AWS AppSync, launched in 2017, is a service that allows you to build, manage, and host GraphQL APIs in the cloud. AWS AppSync connects your GraphQL schema to different data sources using resolvers. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Octoverse 2022: 10 years of tracking open source]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-11-17-octoverse-2022-10-years-of-tracking-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-11-17-octoverse-2022-10-years-of-tracking-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T19:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How is open source changing the world and impacting businesses? In this year's Octoverse report, we identified three big trends to watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Data Cards Playbook: A Toolkit for Transparency in Dataset Documentation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/the-data-cards-playbook-toolkit-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/the-data-cards-playbook-toolkit-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T18:14:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mahima Pushkarna, Senior Interaction Designer, and Andrew Zaldivar, Senior Developer Relations Engineer, Google Research  
As machine learning (ML) research moves toward large-scale models capable of numerous downstream tasks, a shared understanding of a dataset’s origin, development, intent, and evolution becomes increasingly important for the responsible and informed development of ML models. However, knowledge about datasets, including use and implementations, is often distributed across teams, individuals, and even time. Earlier this year at the ACM Conference on Fairness, Accountability, and Transparency (ACM FAccT), we published Data Cards, a dataset documentation framework aimed at increasing transparency across dataset lifecycles. Data Cards are transparency artifacts tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run Tasks Are Now Available in the Terraform Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/run-tasks-are-now-available-in-the-terraform-registry</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/run-tasks-are-now-available-in-the-terraform-registry"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Run tasks can now be accessed from the HashiCorp Terraform Registry, helping developers discover run tasks they can integrate with their existing Terraform workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Match Cutting at Netflix: Finding Cuts with Smooth Visual Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/31c3fc14ae59</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/match-cutting-at-netflix-finding-cuts-with-smooth-visual-transitions-31c3fc14ae59?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T16:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s needed in the art of match cutting is tools to help editors find shots that match well together, which is what we’ve started…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase process productivity with Google Drive, Slack, and SendGrid]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=68045</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/increase-process-productivity-google-drive-slack-sendgrid/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T15:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Camunda Connectors can boost your process orchestration productivity by connecting to popular productivity and communication tools.
The post Increase process productivity with Google Drive, Slack, and SendGrid appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neither here nor there]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44186</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/719706202/0/sethsblog~Neither-here-nor-there/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T08:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s tempting to imagine that mixing half a glass of milk and half a glass of orange juice might get you a hybrid that’s better than either. Alas, not so much. The goal is to find something that is in and of itself. That becomes the very best version of what you’re trying to do, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Mil-asticians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-mil-asticians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-mil-asticians"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the Mil-asticians, an ERG for those that have a connection with the military community, no matter what the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I’m excited about the 2022 Elastic Global Threat Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-im-excited-about-the-2022-elastic-global-threat-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-im-excited-about-the-2022-elastic-global-threat-report"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does the 2022 Elastic Global Threat Report mean for openness and developers?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Meehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet Mil-asticians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-mil-asticians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-mil-asticians"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
At Elastic, we formalized our employee resource groups in 2021, but they’ve been part of our culture since 2016. These groups are aligned with shared identities, experiences, interests, affinities, and allyships.

As formal groups they are ensured structure, budget, and a voice based on any dimension of diversity, identity, allyship, and advocacy. While we’re always working towards change, this is an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy.

Each ERG has its own mission and goals, but as a whole these groups want to create community and belonging around shared interests and experiences. 
Our Core ERGs
We have seven formal ERGs: The Accessibles, Blasticians, ElastAsians, Elasticians Unidos, Rainbow Stack, Mil-asticians, and Women of Elastic. We’ll be spotlig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I’m excited about the 2022 Elastic Global Threat Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-im-excited-about-the-2022-elastic-global-threat-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-im-excited-about-the-2022-elastic-global-threat-report"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
I remember where I was sitting when I read Mandiant’s first M-Trends report on the advanced persistent threat in 2010. I was a technical director at the National Security Agency in the office of Tailored Access Operations (TAO). At that time, my job was to build computer network exploitation (CNE) tools to collect foreign intelligence.


So a public threat report shining a light on advanced and persistent threats like this was a big deal. It was the first of its kind. And everything after the report changed. The cybersecurity industry was growing in its sophistication in counter-intelligence operations to identify and stop attacks. It was an important and symbolic moment. And it meant it would only get harder to conduct cyber operations under an increasingly focused microscope.


Fast fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Meehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 213 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66077</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-213-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T20:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing exciting to report for sprint 213. We spent most of our time fixing issues and continue to make good progress. You will also see the new usability feature added below.
Issue
Templates with Assigned to @me
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 213 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mixture-of-Experts with Expert Choice Routing]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/mixture-of-experts-with-expert-choice.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/mixture-of-experts-with-expert-choice.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T19:32:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yanqi Zhou, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team  
The capacity of a neural network to absorb information is limited by the number of its parameters, and as a consequence, finding more effective ways to increase model parameters has become a trend in deep learning research. Mixture-of-experts (MoE), a type of conditional computation where parts of the network are activated on a per-example basis, has been proposed as a way of dramatically increasing model capacity without a proportional increase in computation. In sparsely-activated variants of MoE models (e.g., Switch Transformer, GLaM, V-MoE), a subset of experts is selected on a per-token or per-example basis, thus creating sparsity in the network. Such models have demonstrated better scaling in multiple domains and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.14 Makes it Easier to Use Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-14-makes-it-easier-to-use-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-14-makes-it-easier-to-use-providers"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform (CDKTF) 0.14 makes it easier to add and upgrade Terraform providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第219話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190246967858110</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190246967858110"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Open–AWS Region in Spain]]></title>
        <id>5c264de4161fdcb63702fb300a75e6c6da7e1566</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-aws-region-in-spain/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T07:19:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Region in Aragón, Spain, is now open. The official name is Europe (Spain), and the API name is eu-south-2. You can start using it today to deploy workloads and store your data in Spain. The AWS Europe (Spain) Region has three Availability Zones (AZ) that you can use to reliably spread your applications […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing our final AWS Heroes of the year – November 2022]]></title>
        <id>b50ce668325333d2e438dd2c02b12bceedc6bcbd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-our-final-aws-heroes-of-the-year-november-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T22:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Heroes program celebrates and recognizes builders who are making an impact within the global AWS community. As we come to the end of 2022, the program is recognizing seven individuals who are passionate about AWS, and focused on organizing and speaking at community events, mentoring, authoring content, and even preserving wildlife. Please meet […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Lacy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The power of GitHub in the palm of your hand]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-11-15-the-power-of-github-in-the-palm-of-your-hand/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-11-15-the-power-of-github-in-the-palm-of-your-hand/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T20:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Mobile helps keep work going while you're going. Untether yourself from your office.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A better way to search, navigate, and understand code on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-11-15-a-better-way-to-search-navigate-and-understand-code-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-11-15-a-better-way-to-search-navigate-and-understand-code-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T19:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reading code is a hugely important task for developers. That’s why we built GitHub’s new code search—to help developers search, navigate, and understand code written by them, their team, and the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The journey of your work has never been clearer]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-11-15-the-journey-of-your-work-has-never-been-clearer/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-11-15-the-journey-of-your-work-has-never-been-clearer/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T18:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July, we launched the general availability of GitHub Projects, and now we are excited to bring you even more features designed to make it easier to plan and track in the same place you build!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helping VFX studios pave a path to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d308ee43c079</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/helping-vfx-studios-pave-a-path-to-the-cloud-d308ee43c079?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T17:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By: Peter Cioni (Netflix), Alex Schworer (Netflix), Mac Moore (Conductor Tech.), Rachel Kelley (AWS), Ranjit Raju (AWS)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at AWS re:Invent: Examining the State of Your Cloud Operating Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-examining-the-state-of-your-cloud-operating-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-examining-the-state-of-your-cloud-operating-model"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your adoption of a cloud operating model. Visit us at AWS re:Invent in Las Vegas, Nov. 28 - Dec. 2 for breakout sessions, expert talks, and product demos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Receives SOC 2 Type 1 Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=67879</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/camunda-soc-2-type-1-certification/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda has received a clean SOC 2 Type 1 attestation report. This is a rigorous, independent assessment of our internal security controls.
The post Camunda Receives SOC 2 Type 1 Certification appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Grund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps client libraries migrated to MSAL]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66066</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-client-libraries-migrated-to-msal/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T12:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft.VisualStudio.Services.InteractiveClient library is a public NuGet package that takes care of authenticating to Azure DevOps Services. It abstracts away the acquisition, management and refreshing of authentication tokens, so developers can focus on their goals and stay productive.
The post Azure DevOps client libraries migrated to MSAL appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Sokolovsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add dev clusters in Camunda Platform 8 SaaS and test models faster]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=67763</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/dev-clusters-camunda-platform-8-saas/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T21:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now take advantage of development clusters on our professional plan to test your models quickly outside of production.
The post Add dev clusters in Camunda Platform 8 SaaS and test models faster appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – November 14, 2022]]></title>
        <id>8b1a5d71f0e93b11bc3e984702e573e8e37d7059</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-november-14-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T17:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s now just two weeks to AWS re:Invent in Las Vegas, and the pace is picking up, both here on the News Blog, and throughout AWS as everyone get ready for the big event! I hope you get the chance to join us, and have shared links and other information at the bottom of this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assessing Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/assessing-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/assessing-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What your security scanner isn’t telling you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Series: Creating Media with Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5067ac110bcd</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/new-series-creating-media-with-machine-learning-5067ac110bcd?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T17:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog series will be showing you how we use the power of machine learning to create stunning media at a global scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning for Fraud Detection in Streaming Services]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b0b4ef3be3f6</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/machine-learning-for-fraud-detection-in-streaming-services-b0b4ef3be3f6?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T17:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Soheil Esmaeilzadeh, Negin Salajegheh, Amir Ziai, Jeff Boote]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Military Service Impacted Two HashiCorp Veterans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-military-service-impacted-two-hashicorp-veterans</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-military-service-impacted-two-hashicorp-veterans"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lisa Argueta and Joshua Blair from the Veterans ERG share how their time in the military shaped their workforce experience and how they find community at HashiCorp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to our Newest Camunda Champions!]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=67505</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/welcome-newest-camunda-champions/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T19:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Champions make interacting in our community a more valuable and meaningful experience for everyone. Welcome to our latest Camunda Champions!
The post Welcome to our Newest Camunda Champions! appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Buchholz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Characterizing Emergent Phenomena in Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/characterizing-emergent-phenomena-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/characterizing-emergent-phenomena-in.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:05:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jason Wei and Yi Tay, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team   
The field of natural language processing (NLP) has been revolutionized by language models trained on large amounts of text data. Scaling up the size of language models often leads to improved performance and sample efficiency on a range of downstream NLP tasks. In many cases, the performance of a large language model can be predicted by extrapolating the performance trend of smaller models. For instance, the effect of scale on language model perplexity has been empirically shown to span more than seven orders of magnitude. 

On the other hand, performance for certain other tasks does not improve in a predictable fashion. For example, the GPT-3 paper showed that the ability of language models to perform mult…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing GitHub Actions Importer]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-11-10-introducing-github-actions-importer/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-11-10-introducing-github-actions-importer/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T17:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions Importer helps you forecast, plan, and facilitate migrations from your current CI/CD tool to GitHub Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new with Codespaces from GitHub Universe 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-11-10-whats-new-with-codespaces-from-github-universe-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-11-10-whats-new-with-codespaces-from-github-universe-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re giving GitHub users 60 free hours each month on Codespaces. Learn what else we shipped for Codespaces at Universe this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seeing through hardware counters: a journey to threefold performance increase]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2721924a2822</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/seeing-through-hardware-counters-a-journey-to-threefold-performance-increase-2721924a2822?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T23:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Vadim Filanovsky and Harshad Sane]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-layered Mapping of Brain Tissue via Segmentation Guided Contrastive Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/multi-layered-mapping-of-brain-tissue.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/multi-layered-mapping-of-brain-tissue.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T22:16:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Peter H. Li, Research Scientist, and Sven Dorkenwald, Student Researcher, Connectomics at Google  
Mapping the wiring and firing activity of the human brain is fundamental to deciphering how we think — how we sense the world, learn, decide, remember, and create — as well as what issues can arise in brain disease or dysfunction. Recent efforts have delivered publicly available brain maps (high-resolution 3D mapping of brain cells and their connectivities) at unprecedented quality and scale, such as H01, a 1.4 petabyte nanometer-scale digital reconstruction of a sample of human brain tissue from Harvard / Google, and the cubic millimeter mouse cortex dataset from our colleagues at the MICrONS consortium. 
 
To interpret brain maps at this scale requires multiple layers of analysis,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Azure DevOps REST APIs now support PAT scopes]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66050</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/all-azure-devops-rest-apis-now-support-pat-scopes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T22:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, the Azure DevOps team completed an initiative to associate all Azure DevOps REST APIs with a granular personal access token (PAT) scope. As part of our ongoing investments in security, we undertook this effort to reduce the risks associated with a leaked PAT credential.
The post All Azure DevOps REST APIs now support PAT scopes appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Wolfson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Todas as novidades do GitHub Universe 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-11-09-todas-as-novidades-do-github-universe-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-11-09-todas-as-novidades-do-github-universe-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T17:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read this post in English Veja o que estamos construindo para aprimorar a plataforma de desenvolvimento mais integrada e que permite que pessoas desenvolvedoras e empresas impulsionem a inovação com mais facilidade. Quinze anos atrás, estava sendo escrita a primeira linha de código para a construção do GitHub. Desde então, o objetivo tem sido equipar [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An open source economy–built by developers, for developers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-11-09-an-open-source-economy-built-by-developers-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-11-09-an-open-source-economy-built-by-developers-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T17:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investing in our open source future by supporting the maintainers of today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything new from GitHub Universe 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-11-09-everything-new-from-github-universe-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-11-09-everything-new-from-github-universe-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T17:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See what we're building to enhance the most integrated developer platform that allows developers and enterprises to drive innovation with ease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New AWS Region Opens in Switzerland]]></title>
        <id>2c6058cf25479e8c490c3088404f8049e234952c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/a-new-aws-region-opens-in-switzerland/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T06:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce today the opening of our 28th AWS Region: Europe (Zurich), also known by its API name: eu-central-2. An AWS Region allows you to deploy your most demanding workloads and replicate your applications and data across distinct groups of data centers called Availability Zones. This new Region has three fully redundant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AWS Resource Explorer – Quickly Find Resources in Your AWS Account]]></title>
        <id>86fb8f6024593cbc90bc1a092dac9ab5ff3b502b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-aws-resource-explorer-quickly-find-resources-in-your-aws-account/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T21:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for a specific Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instance, Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) task, or Amazon CloudWatch log group can take some time, especially if you have many resources and use multiple AWS Regions. Today, we’re making that easier. Using the new AWS Resource Explorer, you can search through the AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReAct: Synergizing Reasoning and Acting in Language Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/react-synergizing-reasoning-and-acting.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/react-synergizing-reasoning-and-acting.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:50:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shunyu Yao, Student Researcher, and Yuan Cao, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team  -->   
Recent advances have expanded the applicability of language models (LM) to downstream tasks. On one hand, existing language models that are properly prompted, via chain-of-thought, demonstrate emergent capabilities that carry out self-conditioned reasoning traces to derive answers from questions, excelling at various arithmetic, commonsense, and symbolic reasoning tasks. However, with chain-of-thought prompting, a model is not grounded in the external world and uses its own internal representations to generate reasoning traces, limiting its ability to reactively explore and reason or update its knowledge. On the other hand, recent work uses pre-trained language models for plannin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.10.0 alpha1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=67112</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/camunda-optimize-3-10-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T16:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest release of Camunda Optimize, we now have smart bar charts, the ability to delete backups via API and more.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.10.0 alpha1 released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Conz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.19.0-alpha1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=66761</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/camunda-automation-platform-7-19-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T16:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.19 features improved engine loading times, support for basic authentication in OpenAPI specification and multiple bug fixes.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.19.0-alpha1 released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kelemen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinite Nature: Generating 3D Flythroughs from Still Photos]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/infinite-nature-generating-3d.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/infinite-nature-generating-3d.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T20:42:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Noah Snavely and Zhengqi Li, Research Scientists, Google Research  
We live in a world of great natural beauty — of majestic mountains, dramatic seascapes, and serene forests. Imagine seeing this beauty as a bird does, flying past richly detailed, three-dimensional landscapes. Can computers learn to synthesize this kind of visual experience? Such a capability would allow for new kinds of content for games and virtual reality experiences: for instance, relaxing within an immersive flythrough of an infinite nature scene. But existing methods that synthesize new views from images tend to allow for only limited camera motion. 
  
In a research effort we call Infinite Nature, we show that computers can learn to generate such rich 3D experiences simply by viewing nature videos and phot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – November 7, 2022]]></title>
        <id>de41f41d29dc6ff00d77b5ed8dc1950ad2920137</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-november-7-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T19:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With three weeks to go until AWS re:Invent opens in Las Vegas, the AWS News Blog Team is hard at work creating blog posts to share the latest launches and previews with you. As usual, we have a strong mix of new services, new features, and a surprise or two. Last Week’s Launches Here are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating Mixed Identities with the Hashi:Blend ERG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/celebrating-mixed-identities-with-the-hashi-blend-erg</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/celebrating-mixed-identities-with-the-hashi-blend-erg"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does it mean to belong? Seven Hashi:Blend Employee Resource Group members talk about the impact multiracialism and multiculturalism have on their identity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find and delete ServiceNow records en masse with the updated Ansible Content Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/find-and-delete-servicenow-records-en-masse-with-the-updated-ansible-content-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/find-and-delete-servicenow-records-en-masse-with-the-updated-ansible-content-collection"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever had to query and remove a long list of ServiceNow records? Yeah, neither have I until recently. Nobody broke into my instance, and this isn't a one-time operation, I just happen to maintain an instance that we use to test our Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for ServiceNow ITSM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a Camunda Platform 8 Connector]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=66548</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/how-to-build-camunda-platform-8-connector/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T17:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build a Camunda Platform 8 Connector. Quickly start building your own custom Connectors using Camunda today.
The post How to build a Camunda Platform 8 Connector appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Live and let live with Kluctl and Server Side Apply]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/11/04/live-and-let-live-with-kluctl-and-ssa/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/11/04/live-and-let-live-with-kluctl-and-ssa/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alexander Block
This blog post was inspired by a previous Kubernetes blog post about
Advanced Server Side Apply.
The author of said blog post listed multiple benefits for applications and
controllers when switching to server-side apply (from now on abbreviated with
SSA). Especially the chapter about
CI/CD systems
motivated me to respond and write down my thoughts and experiences.
These thoughts and experiences are the results of me working on Kluctl
for the past 2 years. I describe Kluctl as "The missing glue to put together
large Kubernetes deployments, composed of multiple smaller parts
(Helm/Kustomize/...) in a manageable and unified way."
To get a basic understanding of Kluctl, I suggest to visit the kluctl.io
website and read through the documentation and tutorials, for exampl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join user experience research and share your feedback with us!]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=66902</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/join-user-experience-research-and-share-your-feedback-with-us/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T20:53:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We invite you to join our research and share your feedback with us. We'll take care of scheduling a call with you and facilitating it. Thank you!
The post Join user experience research and share your feedback with us! appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgeniya Gubenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consistent caching mechanism in Titus Gateway]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6cb89b9ce296</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/consistent-caching-mechanism-in-titus-gateway-6cb89b9ce296?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T19:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Tomasz Bak and Fabio Kung]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Tabula Rasa: Reincarnating Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/beyond-tabula-rasa-reincarnating.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/beyond-tabula-rasa-reincarnating.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T16:56:00.009Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rishabh Agarwal, Senior Research Scientist, and Max Schwarzer, Student Researcher, Google Research, Brain Team  
Reinforcement learning (RL) is an area of machine learning that focuses on training intelligent agents using related experiences so they can learn to solve decision making tasks, such as playing video games, flying stratospheric balloons, and designing hardware chips. Due to the generality of RL, the prevalent trend in RL research is to develop agents that can efficiently learn tabula rasa, that is, from scratch without using previously learned knowledge about the problem. However, in practice, tabula rasa RL systems are typically the exception rather than the norm for solving large-scale RL problems. Large-scale RL systems, such as OpenAI Five, which achieves human-le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Ansible API for ServiceNow ITSM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-the-ansible-api-for-servicenow-itsm</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-the-ansible-api-for-servicenow-itsm"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most popular platform integrations available to Ansible Automation Platform subscribers in Ansible automation hub is the Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for ServiceNow ITSM. This collection helps you create new automation workflows faster based on ServiceNow ITSM while establishing a single source of truth in the ServiceNow configuration management database (CMDB). You can help free teams from hours of manual effort and have greater data integrity within your ServiceNow ITSM instance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>trmcconn@redhat.com (Tricia McConnell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第218話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190246930259876</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190246930259876"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robots That Write Their Own Code]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/robots-that-write-their-own-code.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/robots-that-write-their-own-code.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T13:00:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jacky Liang, Research Intern, and Andy Zeng, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google  -->--> 
A common approach used to control robots is to program them with code to detect objects, sequencing commands to move actuators, and feedback loops to specify how the robot should perform a task. While these programs can be expressive, re-programming policies for each new task can be time consuming, and requires domain expertise.

What if when given instructions from people, robots could autonomously write their own code to interact with the world? It turns out that the latest generation of language models, such as PaLM, are capable of complex reasoning and have also been trained on millions of lines of code. Given natural language instructions, current language models are highly proficien…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Academy – Free, On-Demand Training for All]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=66539</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/camunda-academy-free-on-demand-training/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T01:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Academy provides free, on-demand access to BPMN, DMN and Camunda 8 training for all. See how you can start learning today.
The post Camunda Academy – Free, On-Demand Training for All appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Devine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Telcos Can Add Mutual TLS to 5G Packet Core with HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-telcos-can-add-mutual-tls-to-5g-packet-core-with-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-telcos-can-add-mutual-tls-to-5g-packet-core-with-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As next-generation 5G begins to take shape, learn about a suite of comprehensive, identity-based security solutions for microservice environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – October 31, 2022]]></title>
        <id>29637f7ab6bac856787858b6324877d404e8d5e7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-october-31-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T16:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No tricks, just treats in this weekly roundup of news and announcements. Let’s switch our AWS Management Console into dark mode and dive right into it. Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my attention during the previous week: AWS Local Zones in Hamburg and Warsaw now generally available – AWS Local Zones help […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let Ansible keep an eye on your AWS environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/let-ansible-keep-an-eye-on-your-aws-environment</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/let-ansible-keep-an-eye-on-your-aws-environment"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a cloud model, the security of the environment and compliance becomes the responsibility of both the end users and the cloud provider. This is what we call the shared responsibility model in which every part of the cloud, including the hardware, data, configurations, access rights, and operating system, are protected. Depending on the local legislation and the origin of the data that is handled (for instance laws like HIPAA, the GDPR in Europe, or the Californian CCPA),  you may have to enforce strict rules on your environment and log events for audit purposes. AWS CloudTrail will help you to achieve this goal. The service can collect and record any kind of information coming from your environment and store or send the events to a destination for audit. In addition to security and compliance, this service helps keep track of resource consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gomathi Selvi Srinivasan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Named as a Leader in the 2022 Gartner Cloud Infrastructure & Platform Services (CIPS) Magic Quadrant for the 12th Consecutive Year]]></title>
        <id>90f04a9d62650a4739f4d04add932ad4769dc741</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-named-as-a-leader-in-the-2022-gartner-cloud-infrastructure-platform-services-cips-magic-quadrant-for-the-12th-consecutive-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T16:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, and for the twelfth consecutive year, AWS has been named as a Leader in the 2022 Magic Quadrant for Cloud Infrastructure and Platform Services (CIPS). Per Gartner, AWS is the longest-running CIPS Magic Quadrant Leader. AWS was among the first cloud providers when we launched Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) and Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 212 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65951</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-212-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T19:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In sprint 211 we enabled the “Try the New Boards Hub” banner and popup. This has resulted in a lot of great user feedback, and in turn, a pile of bugs. Our main focus in sprint 212 was fixing these bugs.
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 212 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>