<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-09T01:56:24.171Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-09T01:56:24.171Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sufficient resolution]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46627</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/751865942/0/sethsblog~Sufficient-resolution/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T09:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Johnson is known as the king of the Delta blues. One reason is that his small output was brilliant. The other, bigger reason is that the recordings that remain of his short life are among the earliest that sound good… most audio recordings from before 1936 sound antique and scratchy. The Wizard of Oz […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why External Script Task Users will Love the Camunda Platform 8 Integration Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84827&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=84827</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/external-script-task-connector-integration-framework/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Integration Framework is a significant upgrade over external script tasks, with improved reusability, user-friendliness, and customization.
The post Why External Script Task Users will Love the Camunda Platform 8 Integration Framework appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modular visual question answering via code generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/modular-visual-question-answering-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/modular-visual-question-answering-via.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:01:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sanjay Subramanian, PhD student, UC Berkeley, and Arsha Nagrani, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception Team




Visual question answering (VQA) is a machine learning task that requires a model to answer a question about an image or a set of images. Conventional VQA approaches need a large amount of labeled training data consisting of thousands of human-annotated question-answer pairs associated with images. In recent years, advances in large-scale pre-training have led to the development of VQA methods that perform well with fewer than fifty training examples (few-shot) and without any human-annotated VQA training data (zero-shot). However, there is still a significant performance gap between these methods and state-of-the-art fully supervised VQA methods, such as MaMMU…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Solution – Clickstream Analytics on AWS for Mobile and Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>711a0f0b733911d5daecaf567086b254c8f14f24</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-solution-clickstream-analytics-on-aws-for-mobile-and-web-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T16:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can deploy on your AWS account an end-to-end solution to capture, ingest, store, analyze, and visualize your customers’ clickstreams inside your web and mobile applications (both for Android and iOS). The solution is built on top of standard AWS services. This new solution Clickstream Analytics on AWS allows you to keep your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Language Server Protocol for Plugin Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=369341</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2023/07/lsp-for-plugin-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T14:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Language Server Protocol (LSP) is an open-standard protocol developed by Microsoft that enables communication between development tools and Language Servers. By incorporating LSP into the IntelliJ Platform, we enable plugin developers to introduce support for a custom language by using specific LSP server integration. The Language Server can provide language-specific features such as code […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Chrzanowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Continuous Integration Tools for 2023 ‒ Survey Results]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=369406</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/07/best-ci-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T09:40:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous integration (CI) and continuous delivery or deployment (CD) are key DevOps practices that provide teams with rapid feedback on their latest code changes and help improve code quality. With a good CI/CD process in place, software development teams can move toward more frequent releases, thereby delivering more value to users and benefiting from their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small doses]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44849</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/751494770/0/sethsblog~Small-doses/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you go to a health food store and buy some pills with selenium, colloidal silver or other mysterious substances in them, it’s possible that they’ll make you feel a bit better. On the other hand, if you take a large dose, you’ll get sick or possibly die. In very small doses, all you’re getting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Being one of the only woman in her computer science program didn’t stop Hannah Mudge from pursuing her dream of becoming a software engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-hannah-mudge-dream-of-becoming-software-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-hannah-mudge-dream-of-becoming-software-engineer"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Women in tech: Hannah Mudge is pursuing her dream of becoming a software engineer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating R&D in pharma with Elasticsearch, ESRE, LLMs, and LangChain — Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-development-pharma-elasticsearch-esre-llms-langchain-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-development-pharma-elasticsearch-esre-llms-langchain-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to leverage ESRE and generative AI in order to enable R&D organizations to interact with data effectively and make better decisions in the drug discovery process. The challenges with privacy and missing context will also be addressed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerio Arvizzigno,Dimitri Marx,Francesco Di Stefano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Being one of the only woman in her computer science program didn’t stop Hannah Mudge from pursuing her dream of becoming a software engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-hannah-mudge-dream-of-becoming-software-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-hannah-mudge-dream-of-becoming-software-engineer"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Hannah Mudge was one of the only girls in her computer science program when she enrolled in 2012. 

“Most computer science programs are only 30% women. I was in a smaller program so sometimes I was the only girl in my classes,” she says.

Now a software engineer, she has her master’s degree in the subject.

Hannah had a love of tech from an early age. She was homeschooled until 8th grade and found her passion for coding then, she says. 

“I loved Neopets and I spent a lot of time figuring out how to make my website beautiful,” she says.

Then she was working in HTML and CSS and she knew there was more to coding than just that. 

Now, she works on Elastic’s presentation team, focusing on Kibana and, more specifically, Dashboard. Her day-to-day work is rarely the same — it depends on her t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating R&D in pharma with Elasticsearch, ESRE, LLMs, and LangChain — Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-development-pharma-elasticsearch-esre-llms-langchain-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-development-pharma-elasticsearch-esre-llms-langchain-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Faster drug discovery leading to promising drug candidates is the main objective of the pharmaceutical industry. To support that goal, the industry has to find better ways to utilize both public and proprietary data — at speed and in a safe way.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltc027a3db22757b8a/64a83a20d60b85339768c415/elastic-blog-1-blockbusters.png,elastic-blog-1-blockbusters.png,
According to WIPO, R&D patent analytics can help researchers and innovators to assist to:

Avoid duplicating research and development effort 
Determine the patentability of their inventions 
Avoid infringing other inventors’ patents 
Estimate the value of their or other inventors’ patents
Exploit technology from patent applications that have never been granted, are not valid in c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerio Arvizzigno,Dimitri Marx,Francesco Di Stefano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frankenstein Claim Permutations]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2799/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2799/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/frankenstein_claim_permutations.png" title="When I began trying to form a new claim by stitching together these parts in such an unnatural way, some called me mad." alt="When I began trying to form a new claim by stitching together these parts in such an unnatural way, some called me mad." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seamless Integration with Message Queue Technology through Inbound Subscription Connectors]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84716&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=84716</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/inbound-subscription-connectors-message-queue-integration/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T20:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With new inbound subscription Connectors, you can achieve a seamless and full-featured integration with message queue systems like Kafka, RabbitMQ and more.
The post Seamless Integration with Message Queue Technology through Inbound Subscription Connectors appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pic2Word: Mapping pictures to words for zero-shot composed image retrieval]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/pic2word-mapping-pictures-to-words-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/pic2word-mapping-pictures-to-words-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kuniaki Saito, Student Researcher, Google Research, Cloud AI Team, and Kihyuk Sohn, Research Scientist, Google Research





Image retrieval plays a crucial role in search engines. Typically, their users rely on either image or text as a query to retrieve a desired target image. However, text-based retrieval has its limitations, as describing the target image accurately using words can be challenging. For instance, when searching for a fashion item, users may want an item whose specific attribute, e.g., the color of a logo or the logo itself, is different from what they find in a website. Yet searching for the item in an existing search engine is not trivial since precisely describing the fashion item by text can be challenging. To address this fact, composed image retrieval (CIR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.2 EAP6: Debugger Enhancements]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=370268</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/07/clion-2023-2-eap6-debugger-enhancements/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CLion 232.8660.8 build is available from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package if you are using Ubuntu. You can also update via patch if you are using the previous EAP build. DOWNLOAD CLION EAP ARM assembly CLion now supports ARM assembly languages, which means you’ll see code highlighting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility considerations behind code search and code view]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-06-accessibility-considerations-behind-code-search-and-code-view/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-06-accessibility-considerations-behind-code-search-and-code-view/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at how we improved the readability of code on GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping up with big shifts in tech]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-06-keeping-up-with-big-shifts-in-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-06-keeping-up-with-big-shifts-in-tech/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T16:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deciding whether or not to adopt a tool can be hard enough, but what about when it seems to break the paradigms you know?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space On-Premises 2023.2 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=368412</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2023/07/06/space-on-premises-2023-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T15:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you strive for complete control over your data while developing software? You’ll be glad to know we’ve just released Space On-Premises 2023.2, a more accessible version with new simplified installation options and other useful features. With the new AWS one-click installation option, you can now quickly and easily run Space on the AWS cloud. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgenia Verbina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin 1.9.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=370023</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/07/kotlin-1-9-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T15:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kotlin 1.9.0 release is out and the K2 compiler for the JVM is now in Beta. This release contains new language features as well as improvements for Kotlin Multiplatform and Kotlin/Native. Here are some highlights from this release: For the complete list of changes, refer to What’s new in Kotlin 1.9.0 or release notes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Haggarty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar – OSS Power-Ups: AngleSharp]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=369989</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/07/06/webinar-oss-power-ups-anglesharp/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T14:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us Wednesday, July 12, 2023, 17:00 – 18:30 CEST (11:00 – 12:30 EDT or check other timezones) for our free live webinar, OSS PowerUps – AngleSharp, with Florian Rappl. This is the eleventh episode of our series of OSS Power-Ups, where we put a spotlight on open-source .NET projects. Register now and get a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias Koch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.2 Beta Is Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=369802</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/07/webstorm-2023-2-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T14:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.2 has reached Beta! To see what has already been added to WebStorm 2023.2, take a look at our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. You can also manually download the EAP builds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2023.2 EAP 2: Redis Cluster, New Schema Migration Dialog and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=369859</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2023/07/06/datagrip-2023-2-eap-2-redis-cluster-new-schema-migration-dialog-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T14:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, DataGrip community! The second Early Access Program version for DataGrip 2023.2 is here. If you want to try the new features before the official release, this post is for you! Support for Redis Clusters Now you can connect to Redis Clusters and have the same feature set as with standalone Redis. Choose the dedicated […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maksim Sobolevskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Git and GitHub in 5 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=367823</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/07/06/introduction-to-git-track/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T09:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are your Git skills rusty? Nonexistent? Is your project folder full of files named “Draft-old”,“Draft2”, “Draft2-New”, “FinalDraft”, “FinalDraft (1)”, and “REALFinalDraft”? Would you like to learn how to write better commit messages than “changed some stuff”? If so, we at JetBrains Academy are thrilled to announce that our Introduction to Git learning track is here […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clara Maine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customer traction is the hard part]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46605</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/751242455/0/sethsblog~Customer-traction-is-the-hard-part/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T08:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new business is complicated. It involves weaving together suppliers, partners, customers, processes, technology, leases, employees, logos, capital and more. Along the way, it’s easy to get distracted, but focusing on the hard parts is a useful way to move forward. You could work hard on the logo, or double your supplier roster or, as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Jetbrains' Anton Arhipov on IntelliJ, Java, and so much more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/06/a-bootiful-podcast-jetbrains-anton-arhipov-on-intellij-java-and-so-much-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/06/a-bootiful-podcast-jetbrains-anton-arhipov-on-intellij-java-and-so-much-more"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making the boat faster: Advantages of embedding services and training in software sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/advantages-embedding-services-training-software-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/advantages-embedding-services-training-software-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the advantages of embedding services and training in software sales and understand how it contributes to achieving sustainable growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calizo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How tribal nations can use data to build exceptional customer experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/tribal-nations-data-customer-experiences</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/tribal-nations-data-customer-experiences"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how the industry of tribal resorts, gaming, and entertainment can use data to build exceptional customer experiences and drive revenue, awareness, and support for tribal communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andres Herrera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Courtney Wilburn on the 3 ways leaders can inspire their teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-courtney-wilburn-3-ways-leaders-can-inspire-teams</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-courtney-wilburn-3-ways-leaders-can-inspire-teams"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtney Wilburn's colleagues saw her management potential early on, but she focused on enhancing her programming skills to become a better contributor. She knew she had room to grow before advancing in her career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mara Calvello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making the boat faster: Advantages of embedding services and training in software sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/advantages-embedding-services-training-software-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/advantages-embedding-services-training-software-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In the highly competitive IT industry, staying ahead of the curve is crucial for success. As IT companies strive to meet the evolving needs of their customers, they are discovering that providing embedded services and comprehensive training can significantly enhance their sales efforts. The importance of having services is discussed in this Harvard Business Review article.
By embracing the concept of "making the boat faster," businesses can gain a competitive edge and deliver exceptional value to their clients. 
In this blog, we will explore the advantages of embedding services and training in software sales and understand how it contributes to achieving sustainable growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calizo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How tribal nations can use data to build exceptional customer experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/tribal-nations-data-customer-experiences</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/tribal-nations-data-customer-experiences"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In the competitive industry of resorts, gaming, and entertainment, delivering an exceptional customer experience (CX) is paramount. The fusion of physical and digital experiences plays a significant role in shaping guests’ perception of your brand. The same is true for tribal casinos and resorts, which drive revenue, awareness, and support for tribal communities. As tribal businesses strive for operational excellence and unparalleled experiences, embracing cutting-edge technologies becomes even more imperative.
This industry is changing quickly with the growth of mobile applications and generative artificial intelligence (GAI). The power of these technologies, combined with search and advanced analytics tools, can produce actionable insights that can:

Streamline marketing campaigns
Increase customer spend and loyalty
Optimize IT development efforts

The ability to deliver exceptional customer experiences with the right technology holds immense significance for tribal casinos and resorts, while also empowering their employees with essential information and support.
Below we explore some of the data complexities that might come with these technologies and how Elastic’s search-powered data platform can enable tribal resort, gaming, and entertainment businesses to find the answers that matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andres Herrera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Courtney Wilburn on the 3 ways leaders can inspire their teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-courtney-wilburn-3-ways-leaders-can-inspire-teams</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-courtney-wilburn-3-ways-leaders-can-inspire-teams"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Courtney Wilburn’s colleagues recognized her management potential early in her career.

“I tried engineering leadership in my early 20s and wasn’t ready for it then. I was thrust into it really young because I had the skills and was seen as a natural leader. But, it wasn’t the right time,” she shares.

Instead, Courtney invested in honing her programming skills to become a stronger individual contributor, recognizing that she still had room to grow before taking the next step in her career.

After focusing on skill development, Courtney found her way back into engineering management with a newfound appreciation for the responsibilities of leadership. Now a senior engineering manager at Elastic, she pulls from her learnings as a young professional to boost team morale, encourage honesty, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mara Calvello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Confidential Kubernetes: Use Confidential Virtual Machines and Enclaves to improve your cluster security]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/07/06/confidential-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/07/06/confidential-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Fabian Kammel (Edgeless Systems), Mikko Ylinen (Intel), Tobin Feldman-Fitzthum (IBM)
In this blog post, we will introduce the concept of Confidential Computing (CC) to improve any computing environment's security and privacy properties. Further, we will show how
the Cloud-Native ecosystem, particularly Kubernetes, can benefit from the new compute paradigm.
Confidential Computing is a concept that has been introduced previously in the cloud-native world. The
Confidential Computing Consortium (CCC) is a project community in the Linux Foundation
that already worked on
Defining and Enabling Confidential Computing.
In the Whitepaper,
they provide a great motivation for the use of Confidential Computing:
Data exists in three states: in transit, at rest, and in use. …Protecting sensitive…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub achieves ISO/IEC 27701:2019, 27018:2019, and CSA STAR certifications]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-05-github-achieves-iso-iec-277012019-270182019-and-csa-star-certifications/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-05-github-achieves-iso-iec-277012019-270182019-and-csa-star-certifications/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub’s Information Security and Privacy Management System (ISPMS) has been certified against ISO/IEC 27701:2019 (PII Processor) and 27018:2019 standards, as well as the Cloud Controls Matrix (CCM). These standards and frameworks are internationally recognized for security and privacy program best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service Major Updates: Global View, Import and Export from Local Disk, and Additional Post-launch Actions]]></title>
        <id>14172370fc6fd2b9a6a7a63a8138f20ba11f6302</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-application-migration-service-major-updates-global-view-import-and-export-from-local-disk-and-additional-post-launch-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T17:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service simplifies, expedites, and reduces the cost of migrating your applications to AWS. It allows you to lift and shift many physical, virtual, or cloud servers without compatibility issues, performance disruption, or long cutover windows. You can minimize time-intensive, error-prone manual processes by automating replication and conversion of your source servers from physical, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to SELinux]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-05-introduction-to-selinux/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-05-introduction-to-selinux/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T16:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SELinux is the most popular Linux Security Module used to isolate and protect system components from one another. Learn about different access control systems and Linux security as I introduce the foundations of a popular type system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Consul cluster peering locally with Minikube]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploy-consul-cluster-peering-locally-with-minikube</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploy-consul-cluster-peering-locally-with-minikube"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use Minikube to create multiple Kubernetes clusters with Consul and test cluster peering configurations in your local development environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buy PyCharm. Support Django.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=369711</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/07/buy-pycharm-support-django/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T14:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our annual campaign to support the Django Foundation has launched. Django is super-important to people and companies worldwide! It’s one of Python’s greatest successes. Not just the code, but the project and the non-profit foundation behind it. Django is a tribute to volunteer, open-source development. But Django and the Django Software Foundation need resources, including […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teach Kotlin Now With Our New Pre-made Course]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=369548</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/07/teach-kotlin-with-our-new-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T14:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Kotlin community and ecosystem are expanding – and the demand for Kotlin developers is on the rise – we’re looking to equip computer science educators with the relevant tools and up-to-date resources necessary to meet this need. Programming in Kotlin curriculum An important milestone of our educational initiatives is the release of a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ksenia Shneyveys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | July 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=369407</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/07/05/net-annotated-monthly-july-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T13:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? The acronym “ASP” stands for Active Server Pages, which was released by Microsoft in 1996. In 2002, Microsoft decided to continue using the name, but apply it to their new .NET framework so they added “.NET” to the acronym. Since then, we’ve known this technology as ASP.NET. .NET news Featured content  We’d […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Google Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-google-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-google-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is co-authored by Zack Kayyali and Hicham (he-sham) Mourad]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary Kayyali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Throwing shade or throwing light?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44844</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/750995219/0/sethsblog~Throwing-shade-or-throwing-light/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One takes a little more effort than the other. While throwing shade might be more fun, it eventually runs out of energy. It’s designed to end conversations, not start them, to intimidate, not encourage. Turning on lights helps everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Active Health Check strategies with Spring Cloud Gateway]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/05/active-health-check-strategies-with-spring-cloud-gateway</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/05/active-health-check-strategies-with-spring-cloud-gateway"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ignacio Lozano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector search in Elasticsearch: The rationale behind the design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/vector-search-elasticsearch-rationale</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/vector-search-elasticsearch-rationale"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are different ways to implement a vector database, which have different trade-offs. In this blog, you'll learn more about how vector search has been integrated into Elastisearch and the trade-offs that we made.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrien Grand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector search in Elasticsearch: The rationale behind the design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/vector-search-elasticsearch-rationale</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/vector-search-elasticsearch-rationale"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Are you interested to learn about the characteristics of Elasticsearch for vector search and what the design looks like? As always, design decisions come with pros and cons. This blog aims to break down how we chose to build vector search in Elasticsearch.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrien Grand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Room Temperature]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2798/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2798/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/room_temperature.png" title="They're also refusing to fund my device that demonstrates uncontrolled hot fusion." alt="They're also refusing to fund my device that demonstrates uncontrolled hot fusion." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we cannibals?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43731</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/750690920/0/sethsblog~Are-we-cannibals/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T08:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of the challenge of hanging out with cannibals is that it’s very difficult to get a good night’s sleep. The math of finding a group of people that cares about community is pretty compelling. While individual selfish choices might feel productive in the moment, if they undermine the health of the community, they’re ultimately […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 4th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/04/this-week-in-spring-july-4th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/04/this-week-in-spring-july-4th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leading your platform migration with developer experience]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-03-leading-your-platform-migration-with-developer-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-03-leading-your-platform-migration-with-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T23:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer experience (DevEx) is a key theme when it comes to transforming businesses with GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey 2023: Inside the maturity model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-inside-the-maturity-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-inside-the-maturity-model"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s 2023 State of Cloud Strategy Survey debuts a new cloud-maturity model, which reveals how more-mature organizations enjoy better business outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Generative AI with LLM Hands-on Course, Amazon SageMaker Data Wrangler Updates, and More – July 3, 2023]]></title>
        <id>3fb74ddd0280e06d6387d7abc8383d64678fa7dc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-generative-ai-with-llm-hands-on-course-amazon-sagemaker-data-wrangler-updates-and-more-july-3-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T18:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In last week’s AWS Week in Review post, Danilo mentioned that it’s summer in London. Well, I’m based in Singapore, and it’s mostly summer here. But, June is a special month here as it marks the start of durian season. Starting next week, I’ll be travelling to Thailand, Malaysia, and the Philippines. But before I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pruning incoming log volumes with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/pruning-incoming-log-volumes-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/pruning-incoming-log-volumes-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To drop or not to drop (events) is the question, not only in deciding what events and fields to remove from your logs but also in the various tools used. Learn about using Beats, Logstash, Elastic Agent, Ingest Pipelines, and OTel Collectors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pruning incoming log volumes with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/pruning-incoming-log-volumes-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/pruning-incoming-log-volumes-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[filebeat.inputs:
- type: filestream
  id: my-logging-app
  paths:
    - /var/log/*.logfilebeat.inputs:
- type: filestream
  id: my-logging-app
  paths:
    - /var/tmp/other.log
    - /var/log/*.log
processors:
  - drop_event:
      when:
          and:
            - equals:
              url.scheme: http
            - equals:
              url.path: /profilefilebeat.inputs:
- type: filestream
  id: my-logging-app
  paths:
    - /var/tmp/other.log
    - /var/log/*.log
processors:
  - drop_fields:
      when:
          and:
            - equals:
              url.scheme: http
            - equals:
              http.response.status_code: 200
          fields: ["event.message"]
          ignore_missing: false
input {
  file {
    id => "my-logging-app"
    path => [ "/var/tmp/other.log", "/va…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the future finds us]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43745</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/750460574/0/sethsblog~When-the-future-finds-us/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T09:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future never arrives, of course, but it has a powerful force that’s impossible to avoid. We can see it as a threshold, a doorway toward something new. Or we can fight it as an unwanted change, and discover that it has traction, tenacity and leverage. We can influence the future, but we can’t pretend […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get the best of lexical and AI-powered search with Elastic’s vector database]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/lexical-ai-powered-search-elastic-vector-database</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/lexical-ai-powered-search-elastic-vector-database"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic has all you should expect from a vector database — and much more! You get the best of both worlds: traditional lexical and AI-powered search, including semantic search out of the box with Elastic’s novel Learned Sparse Encoder model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernhard Suhm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get the best of lexical and AI-powered search with Elastic’s vector database]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/lexical-ai-powered-search-elastic-vector-database</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/lexical-ai-powered-search-elastic-vector-database"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Maybe you came across the term “vector database” and are wondering whether it’s the new kid on the block of data retrieval systems. Maybe you are confused by conflicting claims about vector databases. The truth is, the approach used by vector databases has been around for a few years. If you’re looking for the best retrieval performance, hybrid approaches that combine keyword-based search (sometimes referred to as lexical search) with vector-based approaches represent the state of the art. 

In Elasticsearch®, you can get the best of both worlds: lexical and vector search. Elastic® made lexical columnar retrieval popular, implemented in Lucene, and has been perfecting that approach for more than 10 years. In addition, for several years, Elastic has been investing in vector database capab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernhard Suhm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actual Progress]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2797/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2797/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/actual_progress.png" title="Slowly progressing from 'how do protons behave in relativistic collisions?' to 'what the heck are protons even doing when they're just sitting there?'" alt="Slowly progressing from 'how do protons behave in relativistic collisions?' to 'what the heck are protons even doing when they're just sitting there?'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is undermining your brand?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44759</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/750249542/0/sethsblog~Who-is-undermining-your-brand/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-02T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a high-end grocer in a very expensive neighborhood of New York–and they focus all of their energy on Italian food. Everything is imported, and they spend a lot of time and money earning the premium they charge for an authentic Italian shopping experience. And then a lazy brand manager decided to plaster “Sale-A-Bration” signs […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building intelligent Spring Apps with Azure OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/02/building-intelligent-spring-apps-with-azure-openai</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/02/building-intelligent-spring-apps-with-azure-openai"/>
        <updated>2023-07-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actionable feedback]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43703</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/750003911/0/sethsblog~Actionable-feedback/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T08:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Do you want to know what I think?” The best answer might be, “no.” Because this person is not very good at offering useful feedback. Because you didn’t create this product or service or performance to please this person. They’re not the customer. Because you’re not going to revise this any time soon. The movie […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · June 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-30-game-bytes-june-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-30-game-bytes-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T17:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.16 enhances service mesh reliability, user experience, and security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-16-enhances-service-mesh-reliability-user-experience-and-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-16-enhances-service-mesh-reliability-user-experience-and-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.16 adds new reliability, scalability, security, service mesh UX, extensibility, and service discovery capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“And” fatigue]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43662</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/749742842/0/sethsblog~And-fatigue/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital abundance creates a new problem. Most of our lives are filled with “or” decisions. You can have this or that. You can save money for the big party or you can go out for lunch. You can have exactly one thing for dessert–cake or fruit. But the war for our attention has given us […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.8 (aka Jubilee) Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/30/spring-cloud-2021-0-8-aka-jubilee-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/30/spring-cloud-2021-0-8-aka-jubilee-is-available"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcin Grzejszczak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we sped up data ingestion in Elasticsearch 8.6, 8.7, and 8.8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-ingestion-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-ingestion-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data ingestion involves a lot of things that usually take a non-negligible amount of time. Fortunately, we've got improvements in 8.6, 8.7, and 8.8, which enabled some good speedups for end-to-end ingestion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrien Grand,Joe Gallo,Tyler Perkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving the Elastic APM UI performance with continuous rollups and service metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-elastic-apm-ui-performance-continuous-rollups-service-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-elastic-apm-ui-performance-continuous-rollups-service-metrics"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made significant improvements to the UI performance in Elastic APM to make it scale with even the most demanding workloads, by pre-aggregating metrics at the service level, and storing the metrics at different levels of granularity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Barnsteiner,Yngrid Coello,Dario Gieselaar,Carson Ip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we sped up data ingestion in Elasticsearch 8.6, 8.7, and 8.8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-ingestion-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-ingestion-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As some of you already noticed, Elasticsearch 8.6, 8.7, and 8.8 brought good indexing speedups across a wide range of data sets, from simple keywords to heavy KNN vectors, as well as ingest-pipeline-heavy ingestion workloads. Ingestion involves many components — running ingest pipelines, inverting data in memory, flushing segments, merging segments — and all of these usually take a non-negligible amount of time. Fortunately for you, we've made improvements across all of these areas, enabling faster speeds for end-to-end ingestion. 

As an example, 8.8 is 13% faster than 8.6 at ingestion on our benchmark that simulates a realistic logging use-case with multiple data sets, ingest pipelines, etc. The following chart shows the ingestion rate going from ~22.5k docs/s to ~25.5k docs/s over the period of time when we implemented these optimizations.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt99f2525e6b30c673/649eece17c84d215bdc2ac35/elastic-blog-ingestion-speedups.png,elastic-blog-ingestion-speedups.png,
This blog dives into some of the changes that helped achieve ingestion speedups in 8.6, 8.7, and 8.8.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt512a0f1b39217f35/649ef4e0fa183536f118dccb/elastic-blog-total-ingest-pipline.png,elastic-blog-total-ingest-pipline.png,
We expect these speedups to be representative of the improvement that a non-trivial ingest use case would see after an upgrade to 8.7 or a more recent version.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrien Grand,Joe Gallo,Tyler Perkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving the Elastic APM UI performance with continuous rollups and service metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-elastic-apm-ui-performance-continuous-rollups-service-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-elastic-apm-ui-performance-continuous-rollups-service-metrics"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In today's fast-paced digital landscape, the ability to monitor and optimize application performance is crucial for organizations striving to deliver exceptional user experiences. At Elastic, we recognize the significance of providing our user base with a reliable Observability platform that scales with you as you’re onboarding thousands of services that produce terabytes of data each day. We have been diligently working behind the scenes to enhance our solution to meet the demands of even the largest deployments.

In this blog post, we are excited to share the significant strides we have made in improving the UI performance of Elastic APM. Maintaining a snappy user interface can be a challenge when interactively summarizing the massive amounts of data needed to provide an overview of the performance for an entire enterprise-scale service inventory. We want to assure our customers that we have listened, taken action, and made notable architectural changes to elevate the scalability and maturity of our solution.
FAQs,,
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Barnsteiner,Yngrid Coello,Dario Gieselaar,Carson Ip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Estate Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2796/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2796/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/real_estate_analysis.png" title="Mars does get a good score on 'noise levels' and 'scenic views,' but the school district ranking isn't great; the only teacher--the Perseverance rover--is too busy with rock samples to teach more than the occasional weekend class." alt="Mars does get a good score on 'noise levels' and 'scenic views,' but the school district ranking isn't great; the only teacher--the Perseverance rover--is too busy with rock samples to teach more than the occasional weekend class." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the first Machine Unlearning Challenge]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/announcing-first-machine-unlearning.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/announcing-first-machine-unlearning.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T21:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Fabian Pedregosa and Eleni Triantafillou, Research Scientists, Google





Deep learning has recently driven tremendous progress in a wide array of applications, ranging from realistic image generation and impressive retrieval systems to language models that can hold human-like conversations. While this progress is very exciting, the widespread use of deep neural network models requires caution: as guided by Google’s AI Principles, we seek to develop AI technologies responsibly by understanding and mitigating potential risks, such as the propagation and amplification of unfair biases and protecting user privacy.
 

Fully erasing the influence of the data requested to be deleted is challenging since, aside from simply deleting it from databases where it’s stored, it also requires …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-device diffusion plugins for conditioned text-to-image generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/on-device-diffusion-plugins-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/on-device-diffusion-plugins-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:10:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yang Zhao and Tingbo Hou, Software Engineers, Core ML




In recent years, diffusion models have shown great success in text-to-image generation, achieving high image quality, improved inference performance, and expanding our creative inspiration. Nevertheless, it is still challenging to efficiently control the generation, especially with conditions that are difficult to describe with text.



Today, we announce MediaPipe diffusion plugins, which enable controllable text-to-image generation to be run on-device. Expanding upon our prior work on GPU inference for on-device large generative models, we introduce new low-cost solutions for controllable text-to-image generation that can be plugged into existing diffusion models and their Low-Rank Adaptation (LoRA) variants. 




Text-t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.9 is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-29-github-enterprise-server-3-9-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-29-github-enterprise-server-3-9-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.9 is now generally available. Organizations can now take advantage of more features that enable deeper collaboration, greater observability and faster workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Migrating to Camunda Platform 8 Accelerates Existing Process Automation Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84254&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=84254</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/migration-camunda-platform-8-accelerates-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how you can gain a competitive advantage by unlocking the unparalleled capabilities of the latest version of Camunda technology.
The post How Migrating to Camunda Platform 8 Accelerates Existing Process Automation Projects appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Liberadzki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Consul management plane with  cloud-based observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-consul-management-plane-with-cloud-based-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-consul-management-plane-with-cloud-based-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HCP Consul management plane now offers deeper insights to your Consul deployments via cloud-based observability and seamlessly links new and existing self-managed Consul clusters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use the new Constructed Inventory Feature in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-use-the-new-constructed-inventory-feature-in-aap-2.4</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-use-the-new-constructed-inventory-feature-in-aap-2.4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New Constructed Inventory Feature
 
In this blog we introduced the idea for a new smarter way of handling inventory based on the Ansible constructed plugin. Now in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4, we have introduced this as a fully supported feature and this blog aims to introduce you to it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Rominger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The seduction of grad school]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46556</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/749522159/0/sethsblog~The-seduction-of-grad-school/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a certain cohort of high-performing students at famous colleges, graduate school feels irresistible. If you’re good at school, the challenge and offer of law school, med school or a famous business school means you get to do more of what you’re good at. You’re offered a high-status badge, a path to a well-paid job […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Elastic's Philipp Krenn]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/29/a-bootiful-podcast-elastics-philipp-krenn</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/29/a-bootiful-podcast-elastics-philipp-krenn"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Verifying Container Image Signatures Within CRI Runtimes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/06/29/container-image-signature-verification/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/06/29/container-image-signature-verification/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
The Kubernetes community has been signing their container image-based artifacts
since release v1.24. While the graduation of the corresponding enhancement
from alpha to beta in v1.26 introduced signatures for the binary artifacts,
other projects followed the approach by providing image signatures for their
releases, too. This means that they either create the signatures within their
own CI/CD pipelines, for example by using GitHub actions, or rely on the
Kubernetes image promotion process to automatically sign the images by
proposing pull requests to the k/k8s.io repository. A requirement for
using this process is that the project is part of the kubernetes or
kubernetes-sigs GitHub organization, so that they can utilize the community
infrastructure for pushing images…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI with Large Language Models — New Hands-on Course by DeepLearning.AI and AWS]]></title>
        <id>54f117b5accead3dc22e75b2f9aa923036b2bdb2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/generative-ai-with-large-language-models-new-hands-on-course-by-deeplearning-ai-and-aws/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T15:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI has taken the world by storm, and we’re starting to see the next wave of widespread adoption of AI with the potential for every customer experience and application to be reinvented with generative AI. Generative AI lets you to create new content and ideas including conversations, stories, images, videos, and music. Generative AI […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第232話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361388410249</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361388410249"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why transentis consulting Chose Camunda Platform 8 SaaS for Their Vacation Request Process]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84053</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/why-camunda-platform-8-transentis/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T01:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why transentis consulting chose Camunda Platform 8 SaaS to digitize their vacation request process.
The post Why transentis consulting Chose Camunda Platform 8 SaaS for Their Vacation Request Process appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.11, 3.0.6 and 3.1.2 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/28/spring-shell-2-1-11-3-0-6-and-3-1-2-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/28/spring-shell-2-1-11-3-0-6-and-3-1-2-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unifying image-caption and image-classification datasets with prefix conditioning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/unifying-image-caption-and-image.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/unifying-image-caption-and-image.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T21:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kuniaki Saito, Student Researcher, Cloud AI Team, and Kihyuk Sohn, Research Scientist, Perception Team




Pre-training visual language (VL) models on web-scale image-caption datasets has recently emerged as a powerful alternative to traditional pre-training on image classification data. Image-caption datasets are considered to be more “open-domain” because they contain broader scene types and vocabulary words, which result in models with strong performance in few- and zero-shot recognition tasks. However, images with fine-grained class descriptions can be rare, and the class distribution can be imbalanced since image-caption datasets do not go through manual curation. By contrast, large-scale classification datasets, such as ImageNet, are often curated and can thus provide fine-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS AppFabric Improves Application Observability for SaaS Applications]]></title>
        <id>219ecb75a7af29bfa01f68ada61052b158a23ec8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-appfabric-improves-application-observability-for-saas-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T17:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s business landscape, companies strive to equip their employees with the most suitable and efficient tools to perform their jobs effectively. To achieve this goal, many companies turn to Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) applications. This approach allows companies to optimize their workflows, enhance employee productivity, and focus their resources on core business activities rather than software […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The economic impact of the AI-powered developer lifecycle and lessons from GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-27-the-economic-impact-of-the-ai-powered-developer-lifecycle-and-lessons-from-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-27-the-economic-impact-of-the-ai-powered-developer-lifecycle-and-lessons-from-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today at Collision Conference we unveiled breaking new research on the economic and productivity impact of generative AI–powered developer tools. The research found that the increase in developer productivity due to AI could boost global GDP by over $1.5 trillion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp acquires BluBracket to add secrets scanning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-acquisition-of-blubracket</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-acquisition-of-blubracket"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BluBracket’s secrets-scanning functionality will complement HashiCorp Vault’s secrets management to help prevent accidental leaks and fight secret sprawl.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.6 beta adds node pools, UX updates, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-6-adds-node-pools-ux-updates-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-6-adds-node-pools-ux-updates-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.6 introduces node pools to help manage multi-tenant Nomad clusters, along with a redesigned job UI, Nomad Pack improvements, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.4</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T13:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of new features found in the Ansible Automation Platform 2.4 release]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choose an image for your organization]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67205</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/choose-an-image-for-your-organization/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T12:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce that you can now choose an image for your Azure DevOps organization and replace the automatically generated image. Learn how to change your organization’s image
BEFORE
The ability to change an organization’s image has been a long standing feature request in the Developer Community with over 150 votes.
The post Choose an image for your organization appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brenner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Spring for GraphQL with Spring Data Neo4j]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/27/using-spring-for-graphql-with-spring-data-neo4j</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/27/using-spring-for-graphql-with-spring-data-neo4j"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 27th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/27/this-week-in-spring-june-27th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/27/this-week-in-spring-june-27th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Step Functions Versions and Aliases, EC2 Instances with Graviton3E Processors, and More – June 26, 2023]]></title>
        <id>b5f480df9c754ac5d9a62c25e2a998f30d088412</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-step-functions-versions-and-aliases-ec2-instances-with-graviton3e-processors-and-more-june-26-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s now summer in the northern hemisphere, and you can feel it in London where I live. But let’s not get distracted by the nice weather and go through your AWS updates from the previous seven days. Last Week’s Launches Another interesting week with many announcements! Here are some that got more of my attention: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New tool to secure your GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-26-new-tool-to-secure-your-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-26-new-tool-to-secure-your-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T16:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a new tool to monitor and control the permissions of the repository token for GitHub Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Terraform continuous validation use cases for AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/8-terraform-continuous-validation-use-cases-for-aws-google-cloud-and-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/8-terraform-continuous-validation-use-cases-for-aws-google-cloud-and-azure"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can use Terraform check blocks and continuous validation with AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on AWS to AWS GovCloud in the United States]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-aws-to-aws-govcloud-in-the-us</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-aws-to-aws-govcloud-in-the-us"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is co-authored by Zack Kayyali and Hicham (he-sham) Mourad
 
Deploying Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform Foundation
 
The steps below detail how to install Ansible Automation Platform on AWS United States GovCloud from the AWS Marketplace. The steps to deploy into AWS GovCloud and AWS Commercial cloud are nearly identical. Before starting your deployment process, please ensure the AWS account you are using to deploy has the following IAM roles. These IAM roles are required to deploy the AWS foundation stack offering. The foundation stack offering here refers to the base Ansible Automation Platform 2 deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary Kayyali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Ansible Lightspeed with IBM Watson Code Assistant Technical Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/welcome-to-the-ansible-lightspeed-technical-preview</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/welcome-to-the-ansible-lightspeed-technical-preview"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T12:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of what to expect with the technology preview of Ansible Lightspeed with IBM Watson Code Assistant, a new generative AI service available now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Open Source Software Gives You Access to Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84019</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/how-open-source-software-gives-you-access-to-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open source software provides access to innovations and latest technologies. Check out this post to explore some of the ways that open source software gives companies access to innovation.
The post How Open Source Software Gives You Access to Innovation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preference learning with automated feedback for cache eviction]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/preference-learning-with-automated.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/preference-learning-with-automated.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T19:24:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ramki Gummadi, Software Engineer, Google and Kevin Chen, Software Engineer, YouTube





Caching is a ubiquitous idea in computer science that significantly improves the performance of storage and retrieval systems by storing a subset of popular items closer to the client based on request patterns. An important algorithmic piece of cache management is the decision policy used for dynamically updating the set of items being stored, which has been extensively optimized over several decades, resulting in several efficient and robust heuristics. While applying machine learning to cache policies has shown promising results in recent years (e.g., LRB, LHD, storage applications), it remains a challenge to outperform robust heuristics in a way that can generalize reliably beyond benchmar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A HashiCorp Ambassador at HashiDays London]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-hashicorp-ambassador-at-hashidays-london</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-hashicorp-ambassador-at-hashidays-london"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Ambassador Chris van Meer shares his experiences at HashiDays London.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.0 M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/23/spring-modulith-1-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/06/23/spring-modulith-1-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoundStorm: Efficient parallel audio generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/soundstorm-efficient-parallel-audio.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/soundstorm-efficient-parallel-audio.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T18:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zalán Borsos, Research Software Engineer, and Marco Tagliasacchi, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Research







The recent progress in generative AI unlocked the possibility of creating new content in several different domains, including text, vision and audio. These models often rely on the fact that raw data is first converted to a compressed format as a sequence of tokens. In the case of audio, neural audio codecs (e.g., SoundStream or EnCodec) can efficiently compress waveforms to a compact representation, which can be inverted to reconstruct an approximation of the original audio signal. Such a representation consists of a sequence of discrete audio tokens, capturing the local properties of sounds (e.g., phonemes) and their temporal structure (e.g., prosody). By re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.14 brings ACME for PKI, AWS roles, and more improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-14-brings-acme-for-pki-aws-roles-and-more-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-14-brings-acme-for-pki-aws-roles-and-more-improvements"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.14 includes the Vault Secrets Operator GA, ACME PKI, and a new OpenLDAP secrets engine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Cloud Automation with amazon.aws 6.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-6.0.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-6.0.0"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to Amazon Web Services (AWS) infrastructure automation, the latest release of the certified amazon.aws Collection for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform brings a number of enhancements to improve the overall user experience and speed up the process from development to production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source challenge results from Gamedev.js Jam 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-06-21-gamedev-js-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-06-21-gamedev-js-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T22:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlighting 13 of the top games plus source from the latest Gamedev.js jam–by GitHub Star and event organizer, Andrzej Mazur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: AI for Social Good]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/responsible-ai-at-google-research-ai.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/responsible-ai-at-google-research-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T20:57:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jimmy Tobin and Katrin Tomanek, Software Engineers, Google Research, AI for Social Good


Google’s AI for Social Good team consists of researchers, engineers, volunteers, and others with a shared focus on positive social impact. Our mission is to demonstrate AI’s societal benefit by enabling real-world value, with projects spanning work in public health, accessibility, crisis response, climate and energy, and nature and society. We believe that the best way to drive positive change in underserved communities is by partnering with change-makers and the organizations they serve.


 


In this blog post we discuss work done by Project Euphonia, a team within AI for Social Good, that aims to improve automatic speech recognition (ASR) for people with disordered speech. For people with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s first braiding of non-Abelian anyons]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/the-worlds-first-braiding-of-non.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/the-worlds-first-braiding-of-non.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T17:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Trond Andersen and Yuri Lensky, Research Scientists, Google Quantum AI Team  






Imagine you’re shown two identical objects and then asked to close your eyes. When you open your eyes, you see the same two objects in the same position. How can you determine if they have been swapped back and forth? Intuition and the laws of quantum mechanics agree: If the objects are truly identical, there is no way to tell. 



While this sounds like common sense, it only applies to our familiar three-dimensional world. Researchers have predicted that for a special type of particle, called an anyon, that is restricted to move only in a two-dimensional (2D) plane, quantum mechanics allows for something quite different. Anyons are indistinguishable from one another and some, non-Abelian anyons, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ready or Not? Two Approaches for a Smoother Camunda 7 to Camunda 8 Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83750</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/ready-or-not-two-approaches-for-a-smoother-camunda-7-to-camunda-8-migration/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T16:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two approaches to making it easier to migrate from Camunda 7 to Camunda 8. Read this post to learn which tools you'll need.
The post Ready or Not? Two Approaches for a Smoother Camunda 7 to Camunda 8 Migration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 Hpc7g Instances Powered by AWS Graviton3E Processors Optimized for High Performance Computing Workloads]]></title>
        <id>5ea979c45bdfa8e4b408386066d2c67700c1c40d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-hpc7g-instances-powered-by-aws-graviton3e-processors-optimized-for-high-performance-computing-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T20:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2022, Adam Selipsky, CEO of AWS, explained high performance computing (HPC) workloads typically can either be compute-intensive, compute- and networking-intensive, or data- and memory-intensive in his keynote. Compute workloads include weather forecasting, computational fluid dynamics, and financial options pricing. To help with this, you have Amazon EC2 Hpc6a instances, which deliver up […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon EC2 C7gn Instances: Graviton3E Processors and Up To 200 Gbps Network Bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>4b5a7a85829664e1b14fef7adcba05a5d8436262</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c7gn-instances-graviton3e-processors-and-up-to-200-gbps-network-bandwidth/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T20:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The C7gn instances that we previewed last year are now available and you can start using them today. The instances are designed for your most demanding network-intensive workloads (firewalls, virtual routers, load balancers, and so forth), data analytics, and tightly-coupled cluster computing jobs. They are powered by AWS Graviton3E processors and support up to 200 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to streamline and secure your SaaS applications at AWS Applications Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>5dc3826279a8cfb6eabd79bfa44f3c629827141f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/learn-how-to-streamline-and-secure-your-saas-applications-at-aws-applications-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T18:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies continue to adopt software as a service (SaaS) applications at a rapid clip, with recent research showing that the average SaaS portfolio now has at least 200 applications. While organizations purchase these purpose-built tools to make their employees more productive, they now must contend with growing security complexities, context switching, and data silos. If […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Goldstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Scene Changes in Audiovisual Content]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/77a61d3eaad6</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/detecting-scene-changes-in-audiovisual-content-77a61d3eaad6?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T16:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avneesh Saluja, Andy Yao, Hossein Taghavi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking the 2023 HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey [Video]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/unpacking-the-2023-hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-video</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/unpacking-the-2023-hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-video"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch this 10-minute video for an insightful overview of the survey’s key findings and how HashiCorp can help your organization make the most of the cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Amazon EC2 Instance Connect Endpoint, Detective, Amazon S3 Dual Layer Encryption, Amazon Verified Permission – June 19, 2023]]></title>
        <id>3652b5bcb9a6bda391b1dd7ad03ab1fb81ac3d06</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-amazon-ec2-instance-connect-endpoint-detective-amazon-s3-dual-layer-encryption-amazon-verified-permission-june-19-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T19:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I’ll meet you at AWS partner’s Jamf Nation Live in Amsterdam where we’re showing how to use Amazon EC2 Mac to deploy your remote developer workstations or configure your iOS CI/CD pipelines in the cloud. Last Week’s Launches While I was traveling last week, I kept an eye on the AWS News. Here […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 223]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67177</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-223/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T18:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the risk of sounding repetitive, sprint 223 was dedicated to resolving bugs. Looks like sprint 224 will be much of the same. We continue to make great progress, but we have a little way to go before the New Boards Hub is ready for general availability.
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 223 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at CVPR 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/google-at-cvpr-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/google-at-cvpr-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T18:00:00.018Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shaina Mehta, Program Manager, Google




This week marks the beginning of the premier annual Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition conference (CVPR 2023), held in-person in Vancouver, BC (with additional virtual content). As a leader in computer vision research and a Platinum Sponsor, Google Research will have a strong presence across CVPR 2023 with ~90 papers being presented at the main conference and active involvement in over 40 conference workshops and tutorials.




If you are attending CVPR this year, please stop by our booth to chat with our researchers who are actively exploring the latest techniques for application to various areas of machine perception. Our researchers will also be available to talk about and demo several recent efforts, including on-device ML applic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GoDaddy Implemented a Multi-Region Event-Driven Platform at Scale]]></title>
        <id>a98489d395f0c435cc777fcf89a3a9ff10dd4933</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-godaddy-implemented-a-multi-region-event-driven-platform-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T17:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoDaddy, a leading global provider of domain registration and web hosting services, has served over 84 million domains and 22 million customers since its establishment in 1997. Among its various internal systems, the Customer Signal Platform provides tooling to capture, analyze, and act on customer and product data to drive better business outcomes. With this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speed is all you need: On-device acceleration of large diffusion models via GPU-aware optimizations]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/speed-is-all-you-need-on-device.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/speed-is-all-you-need-on-device.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Juhyun Lee and Raman Sarokin, Software Engineers, Core Systems & Experiences




The proliferation of large diffusion models for image generation has led to a significant increase in model size and inference workloads. On-device ML inference in mobile environments requires meticulous performance optimization and consideration of trade-offs due to resource constraints. Running inference of large diffusion models (LDMs) on-device, driven by the need for cost efficiency and user privacy, presents even greater challenges due to the substantial memory requirements and computational demands of these models.
 

We address this challenge in our work titled “Speed Is All You Need: On-Device Acceleration of Large Diffusion Models via GPU-Aware Optimizations” (to be presented at the CVPR 20…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline Processes by Using Inbound Webhook Connectors as Intermediate Events]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83717&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83717</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/streamline-processes-inbound-webhook-connectors-intermediate-events/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can use our inbound connectors within a process as an Intermediate Event, making your processes more efficient.
The post Streamline Processes by Using Inbound Webhook Connectors as Intermediate Events appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Forms Faster with Camunda Form Builder and Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83625&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83625</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/build-forms-faster-camunda-form-builder-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can take advantage of generative AI to build forms faster and incorporate them into your processes.
The post Build Forms Faster with Camunda Form Builder and Generative AI appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover How AWS Designed Silicon Fuels Customer Outcomes at AWS Silicon Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>bb29bbbb082903bdd1939aafdeb231b3d1b0b260</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/discover-how-aws-designed-silicon-fuels-customer-outcomes-at-aws-silicon-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We hope you will join us on Wednesday, June 21, for a free-to-attend online event, AWS Silicon Innovation Day. AWS will stream the event simultaneously across multiple platforms, including LinkedIn Live, Twitter, YouTube, and Twitch. AWS Silicon Innovation Day is a one-day virtual event on June 21, 2023, that will allow you to better understand […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating Netflix to GraphQL Safely]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8e1e4d4f1e72</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/migrating-netflix-to-graphql-safely-8e1e4d4f1e72?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T17:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jennifer Shin, Tejas Shikhare, Will Emmanuel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reconstructing indoor spaces with NeRF]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/reconstructing-indoor-spaces-with-nerf.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/reconstructing-indoor-spaces-with-nerf.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marcos Seefelder, Software Engineer, and Daniel Duckworth, Research Software Engineer, Google Research




When choosing a venue, we often find ourselves with questions like the following: Does this restaurant have the right vibe for a date? Is there good outdoor seating? Are there enough screens to watch the game? While photos and videos may partially answer questions like these, they are no substitute for feeling like you’re there, even when visiting in person isn't an option.



Immersive experiences that are interactive, photorealistic, and multi-dimensional stand to bridge this gap and recreate the feel and vibe of a space, empowering users to naturally and intuitively find the information they need. To help with this, Google Maps launched Immersive View, which uses advances in machin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第231話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361338687718</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361338687718"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[June patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67125</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/june-patches-for-azure-devops-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T22:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1
Azure DevOps Server 2022
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 Patch 1
The post June patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.11.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83469&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83469</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/camunda-optimize-3-11-alpha2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the latest release of Camunda Optimize. Optimize makes it possible to evaluate the success of your process automation initiative.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.11.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating Critical Traffic At Scale with No Downtime — Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4b1c8c7155c1</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/migrating-critical-traffic-at-scale-with-no-downtime-part-2-4b1c8c7155c1?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shyam Gala, Javier Fernandez-Ivern, Anup Rokkam Pratap, Devang Shah]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling delightful user experiences via predictive models of human attention]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/enabling-delightful-user-experiences.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/enabling-delightful-user-experiences.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:18:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Junfeng He, Senior Research Scientist, and Kai Kohlhoff, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research




People have the remarkable ability to take in a tremendous amount of information (estimated to be ~1010 bits/s entering the retina) and selectively attend to a few task-relevant and interesting regions for further processing (e.g., memory, comprehension, action). Modeling human attention (the result of which is often called a saliency model) has therefore been of interest across the fields of neuroscience, psychology, human-computer interaction (HCI) and computer vision. The ability to predict which regions are likely to attract attention has numerous important applications in areas like graphics, photography, image compression and processing, and the measurement of visual quali…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon S3 Dual-Layer Server-Side Encryption with Keys Stored in AWS Key Management Service (DSSE-KMS)]]></title>
        <id>39a5ab2cc8c64f5065441628593ff4c960f92836</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-s3-dual-layer-server-side-encryption-with-keys-stored-in-aws-key-management-service-dsse-kms/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are launching Amazon S3 dual-layer server-side encryption with keys stored in AWS Key Management Service (DSSE-KMS), a new encryption option in S3 that applies two layers of encryption to objects when they are uploaded to an S3 bucket. DSSE-KMS is designed to meet National Security Agency CNSSP 15 for FIPS compliance and Data-at-Rest Capability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at AWS re:Inforce: Zero trust security and secrets sync with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-re-inforce-zero-trust-security-and-secrets-sync</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-re-inforce-zero-trust-security-and-secrets-sync"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp is at AWS re:Inforce sharing expert talks, product demos, and several news announcements..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify How You Manage Authorization in Your Applications with Amazon Verified Permissions – Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>a981b6168d5668e3fdbb5ece89da38241976219a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-how-you-manage-authorization-in-your-applications-with-amazon-verified-permissions-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T16:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing a new application or integrating an existing one into a new environment, user authentication and authorization require significant effort to be correctly implemented. In the past, you would have built your own authentication system, but today you can use an external identity provider like Amazon Cognito. Yet, authorization logic is typically implemented in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Kerberos for Windows in Ansible Automation Platform 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/using-kerberos-for-windows-in-ansible-automation-platform-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/using-kerberos-for-windows-in-ansible-automation-platform-2"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kerberos is often the preferred authentication method for managing Windows servers in a domain environment. Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform has allowed customers to leverage Kerberos authentication for a number of years now. So why revisit this subject?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Vault Secrets public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-vault-secrets-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-vault-secrets-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Secrets is a new SaaS-based secrets management platform that enables developers to centrally store, access, and sync secrets when and where they need them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault Secrets Operator for Kubernetes now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-secrets-operator-for-kubernetes-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-secrets-operator-for-kubernetes-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vault Secrets Operator implements a first-class Kubernetes Operator for Vault, along with CRDs responsible for synchronizing Vault secrets to Kubernetes Secrets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Boundary session recording, self-managed Boundary Enterprise, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-13-introduces-ssh-session-recording-boundary-enterprise-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-0-13-introduces-ssh-session-recording-boundary-enterprise-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Additional new HashiCorp Boundary 0.13 capabilities include LDAP auth method, customer-specified HCP Boundary maintenance windows, and other improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Cloud capabilities to import, view, and manage infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-cloud-capabilities-to-import-view-and-manage-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-cloud-capabilities-to-import-view-and-manage-infrastructure"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds an explorer for workspace visibility and upcoming ephemeral workspaces, while bringing checks into continuous validation and config-driven import from Terraform 1.5.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Automate DLQ Redrive for SQS, Lambda Supports Ruby 3.2, and More – June 12, 2023]]></title>
        <id>47ede5cd57805e92230d6b074902e95e9f86e431</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-automate-dlq-redrive-for-sqs-lambda-supports-ruby-3-2-and-more-june-12-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I’m boarding a plane for Madrid. I will attend the AWS Summit Madrid this Thursday, and I will take Serverlesspresso with me. Serverlesspresso is a demo that we take to events, in where you can learn how to build event-driven architectures with serverless. If you are visiting an AWS Summit, most probably you will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Escrow Buddy: An open-source tool from Netflix for remediation of missing FileVault keys in MDM]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/815aef5107cd</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/escrow-buddy-an-open-source-tool-from-netflix-for-remediation-of-missing-filevault-keys-in-mdm-815aef5107cd?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix has open-sourced Escrow Buddy, which helps Security and IT teams ensure they have valid FileVault recovery keys for all their Macs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.5 brings config-driven import and checks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-5-brings-config-driven-import-and-checks</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-5-brings-config-driven-import-and-checks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform 1.5 is now generally available, featuring a config-driven import workflow and a new language primitive for infrastructure validations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Move Payment Processing to the Cloud with AWS Payment Cryptography]]></title>
        <id>c1170395355163b53838018742052c096320018c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-move-payment-processing-to-the-cloud-with-aws-payment-cryptography/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T15:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptography is everywhere in our daily lives. If you’re reading this blog, you’re using HTTPS, an extension of HTTP that uses encryption to secure communications. On AWS, multiple services and capabilities help you manage keys and encryption, such as: AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS), which you can use to create and protect keys to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey 2023: Maturity drives operational efficiency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-maturity-drives-operational-efficiency</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-maturity-drives-operational-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite macroeconomic pressure, cloud-mature companies — as measured by technological and operational best practices — boosted cloud investment and realized better business outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to Approvals and Checks]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67096</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/updates-to-approvals-and-checks/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T07:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approvals and Checks provide increased security to your YAML pipelines. They allow you to control if a pipeline run is allowed to access a resource.
The post Updates to Approvals and Checks appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silviu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep-Dive into the Architecture of Connectors]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=83340&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=83340</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/architecture-connectors/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T19:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this deep-dive into the architecture of Camunda Connectors. Learn about custom Connectors, Connector reusability, and more.
The post A Deep-Dive into the Architecture of Connectors appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagen Editor and EditBench: Advancing and evaluating text-guided image inpainting]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/imagen-editor-and-editbench-advancing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/imagen-editor-and-editbench-advancing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T19:09:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Su Wang and Ceslee Montgomery, Research Engineers, Google Research





In the last few years, text-to-image generation research has seen an explosion of breakthroughs (notably, Imagen, Parti, DALL-E 2, etc.) that have naturally permeated into related topics. In particular, text-guided image editing (TGIE) is a practical task that involves editing generated and photographed visuals rather than completely redoing them. Quick, automated, and controllable editing is a convenient solution when recreating visuals would be time-consuming or infeasible (e.g., tweaking objects in vacation photos or perfecting fine-grained details on a cute pup generated from scratch). Further, TGIE represents a substantial opportunity to improve training of foundational models themselves. Multimodal mode…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>