<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-27T00:18:04.933Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-27T00:18:04.933Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68362</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T18:26:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our fall update, we acknowledged the necessity to pause the rollout of New Boards Hub. Our focus was on enhancing its quality, performance, accessibility, and addressing an long list of bugs and issues. We’re pleased with the progress achieved in the past few months and want to highlight a few key points as we prepare to make New Boards Hub the default experience for our next group of customers.
The post New Boards Hub Update, January 2024 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New version of Publish Code Coverage Results task]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68323</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-pccr-task/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T11:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve introduced a new V2 version of the publish code coverage results task (known as PCCR) in Azure Pipelines recently. The main benefit of the V2 task is the support for more formats of the code coverage results and therefore more programming languages than the V1 task,
The post New version of Publish Code Coverage Results task appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bohdan Janousek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coercion]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44846</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/865951328/0/sethsblog~Coercion/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One way to look at power is “you get to tell people what to do.” But an alternative is that the most powerful institutions, brands and people are the ones who are in alignment with their audience. Trust and the benefit of the doubt are more powerful and resilient than command and control. It’s more […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.3.3 Is Out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=437465</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2024/01/webstorm-2023-3-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T08:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.3.3, the third update for WebStorm 2023.3, is now available! You can update to v2023.3.3 by using the Toolbox App, installing it right from the IDE, or downloading it from our website. Syntax highlighting for React Client and Server components We’re ready to release a feature a lot of you have been anticipating since […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know if all your repositories have up-to-date dependencies?]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-25-do-you-know-if-all-your-repositories-have-up-to-date-dependencies/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-25-do-you-know-if-all-your-repositories-have-up-to-date-dependencies/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T22:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Consider deploying the GitHub Action: Evergreen so that you know each of your repositories are leveraging active dependency management with Dependabot.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-25-do-you-know-if-all-your-repositories-have-up-to-date-dependencies/">Do you know if all your repositories have up-to-date dependencies?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.3.3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=436976</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/01/intellij-idea-2023-3-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T21:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released the third bug-fix update for v2023.3. You can update to this version from inside the IDE, using the Toolbox App, or using snaps if you are a Ubuntu user. You can also download it from our website. In this latest update, we’ve included a range of fixes and enhancements: For more information about the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Fund 2024 and beyond: Looking to the future]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-25-github-fund-2024-and-beyond-looking-to-the-future/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-25-github-fund-2024-and-beyond-looking-to-the-future/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T20:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Celebrate the first year of GitHub Fund, our first investments, and a brief look of where we’re going. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-25-github-fund-2024-and-beyond-looking-to-the-future/">GitHub Fund 2024 and beyond: Looking to the future</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Version of ServiceNow Terraform catalog enables custom workspace naming and tags]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-servicenow-terraform-catalog-custom-workspace-naming-tags</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-version-servicenow-terraform-catalog-custom-workspace-naming-tags"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new ServiceNow Service Catalog for Terraform version 2.4 allows you to customize workspace names and add tags to your Terraform workspaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Annotated – January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=437747</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2024/01/php-annotated-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T12:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the January edition of PHP Annotated! We’ll recap the most interesting developments in the PHP community over the past month, featuring handpicked news, articles, tools, and videos. Highlights PHP 8.2.15 and PHP 8.3.2 released 🐛 These are bug-fix updates. The PHP Foundation Team Update 2024 This year, four additional developers joined the PHP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A good idea, well executed]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48356</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/865600766/0/sethsblog~A-good-idea-well-executed/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T09:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why isn’t this enough? There are plenty of good ideas, easy to learn from and copy. There are countless projects, well executed, with the steps on display. Any entrepreneur could find a local business and bring a version of it from over here to over there. And a social change maker could find a successful […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring trainer extraordinairre Patrick Baumgartner]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/25/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-trainer-extraordinairre-patrick-baumgartner</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/25/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-trainer-extraordinairre-patrick-baumgartner"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic AI Assistant for Security and Amazon Bedrock can empower security analysts for enhanced performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-ai-assistant-amazon-bedrock-security-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-ai-assistant-amazon-bedrock-security-analysts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic AI Assistant for Security coupled with Anthropic’s Claude model via Amazon Bedrock can elevate a security team’s posture and eliminate mundane tasks....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy (Uday),James Spiteri,Ayan Ray, AWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic AI Assistant for Security and Amazon Bedrock can empower security analysts for enhanced performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-ai-assistant-amazon-bedrock-security-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-ai-assistant-amazon-bedrock-security-analysts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI and large language models (LLMs) are revolutionizing natural language processing (NLP), offering enhanced conversational AI experiences for customer service and boosting productivity. To meet enterprise needs, it’s important to ensure the responses that are generated are accurate as well as respect the permissions model associated with the underlying content. Retrieval augmented generation (RAG) emerges as a key technique, retrieving relevant information from enterprise knowledge bases. 

Enterprises are not only in pursuit of high-performance infrastructure but also a secure platform that unlocks the potential of generative AI without jeopardizing sensitive data and intellectual property. Large language models endeavor to comprehend and generate text that mirrors human langu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayasimha Theepireddy (Uday),James Spiteri,Ayan Ray, AWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub’s Developer Experience team improved innerloop development]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-24-how-githubs-developer-experience-team-improved-innerloop-development/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-24-how-githubs-developer-experience-team-improved-innerloop-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T23:21:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our latest solution to the ubiquitous engineering problem of integration testing in a distributed service ecosystem here at GitHub.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-24-how-githubs-developer-experience-team-improved-innerloop-development/">How GitHub’s Developer Experience team improved innerloop development</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Marketplace Highlights of 2023: Major Updates & Community News]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=436554</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2024/01/jetbrains-marketplace-highlights-of-2023-major-updates-community-news/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T15:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout 2023, the JetBrains Marketplace team invested serious effort in enhancing the capabilities of the platform for both plugin developers and users.  Our key areas of focus have been improving the platform’s compliance, enhancing plugin feedback capabilities, and building a strong community.  If you missed out on news throughout the year, don’t worry – here’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Kerpeleva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第245話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:10044607041234842720</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/10044607041234842720"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Refactorings in IntelliJ IDEA]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=436368</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2024/01/ai-refactorings-in-intellij-idea/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T13:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neat, efficient code is undoubtedly a cornerstone of successful software development. But the ability to refine code quickly is becoming increasingly vital as well.  Fortunately, the recently introduced AI Assistant from JetBrains can help you satisfy both of these demands. In this article, we’ll showcase how several easy AI actions and chat prompts can make […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Maryasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2024.1 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=437088</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/01/24/resharper-2024-1-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T13:12:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Early Access Program for ReSharper version 2024.1 has started! As the newest features start trickling into the preview builds, we’d like to give you an overview of the plans we have for the next major version of ReSharper. This roadmap is just a preliminary plan and may be adjusted depending on our priorities and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2024.1 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=437062</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/01/24/rider-2024-1-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T13:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Early Access Program for Rider version 2024.1 is already in progress, but that doesn’t mean it’s too late to give you a glimpse into the future of your favorite .NET IDE with an overview of our plans for the next major release.  This roadmap is just a preliminary plan and may be adjusted depending […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy: The Top Courses and Projects of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=436743</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2024/01/24/jetbrains-academy-the-top-courses-and-projects-of-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T11:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for inspiration for your next learning challenge? We’ve handpicked the most popular development technologies, courses, and projects that our learners devoted the most time to last year and decided to bring them all together in one place. At JetBrains Academy, we provide a flexible approach to project-based learning and host our courses and projects […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Regina Muradova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Direct questions worth answering]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46596</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/865095128/0/sethsblog~Direct-questions-worth-answering/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T09:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For everyone on the team… Do you care enough to do great work? Can we agree on what great work looks like? When the world changes, do we have a process to redefine great work? Do you have the tools you need to reach your goals? How could we create a system where great work […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building secure and resilient telco networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-secure-and-resilient-telecom-networks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-secure-and-resilient-telecom-networks"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using the NIST framework, ThoughtLab recently concluded a cybersecurity benchmark study that spanned across industries, including telecommunications. How well armed is the industry to protect critical...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Riya Juneja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do telco security teams need from a SIEM?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-do-telecom-security-teams-need-from-a-siem</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-do-telecom-security-teams-need-from-a-siem"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past couple of years, two things stood out for the telecom industry: 5G and cloud adoption. Put together, there is a need for a completely revamped approach to security. And the journey begins ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Riya Juneja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is support engineering the right fit for you?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-is-support-engineering-the-right-fit-for-you-</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-is-support-engineering-the-right-fit-for-you-"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We sat down with Kesia to learn more about the road that led to support engineering, along with four questions to ask yourself before diving into the field....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building secure and resilient telco networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-secure-and-resilient-telecom-networks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/building-secure-and-resilient-telecom-networks"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) framework, ThoughtLab concluded a cybersecurity benchmark study that spanned across industries, including telecommunications. There is an urgent call to action for organizations to think about and implement cybersecurity processes and technologies more strategically. The study shed some positive light for telecom companies as compared to peer industries. But, the MTTx (detect, respond, mitigate) and threat dwell time are high enough to raise serious concerns about how well armed the industry is to protect such critical network infrastructure.
[Download the cybersecurity benchmark study here]
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.

In this blog post, we may have used or referred to third party generative AI tools, which are owned and operated by their respective owners. Elastic does not have any control over the third party tools and we have no responsibility or liability for their content, operation or use, nor for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of such tools. Please exercise caution when using AI tools with personal, sensitive or confidential information. Any data you submit may be used for AI training or other purposes. There is no guarantee that information you provide will be kept secure or confidential. You should familiarize yourself with the privacy practices and terms of use of any generative AI tools prior to use.

Elastic, Elasticsearch, ESRE, Elasticsearch Relevance Engine and associated marks are trademarks, logos or registered trademarks of Elasticsearch N.V. in the United States and other countries. All other company and product names are trademarks, logos or registered trademarks of their respective owners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Riya Juneja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do telco security teams need from a SIEM?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-do-telecom-security-teams-need-from-a-siem</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/what-do-telecom-security-teams-need-from-a-siem"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2023, many of the major telecom companies in the United States were hit with a cyber attack that compromised the personal data of millions of customers. A leading telecom provider1 in the US cited a 13% jump in ransomware attacks in the past year. And in Europe, the latest cybersecurity report from European Union Agency for Cybersecurity (ENISA)2 states that telecommunications were the target for 26% of DDoS attacks, a fourfold increase from 2021 due to remote working.
So what has changed in the past couple of years? For the telecom industry in particular, two things stand out: 5G and cloud adoption. These technologies provide the backbone for various mission critical services in public safety, healthcare, and national security in addition to enabling connectivity for m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Riya Juneja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is support engineering the right fit for you?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-is-support-engineering-the-right-fit-for-you-</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-is-support-engineering-the-right-fit-for-you-"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kesia Milesi likes to joke that she was dragged into support engineering.
“In college, I didn’t even know support was an option. I thought I would end up working at a help desk or as a developer in a company,” Kesia shares. “My first exposure to support was actually as a trainee with IBM. They allocated me to this thing called ‘support’ and had me start debugging files.”
Despite her hesitancy at the jump, that trainee experience opened Kesia’s eyes to a new realm of possibilities — one that aligned perfectly with both her social disposition and love of solving problems. Fast forward 10 years, and Kesia is now thriving as a full-time support engineer with Elastic, the leading platform for search-powered solutions with a robust support department.
“I might have fallen into this field, but I …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Lindauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spelling]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2885/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2885/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/spelling.png" title="Any time I misspell a word it's just because I have too much integrity to copy answers from the dictionary." alt="Any time I misspell a word it's just because I have too much integrity to copy answers from the dictionary." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A guide to open source for the social sector]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-23-a-guide-to-open-source-for-the-social-sector/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-23-a-guide-to-open-source-for-the-social-sector/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T20:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Calling all nonprofits! Do you want to implement open source software but don’t know where to start? We’ve got good news; you can easily get started by consulting our new guide.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-23-a-guide-to-open-source-for-the-social-sector/">A guide to open source for the social sector</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, good DevEx increases productivity. Here is the data.]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-23-good-devex-increases-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-23-good-devex-increases-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore how DevEx boosts productivity and innovation according to new research.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-23-good-devex-increases-productivity/">Yes, good DevEx increases productivity. Here is the data.</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Communications hygiene (and the demise of texting)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48300</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/864694115/0/sethsblog~Communications-hygiene-and-the-demise-of-texting/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attention is scarce. Decisions are difficult. Searching takes effort. For thirty years, texting has been a powerful medium. It’s the thing that vibrates in our pocket. It promises something urgent, and a reply that’s demanded equally urgently. “I’m running ten minutes late,” is a fine text, and “okay” is a great response. Like all digital […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Commons 4.1.1 has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/23/spring-cloud-commons-4-1-1-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/23/spring-cloud-commons-4-1-1-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Maciaszek-Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Splunk customers face a choice for observability and modernization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-splunk-customers-face-a-choice-for-observability-and-modernization</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-splunk-customers-face-a-choice-for-observability-and-modernization"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluating Elastic capabilities vs. Splunk for observability? It's time to dump Splunk. Elastic offers a simpler, unified solution that positions companies for the future. Modern application and opera...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Blog - Elasticsearch, Kibana, and ELK Stack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.17 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-17-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-17-released"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Ruflin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Splunk customers face a choice for observability and modernization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-splunk-customers-face-a-choice-for-observability-and-modernization</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-splunk-customers-face-a-choice-for-observability-and-modernization"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Businesses everywhere are facing a challenging environment: increased cost pressures coupled with high volumes of data generated by complex, distributed, cloud-native environments. As a result, teams need smarter analytics, access, and retention across all their data — instantly and from anywhere — to resolve issues, make decisions, and ensure resiliency.
Many companies have adopted Splunk Enterprise and have a choice to make, since Splunk offers multiple solutions with Splunk Enterprise, Splunk Cloud, and Splunk Observability with different pricing models. Splunk was built as a logging platform with additional features added over time.
Elastic® offers a fast, simple solution that positions companies for the future. Modern application and operations teams are finding freedom, flexibility, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Blog - Elasticsearch, Kibana, and ELK Stack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.17 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-17-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-17-released"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.17.17 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.17 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
The 7.17.17 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security advisory for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Ruflin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image Filesystem: Configuring Kubernetes to store containers on a separate filesystem]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/01/23/kubernetes-separate-image-filesystem/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/01/23/kubernetes-separate-image-filesystem/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Kevin Hannon (Red Hat)
A common issue in running/operating Kubernetes clusters is running out of disk space.
When the node is provisioned, you should aim to have a good amount of storage space for your container images and running containers.
The container runtime usually writes to /var.
This can be located as a separate partition or on the root filesystem.
CRI-O, by default, writes its containers and images to /var/lib/containers, while containerd writes its containers and images to /var/lib/containerd.
In this blog post, we want to bring attention to ways that you can configure your container runtime to store its content separately from the default partition.
One area that needs more explaining is where/what Kubernetes is writing to disk.
Understanding Kubernetes disk usage
Kuber…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get in the flow while coding (and why it’s important)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-22-how-to-get-in-the-flow-while-coding-and-why-its-important/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-22-how-to-get-in-the-flow-while-coding-and-why-its-important/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T19:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore what flow state entails, its benefits, and three tips for reaching it the next time you code.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-22-how-to-get-in-the-flow-while-coding-and-why-its-important/">How to get in the flow while coding (and why it’s important)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Amazon ECS, RDS for MySQL, EMR Studio, AWS Community, and more — January 22, 2024]]></title>
        <id>b4a977dc5a5efd9f7b1f3fc77b19b96d7576caed</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-ecs-rds-for-mysql-emr-studio-aws-community-and-more-january-22-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T18:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As usual, a lot has happened in the Amazon Web Services (AWS) universe this past week. I’m also excited about all the AWS Community events and initiatives that are happening around the world. Let’s take a look together! Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention: Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 unexpected ways to use GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-22-10-unexpected-ways-to-use-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-22-10-unexpected-ways-to-use-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub Copilot is widely known for its code generation feature. Learn how the AI assistant’s abilities can extend beyond just code generation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-22-10-unexpected-ways-to-use-github-copilot/">10 unexpected ways to use GitHub Copilot</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Set of Bug-fixes for ReSharper and Rider 2023.3 Is Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=436478</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2024/01/22/2023-3-3-rsrp-rd/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper and Rider have just received their third set of bug-fix updates for the 2023.3 release! Let’s take a look at the most important issues that have been resolved in this update. ReSharper For the full list of resolved issues, please refer to our issue tracker. Rider For the full list of resolved issues, please […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Test Software Automatically with Selenium and Python]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=433123</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2024/01/22/learn-selenium/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T15:26:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🤖 Automation is in the air, and software testing is no exception! Learn how to make the jump from manual to automated tests with our new course, UI Test Automation with Selenium and Python. This course is fantastic for anyone interested in Quality Assurance (QA) testing and has some introductory Python knowledge. The course can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clara Maine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2024.1 Early Access Program Is Now Open]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=436206</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2024/01/phpstorm-2024-1-early-access-program-is-now-open/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T10:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re opening the Early Access Program (EAP) for the next version of PhpStorm! This EAP build brings support for PHPUnit 11, improvements for the Pest test framework, enhancements to code analysis features, and more. Feel free to give it a try, and remember to share your thoughts and feedback however is most convenient for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tania Goral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Mac Day (#40)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48342</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/864524366/0/sethsblog~Its-Mac-Day/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot shifted when the Apple Macintosh was introduced, and it wasn’t about the RAM, the chips or the processor speed. Our world changed forty years ago today. Marketing, technology, commerce, luxury brands, communities, communication and our expectations for how we might spend our future all shifted, and fairly quickly. Guy Kawasaki brought me one […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - January 23rd, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/22/this-week-in-spring-january-23rd-2024</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/22/this-week-in-spring-january-23rd-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 3.1.8 and 3.2.1 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/22/spring-shell-3-1-8-and-3-2-1-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/22/spring-shell-3-1-8-and-3-2-1-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-22233: Spring Framework server Web DoS Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/22/cve-2024-22233-spring-framework-server-web-dos-vulnerability</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/22/cve-2024-22233-spring-framework-server-web-dos-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transforming SAP observability: The Elastic-Kyndryl partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/sap-observability-elastic-kyndryl-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/sap-observability-elastic-kyndryl-partnership"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic-Kyndryl partnership offers a revolutionary solution for real-time SAP system monitoring. This innovative approach ensures comprehensive SAP observability, optimizing performance and promot...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesco Di Stefano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized with 2024 EMA Allstars award for its AI-assisted observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-2024-ema-allstars-award-ai-assisted-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-2024-ema-allstars-award-ai-assisted-observability"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability is recognized for not only breaking down data silos but allowing more effective analysis of system and app performance — on a platform that embraces open standards and a holistic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbots, AI, and human resources: A winning combination for telco and enterprise organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatbots-ai-human-resources-telco-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatbots-ai-human-resources-telco-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration of generative AI with Elastic Stack can transform the onboarding experience into something that is not just efficient, but also engaging and reassuring for new employees in telecommuni...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jürgen Obermann,Piotr Kobziakowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transforming SAP observability: The Elastic-Kyndryl partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/sap-observability-elastic-kyndryl-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/sap-observability-elastic-kyndryl-partnership"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Across industries and geographies, businesses rely heavily on Systems Applications and Products (SAP) systems. These powerful and versatile systems streamline operations and manage critical data spanning areas like finance, human resources, and supply chain. However, the real-time monitoring of these systems, with an in-depth understanding of performance metrics and quick anomaly detection, is paramount for smooth operations and business continuity. It's here that our unique offering steps in.

This blog post will take you on a journey through the joint solution crafted by Elastic® and Kyndryl that offers comprehensive SAP observability. We'll discuss how this offering brings business and operational value to enterprises running SAP systems.
The necessity of SAP observability
Understanding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesco Di Stefano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized with 2024 EMA Allstars award for its AI-assisted observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-2024-ema-allstars-award-ai-assisted-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-2024-ema-allstars-award-ai-assisted-observability"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to be recognized with the 2024 EMA Allstars award. This award acknowledges Elastic’s focus on delivering a full-stack observability solution that provides unified visibility and AI-powered insights into complex hybrid cloud deployments. 

The EMA Allstars award celebrates trailblazers and innovators who are reshaping the enterprise technology landscape. EMA lauds Elastic Observability for an approach that not only breaks down data silos but also facilitates a more effective analysis of system and application performance. This recognition underscores our role in pioneering solutions that will pave the way for future advancements in technology management and operational excellence.
The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbots, AI, and human resources: A winning combination for telco and enterprise organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatbots-ai-human-resources-telco-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatbots-ai-human-resources-telco-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's talk about something cool and game-changing in the world of big business HR: the awesome duo of generative AI and the Elastic Stack. Now, imagine your typical HR department in a large telecommunications company — they're juggling a million things, right? From answering endless employee queries to handling the nitty-gritty of data and reports, it can get pretty overwhelming, especially in industries like telecommunications with employees geographically dispersed and in a variety of roles in the field, in the office, and at home. But here's where our tech superheroes come into play.

Think of generative AI as that smart and savvy friend who knows just what to say and when to say it. This isn't your run-of-the-mill AI; we're talking about a system that can whip up responses, make predic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jürgen Obermann,Piotr Kobziakowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Log Alignment]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2884/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2884/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/log_alignment.png" title="A video can have a log scale that's misaligned with both the time AND space axes." alt="A video can have a log scale that's misaligned with both the time AND space axes." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stumbling in the dark]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46588</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/864412574/0/sethsblog~Stumbling-in-the-dark/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T09:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning is complicated. While we’re doing it, it’s easy to imagine that those around us are completely sure of themselves, moving forward in a well-lit space. In fact, if you visit a growing company, a useful school or anywhere that growth is happening, you’ll quickly see that everyone is stumbling forward in the shadows. That’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Out to get you]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46586</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/864298442/0/sethsblog~Out-to-get-you/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T09:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to believe that in some moments, the world is out to get you. This is unlikely. The world hardly knows you exist. There is injustice and trauma and systems of caste. There are tiny pockets of humanity that hold a grudge. But most of the time, in most situations, what happened happened and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final notice of alternate credentials deprecation]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68309</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/final-notice-of-alternate-credentials-deprecation/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2019, we announced that the alternate credentials feature will be formally deprecated in March 2020. Since then, a small number of users were grandfathered in with continued usage of existing alternate credentials, which have remained active until today.
The post Final notice of alternate credentials deprecation appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2024.1 Early Access Program Is Now Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=435842</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2024/01/webstorm-2024-1-eap1/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T18:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re ready to kick off WebStorm 2024.1 with a new Early Access Program (EAP). Please check out this blog post, where we explain the benefits of the program. If you haven’t already seen what to expect in WebStorm 2024.1, take a moment to explore our roadmap. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vladislav Minaev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Radar begins limited beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-radar-begins-limited-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-radar-begins-limited-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Radar is a new SaaS-based secrets discovery product that enables organizations to proactively remediate unmanaged or leaked secrets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoding ‘story’]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48327</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/864049769/0/sethsblog~Decoding-story/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T09:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marketers like to talk about the story we tell. And non-marketers imagine that we’re referring to Goldilocks and other ‘once upon a time’ moments. Because stories are the basic building block of culture, it’s difficult to see the nuance in this simple word. But one or two examples can help. A new saw might have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 1.0.5, 1.1.2 and 1.2 M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/19/spring-modulith-1-0-5-1-1-2-and-1-2-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/19/spring-modulith-1-0-5-1-1-2-and-1-2-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/19/spring-boot-3-2-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/19/spring-boot-3-2-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Frederick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.3.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/19/spring-boot-3-3-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/19/spring-boot-3-3-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Frederick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.3 Adds Passive JDK Serialization/Deserialization for Seamless Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/19/spring-security-6-3-adds-passive-jdk-serialization-deserialization-for</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/19/spring-security-6-3-adds-passive-jdk-serialization-deserialization-for"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcus Hert Da Coregio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.8 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/19/spring-boot-3-1-8-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2024/01/19/spring-boot-3-1-8-available-now"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moritz Halbritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronaut Guests]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2883/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2883/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/astronaut_guests.png" title="They didn't bring us a gift, but considering the kinetic energy of a bottle of wine at orbital speed, that's probably for the best." alt="They didn't bring us a gift, but considering the kinetic energy of a bottle of wine at orbital speed, that's probably for the best." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-18-game-bytes-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-18-game-bytes-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T21:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-18-game-bytes-january-2024/">Game Bytes · January 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insider newsletter digest: Build from anywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-18-insider-newsletter-digest-build-from-anywhere/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-18-insider-newsletter-digest-build-from-anywhere/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T17:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore the August 2023 edition, featuring easy tips and tricks for GitHub Mobile.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-18-insider-newsletter-digest-build-from-anywhere/">Insider newsletter digest: Build from anywhere</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Operator adds project support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-operator-adds-project-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-operator-adds-project-support"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Operator for Kubernetes adds more Day 2 operations.  Users can now streamline workspace management and enhance self-service capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New data and visualizations highlight the resilience of international developer collaboration]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-01-18-new-data-and-visualizations-highlight-the-resilience-of-international-developer-collaboration/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-01-18-new-data-and-visualizations-highlight-the-resilience-of-international-developer-collaboration/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T16:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover the latest trends and insights on public software development activity on GitHub with the release of Q3 2023 data for the Innovation Graph.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-01-18-new-data-and-visualizations-highlight-the-resilience-of-international-developer-collaboration/">New data and visualizations highlight the resilience of international developer collaboration</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I didn’t get in”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46580</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/863166617/0/sethsblog~I-didnt-get-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two ways to process this: The selection committee saw me, understood me, and then decided to reject me. or The selection committee didn’t get what I had to offer. I wasn’t rejected, my application was. It’s not that I didn’t get in, it’s that they didn’t engage with the story I told. We […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EMA explores Elastic AI Assistant for Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ema-explores-elastic-ai-assistant-for-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ema-explores-elastic-ai-assistant-for-security"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EMA’s recent publication focuses on the Elastic AI Assistant for Security and investigates the impact that the generative AI assistant will have on the security landscape. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa VanNice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EMA explores Elastic AI Assistant for Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ema-explores-elastic-ai-assistant-for-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ema-explores-elastic-ai-assistant-for-security"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security has been making waves among busy security analysts everywhere with the launch of Elastic AI Assistant. Whether it’s synthesizing alert details and suggesting next steps, or the recent addition from Elastic 8.11 to generate ES|QL queries from natural language, there’s a lot to love about Elastic AI Assistant for security efforts. The impact of this new capability has been cataloged in a recent impact brief from Enterprise Management Associates (EMA): AI at Your Fingertips: How Elastic AI Assistant Simplifies Cybersecurity. 
By EMA’s estimate, Elastic AI Assistant will reshape the security landscape. Highlights include: 

The unique advantage that the Elasticsearch Relevance EngineTM (ESRE) gives to the AI Assistant  

How the Assistant reduces the security learning curve by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa VanNice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.7 adds test mocking and config-driven remove]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-7-adds-test-mocking-and-config-driven-remove</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-7-adds-test-mocking-and-config-driven-remove"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now generally available, HashiCorp Terraform 1.7 adds mocking capabilities to the Terraform test framework and a config-driven state removal workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who pays?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=48270</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/862101713/0/sethsblog~Who-pays/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T10:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supply and demand are always in a dance, with one outpacing the other from time to time. In the last three years, the green tech revolution has accelerated dramatically. Countless companies are being created to change how food is grown, people are transported and energy is created. I’ve been stunned by the pace as well […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Net Rotations]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2882/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2882/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/net_rotations.png" title="For decades I've been working off the accumulated rotation from one long afternoon on a merry-go-round when I was eight." alt="For decades I've been working off the accumulated rotation from one long afternoon on a merry-go-round when I was eight." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server Product Lifecycle and Servicing]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=68265</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-product-lifecycle-and-servicing/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T18:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server follow the Microsoft Product Fixed Lifecycle Policy of 10 years. The first 5 years of Mainstream Support provide feature updates, platform updates, security updates, functionality fixes, and quality improvements. The second 5 years of Extended Support provide critical security updates only for the latest release of each version.
The post Azure DevOps Server Product Lifecycle and Servicing appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Supply Chain update: Three new modules supporting upstream activities]]></title>
        <id>a50b16008e5591a43629f34d718bd208efad92f5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-supply-chain-update-three-new-modules-supporting-upstream-activities/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T17:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are launching three new modules for AWS Supply Chain today. These modules are designed to help you collaborate with your suppliers across all tiers of your supply chain, with the goal of helping you to maintain optimum inventory levels at each site in the chain. Here’s an overview: Supply Planning – This module helps […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing HashiCorp Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/testing-hashicorp-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/testing-hashicorp-terraform"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn testing strategies for Terraform modules and configuration, and learn how to run tests against infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup—Amazon Route53, Amazon EventBridge, Amazon SageMaker, and more – January 15, 2024]]></title>
        <id>ad10cf5aba53456f1f1f76f47ca45b34047b64ff</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-route53-amazon-eventbridge-amazon-sagemaker-and-more-january-15-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T16:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are in January, the start of a new year, and I imagine many of you have made a new year resolution to learn something new. If you want to learn something new and get a free Amazon Web Services (AWS) Learning Badge, check out the new Events and Workflows Learning Path. This learning path […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on SIG Release (Release Team Subproject)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/01/15/sig-release-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/01/15/sig-release-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Nitish Kumar
The Release Special Interest Group (SIG Release), where Kubernetes sharpens its blade
with cutting-edge features and bug fixes every 4 months. Have you ever considered how such a big
project like Kubernetes manages its timeline so efficiently to release its new version, or how
the internal workings of the Release Team look like? If you're curious about these questions or
want to know more and get involved with the work SIG Release does, read on!
SIG Release plays a crucial role in the development and evolution of Kubernetes.
Its primary responsibility is to manage the release process of new versions of Kubernetes.
It operates on a regular release cycle, typically every three to four months.
During this cycle, the Kubernetes Release Team works closely with other SIGs an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMIE: A research AI system for diagnostic medical reasoning and conversations]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/01/amie-research-ai-system-for-diagnostic_12.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/01/amie-research-ai-system-for-diagnostic_12.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alan Karthikesalingam and Vivek Natarajan, Research Leads, Google Research




The physician-patient conversation is a cornerstone of medicine, in which skilled and intentional communication drives diagnosis, management, empathy and trust. AI systems capable of such diagnostic dialogues could increase availability, accessibility, quality and consistency of care by being useful conversational partners to clinicians and patients alike. But approximating clinicians’ considerable expertise is a significant challenge. 





Recent progress in large language models (LLMs) outside the medical domain has shown that they can plan, reason, and use relevant context to hold rich conversations. However, there are many aspects of good diagnostic dialogue that are unique to the medical domain. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can large language models identify and correct their mistakes?]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/01/can-large-language-models-identify-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/01/can-large-language-models-identify-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T22:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Gladys Tyen, Intern, Google Research




LLMs are increasingly popular for reasoning tasks, such as multi-turn QA, task completion, code generation, or mathematics. Yet much like people, they do not always solve problems correctly on the first try, especially on tasks for which they were not trained. Therefore, for such systems to be most useful, they should be able to 1) identify where their reasoning went wrong and 2) backtrack to find another solution.



This has led to a surge in methods related to self-correction, where an LLM is used to identify problems in its own output, and then produce improved results based on the feedback. Self-correction is generally thought of as a single process, but we decided to break it down into two components, mistake finding and output corre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon ECS supports a native integration with Amazon EBS volumes for data-intensive workloads]]></title>
        <id>aa651b9a68332fa0b11be808f87f4175a6e2ddba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ecs-supports-a-native-integration-with-amazon-ebs-volumes-for-data-intensive-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T22:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing that Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) supports an integration with Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS), making it easier to run a wider range of data processing workloads. You can provision Amazon EBS storage for your ECS tasks running on AWS Fargate and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) without […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf 2024 scholarship program now open for applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-2024-scholarship-program-now-open-for-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-2024-scholarship-program-now-open-for-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is your chance to apply for a scholarship to attend HashiConf in Boston, October 14-16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding Netflix Video Processing Pipeline with Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4e5e6310e359</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/rebuilding-netflix-video-processing-pipeline-with-microservices-4e5e6310e359?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T23:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first blog in a multi-part series on how Netflix rebuilt its video processing pipeline with microservices, so we can maintain…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDKTF 0.20 improves implementation of iterators and enables HCL output]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdktf-0-20-improves-implementation-of-iterators-and-enables-hcl-output</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdktf-0-20-improves-implementation-of-iterators-and-enables-hcl-output"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.20 improves the existing implementation of iterators, allowing developers to handle complex scenarios related to dynamic resource creation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad JWT auth with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-jwt-auth-with-github-actions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-jwt-auth-with-github-actions"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how JWT-based authentication works in HashiCorp Nomad using a custom GitHub Action as an example of machine-to-machine authentication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use the Backstage HCP Consul plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-use-the-backstage-hcp-consul-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-use-the-backstage-hcp-consul-plugin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating HCP Consul Central with Backstage can enhance your organization’s infrastructure-management capabilities. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: User Experience Team]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.research.google/2024/01/responsible-ai-at-google-research-user.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.research.google/2024/01/responsible-ai-at-google-research-user.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T22:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ayça Çakmakli, UX Lead, Google Research, Responsible AI and Human Centered Technology Team




Google’s Responsible AI User Experience (Responsible AI UX) team is a product-minded team embedded within Google Research. This unique positioning requires us to apply responsible AI development practices to our user-centered user experience (UX) design process. In this post, we describe the importance of UX design and responsible AI in product development, and share a few examples of how our team’s capabilities and cross-functional collaborations have led to responsible development across Google.



First, the UX part. We are a multi-disciplinary team of product design experts: designers, engineers, researchers, and strategists who manage the user-centered UX design process from early-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! AWS Weekly Roundup – January 8, 2024]]></title>
        <id>cfad3721391555e841453d11e345c33fc090054d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-new-year-aws-weekly-roundup-january-8-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T20:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! Cloud technologies, machine learning, and generative AI have become more accessible, impacting nearly every aspect of our lives. Amazon CTO Dr. Werner Vogels offers four tech predictions for 2024 and beyond: Generative AI becomes culturally aware FemTech finally takes off AI assistants redefine developer productivity Education evolves to match the speed of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Target CLI: The context switcher for HashiCorp tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/target-cli-the-context-switcher-for-hashicorp-tools</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/target-cli-the-context-switcher-for-hashicorp-tools"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing multiple clusters of HashiCorp tools can be complicated. Target CLI eases the burden by using context profiles to easily switch between different clusters and environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top PKI use cases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/top-pki-use-cases</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/top-pki-use-cases"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PKI provides a flexible and scalable identity-first security solution that aligns with zero trust and secures a wide variety of enterprise use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 year in review]]></title>
        <id>http://martin.kleppmann.com/2024/01/04/year-in-review.html</id>
        <link href="http://martin.kleppmann.com/2024/01/04/year-in-review.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot has happened in the last year, so I thought it would be good to write up a review. My biggest change in 2023 was that my wife and I had a baby! This has brought a mixture of joys and frustrations, but overall it has been very good....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Kleppmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds aggregated VCS reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-aggregated-vcs-reviews</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-aggregated-vcs-reviews"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline the verification process across multiple workspaces by aggregating status checks directed to external VCS providers and review changes that affect multiple workspaces on a single page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[年賀イラスト] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:14079602755593132482</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/14079602755593132482"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>