<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-04-05T01:26:58.568Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-05T01:26:58.568Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 4, 2022]]></title>
        <id>6e8469ff0f01ab8c8b1e0c9ad99babde49d94aea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-4-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T20:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Welcome to the April 4 edition of the AWS Week in Review. This week, alongside the main launches, I also captured a couple of new capabilities, such as a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A primer to understanding observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/primer-to-understanding-observability-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/primer-to-understanding-observability-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The one certainty you will find in IT, developer, and SRE roles is that things always change! One hot topic in DevOps communities is observability. A long word, you may be wondering what it really means and how you can add it to your skillset. Here’s a quick primer to get you going on your path to observability.
Where did the term “observability” come from?
The concept of observability dates back to the mid-20th century, where it was originally used in control theory to describe how the internal states of a system can be inferred from knowledge of the system’s external outputs. Rudolf E. Kalman, a Hungarian-American electrical engineer and mathematician, coined the term in the 1960s in several seminal papers around dynamical and observable systems. 
While the term is still used in the math…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Wen,Jamie Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A primer to understanding observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/primer-to-understanding-observability-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/primer-to-understanding-observability-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A long word, you may be wondering what it really means and how you can add it to your skill set. Here’s a quick primer to get you going on your path to observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Wen,Jamie Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63769</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-lean-product-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T18:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of our “DevOps Dojo: Lean Product” blog, we discussed the need to build foundational concepts of the product-centric model. This enables us to explore more advanced concepts in the lean product-centric model.
I: Intro of Lean Product in Orange Belt
The post DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 2 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proactively prevent secret leaks with GitHub Advanced Security secret scanning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-04-04-push-protection-github-advanced-security/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-04-04-push-protection-github-advanced-security/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T17:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations with GitHub Advanced Security can now proactively protect against secret leaks with secret scanning’s new push protection feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pathways Language Model (PaLM): Scaling to 540 Billion Parameters for Breakthrough Performance]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pathways-language-model-palm-scaling-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pathways-language-model-palm-scaling-to.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T16:01:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sharan Narang and Aakanksha Chowdhery, Software Engineers, Google Research 
In recent years, large neural networks trained for language understanding and generation have achieved impressive results across a wide range of tasks. GPT-3 first showed that large language models (LLMs) can be used for few-shot learning and can achieve impressive results without large-scale task-specific data collection or model parameter updating. More recent LLMs, such as GLaM, LaMDA, Gopher, and Megatron-Turing NLG, achieved state-of-the-art few-shot results on many tasks by scaling model size, using sparsely activated modules, and training on larger datasets from more diverse sources. Yet much work remains in understanding the capabilities that emerge with few-shot learning as we push the limits of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Kubernetes Secrets for Flux with HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/manage-kubernetes-secrets-for-flux-with-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/manage-kubernetes-secrets-for-flux-with-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure the Secrets Store CSI driver with HashiCorp Vault to securely inject secrets into Flux or other GitOps tools on Kubernetes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a “Camunda Champion?”]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=47278</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/what-is-a-camunda-champion/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curious about becoming a Camunda Champion? You can still apply by May 1. Read about Markus' experience in the Camunda Champion program.
The post What is a “Camunda Champion?” appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Stahl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The surprising thing about expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41800</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/689189584/0/sethsblog~The-surprising-thing-about-expectations/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T09:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you meet expectations, when you make a promise and keep it, when your quality is on spec—we say “of course.” On the other hand, if you relentlessly raise expectations, if you overpromise and add a bit of hype, you’re almost certain to fail to meet our dreams and hopes. At the same time, though, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build and lead a data-driven organization—and why it matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-and-lead-a-data-driven-organization-and-why-it-matters</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-and-lead-a-data-driven-organization-and-why-it-matters"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise tech board advisor Shelley Leibowitz on overcoming cultural challenges, moving to the cloud to show impact, and discovering the unexpected from data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Burrows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build and lead a data-driven organization—and why it matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-and-lead-a-data-driven-organization-and-why-it-matters</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-build-and-lead-a-data-driven-organization-and-why-it-matters"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Technology, it turns out, isn’t the biggest obstacle to becoming a data-driven organization. Nine in 10 executives say cultural impediments remain the greatest barriers to becoming data-driven, according to a 2022 survey by NewVantage Partners.
What should CIOs and IT decision makers do to lead their organizations forward? 
To answer that question, we interviewed Shelley Leibowitz, former CIO of the World Bank and Morgan Stanley, and a prominent technology advisor and board director who recently joined Elastic’s Board of Directors. Following are highlights of the conversation.
What sets apart data-driven companies? 
Data-driven companies have an agility that other companies don’t have. It is an awareness, an ability to understand and have intelligence into the key drivers, risks, and dep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Burrows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anytimed]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42635</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/689010222/0/sethsblog~Anytimed/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-03T12:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not a word, but perhaps it should be. If a competitor goes after your customers by offering them faster service, all day and all night, you’ve been anytimed. And if your boss, fearing that event, or simply trying to boost output for free, pushes you to be available all hours of the day and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catastrophization]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42627</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/688837180/0/sethsblog~Catastrophization/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-02T08:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life’s a tragedy. It always surprises us, and eventually, we all die. But tragedies don’t have to lead to catastrophes. A catastrophe is a shared emergency that overwhelms our interactions and narratives. Lately, they’ve become a business model and a never-ending part of our days. If we live in a world driven by attention, catastrophization […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.04]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63811</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-01-04/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T18:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s April in April! It’s no joke, the top stories from the #AzureDevOps #Community are back this week! We have been on a short hiatus in support of the people in Ukraine. We do hope that everyone out there is safe and healthy.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.01.04 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CVSS: A Massively Multilingual Speech-to-Speech Translation Corpus]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/introducing-cvss-massively-multilingual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/introducing-cvss-massively-multilingual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T16:06:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ye Jia and Michelle Tadmor Ramanovich, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Automatic translation of speech from one language to speech in another language, called speech-to-speech translation (S2ST), is important for breaking down the communication barriers between people speaking different languages. Conventionally, automatic S2ST systems are built with a cascade of automatic speech recognition (ASR), text-to-text machine translation (MT), and text-to-speech (TTS) synthesis sub-systems, so that the system overall is text-centric. Recently, work on S2ST that doesn’t rely on intermediate text representation is emerging, such as end-to-end direct S2ST (e.g., Translatotron) and cascade S2ST based on learned discrete representations of speech (e.g., Tjandra et al.). While early vers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat, Datadog, and More Partners Add Vault Ecosystem Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/red-hat-datadog-and-more-partners-add-vault-ecosystem-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/red-hat-datadog-and-more-partners-add-vault-ecosystem-integrations"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We welcome six new HCP Vault verified integrations from Datadog, Grafana Labs, Redis, Red Hat, Splunk, and Ui Path, plus four new self-managed HashiCorp Vault integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63764</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-lean-product-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T14:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being smart is about knowing what you want.
To become wise, you need to have models in your head. Models are formal structures represented in mathematics and diagrams that help us to understand the world.
The post DevOps Dojo: Lean Product – Part 1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.1 EAP 4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=237103</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/04/01/datagrip-2022-1-eap-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T13:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! A new EAP build for DataGrip 2022.1 is now available. [H2] Support for version 2.X We’ve added support for H2 version 2.X. Here’s the list of the most important changes: DataGrip now correctly introspects types. Most of the issues were related to the composite types ARRAY and ROW. Columns with built-in sequences (auto_increment, generated […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six ways to streamline development with Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-benefits-elastic-cloud-delivers-to-developers</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-benefits-elastic-cloud-delivers-to-developers"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quickly deploy Elastic Cloud to spin up instances for development, testing, and production — securely and at scale. Leverage cloud-native features and serverless integrations to accelerate results that matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six ways to streamline development with Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-benefits-elastic-cloud-delivers-to-developers</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-benefits-elastic-cloud-delivers-to-developers"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic helps developers enhance customer search experiences, keep mission-critical applications running smoothly, and protect against cyber threats. As many developers shift to the cloud for the speed, flexibility, and cost-efficiency, they can deploy Elastic in their preferred public cloud, or in multiple clouds, and extend the value of Elastic with cloud-native features. Spin up instances for development, testing, and production to accelerate results that matter — securely and at scale.
In this blog, we'll cover 6 ways Elastic Cloud delivers benefits to developers.
1. Get started quickly — it's easy
Don't waste time sourcing, configuring, and managing hardware and software packages. You can quickly deploy Elastic on your preferred cloud service provider — no waiting around! You can ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Elastic Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework RCE, Mitigation Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/01/spring-framework-rce-mitigation-alternative</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/04/01/spring-framework-rce-mitigation-alternative"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T11:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday we announced a Spring Framework RCE vulnerability CVE-2022-22965, listing Apache Tomcat as one of several preconditions. The Apache Tomcat team has since released versions 10.0.20, 9.0.62, and 8.5.78 all of which close the attack vector on Tomcat’s side. While the vulnerability is not in Tomcat itself, in real world situations, it is important to be able to choose among multiple upgrade paths that in turn provides flexibility and layered protection. 

Upgrading to Spring Framework 5.3.18+ or 5.2.20+ continues to be our main recommendation not only because it addresses the root cause and prevents other possible attack vectors, but also because it adds protection for other CVEs addressed since the current version in use. 

For older, unsupported versions of the Spring Framework, the Tomcat releases provide an adequate solution for the reported attack vector. Nevertheless, we must stress that this should only be seen as a tactical solution, while the main goal should still be to upgrade to a currently supported Spring Framework version as soon as possible.

Last but not least, it’s worth mentioning that downgrading to Java 8 provides another viable workaround, which may be another tactical solution option.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Not a heavy lift”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40832</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/688626980/0/sethsblog~Not-a-heavy-lift/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T09:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work with your hands and your back, avoiding a heavy lift is totally understandable. For many of us, though, we work with time or with trust. If someone asks you to endorse their new project, “it’ll only take a minute,” they’re offering to save you time, but at the risk of the trust […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Protects Against Ransomware and Linux Threats in MITRE Engenuity Round 4 Eval]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-protects-against-ransomware-and-linux-threats-in-mitre-engenuity-round-4-eval</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-protects-against-ransomware-and-linux-threats-in-mitre-engenuity-round-4-eval"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic participated in MITRE Engenuity Round 4 2022 Evaluation — the solution thrived due to its new ransomware protection, memory threat protection, and malicious behavior detection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ewing,James Spiteri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Protects Against Ransomware and Linux Threats in MITRE Engenuity Round 4 Eval]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-protects-against-ransomware-and-linux-threats-in-mitre-engenuity-round-4-eval</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-protects-against-ransomware-and-linux-threats-in-mitre-engenuity-round-4-eval"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Want to view the MITRE Engenuity ATT&CK® Eval Round 4 Kibana dashboard? Go here.
The latest MITRE Engenuity Evaluation, Wizard Spider and Sandworm

That’s right all, it’s time for the latest MITRE Engenuity ATT&CK® evaluation. As we have come to expect each year, Elastic — along with other security vendors — are evaluated by MITRE Engenuity, a tech foundation that brings MITRE research to the public. The evaluation focuses on emulating techniques from the MITRE ATT&CK (Adversarial Tactics, Techniques, and Common Knowledge) framework to assess vendor protection capabilities.

Each year, MITRE Engenuity focuses on a new attacker emulation. We have seen living-off-the-land techniques and, most recently, the targeting of Linux systems. But this year brings data impact to the forefront. The r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ewing,James Spiteri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Steps for automating Elastic workload migration from on-prem to Elastic on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/10-steps-for-automating-elastic-workload-migration-from-on-prem-to-elastic-on-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/10-steps-for-automating-elastic-workload-migration-from-on-prem-to-elastic-on-aws"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline your Elastic on-premises migration to AWS with a proven methodology and simple steps to success. Take advantage of everything that the cloud has to offer — scalability, affordability, and simplicity with Elastic on AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uday Theepireddy,Battulga Purevragchaa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Steps for automating Elastic workload migration from on-prem to Elastic on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/10-steps-for-automating-elastic-workload-migration-from-on-prem-to-elastic-on-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/10-steps-for-automating-elastic-workload-migration-from-on-prem-to-elastic-on-aws"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Are you ready to migrate your self-managed Elastic workloads to Elastic on Amazon Web Services (AWS) to leverage cost, time and scale efficiencies? Take advantage of the best practices and tools we developed with AWS to ensure your fast and smooth transition. Let’s run through your self-service migration path options, then go over the simple “how-to” steps to automate your migration.
Choose your path 
The three main options to add your on-premises data sets to Elastic in your AWS environment are data re-ingestion, snapshot and restore, and reindexing from a cluster.
1. If your data source (applications, databases and infrastructure) is also going to be migrated to AWS, then the data can then be re-ingested into Elastic from your source. Elastic provides integrations with popular AWS serv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uday Theepireddy,Battulga Purevragchaa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instructions]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2601/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2601/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/instructions.png" title="Happy little turtles" alt="Happy little turtles" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.1 Goes Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=237005</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/03/clion-2022-1-goes-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T19:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Beta version of CLion 2022.1 is now available. Build 221.5080.93 is available for download from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package (for Ubuntu). No license is required, as this build is still free to use. DOWNLOAD CLION 2022.1 BETA Here are the main highlights: C++23: Added support for uz […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic approaches accessibility in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-elastic-approaches-accessibility-in-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-elastic-approaches-accessibility-in-kibana"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T18:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When was the last time you visited a website and got frustrated because you had trouble using it? Maybe the site was using WebGL technology that your browser didn’t support, you couldn’t read its text due to it being so small. If you think back to these annoying experiences where you functionally could not navigate a site, chances are you’ve experienced inaccessibility in one form or another.

This is not to say that all frustrating experiences are inaccessible, but there are definitely overlaps between bad UX and inaccessibility.
Specifically, it focuses on people who have disabilities that impede their vision, hearing, and movement. Web accessibility means that websites, tools, and technologies are designed and developed so that people with disabilities can use them. More specifically, p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rashmi Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic approaches accessibility in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-elastic-approaches-accessibility-in-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-elastic-approaches-accessibility-in-kibana"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T18:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Rashmi Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Provider Support Comes to the Terraform Private Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/provider-support-comes-to-the-terraform-private-registry</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/provider-support-comes-to-the-terraform-private-registry"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now publish and distribute providers from the private registry in Terraform Cloud and Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub does take home technical interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-31-how-github-does-take-home-technical-interviews/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-31-how-github-does-take-home-technical-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T17:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We believe our technical interviews should be as similar as possible to the way we work at GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Kubernetes cofounder and vice president of R&D at VMware, Craig McLuckie]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/31/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-cofounder-and-vice-president-of-r-d-at-vmware-craig-mcluckie</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/31/a-bootiful-podcast-kubernetes-cofounder-and-vice-president-of-r-d-at-vmware-craig-mcluckie"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of a Bootiful Podcast! In this episode, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Kubernetes cofounder, all-around nice person, and vice president of R&D at VMware, Craig McLuckie (@cmcluck).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Integration and Support for All Kinds of Multiplatform Projects in the Kotlin Multiplatform Mobile Plugin for AppCode]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=236898</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/03/appcode-kmm-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T15:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin Multiplatform Mobile plugin for AppCode just got a huge update. We’ve got some exciting news to share with you! Support for All Kinds of Multiplatform Projects For a long time, the only supported project model in our plugin was the Gradle DSL with a special iOS/macOS part. Now we support opening Kotlin Multiplatform Mobile […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanislav Dombrovsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EduTools Plugin 2022.3 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=236421</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/03/31/edutools-plugin-2022-3-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T14:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2022.3 of EduTools has arrived. With this release we’ve focused on the overall quality of the plugin and fixed many bugs. Read on to learn about the most notable fixes and improvements. INSTALL EDUTOOLS PLUGIN For JetBrains Academy learners EDU-4759: You will no longer receive HTML-encoded feedback messages when solving tasks in your IDE. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/31/spring-boot-2-6-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/31/spring-boot-2-6-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T14:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.6 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

The Spring Framework version in this release includes a fix for CVE-2022-22965, check the dedicated blog post for more details.

This release includes 6 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.12 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/31/spring-boot-2-5-12-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/31/spring-boot-2-5-12-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T13:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.12 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

The Spring Framework version in this release includes a fix for CVE-2022-22965, check the dedicated blog post for more details.

This release includes 5 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to be an ally to your transgender co-workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-to-be-an-ally-to-your-transgender-co-workers</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-to-be-an-ally-to-your-transgender-co-workers"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[International Day of Transgender Visibility is celebrated on March 31st as a way to celebrate transgender and non-binary people and raise awareness of the challenges they face. Learn how to become an ally and start your own allyship journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to be an ally to your transgender co-workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-to-be-an-ally-to-your-transgender-co-workers</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-to-be-an-ally-to-your-transgender-co-workers"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
International Day of Transgender Visibility is celebrated on March 31st as a way to celebrate transgender and non-binary people and raise awareness of the challenges they face. This extends to the workplace. 
More than half of transgender employees say they are not comfortable being out at work, according to a recent McKinsey report. People who identify as transgender feel far less supported in the workplace than their cisgender colleagues do. They report that it’s more difficult to understand workplace culture and benefits, and harder to get promoted. They also feel less supported by their managers.
Here at Elastic, our source code encourages people to come as they are to build a culture of support. A culture that allows people to be who they are, proudly. That includes being an ally.
W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1 Beta 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=236953</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/03/webstorm-2022-1-beta-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T11:46:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.1 Beta 2 is now available! You can upgrade to the latest build using the Toolbox App or from our website. DOWNLOAD WEBSTORM 2022.1 BETA We are now in the process of fine-tuning the build for the upcoming release candidate. For the list of improvements available in WebStorm 2022.1 Beta 2, check out the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Aganezova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework RCE, Early Announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/31/spring-framework-rce-early-announcement</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/31/spring-framework-rce-early-announcement"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T10:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates 


  
[04-04 10:45 BST] Updated Am I Impacted with improved description for deployment requirements

  
[04-01 16:35 BST] Updated Am I Impacted with additional notes

  
[04-01 13:05 BST] Updated Suggested Workarounds section for Apache Tomcat upgrades and Java 8 downgrades

  
[04-01 12:51 BST] Apache Tomcat releases versions 10.0.20, 9.0.62, and 8.5.78 which close the attack vector on Tomcat’s side, see mitigation alternative

  
[03-31 15:40 BST] Spring Boot 2.6.6 is available

  
[03-31 14:38 BST] Spring Boot 2.5.12 is available

  
[03-31 14:00 BST] CVE-2022-22965 is published

  
[03-31 13:03 BST] Added section “Misconceptions”

  
[03-31 12:34 BST] Added section “Am I Impacted”

  
[03-31 12:11 BST] Fix minor issue in the workaround for adding disallowedFields

 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in Datalore: Enterprise Release, Statistics Tab, Interactive Reports, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=236173</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2022/03/31/new-in-datalore-enterprise-release-statistics-tab-interactive-reports-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T09:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Community, Professional, and Enterprise plan users, In the past months, we’ve been working hard on improving the data exploration and collaboration workflows in Datalore. In this blog post, we’ll give you an overview of what’s new! Before we start, we have a quick question, is there anyone here from Berlin? On April 11th, our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Datalore Enterprise 2022.1: Statistics Tab, Interactive Reports Upgrade, CSV File Editing, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=235913</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2022/03/31/introducing-datalore-enterprise-2022-1-statistics-tab-interactive-reports-upgrade-csv-file-editing-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T09:26:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, Back in November 2021, we introduced two major features to Datalore Enterprise: interactive reports for sharing data insights and the Visualize tab for faster data exploration. In Datalore Enterprise 2022.1, we’ve made improvements to these two workflows, and more. Read on to learn what else is new! Interactive reports upgrade Introducing Reactive mode to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 Beta 2 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=236416</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/03/intellij-idea-2022-1-beta-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T08:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 Beta 2 is here.  You can download the new build from our website. You can also get it via the free Toolbox App or by using snaps for Ubuntu.  IntelliJ IDEA 2022.1 Beta 2 includes some changes and improvements that we haven’t yet covered in our previous EAP blog posts. Read on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The physical therapy metaphor]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42578</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/688385702/0/sethsblog~The-physical-therapy-metaphor/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many ailments, physical therapy shows some of the best results. We can learn a lot from this for our own projects, organizations and narratives. Physical therapy often works better than pills or surgery. Here’s why: –it’s self-produced. Even though we work with a professional, it’s done BY us, not TO us. –it’s gradual. No […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Brave, Bold, and Boring YugabyteDB]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/31/spring-tips-brave-bold-and-boring-yugabytedb</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/31/spring-tips-brave-bold-and-boring-yugabytedb"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment we dare to be boring with YugabyteDB, a distributed database that just works. It’s a database that feels like PostgreSQL but scales like Apache Cassandra.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to automate verification of deployments with Argo Rollouts and Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/automate-verification-of-deployments-with-argo-rollouts-and-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/automate-verification-of-deployments-with-argo-rollouts-and-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post was written by Daniel Hoang, developer advocate from Akuity.
Shipping complex applications at high velocity lead to increased failures. Longer pipelines, scattered microservices, and more code inherently lead to bigger complexity where small mistakes may cost you big time.
We can’t promise that this blog post will help you get rid of failed deployments, however, we can promise that automated verification of deployments using Argo Rollouts and Elastic Observability will minimize damage, and help you feel more confident when shipping complex applications to Kubernetes.
What is Argo?
Argo is a collection of open-source tools for Kubernetes to run workflows, manage clusters, and do GitOps right. It’s also an open-source project that saw an incredible 115% year-on-year increase i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ricardo Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to automate verification of deployments with Argo Rollouts and Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/automate-verification-of-deployments-with-argo-rollouts-and-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/automate-verification-of-deployments-with-argo-rollouts-and-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deployment strategies like blue-green and canary allow building and shipping your software releases with control. But this doesn't mean that you are error-free. But you can minimize the damage by integrating Argos Rollout and Elastic Observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ricardo Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.17.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.2 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
This version also contains fixes to the Upgrade Assistant for 7.17 to 8.x upgrades in the presence of deprecated settings:
Investigate severity of upgrading to 8.0.1 despite terminal deprecation of old features
Add deprecation logging as step on overview page
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
7.17.2 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.1.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.1.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
This release fixes three notable issues in our Observability and Security solutions:
a bug where the APM Server would run out of memory due to lock contention under specific circumstances and when under heavy load. Users running APM Server versions 8.0.1 up to 8.1.1 are advised to upgrade immediately;
a bug that prevents Real User Monitoring data from showing up in the APM UI when capturing personal data is disabled. Users running APM Server versions 8.0.0 and above are advised to upgrade.
an issue affected the responsiveness and page load times of the Elastic Security application. Users may have noticed that the application becomes unresponsive on most pages. This affects version 8.1.0. The issue was addressed with a code change.
This 8.1.2 patch release contains other fixes and small enhancements for the stack. For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
8.1.2 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Duarte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.2 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Logstash, Beats, APM, Enterprise Search, Elastic Security, and ECK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.1.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-1-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.1.2 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Logstash, Beats, APM, Enterprise Search, Elastic Security, and ECK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Duarte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper and .NET Tools 2021.3.4 has been released!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=235201</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/03/30/resharper-2021-3-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T18:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone!  Today we’ve released ReSharper and .NET Tools 2021.3.4.  If you are using ReSharper or our .NET tools with Visual Studio 2022 version 17.2 Preview 2.0, you may have experienced issues with the integration. This is because of breaking changes to the Visual Studio API, which we relied on. The 2021.3.4 release fixes the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Kurakin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BeamSearch in code generation]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=236615</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/blog/2022/03/30/beamsearch-in-code-generation/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T17:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous article devoted to full-line code completion, we looked into the vocabulary that the neural net of our full line completion plugin uses for Python. However, just having 16384 tokens like self., or, s.append(, return value, and others described in the article is not enough to generate even a single line. We need […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Poborchiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.10 Adds Multi-Stack Deployments and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-10-adds-multi-stack-deployments-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-10-adds-multi-stack-deployments-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform 0.10 (CDKTF) enables multi-stack deployments and improves the CLI experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring an AWS dynamic inventory with Automation controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/configuring-an-aws-dynamic-inventory-with-automation-controller</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/configuring-an-aws-dynamic-inventory-with-automation-controller"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the core components of Ansible is inventories. In its most basic form, an inventory provides host information to Ansible so it can trigger the tasks on the right host or system. In most environments, the static inventory is sufficient for the Ansible control node to work from, however as we expand our use of automation, we need to transition to more effective methods of gathering ever-changing environment details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Test Practices For Helm Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=46451</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/test/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into the detailed learnings and experiences from our journey to find a sufficient way to write automated tests for Helm charts.
The post Advanced Test Practices For Helm Charts appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Zell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guest Post: 5 Things You Should Know Before Coding an IntelliJ Platform Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=231875</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2022/03/5-things-you-should-know-before-coding-an-intellij-platform-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T12:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a guest blog post by Jules Faucherre, Software Engineer at Ponicode. Hello, my name is Jules. I am a software engineer at Ponicode, a startup company dedicated to making code quality even more accessible than ever. One of my latest projects was to manage the development and deployment of our first plugin for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Chrzanowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Cloud NGFW for AWS]]></title>
        <id>5419ef265e15cd23d7d20fc3aafb456bd449eedb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-cloud-ngfw-for-aws/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T12:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2018 I wrote about AWS Firewall Manager (Central Management for Your Web Application Portfolio) and showed you how you could host multiple applications, perhaps spanning multiple AWS accounts and regions, while maintaining centralized control over your organization’s security settings and profile. In the same way that Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS) supports multiple database […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing new ideas]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42589</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/688216016/0/sethsblog~Testing-new-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T08:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What would a focus group have said about the title of Harper Lee’s To Kill a Mockingbird? Is it easy to understand, did you know what it’s about before you pick up the book? What about the consumer testing on a name like Nike or Starbucks? Some objective measures of new names and concepts are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Azure 4.0 is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/30/spring-cloud-azure-4-0-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/30/spring-cloud-azure-4-0-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NOTE: Hi, Spring fans! This is a guest post from Sean Li, our friend at Microsoft

I am pleased to announce that Spring Cloud Azure 4.0 is now generally available. With this major release we aim to bring better security, leaner dependencies, support for production readiness and more. Version 4 represents a significant milestone in our product roadmap that we couldn’t have delivered without the collective wisdom of the Spring community and customer feedback. On behalf of the Spring on Azure product team, thank you for making this happen!
Unified Development Experience

At the Developer Division of Microsoft, we are big on developer experience. We constantly challenge ourselves on how we can make things more consistent and easier to understand, so our customers are not confronted with haph…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE report published for Spring Cloud Function]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/29/cve-report-published-for-spring-cloud-function</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/29/cve-report-published-for-spring-cloud-function"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T00:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Spring Cloud Function 3.1.7 & 3.2.3 to address the following CVE report.


  
CVE-2022-22963: Remote code execution in Spring Cloud Function by malicious Spring Expression


Please review the information in the CVE report and upgrade immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rejected Question Categories]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2600/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2600/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/rejected_question_categories.png" title="You can click to preorder to get a copy of What If? 2 when it comes out 9/13, assuming we all make it past the spider situation(?) on Tuesday(?)." alt="You can click to preorder to get a copy of What If? 2 when it comes out 9/13, assuming we all make it past the spider situation(?) on Tuesday(?)." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Simplifies Reusable Variable Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-simplifies-reusable-variable-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-simplifies-reusable-variable-management"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud variable sets let you simplify the management of reusable variables across an entire organization — the feature is now generally available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot now available for Visual Studio 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-29-github-copilot-now-available-for-visual-studio-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-29-github-copilot-now-available-for-visual-studio-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T16:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot is now available from Visual Studio 2022 for everyone in the technical preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Documents 2.0: Upload Any File, Manage and Automate Everything Centrally]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=236420</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2022/03/29/new-documents-upload-preview-share-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T15:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Space Documents got a bit of an overhaul, and we hope you’ll enjoy a new, cleaner workflow. In short, you can now upload, preview, and share all kinds of files in Documents. Thanks to the new unified UI experience, managing files has never been easier. And finally, API automation is available for everyone! Let’s explore […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilia Afanasiev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New and Updated Vault Tutorials for 1.10 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-and-updated-vault-tutorials-for-1-10-release</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-and-updated-vault-tutorials-for-1-10-release"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try out the new and enhanced features introduced in Vault 1.10 with step-by-step tutorials on HashiCorp Learn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Career tips for beginner developers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-29-career-tips-for-beginner-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-29-career-tips-for-beginner-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T10:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advice on fundamentals, picking languages to learn, social media presence, interviewing, and more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hospitality systems gap]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42503</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/688072492/0/sethsblog~The-hospitality-systems-gap/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T08:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the variance in customer service at your organization? Even if there’s just one employee, the question is: If an issue is handled by a committed employee having a good attitude, vs a cranky one who is a bit off–can the customer tell? One philosophy is to make this gap as small as possible. Create […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - March 29th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/29/this-week-in-spring-march-29th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/29/this-week-in-spring-march-29th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, Spring fans, from beautiful Maui, Hawaii, where I am with my family on a bit of vacation. It’s our daughter’s Spring break and so we’re enjoying the family time while we can get it! I wanted to take a brief interlude in between the never-enough time on the beach and all the rum to get this week’s installment out for y’all, so let’s dive right into it! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Event streaming guru Jan Svoboda on Apache Kafka Design Patterns

  
An update on Java 17 adoption

  
Build To Manage: Proper Exception Handling Makes Your Applications Easier to Build and Manage

  
CVE report published for Spring Framework

  
Getting Started with Spring WebFlux

  
Initial AOT support in Spring Framework 6.0.0-M3

  
Java 18 is out! Get the bits while they’re hot! Or at least get Java 17. Wouldn’t want to be two major versions behind, would ya?

  
Java Records tortured with Lombok yet again (builder edition)

  
Want an industrial grade Kubernetes distribution? Check out this blog on how to run Tanzu Application Platform locally on your laptop 

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.2.3 available now

  
Spring Batch 5.0 M2 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.5.11 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.6.5 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.7.0-M3 available now

  
Spring Boot 3.0.0-M2 available now

  
Spring Security 6.0.0-M3 and 5.7.0-M3 available now

  
Spring Security and Thymeleaf - a great post over on the Okta blog

  
In this installment of Spring Tips , I look at: Multitenant JDBC: enjoy!

  
Spring for GraphQL 1.0 Milestone 6 Released

  
The Spring for GraphQL Team  is now on Twitter! AND they took the occasion recently to announce that there will soon be Spring GraphQL on RSocket support available! Huzzah!

  
I dig this: kagkarlsson/db-scheduler is a persistent cluster-friendly scheduler for Java

  
and this: digitalfondue/npjt-extra: A small layer over Spring’s NamedParameterJdbcTemplate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“New Boards Hub” Public Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63721</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T19:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December we posted about the “New Boards Hub” being available for everyone as an opt-in experience. We got a lot of feedback from our users. You let us know the experience was far from ready. As a result, we buckled down and spent the last 3 months fixing bugs (over 300) and tightening it up.
The post “New Boards Hub” Public Preview appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 28, 2022]]></title>
        <id>36fca099d51da2eb5217d3b6cd96385675ea994c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-28-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T19:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Welcome to another round up of the most significant AWS launches from the previous week. Among the most relevant news, we have improvements done in AWS Lambda, a new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to secure your end-to-end supply chain on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-28-how-to-secure-your-end-to-end-supply-chain-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-28-how-to-secure-your-end-to-end-supply-chain-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securing your projects is no easy task, but end-to-end supply chain security is more top of mind than ever. We&#8217;ve seen bad actors expand their focus to taking over user accounts, commonly used dependencies, and also build systems. Defending against these attacks is hard, because there&#8217;s no one thing you can do to protect your [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the newest features in the Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for ServiceNow ITSM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-the-newest-features-in-the-red-hat-ansible-certified-content-collection-for-servicenow-itsm</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/inside-the-newest-features-in-the-red-hat-ansible-certified-content-collection-for-servicenow-itsm"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for ServiceNow helps you create automated workflows targeting IT service management (ITSM) tasks faster while establishing and maintaining a single source of truth in the ServiceNow configuration management database (CMDB). In this blog, I’ll share the latest features we’ve added to the Collection, and you can find additional resources about existing features at the end of this blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Four HashiCorp Women Got Into Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-women-leaders-got-into-tech</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-women-leaders-got-into-tech"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four women at HashiCorp talk about their journey to a career in tech and offer lessons, inspiration, and advice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An update on Java 17+ adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/28/an-update-on-java-17-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/28/an-update-on-java-17-adoption"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T14:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a follow-up to my blog post from last year’s SpringOne, it is time for an update on our Java 17+ baseline efforts!

We established the new baseline on our main branches, with a few milestones out already. The feedback has been very positive, not only in terms of framework improvements but also in terms of the motivation for a Java upgrade at the application level. Of course, it does not end with JDK 17 LTS: JDK 18 is an immediate option already, JDK 19 will be the current release when we go final later this year, with JDK 20 to be in early access by then - and JDK 21 LTS on the horizon already…

On a related note, the recent JRebel 2022 Java Developer Productivity Report included some interesting numbers on JDK 17: 62% of the participants indicated a plan for a JDK 17 upgrade within t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Domain Name for Camunda Artifactory]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=46342</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/a-new-domain-name-for-camunda-artifactory/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make sure to switch to the new domain between April 1 - Sept. 30, 2022, before the old URLs will be shut down. 
The post A New Domain Name for Camunda Artifactory appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaima Mansouri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-calibrating]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41688</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687915014/0/sethsblog~Recalibrating/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T08:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When an entrepreneur gets funded, it’s often difficult for them to start spending money on assets–the old limits fade slowly. What used to be smart is now dumb. What used to too risky is now the safe thing to do. When someone gets older or is injured, one of the dangers is that they’ll fail […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE report published for Spring Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/28/cve-report-published-for-spring-framework</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/28/cve-report-published-for-spring-framework"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Spring Framework 5.3.17 to address the following CVE report.


  
CVE-2022-22950: Spring Expression DoS Vulnerability


Please review the information in the CVE report and upgrade immediately.

Spring Boot users should upgrade to 2.5.11 or 2.6.5.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spacecraft Debris Odds Ratio]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2599/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2599/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/spacecraft_debris_odds_ratio.png" title="You say this daily walk will reduce my risk of death from cardiovascular disease by 30%, but also increase my risk of death by bear attack by 300%? That's a 280% increased! I'm not a sucker; I'm staying inside." alt="You say this daily walk will reduce my risk of death from cardiovascular disease by 30%, but also increase my risk of death by bear attack by 300%? That's a 280% increased! I'm not a sucker; I'm staying inside." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speeding up for the red light]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41683</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687775406/0/sethsblog~Speeding-up-for-the-red-light/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-27T08:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad drivers do this often, everywhere I’ve ever been in the world. Instead of gracefully and safely slowing for a light they know will be red by the time they get there, or even a stop sign, they hit the gas and then slam the brakes. One big reason is that the certainty of on-then-off […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expertise vs Attitude]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40748</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/687666300/0/sethsblog~Expertise-vs-Attitude/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-26T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The typical online job site lists millions of jobs. And just about every one of them is a cry for expertise. From the title to the requirements, companies hire for expertise. Logic helps us understand that only one out of ten people are in the top 10% when it comes to expertise. And that means […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock all the GitHub secrets within .Tech Domains newest experience: Break The Code 2!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-25-unlock-github-secrets-next-techs-break-the-code-2/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-25-unlock-github-secrets-next-techs-break-the-code-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T18:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Education is fired up for the return of .Tech Domains developer community competition: Break The Code 2. We've hacked in some new enigmas, cheat codes, and easter eggs for digital sleuths to uncover!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: The One Where You Completely Delete a Process Definition]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=46316</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/qa-the-one-where-you-completely-delete-a-process-definition/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a process definition cluttering up your deployment? Learn how to delete it once you no longer want to run it anymore. 
The post Q&A: The One Where You Completely Delete a Process Definition appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Event streaming guru Jan Svoboda on Apache Kafka Design Patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/a-bootiful-podcast-event-streaming-guru-jan-svoboda-on-apache-kafka-design-patterns</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/a-bootiful-podcast-event-streaming-guru-jan-svoboda-on-apache-kafka-design-patterns"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to event streaming guru at Confluent, the company behind Apache Kafka, Jan Svoboda about Apache Kafka design patterns. 


  
Kafka summit in London Europe end of April 2022 Kafka Summit London 2022 | April 25-26 | London, UK

  
the Confluent Developer Education Portal: Your Apache Kafka® Journey begins here

  
check out the upcoming Kafka Summit London event April 25-26, 2022]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-3-0-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-3-0-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-M2 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 50 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Reinstated Support for EhCache 3

  
Reinstated Support for H2 Console

  
Improved @ConstructorBinding Detection


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.0-M3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-7-0-m3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-7-0-m3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.0-M3 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes over 90 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Notable new features include:


  
Support for generating Docker images with Podman

  
Improved SanitizingFunction support

  
Spring GraphQL 1.0.0-M6 support, including the new GraphQL client


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graphic Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2598/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2598/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/graphic_designers.png" title="They might make it past that first line of defense. For the second, you'll need some picture frames, a level, and a protractor that can do increments of less than a degree." alt="They might make it past that first line of defense. For the second, you'll need some picture frames, a level, and a protractor that can do increments of less than a degree." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda Now Supports Up to 10 GB Ephemeral Storage]]></title>
        <id>57c25c20e6d01488a25def63e79d1c56dd2638df</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-lambda-now-supports-up-to-10-gb-ephemeral-storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T20:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless applications are event-driven, using ephemeral compute functions ranging from web APIs, mobile backends, and streaming analytics to data processing stages in machine learning (ML) and high-performance applications. While AWS Lambda includes a 512 MB temporary file system (/tmp) for your code, this is an ephemeral scratch resource not intended for durable storage such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Signs of Disease from External Images of the Eye]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/detecting-signs-of-disease-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/detecting-signs-of-disease-from.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T17:10:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Boris Babenko, Software Engineer and Naama Hammel, Clinical Research Scientist, Google Health 
Three years ago we wrote about our work on predicting a number of cardiovascular risk factors from fundus photos (i.e., photos of the back of the eye)1 using deep learning. That such risk factors could be extracted from fundus photos was a novel discovery and thus a surprising outcome to clinicians and laypersons alike. Since then, we and other researchers have discovered additional novel biomarkers from fundus photos, such as markers for chronic kidney disease and diabetes, and hemoglobin levels to detect anemia.  
A unifying goal of work like this is to develop new disease detection or monitoring approaches that are less invasive, more accurate, cheaper and more readily available. How…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AzureRM 3.0 Brings Enhanced Azure Function Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-azurerm-3-0-brings-enhanced-azure-function-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-azurerm-3-0-brings-enhanced-azure-function-support"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureRM 3.0 brings significant parity between the Azure provider for Terraform and Azure services currently available. Review the breaking changes as you prepare to upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-6-5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-6-5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T15:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.5 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 66 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.11 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-5-11-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-boot-2-5-11-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T13:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.11 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 56 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.2.3 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-authorization-server-0-2-3-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/24/spring-authorization-server-0-2-3-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.2.3.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




compile 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.2.3'




See the release notes for complete details.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the sample to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues |  ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Aren’t There Legacy App Stores?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=46225</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/why-arent-there-legacy-app-stores/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover what we're doing to provide more options for enterprises to connect their legacy apps to other components of their modern IT stack.
The post Why Aren’t There Legacy App Stores? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0 M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/spring-batch-5-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/spring-batch-5-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T22:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M2 is now available from our milestone repository.

This second milestone comes with two major features:


  
Introduction of the new Observation API from Micrometer 2.0 which gives you both metrics and tracing for your batch jobs!

  
Addition of SAP HANA as a supported database for the job repository


Moreover, this release comes with a number of enhancements and dependencies updates. For more details about all the changes, please check the change log.

I would like to thank all contributors who had a role in this release! As we continue our work on Spring Batch 5, we look forward to your feedback on this second milestone!

Spring Batch Home|Source on Github|Reference documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An update on recent service disruptions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-23-an-update-on-recent-service-disruptions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-23-an-update-on-recent-service-disruptions/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T20:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few weeks, we have experienced multiple incidents due to the health of our database. We wanted to share what we know about these incidents while our team continues to address them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-generated Summaries in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/auto-generated-summaries-in-google-docs.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/auto-generated-summaries-in-google-docs.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mohammad Saleh, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team and Anjuli Kannan, Software Engineer, Google Docs  
For many of us, it can be challenging to keep up with the volume of documents that arrive in our inboxes every day: reports, reviews, briefs, policies and the list goes on. When a new document is received, readers often wish it included a brief summary of the main points in order to effectively prioritize it. However, composing a document summary can be cognitively challenging and time-consuming, especially when a document writer is starting from scratch. 
 To help with this, we recently announced that Google Docs now automatically generates suggestions to aid document writers in creating content summaries, when they are available. Today we describe how this was enab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Native Images with GraalVM and Spring Native on Apple's M1 Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/building-native-images-with-graalvm-and-spring-native-on-apple-s-m1-architecture</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/building-native-images-with-graalvm-and-spring-native-on-apple-s-m1-architecture"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It finally happened! They did it! They did it just in time for me to get on the road and start building applications on the road with my shiny new laptop, too! JOY!! Oracle and the GraalVM team released GraalVM and the GraalVM native image capability for Apple M1! I’ve been waiting for this day for so, so, so long! I bought the first Apple M1 the day of the announcement way back in 2020 (does anybody remember that far back? That was, meteorologically speaking, the early pandemic period). 

Apple’s M1 devices are insanely fast, energy-efficient beasts of machines that run circles around all but the beefiest and latest-and-greatest Intel/NVidia configurations while also consuming a pittance of the power that other configuration does. In short, I’m a big fan. But the move to this new archite…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: secure self-hosted runners by limiting them to specific workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-23-github-actions-secure-self-hosted-runners-specific-workflows/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-23-github-actions-secure-self-hosted-runners-specific-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T16:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now enforce consistent usage of self-hosted runner groups across your organization and enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.10 Adds Login MFA, PKI to Use HSMs, Usage Metrics, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-10</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-10"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.10 improves Vault’s core workflows and makes key features production-ready to better serve your use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第206話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496829058927</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496829058927"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Level Set at the Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/lets-level-set-at-the-edge</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/lets-level-set-at-the-edge"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
 
Typically when people hear the word edge, everyone gets a little apprehensive of what that means. So Josh, Andy, Martin and Chad got together to collaborate on what that means from their collective experiences across multiple industries. In this blog we will cover what the difference is between the near edge and far edge, as well as give some examples of what we have seen in these environments across multiple industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chad Ferman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Multitenant JDBC]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/spring-tips-multitenant-jdbc</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/03/23/spring-tips-multitenant-jdbc"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment we look at how to use Spring’s AbstractRoutingDataSource to build multi-tenant JDBC database code. 

code: https://github.com/spring-tips/multitenant-jdbc
speaker: Josh Long (@starbuxman)

</iframe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving your GitHub feed]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-22-improving-your-github-feed/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-22-improving-your-github-feed/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T23:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are rolling out a new beta version of GitHub’s home feed, making it easier to discover projects, developers and more across GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the GHES repository cache]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-03-22-introducing-the-ghes-repository-cache/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-03-22-introducing-the-ghes-repository-cache/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T17:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a GHES customer with heavy read traffic on your monorepo, check out the repository cache, especially if you have CI workloads distributed around the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elegant Cert Governance with Vault Identity and Sentinel Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/elegant-cert-governance-with-vault-identity-and-sentinel-policy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/elegant-cert-governance-with-vault-identity-and-sentinel-policy"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how using policy as code to enforce governance for certificate creation inside HashiCorp Vault reduces cost of ownership and lowers risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Goldman Sachs Built a Brand New Platform on Camunda Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=46053</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/why-goldman-sachs-built-a-brand-new-platform-on-camunda-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get the details behind Goldman Sachs' new platform to provide microservice orchestration across all of its teams and meet client demands.
The post Why Goldman Sachs Built a Brand New Platform on Camunda Cloud appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 21, 2022]]></title>
        <id>55b35723d9259f39ac1ad27522fdece23d9b4c0f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-21-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Another week, another round up of the most significant AWS launches from the previous seven days! Among the news, we have new AWS Heroes and a cost reduction. Also, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in the Ansible Content Collection for Kubernetes 2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-the-ansible-content-collection-for-kubernetes-2.3</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-the-ansible-content-collection-for-kubernetes-2.3"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With increased adoption of container automation, IT organizations continue to expand their requirements when it comes to deploying and managing their Kubernetes clusters. As such, we at Red Hat continue to add new features and capabilities to meet those demands by announcing the availability of kubernetes.core version 2.3, our Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for Kubernetes and Helm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Artifacts feed continues to make product accessible to everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63598</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-artifacts-feed-continues-to-make-product-accessible-to-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T18:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Azure Artifacts continues to be a central place where thousands of developers host, consume, manage packages and share build artifacts, it remains imperative that our user interfaces are accessible.
The post Azure Artifacts feed continues to make product accessible to everyone appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Omokoh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offline Optimization for Architecting Hardware Accelerators]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/offline-optimization-for-architecting.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/offline-optimization-for-architecting.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T18:04:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Amir Yazdanbakhsh, Research Scientist and Aviral Kumar, Student Researcher, Google Research 
Advances in machine learning (ML) often come with advances in hardware and computing systems. For example, the growth of ML-based approaches in solving various problems in vision and language has led to the development of application-specific hardware accelerators (e.g., Google TPUs and Edge TPUs). While promising, standard procedures for designing accelerators customized towards a target application require manual effort to devise a reasonably accurate simulator of hardware, followed by performing many time-intensive simulations to optimize the desired objective (e.g., optimizing for low power usage or latency when running a particular application). This involves identifying the right ba…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Artifacts now provides native support to use packages from more repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63606</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-artifacts-now-provides-native-support-to-use-packages-from-more-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T17:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously, Azure Artifacts customers were only able to natively consume packages from Maven Central as an upstream source, which has been a blocker for customers who want to fully leverage our services as they depend on other vital repos for DevOps.
The post Azure Artifacts now provides native support to use packages from more repositories appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Omokoh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: The One Where You’re Retrieving Process Variables from an External Task Worker]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/qa-the-one-where-youre-retrieving-process-variables-from-an-external-task-worker/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you go about retrieving a variable in your process instance that you’re not sure what or where it is? Let us show you.
The post Q&A: The One Where You’re Retrieving Process Variables from an External Task Worker appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New and Updated AWS Well-Architected Lenses]]></title>
        <id>34ce16af41c5307d25c3a7835f037d791ed25f0d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-and-updated-aws-well-architected-lenses/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T22:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since 2015, the AWS Well-Architected Framework has been helping AWS customers and partners improve their cloud architectures. The framework consists of design principles, questions, and best practices across multiple pillars: Operational Excellence, Security, Reliability, Performance Efficiency, and Cost Optimization. At AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced a new Sustainability Pillar to help organizations learn, measure, and improve their workloads using environmental best practices […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know the first AWS Heroes of 2022!]]></title>
        <id>b69882dff9b6088e2fe49ea33224aa377fd9b88f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/get-to-know-the-first-aws-heroes-of-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T21:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Heroes program is a worldwide initiative which acknowledges individuals who have truly gone above and beyond to share knowledge in technical communities. AWS Heroes share knowledge by hosting events, Meetups, workshops, and study groups, or by authoring blogs, creating videos, speaking at conferences, or contributing to open source projects. You can see some […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid Quantum Algorithms for Quantum Monte Carlo]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/hybrid-quantum-algorithms-for-quantum.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/hybrid-quantum-algorithms-for-quantum.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T16:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by William J. Huggins, Research Scientist, Google Quantum AI 
The intersection between the computational difficulty and practical importance of quantum chemistry challenges run on quantum computers has long been a focus for Google Quantum AI. We’ve experimentally simulated simple models of chemical bonding, high-temperature superconductivity, nanowires, and even exotic phases of matter such as time crystals on our Sycamore quantum processors. We’ve also developed algorithms suitable for the error-corrected quantum computers we aim to build, including the world’s most efficient algorithm for large-scale quantum computations of chemistry (in the usual way of formulating the problem) and a pioneering approach that allows for us to solve the same problem at an extremely high spatial res…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women’s History Month: Stories of Making a Difference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/women-s-history-month-stories-of-making-a-difference</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/women-s-history-month-stories-of-making-a-difference"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In honor of Women’s History Month, five women at HashiCorp share stories on how they work to make a difference in their communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multimodal Bottleneck Transformer (MBT): A New Model for Modality Fusion]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/multimodal-bottleneck-transformer-mbt.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/multimodal-bottleneck-transformer-mbt.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T20:47:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Arsha Nagrani and Chen Sun, Research Scientists, Google Research, Perception Team 
People interact with the world through multiple sensory streams (e.g., we see objects, hear sounds, read words, feel textures and taste flavors), combining information and forming associations between senses. As real-world data consists of various signals that co-occur, such as video frames and audio tracks, web images and their captions and instructional videos and speech transcripts, it is natural to apply a similar logic when building and designing multimodal machine learning (ML) models.  
 Effective multimodal models have wide applications — such as multilingual image retrieval, future action prediction, and vision-language navigation — and are important for several reasons; robustness, which …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecating weak cryptographic standards (TLS 1.0 and 1.1) in Azure DevOps Services]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63575</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deprecating-weak-cryptographic-standards-tls-1-0-and-1-1-in-azure-devops-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T11:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps team needed to partially rollback the previous release of TLS 1.0/1.1 deprecation that was run on Jan 31st, 2022. This was due to unexpected issues caused by the change. Here’s a link to the previous blog post related to that release.
The post Deprecating weak cryptographic standards (TLS 1.0 and 1.1) in Azure DevOps Services appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Camunda Cloud in a (Nut)shell]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45665</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/managing-camunda-cloud-in-a-nutshell/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how the CLI allows you to troubleshoot and get information from your Camunda Cloud cluster, deploy processes, and run job workers. 
The post Managing Camunda Cloud in a (Nut)shell appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nele Uhlemann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 14, 2022]]></title>
        <id>1400c50e1d58b518d15c77730287ed5e1c6705e4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-14-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T23:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Welcome to the March 14 AWS Week in Review post, and Happy Pi Day! I hope you managed to catch some of our livestreamed Pi day celebration of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to AWS Pi Day 2022]]></title>
        <id>9ff88e5b6aa3475bbb879efe35f7c2d66532ccfe</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/welcome-to-aws-pi-day-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T16:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) sixteen years ago today! As I often told my audiences in the early days, I wanted them to think big thoughts and dream big dreams! Looking back, I think it is safe to say that the launch of S3 empowered them to do just that, and initiated […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform, Packer, and CI/CD Videos from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-packer-and-ci-cd-videos-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-packer-and-ci-cd-videos-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several of this year’s HashiTalks speakers presented useful Terraform, Packer, and CI/CD tips and tricks. Learn from this list of highlights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Simple Ways Automation Can Save You Money on Your AWS Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/two-simple-ways-automation-can-save-money-on-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/two-simple-ways-automation-can-save-money-on-aws"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform is an excellent automation and orchestration tool for public clouds. For this post, I am going to walk through two common scenarios where Ansible Automation Platform can help out. I want to look outside the common public cloud use-case of provisioning and deprovisioning resources and instead look at automating common operational tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault, Boundary, and Zero Trust Videos from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-boundary-and-zero-trust-videos-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-boundary-and-zero-trust-videos-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several of this year’s HashiTalks showcased useful strategies and use cases for HashiCorp Vault and Boundary. Watch the videos here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 X2idn and X2iedn Instances for Memory-Intensive Workloads with Higher Network Bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>f702f965974bf29a23cdde80bb0f3dacddcfcbc5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-x2idn-and-x2iedn-instances-for-memory-intensive-workloads-with-higher-network-bandwidth/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T21:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2016, we launched Amazon EC2 X1 instances designed for large-scale and in-memory applications in the cloud. The price per GiB of RAM for X1 instances is among the lowest. X1 instances are ideal for high performance computing (HPC) applications and running in-memory databases like SAP HANA and big data processing engines such as Apache […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul and Chaos Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-and-chaos-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-and-chaos-engineering"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn more about how HashiCorp Consul can help improve application resiliency, and how to test whether it’s working with chaos engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Community Summit 2022: Dedicated to Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=45372</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/camunda-community-summit-2022-dedicated-to-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Expert Sessions agenda is now live for you to preview. Join us on April 26 - 28 for our virtual, interactive conference.
The post Camunda Community Summit 2022: Dedicated to Developers appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Thengvall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Airline Tail Assignments for Cleaner Skies]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/optimizing-airline-tail-assignments-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/optimizing-airline-tail-assignments-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T18:52:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Emily Masten, Software Engineer, Google Research, Operations Research Team  
Airlines around the world are exploring several tactics to meet aggressive CO2 commitments set by the International Civil Aviation Organization (ICAO). This effort has been emphasized in Europe, where aviation accounts for 13.9% of the transportation industry’s carbon emissions. The largest push comes from the European Green Deal, which aims to decrease carbon emissions from transportation by 90% by 2051. The Lufthansa Group has gone even further, committing to a 50% reduction in emissions compared to 2019 by the year 2030 and to reach net-zero emissions by 2050.  
 One unexpected approach that airlines can use to lower carbon emissions is through optimizing their tail assignment, i.e., how to assign air…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[User Story Videos from HashiTalks 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/user-story-videos-from-hashitalks-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/user-story-videos-from-hashitalks-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insightful case-study sessions were plentiful at this year’s HashiTalks. Check them out in these user-story video highlights from the virtual conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第205話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496802660149</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496802660149"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ansible cookie: Magic in the middle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-ansible-cookie-magic-in-the-middle</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-ansible-cookie-magic-in-the-middle"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Ansible Automation Platform was compared to the crunchy goodness of a cookie, private automation hub would be the sweet center bringing it all together and making your mouth water!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust Graph Neural Networks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/robust-graph-neural-networks.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/robust-graph-neural-networks.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T19:44:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bryan Perozzi, Research Scientist and Qi Zhu, Research Intern, Google Research 
Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) are powerful tools for leveraging graph-structured data in machine learning. Graphs are flexible data structures that can model many different kinds of relationships and have been used in diverse applications like traffic prediction, rumor and fake news detection, modeling disease spread, and understanding why molecules smell. 
 

Graphs can model the relationships between many different types of data, including web pages (left), social connections (center), or molecules (right).

        
As is standard in machine learning (ML), GNNs assume that training samples are selected uniformly at random (i.e., are an independent and identically distributed or “IID” sample). This i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 70 – Intro to @Azure Stream Analytics with @fleid_bi]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63507</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-70-intro-to-azure-stream-analytics-with-fleid_bi/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T16:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 70 – Intro to @Azure Stream Analytics with @fleid_bi appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the Bias – Women at AWS Developer Relations]]></title>
        <id>660bac839b3d1f53837ae0f822bfc533a449a9fc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/breaking-the-bias-women-at-aws-developer-relations/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T15:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today for International Women’s Day we’re joined by a special guest writer, Rashmi Nambiar. She’s here to share her conversations with a few other members of the AWS Developer Relations team, talking about their work and experience as women in tech. Enjoy! – The AWS News Blog Team When I was contemplating joining AWS, many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rashmi Nambiar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International Women's Day: HashiCorp Leaders Share Their Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/international-women-s-day-hashicorp-leaders-share-their-stories</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/international-women-s-day-hashicorp-leaders-share-their-stories"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In honor of International Women’s Day, three HashiCorp leaders talk about their inspirations, their challenges, and their hopes for the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0-alpha5 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=44937</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/03/camunda-automation-platform-7-17-0-alpha5-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0. Check out the improvements featured in this release.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0-alpha5 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 7, 2022]]></title>
        <id>333419a96f3de40ad13a5947d1445b7bfe0a3156</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-7-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T21:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick round up of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Hello Again The AWS Week in Review is back! Many years ago, I tried to write a weekly post that captured the most significant AWS activity. This was easy […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer provides automation, collaboration, and security for managing images across multiple clouds. It includes image security and compliance workflows with Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning from Weakly-Labeled Videos via Sub-Concepts]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/learning-from-weakly-labeled-videos-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/03/learning-from-weakly-labeled-videos-via.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T18:08:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zizhao Zhang and Guanhang Wu, Software Engineers, Google Research, Cloud AI Team  
Video recognition is a core task in computer vision with applications from video content analysis to action recognition. However, training models for video recognition often requires untrimmed videos to be manually annotated, which can be prohibitively time consuming. In order to reduce the effort of collecting videos with annotations, learning visual knowledge from videos with weak labels, i.e., where the annotation is auto-generated without manual intervention, has attracted growing research interest, thanks to the large volume of easily accessible video data. Untrimmed videos, for example, are often acquired by querying with keywords for classes that the video recognition model aims to classify.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate your Ansible Playbooks to Support AWS boto3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-migrate-your-ansible-playbooks-to-support-aws-boto3</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-migrate-your-ansible-playbooks-to-support-aws-boto3"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform is known for automating Linux, Windows and networking infrastructure. While both the community version of Ansible and our enterprise offering, Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, are prominently known for configuration management, this is just a small piece of what you can really achieve with Ansible’s automation. There are many other use-cases that Ansible Automation Platform is great at automating, such as your AWS, Azure or Google public cloud]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Tencent Cloud Secrets Engine and Authentication Method in HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-tencent-cloud-secrets-engine-authentication-method-in-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-tencent-cloud-secrets-engine-authentication-method-in-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T05:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tencent Cloud has announced new HashiCorp Vault integrations. See how they are implemented in this guest post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>