<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-07-07T02:14:54.183Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-07T02:14:54.183Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLGO: A Machine Learning Framework for Compiler Optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/mlgo-machine-learning-framework-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/07/mlgo-machine-learning-framework-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yundi Qian, Software Engineer, Google Research and Mircea Trofin, Software Engineer, Google Core 
The question of how to compile faster and smaller code arose together with the birth of modem computers. Better code optimization can significantly reduce the operational cost of large datacenter applications. The size of compiled code matters the most to mobile and embedded systems or software deployed on secure boot partitions, where the compiled binary must fit in tight code size budgets. With advances in the field, the headroom has been heavily squeezed with increasingly complicated heuristics, impeding maintenance and further improvements.  
 Recent research has shown that machine learning (ML) can unlock more opportunities in compiler optimization by replacing complicated heuri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: June 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-06-github-availability-report-june-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-06-github-availability-report-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June, we experienced four incidents resulting in significant impact to multiple GitHub.com services. This report also sheds light into an incident that impacted several GitHub.com services in May.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many shards should I have in my Elasticsearch cluster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch is a very versatile platform that supports a variety of use cases and provides great flexibility around data organisation and replication strategies. This flexibility can, however, sometimes make it hard to determine up-front how to best organize your data into indices and shards, especially if you are new to the Elastic Stack. While suboptimal choices will not necessarily cause problems when first starting out, they have the potential to cause performance problems as data volumes grow over time. The more data the cluster holds, the more difficult it also becomes to correct the problem, as reindexing of large amounts of data can sometimes be required.
When we come across users that are experiencing performance problems, it is not uncommon that this can be traced back to issue…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Dahlqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many shards should I have in my Elasticsearch cluster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-many-shards-should-i-have-in-my-elasticsearch-cluster"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Dahlqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking Automation to the Next Level: Using Ansible + GitOps to Manage the Lifecycle of a Containerized Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/taking-automation-to-the-next-level-using-ansible-gitops-to-manage-the-lifecycle-of-a-containerized-application</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/taking-automation-to-the-next-level-using-ansible-gitops-to-manage-the-lifecycle-of-a-containerized-application"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the great advantages of combining GitOps with Ansible is that you get to streamline the automation delivery and the lifecycle of a containerized application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Do you have a plan?”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41304</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701795856/0/sethsblog~Do-you-have-a-plan/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First, let’s agree that there’s a problem. It may be that I think we’re facing something serious, something costly, something urgent–and you don’t. We can have an honest conversation about the problem without worrying about whether there’s an easy or certain solution. We can also have a conversation about whether it’s a problem (problems have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing a game dev community with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-06-managing-a-game-dev-community/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-06-managing-a-game-dev-community/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T08:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Little Game Called Mario is an open source, collectively developed hell project. Anyone and everyone is welcome to contribute their unique talents to make both the player and developer experience more enjoyable. Find out how the collective leverages GitHub Actions to manage this wonderful little community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No One Was Hurt]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2642/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2642/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/no_one_was_hurt.png" title="See how the smoke obscures things so you don't see the approaching tornado until the firework streamers start to swirl right before the lightning hits the launcher. Thank God Cousin Ed was filming in slow motion. And, uh, that no one was hurt." alt="See how the smoke obscures things so you don't see the approaching tornado until the firework streamers start to swirl right before the lightning hits the launcher. Thank God Cousin Ed was filming in slow motion. And, uh, that no one was hurt." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTrack Now With More Powerful Time Tracking]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=youtrack&amp;p=258030</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/youtrack/2022/07/youtrack-now-with-more-powerful-time-tracking/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTrack 2022.2 comes with an incredible set of enhancements for your time tracking routines. It offers timesheets for working groups and custom attributes for work items. Additionally, you can now migrate your issues from Google Sheets, as well as from CSV and XLSX files to YouTrack with a new built-in import feature, and use color […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Bartasheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | July 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=261573</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/07/05/net-annotated-monthly-july-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T14:24:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? Atari celebrates its 50th anniversary this year. While the organization has changed hands a few times in 50 years, the original Atari, Inc., was founded in Sunnyvale, California, in 1972 and is currently owned by Atari SA. Atari made video games in the home a popular pastime. Happy anniversary Atari!  .NET news […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy: New Projects and Topics in June]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=261623</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/07/05/jetbrains-academy-new-projects-and-topics-in-june-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow, it’s summer already! We hope you won’t forget to take a break to fully enjoy it. Unless you’re in the southern hemisphere, in which case — don’t forget about a well-deserved break too! One great way to get into it is to enjoy one of our educational great games, like Last Pencil. You’ll also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Khramushina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Live Stream Recording: WebStorm’s Power User Manual: Angular Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=261197</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/07/recording-webstorms-power-user-manual-angular-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recording from the WebStorm’s Power User Manual: Angular Edition live stream is now available on the JetBrains YouTube channel! In this live stream, WebStorm Power User Chau Tran shared some of his favorite Angular tips and tricks that he uses in his day-to-day work. Whether you are just starting out with WebStorm or have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Aganezova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster Django Queries With Materialized Views]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=261150</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/07/faster-django-queries-with-materialized-views/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T11:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repeatedly running queries that span multiple tables can be burdensome on your database. In this blog post, we’re going to talk about materialized views, how and why they help us cut down on query costs, and how to integrate them into your Django application. Read on to learn more or check out this video overview. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2022.2 EAP 2 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=261294</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2022/07/2022-2-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T10:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new build is equipped with a bunch of improvements to the Jupyter cells UX. It also provides a new capability to set up and use WSL-based interpreters for your projects from inside DataSpell. Here is an overview of what you can expect from the second EAP for DataSpell 2022.2. You can download the EAP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 5th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/05/this-week-in-spring-july-5th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/07/05/this-week-in-spring-july-5th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! This week’s all sorts of weird for me. It’s Tuesday! But here in the US we just celebrated the 4th of July, and I, like many Americans, took a long weekend. Took some time with the family to do a little road trip up north to visit Mt. Shasta, Crater Lake, Lassen National Park, etc. It was a ton of fun, and a lot of driving! Anyway, it all kinda blurs together and felt like just one weekend, and today feels like Monday. I only just realized it was Tuesday! And you know what that means? It’s time for our weekly dive into the wild and wonderful world of Springdom! 


  
The last of my eight part series on building GraphQL applications with Spring for GraphQL is up! Check that page out and find links to all eight videos, each of which introduces one interesting dimension of the powerful and novel new Spring for GraphQL project.

  
In last week’s installment of A Bootiful Podcast, I talk to Spring Developer Advocate Dan Vega

  
Processing the Response Body in Spring Cloud Gateway

  
Spring Cloud 2020.0.6 is available

  
UUID as Entity ID in MongoDB

  
I liked this post over on Dzone: Are All Kubernetes Ingresses the Same?

  
Want to learn more about how to build GraalVM native images for Spring Boot 2.x-generation applications? Check out this article I wrote for InfoQ on Spring Native and GraalVM

  
The good folks over at Vaadin have put together a nice tutorial on building full-stack Spring Boot applications using their Java web framework called Hilla - check it out!

  
our friends over at Sivalabs have put together an interesting looking tutorial on how to use Spring Boot and Kubernetes together

  
Spring Boot team member Stéphane Nicoll did a French-language presentation for DevFest Lille recently introducing Spring AOT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Significant hurdles]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42308</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701675576/0/sethsblog~Significant-hurdles/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T08:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your plan, your idea or your art doesn’t involve any significant hurdles in moving forward, it’s probably not worth that much. If it were easy, everyone would do it. The tactic is to seek a path where you see and understand the significant hurdles that kept others away. And then dance with them. They’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving quantified success with Elastic Enterprise Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-enterprise-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-enterprise-search"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recently ran a customer Results that Matter survey managed and analyzed by Socratic Technologies. With 98% of customers saying that they will continue to use Elastic as much or more in the next year, the results were compelling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving quantified success with Elastic Enterprise Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-enterprise-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/driving-quantified-success-with-elastic-enterprise-search"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Locating information and content is a universal problem that extends across industries, geographies, and use cases. This challenge is only getting more complex as data volumes grow and organizations experience tool sprawl.

Elasticsearch was created over a decade ago to solve this issue. Since then, millions of people have chosen Elasticsearch to implement robust, modern search experiences. 

This year, Elastic ran a customer study through a survey managed and analyzed by Socratic Technologies. Its purpose was to take a closer look at the problems customers are solving with Enterprise Search. Our findings not only inform the future of Elastic Enterprise Search, but they also serve as an example of how customers can best leverage the tool to be most successful in their search endeavors.

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – July 4, 2022]]></title>
        <id>7ed012657b91a09f4a4432a1cd0a97f3cc7ca3d4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-july-04-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T18:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Summer has arrived in Finland, and these last few days have been hotter than in the Canary Islands! Today in the US it is Independence Day. I hope that if […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.2 EAP #6: Mockery Support, Enhanced Inspections Configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=260896</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/07/phpstorm-2022-2-eap-6/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T16:42:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to the 2022.2 EAP series! If you’re unsure about what our Early Access Program is, make sure to read this blog post. Let’s take a look at what’s new in this week’s EAP build. Download PhpStorm 2022.2 EAP Mockery support We’ve been working on implementing support in PhpStorm for Mockery, one of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demand responsibility]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42316</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701569946/0/sethsblog~Demand-responsibility/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T08:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plenty of people insist on freedom and independence. More rare and far more effective is to claim responsibility instead. “I’ve got this,” can go a long way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mouse Turbines]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2641/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2641/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/mouse_turbines.png" title="It's sad seeing those videos of turbine blade being torn apart in high winds, but it's the only way they can disperse their seeds." alt="It's sad seeing those videos of turbine blade being torn apart in high winds, but it's the only way they can disperse their seeds." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two kinds of good cooks]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41514</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701467750/0/sethsblog~Two-kinds-of-good-cooks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One is very skilled at following the recipe. Quality control, consistency and diligence. The other understands how the recipe works, sees patterns and opportunities and changes the recipe to fit the problem to be solved. It’s about metaphor in addition to process. Both are useful. If you think this is a post about cooking, you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 reps]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42310</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701365800/0/sethsblog~reps/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you can do it once, you might be able to do it ten times. And if you do it ten times, it will become a skill and a practice. You’ll do it more naturally and more often. Sending a note, changing your mind, throwing a ball, offering a kind word, doing leg presses. Ten […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extend your dependency information in the GitHub Dependency Graph with new GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-01-extend-your-dependency-information-in-the-github-dependency-graph-with-new-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-01-extend-your-dependency-information-in-the-github-dependency-graph-with-new-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T17:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Actions from Anchore, NowSecure, SBT, and Trivy are now available to create a more comprehensive GitHub Dependency Graph.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the GitHub Security Team uses projects and GitHub Actions for planning, tracking, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-07-01-how-the-github-security-team-uses-projects-and-github-actions-for-planning-tracking-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-07-01-how-the-github-security-team-uses-projects-and-github-actions-for-planning-tracking-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T15:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can projects and GitHub Actions be used by your non-developer teams? They absolutely can. Check out how our Security Team uses GitHub to run the department effortlessly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Support for fmt.Appendf, Resolve Modes for Databases, and More in GoLand 2022.2 EAP #7]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=261006</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/07/01/support-for-fmt-appendf-resolve-modes-for-databases-and-more-in-goland-2022-2-eap-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T15:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.2 EAP #7 is now available! You can get the EAP build via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package for Ubuntu, or from inside GoLand select Check IDE updates for Early Access Program in Preferences / Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System Settings | Updates.  Download GoLand […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand is looking for Developer Advocate and Technical Content Creator]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=260825</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/07/01/goland-is-looking-for-developer-advocate-and-technical-content-creator/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T10:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction The GoLand team has opened two positions: Developer Advocate and Technical Content Creator. Please refer to the position descriptions for the requirements and expectations, and be sure to check out this blog post to find out what it’s like to be a developer advocate at JetBrains. Even though it was written in the pre-COVID […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Khvastunov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why We Need Hive Metastore]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=big-data-tools&amp;p=259472</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/big-data-tools/2022/07/01/why-we-need-hive-metastore/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody in IT works with data, including frontend and backend developers, analysts, QA engineers, product managers, and people in many other roles. The data used and the data processing methods vary with the role, but data itself is more often than not the key. — “It’s a very special key, meant only for The One”— […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pasha Finkelshteyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode 2022.2 EAP5: Code Highlighting in the Documentation Popup and Other Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=260813</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/07/appcode-2022-2-eap5-code-highlighting-in-the-documentation-popup-and-other-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T08:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, A new AppCode 2022.2 EAP build (222.3244.12) is available for download. Builds are available from our website and via the Toolbox App. You can also update from the 2022.2 EAP4 build via patch. DOWNLOAD APPCODE EAP Code highlighting in the documentation popup Code documentation makes maintaining your code base easier, while a convenient layout […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting with agreement]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43060</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701231586/0/sethsblog~Starting-with-agreement/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T07:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resilient systems are better than fragile ones. Leave the campsite better than you found it. Clean air is better than dirty air. It’s more reliable to invest in things that produce positive impacts over time. When the numbers add up, believe them People who show their work are more likely to be right. Important work […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Universe by Scientific Field]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2640/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2640/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/the_universe_by_scientific_field.png" title="The math and philosophy people also claim everything, but the astronomers argue that the stuff they study really only comprises a small number of paper surfaces." alt="The math and philosophy people also claim everything, but the astronomers argue that the stuff they study really only comprises a small number of paper surfaces." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 EAP #7: Improvements for Docker and HTTP Client]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=260543</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/06/webstorm-2022-2-eap-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T20:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 EAP build #7 is now available! To catch up on all the new features, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. You can also manually download the EAP builds from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying Disfluencies in Natural Speech]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/identifying-disfluencies-in-natural.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/identifying-disfluencies-in-natural.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T20:09:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dan Walker and Dan Liebling, Software Engineers, Google Research 
People don’t write in the same way that they speak. Written language is controlled and deliberate, whereas transcripts of spontaneous speech (like interviews) are hard to read because speech is disorganized and less fluent. One aspect that makes speech transcripts particularly difficult to read is disfluency, which includes self-corrections, repetitions, and filled pauses (e.g., words like “umm”, and “you know”). Following is an example of a spoken sentence with disfluencies from the LDC CALLHOME corpus: 
But that's it's not, it's not, it's, uh, it's a word play on what you just said.
It takes some time to understand this sentence — the listener must filter out the extraneous words and resolve all of the nots. Remo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Developer Advocate Dan Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-developer-advocate-dan-vega</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-developer-advocate-dan-vega"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to fellow Spring Developer Advocate Dan Vega (@therealdanvega)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Better Commits, Build Better Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-30-write-better-commits-build-better-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-30-write-better-commits-build-better-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T19:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High-quality Git commits are the key to a maintainable and collaborative open- or closed-source project. Learn strategies to improve and use commits to streamline your development process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minerva: Solving Quantitative Reasoning Problems with Language Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/minerva-solving-quantitative-reasoning.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/minerva-solving-quantitative-reasoning.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T16:34:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ethan Dyer and Guy Gur-Ari, Research Scientists, Google Research, Blueshift Team 
Language models have demonstrated remarkable performance on a variety of natural language tasks — indeed, a general lesson from many works, including BERT, GPT-3, Gopher, and PaLM, has been that neural networks trained on diverse data at large scale in an unsupervised way can perform well on a variety of tasks. 
Quantitative reasoning is one area in which language models still fall far short of human-level performance. Solving mathematical and scientific questions requires a combination of skills, including correctly parsing a question with natural language and mathematical notation, recalling relevant formulas and constants, and generating step-by-step solutions involving numerical calculations and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waypoint 0.9 Adds New Runner Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-9-adds-new-runner-commands</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/waypoint-0-9-adds-new-runner-commands"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint 0.9 introduces on-demand runner introspection, a runner install command, and support for HCP Waypoint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to do when your open source project becomes a community?]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-30-what-to-do-when-your-open-source-project-becomes-a-community/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-30-what-to-do-when-your-open-source-project-becomes-a-community/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T15:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintainers answer your questions about how to manage an open source project that grows into a community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the summer 2022 MLH Fellowship GitHub Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-30-announcing-the-summer-2022-mlh-fellowship-github-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-30-announcing-the-summer-2022-mlh-fellowship-github-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T15:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the 2022 MLH Fellowship cohort! This 12-week internship alternative is for aspiring software engineers, and powered by GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2020.0.6 is available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/spring-cloud-2020-0-6-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/30/spring-cloud-2020-0-6-is-available"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce the Spring Cloud 2020.0.6 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Maven Central. You can check out the 2020.0.6 release notes for more information. Please consider upgrading to the latest 2021.0.x release train since the 2020.0.x release train has reached the end of OSS support.
Notable Changes in the 2020.0.6 Release

This is primarily a bugfix and dependency upgrade release, including backports of various issues over from 2021.0.x releases. Some enhancements have also been backported. 

See the project page for all issues included in the release.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Backported bug fixes from 2021.0.x

  
Backported passing on request data to LoadBalancerLifecycle beans for the blocking Spring Cloud Load…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compounded luck]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43239</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/701114180/0/sethsblog~Compounded-luck/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T09:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you and I play a game of cards, the winner will largely be decided by luck. Get good cards and you come out ahead. If you and I play 100 games of backgammon, the better player will win, because the luck of the dice regress to the mean, evening out over time, leaving skill […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.3.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.3.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.3.1 over the previous versions in 8.3.x.
The release contains fixes for security vulnerabilities. Please see our security announcements for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
8.3.1 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Version 8.3.1 fixes an Elasticsearch issue where certain Azure SAS tokens are sanitized incorrectly by the SDK.
It also contains a Kibana fix for an issue where importing/copying the same saved object to the same space multiple times using the "Check for existing objects" option could fail or cause duplicates to be created.
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norrie Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.3.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-3-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norrie Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Chromium super (inline cache) type confusion]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-29-the-chromium-super-inline-cache-type-confusion/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-29-the-chromium-super-inline-cache-type-confusion/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T18:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post I'll exploit CVE-2022-1134, a type confusion in Chrome that I reported in March 2022, which allows remote code execution (RCE) in the renderer sandbox of Chrome by a single visit to a malicious site. I'll also look at some past vulnerabilities of this type and some implementation details of inline cache in V8, the JavaScript engine of Chrome.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Git monorepo performance with a file system monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-29-improve-git-monorepo-performance-with-a-file-system-monitor/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-29-improve-git-monorepo-performance-with-a-file-system-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monorepo performance can suffer due to the sheer number of files in your working directory. Git’s new builtin file system monitor makes it easy to speed up monorepo performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflections on Juneteenth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/reflections-on-juneteenth</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/reflections-on-juneteenth"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight members of the HashiCorp Blacksmiths’ employee resource group share how they spent Juneteenth this year, and reflect on what they learned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“And then what happens”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42283</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/700974354/0/sethsblog~And-then-what-happens/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T08:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re not very good at predicting the future. We’re very good at being aware of the urgency of the moment, and familiar with our need to deal with emergencies. Before we react, though, it might be worth asking “and then what happens,” five times. Five steps from here to there… If any of the steps […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 important tips to manage your next cybersecurity breach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-important-tips-to-manage-your-next-cybersecurity-breach</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-important-tips-to-manage-your-next-cybersecurity-breach"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent study of 1,200 cybersecurity professionals emphasized these tactics for more effective incident response and recovery from a cybersecurity breach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Radogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how Machine Learning puts the ‘personal’ in ecommerce personalization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/machine-learning-puts-the-personal-in-ecommerce-personalization</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/machine-learning-puts-the-personal-in-ecommerce-personalization"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can transform your search box into your sales rep—when you have the right tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trish Sammer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 important tips to manage your next cybersecurity breach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-important-tips-to-manage-your-next-cybersecurity-breach</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-important-tips-to-manage-your-next-cybersecurity-breach"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
When the average organization experiences 26 cyber attacks per year, being prepared for the aftermath of a breach is just as important as prevention.

With the ever-evolving nature of attacks and the increasing complexity of organizational systems, it’s harder than ever to have a fast response ready to go for any potential scenario that might arise.Case in point: a recent survey of 1,200 organizations by ThoughtLab (and cosponsored by Elastic) shows that more than a quarter of executives fear their organizations aren’t fully prepared for cyber attacks. 

However, Cybersecurity Solutions for a Riskier World also reveals best practices for incident response and recovery from the top cybersecurity executives in 16 countries and across 14 industries. In the unfortunate event of a breach, pri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Radogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how Machine Learning puts the ‘personal’ in ecommerce personalization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/machine-learning-puts-the-personal-in-ecommerce-personalization</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/machine-learning-puts-the-personal-in-ecommerce-personalization"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
An impactful customer experience that drives purchases and loyalty isn't just about delivering what a customer says they want — it's about predicting and proactively serving up what they need. 

We might be able to imagine this work in a store with salespeople. But as organizations scale and customer interactions happen across digital and in-person mediums, their data grows. E-commerce must lean on the latest in machine learning and artificial intelligence to deliver a personalized sales experience. 

That means relying on a powerful search box.

Let’s take a look at how Elastic’s machine learning capabilities are powering this kind of e-commerce personalization. But first, let’s talk about what’s at stake. 

What is e-commerce personalization and why is it important?

E-commerce persona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trish Sammer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Periodic Table Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2639/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2639/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/periodic_table_changes.png" title="It's nice how the end of the periodic table is flush with the edge these days, so I think we should agree no one should find any new elements after #118 unless they discover a whole row at once." alt="It's nice how the end of the periodic table is flush with the edge these days, so I think we should agree no one should find any new elements after #118 unless they discover a whole row at once." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Git protocol security on GitHub Enterprise Server]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-06-28-improving-git-protocol-security-on-github-enterprise-server/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-06-28-improving-git-protocol-security-on-github-enterprise-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent changes to improve protocol security on GitHub.com are now coming to GitHub Enterprise Server, starting with version 3.6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault Logging and Alerting on Day 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-logging-and-alerting-on-day-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-logging-and-alerting-on-day-1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a step-by-step guide to building a free solution for Day 1 Vault logging and alerting on AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 8.3: More ingestion options for searching across any dataset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 8.3, create new data connectors that you can embed into your existing workplace search solutions using a new open code framework. Plus, use the web crawler to index and sync all your PDF content, and build solutions that take advantage of JWT-based (JSON web token) authentication schemes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin,Deepak Mohan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Enterprise Search 8.3: More ingestion options for searching across any dataset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-enterprise-search-8-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The latest release of Elastic Enterprise Search brings to market enhancements to getting data into Elastic Enterprise Search. Depending on the type of content you are looking to index, there are a plethora of ways to ingest that content, from pre-built tools with seamless user interfaces to a fully-formed robust set of APIs to fine-tune how your content is structured once it is in Elastic. 
Elastic Enterprise Search 8.3 brings functionality for:

Creating new connectors that you can embed into your existing workplace search solutions using a new open code framework as well as additional first-party connectors to index data from various sources.
The ability to extract content from PDF documents with the Elastic Enterprise Search web crawler, providing the added benefit of indexing text in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Levin,Deepak Mohan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Achieve Geo-redundancy with Zeebe]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57477</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/how-to-achieve-geo-redundancy-with-zeebe/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations can use Camunda Platform 8 to build resilient systems that can withstand disasters in the form of complete data center outages.
The post How to Achieve Geo-redundancy with Zeebe appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snake handling]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42281</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/700848324/0/sethsblog~Snake-handling/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T08:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a very different task than snake charming. The first is far more common, but it requires heavy equipment and is often dangerous… On the other hand, if you have empathy and patience, it’s possible to learn to charm the snakes instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today is the last day to submit to the SpringOne 2022 Call For Papers!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/28/today-is-the-last-day-to-submit-to-the-springone-2022-call-for-papers</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/28/today-is-the-last-day-to-submit-to-the-springone-2022-call-for-papers"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! This year, SpringOne is back in person, and being held in my hometown of San Francisco, California, December 6th-8th. (Have you registered?) and today (June 28th, 2022) is the last day to submit to the Call For Papers! If you have a good idea or story you want to share, submit today!

Either way, I hope to see you in December in San Francisco, a city so famous for its foggy nightscapes that I think it’s fair to say we are the original cloud natives!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 28th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/28/this-week-in-spring-june-28th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/28/this-week-in-spring-june-28th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I’m writing this from the Big Apple, New York City! I’m here for the SpringOne Tour 2022 NYC event. This is my first time back in New York City since before the pandemic and it has been so much fun. I’ve been catching up with people I’ve not seen in years. I even accidentally bumped into people I had no idea was going to also be in town at the same time as I was. New York City is like a magnet for fun, and for fun people. Anyway, we’ve got a lot of stuff to get to this roundup, so let’s dive right into it. 

Also: if you’re just reading this, today - the 28th of June - is the last day to submit to SpringOne 2022, being held in my hometown of San Francisco, California, in December of this year! 


  
A Bootiful Podcast: JVM and .NET legend Ted Neward on… just about everything

  
JavaScript Function Call with Thymeleaf

  
Spring Boot 2.6.9 available now

  
Spring Boot 2.7.1 available now

  
Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (the last two episodes: parts 7 and 8)

  
Unique Field in MongoDB Document in Spring Data

  
Build 27 of Java 19, early access, is now available

  
On that note, Build 2 of Java 20 - yes, Java 20! - is also available now!

  
The Apache Software Foundation has also released Apache Tomcat 8.5.81 

  
This is an interesting review of the first principles of Spring and static code

  
I liked this article, exhaustive JUnit 5 testing with combinations, permutations, and products]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide To: Your first job after graduation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-guide-to-first-job-after-graduation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-guide-to-first-job-after-graduation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re not alone if you find post-graduate life to be overwhelming. You’re starting an entirely new phase and there’s no playbook for how to get it ‘right’. But don’t be intimidated by interviews and the relative unknown — we're here to help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 8.3: Easily revive that old data archive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-8-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-8-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t let data go end of life. Simply use snapshots as archives in Elasticsearch 8.3 to easily and quickly search your old data for governance, security investigations, and historical lookbacks – now GA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.3: Broader observability for cloud, SaaS, and big data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.3 continues to simplify and streamline visibility for a wide variety of modern environments, including serverless logs forwarding for AWS and performance insights for Salesforce and Hadoop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving performance and optimizing cost on Elastic Cloud has never been easier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/cloud-hardware-profile-migration-template</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/cloud-hardware-profile-migration-template"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hardware profile migration streamlines the migration process with no downtime and allows you to choose the most cost-effective hardware for your needs. Always ensure you're running the right combination of compute, memory, and storage for your workload.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuvraj Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud 8.3: Search & replicate across any cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 8.3, search and replicate data in any environment. Query old snapshots without the need of an old Elasticsearch cluster. Try out new alerting capabilities in Kibana and template migration for Elastic Cloud users to easily migrate deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeline Tan,Brian Bergholm,George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide To: Your first job after graduation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-guide-to-first-job-after-graduation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-guide-to-first-job-after-graduation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
You made it! You have your shiny new undergraduate degree and are ready to fly. 

You’re not alone if you find post-graduate life to be overwhelming. You’re starting an entirely new phase and there’s no playbook for how to get it ‘right’. But don’t be intimidated by interviews and the relative unknown, because we’re here to help! 

Roxy Wolfe, Global Lead of Early Talent, ElasticGrad, has more than 10 years of experience in recruitment—specializing in university recruitment—and has some advice specifically for those navigating the job scene for the first time. 

“As a recruiter, you’re truly impacting someone’s life”, Roxy says. “You’re helping them to find what they love and are passionate about.”

ElastiGrad is Elastic’s recruitment program that hires new graduates into a variety of ro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 8.3: Easily revive that old data archive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-8-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-8-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today, we are pleased to announce the general availability Elasticsearch 8.3.  If you are looking for Kibana and Elastic Cloud be sure to head over to this blog. In 8.3, you can query old snapshots as simple archives without the need of an old Elasticsearch cluster. Plus new sharding guidance, a new geo grid query and finally a new third party ML model for question and answer.

Ready to dive in and get started? We have the links you need:


Try the new features on Elastic Cloud
Download the latest versions of Elasticsearch
Refer to the Elasticsearch release notes
See other Elastic 8.3 highlights in the Elastic 8.3 announcement post
See Elasticsearch breaking changes



New era in snapshots 
We’ve got your back, ups 
Since the release of Elasticsearch 1.0, snapshots have undergone many te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability 8.3: Broader observability for cloud, SaaS, and big data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-observability-8-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Visibility is crucial for ensuring application performance but it can be difficult to efficiently scale monitoring across all your critical infrastructures, platforms, and services. By simplifying and streamlining data ingest, you can maximize coverage across a wide variety of modern environments.

With Elastic Observability 8.3, DevOps and SRE teams can now leverage additional out-of-the-box integrations for more applications and platforms, gain finer-grain control over agents at scale, and easily ingest logs and container metrics for greater visibility into AWS services.

These new features allow customers to:

Reduce time to insight with serverless cloud integrations for AWS
Simplify and centralize agent management with Elastic Agent enhancements
Optimize performance of SaaS and big d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amena Siddiqi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving performance and optimizing cost on Elastic Cloud has never been easier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/cloud-hardware-profile-migration-template</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/cloud-hardware-profile-migration-template"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,

Support for new hardware profiles are continuously added to provide better price-performance on our Cloud platform.

With the release of the hardware profile migration capability, you now have the flexibility to switch between hardware profiles on your existing deployment. You can see the current hardware profile on each deployment’s Overview page, have the ability to edit the profile, and select a new one. This allows you to take advantage of more efficient hardware available on cloud providers, like Graviton2-based instances on AWS, N2 machines on GCP, or Edsv4, Ddv4, or Fsv2 VMs on Azure, with the added benefit of simplifying your migration process.

Getting started
First, click  the ‘Edit’ link next to the hardware profile name:
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuvraj Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud 8.3: Search & replicate across any cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elasticsearch-kibana-cloud-8-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In 8.3, you can search and replicate data across Elasticsearch clusters, from on-premises to cloud and vice versa. You can also query snapshots as simple archives without the need of an old Elasticsearch cluster. Achieve troubleshooting success in Kibana 8.3 with alerting in Discover, user-friendly dashboard filters, and an action that turns a visualization into a machine learning job. Plus, take advantage of migration templates that make migrating your existing deployments to the most optimal hardware type as easy as a button click.
Ready to dive in and get started? We have the links you need:


Try the new features on Elastic Cloud
Download the latest versions of Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes
Refer to the release notes on Elasticsearch, Kibana, Elastic Cloud, Elast…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adeline Tan,Brian Bergholm,George Kobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – June 27, 2022]]></title>
        <id>56fd8c2cc8a76ab65b87b44700ad43152791e34f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-27-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T21:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! It’s the beginning of a new week, and I’d like to start with a recap of the most significant AWS news from the previous 7 days. Last week was special […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new: network automation with ansible.netcommon 3.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-network-automation-with-ansible.netcommon-3.0.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-network-automation-with-ansible.netcommon-3.0.0"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the recent release of the ansible.netcommon Collection version 3.0.0, we have promoted two features as standard: libssh transport and import_modules. These features provide increased performance and resiliency for your network automation. These two features, which have been available since July 2020 (libssh) and March 2021 (import_modules), are now turned on by default for playbooks running the latest version of the netcommon Collection, so let's take a look at what makes these changes so exciting!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Case</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What makes it a profession?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42278</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/700721376/0/sethsblog~What-makes-it-a-profession/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T09:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malpractice by one of us is malpractice by all of us. When a calling turns into an industry, that can change. In an industry, it’s buyer beware. It’s us against the rest. It’s a quiet line of self-preservation. But in a profession, it’s clear that a service is on offer, and that standards and trust […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Learn Spring for GraphQL (the last two episodes: parts 7 and 8)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-the-last-two-episodes-parts-7-and-8</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-tips-learn-spring-for-graphql-the-last-two-episodes-parts-7-and-8"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In thi^^^ these installments, we continue our series introducing the Spring for GraphQL project. This series features Spring for GraphQL lead Rossen Stoyanchev (@rstoya05) - whose work you may know from basically everything in the wide and wonderful world of Springdom having to do with the web (HTTP, RSocket, WebSockets, GraphQL, JSF, MVC, etc) - and GraphQL Java engine founder and lead Andi Marek (@andimarek) and of course yours truly, Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long (@starbuxman). It provides an in-depth look at all things Spring for GraphQL.

This week I’m publishing two new installments. 

The first episode this week is part seven of eight, focusing on how to secure a Spring for GraphQL application with Spring Security. 


The last episode this week is part eig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: JVM and .NET legend Ted Neward on... just about everything]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/a-bootiful-podcast-jvm-and-net-legend-ted-neward-on-just-about-everything</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/a-bootiful-podcast-jvm-and-net-legend-ted-neward-on-just-about-everything"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, I (@starbuxman) talk to my old friend, world-famous polyglot and code curmudgeon, software philosopher, industry veteran, and legend of ecosystems aplenty, Ted Neward (@tedneward)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth Now Supports Synthetic Data Generation]]></title>
        <id>e413b62195858c26995a1f34b009da37b2b848a4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-sagemaker-ground-truth-now-supports-synthetic-data-generation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T16:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am happy to announce that you can now use Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth to generate labeled synthetic image data. Building machine learning (ML) models is an iterative process that, at a high level, starts with data collection and preparation, followed by model training and model deployment. And especially the first step, collecting large, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now in Preview – Amazon CodeWhisperer- ML-Powered Coding Companion]]></title>
        <id>43dc07fa1c6f9a27c44cdcc33417d7d205f91116</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-in-preview-amazon-codewhisperer-ml-powered-coding-companion/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T16:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I was getting ready to write this post I spent some time thinking about some of the coding tools that I have used over the course of my career. This includes the line-oriented editor that was an intrinsic part of the BASIC interpreter that I used in junior high school, the IBM keypunch that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul on Amazon ECS 0.5 Supports AWS IAM and Mesh Gateways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-5-supports-aws-iam-and-mesh-gateways</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-on-amazon-ecs-0-5-supports-aws-iam-and-mesh-gateways"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest version of HashiCorp Consul on Amazon ECS adds support for AWS IAM authentication and mesh gateways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New on HCP: Boundary, Waypoint, Drift Detection, and Azure Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-on-hcp-boundary-waypoint-and-drift-detection</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-on-hcp-boundary-waypoint-and-drift-detection"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Cloud Platform has added several new capabilities, including managed services for HashiCorp Boundary and Waypoint, and Drift Detection for Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-boot-2-7-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-boot-2-7-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T12:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.1 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 66 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.9 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-boot-2-6-9-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/23/spring-boot-2-6-9-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T11:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.9 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 44 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Advantage in Learning from Experiments]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/quantum-advantage-in-learning-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/quantum-advantage-in-learning-from.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T18:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jarrod McClean, Staff Research Scientist, Google Quantum AI, and Hsin-Yuan Huang, Graduate Student, Caltech 
In efforts to learn about the quantum world, scientists face a big obstacle: their classical experience of the world. Whenever a quantum system is measured, the act of this measurement destroys the “quantumness” of the state. For example, if the quantum state is in a superposition of two locations, where it can seem to be in two places at the same time, once it is measured, it will randomly appear either ”here” or “there”, but not both. We only ever see the classical shadows cast by this strange quantum world. 
A growing number of experiments are implementing machine learning (ML) algorithms to aid in analyzing data, but these have the same limitations as the people they a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Urban Trees Across North America with the Auto Arborist Dataset]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/mapping-urban-trees-across-north.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/mapping-urban-trees-across-north.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T18:04:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Beery, Student Researcher, and Jonathan Huang, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception Team 
Over four billion people live in cities around the globe, and while most people interact daily with others — at the grocery store, on public transit, at work — they may take for granted their frequent interactions with the diverse plants and animals that comprise fragile urban ecosystems. Trees in cities, called urban forests, provide critical benefits for public health and wellbeing and will prove integral to urban climate adaptation. They filter air and water, capture stormwater runoff, sequester atmospheric carbon dioxide, and limit erosion and drought. Shade from urban trees reduces energy-expensive cooling costs and mitigates urban heat islands. In the US alone, urban fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modeling a Bill’s Journey through the U.S. House of Representatives]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57197</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/modeling-a-bills-journey-through-the-u-s-house-of-representatives/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bill's journey through the U.S. House of Representatives is modeled in Camunda Platform 8 and BPMN. Along the way, see how forms incorporate human tasks throughout the process and how DMN helps minimize errors.
The post Modeling a Bill’s Journey through the U.S. House of Representatives appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第211話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270296674428450886</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270296674428450886"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digitally signing Ansible Content Collections using private automation hub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/digitally-signing-ansible-content-collections-using-private-automation-hub</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/digitally-signing-ansible-content-collections-using-private-automation-hub"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform can manage and execute automation made from many different origins, coming from Red Hat product teams, ISV partners, community and private contributors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.11 Adds Kubernetes Secrets Engine, PKI Updates, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-11</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-11"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.11 focuses on improving Vault’s core workflows and making key features production-ready.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Launch and Free Public Beta of HCP Boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-and-free-public-beta-of-hcp-boundary</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-launch-and-free-public-beta-of-hcp-boundary"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary is now available as a managed service on the HashiCorp Cloud Platform in  free public beta to standardize secure remote access to critical infrastructure regardless of where it resides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.3 Introduces HA Logical Gateways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-3-introduces-ha-logical-gateways</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-3-introduces-ha-logical-gateways"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest release of the HashiCorp Consul API Gateway allows users to generate multiple instances of a logical gateway — avoiding single points of failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.13 Tech Preview: Cluster Peering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-tech-preview-cluster-peering</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-13-tech-preview-cluster-peering"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cluster peering in Consul 1.13 offers a whole new model of how Consul handles cross-cluster federation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Azure to go GA, Plus More Consul News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure-to-go-ga-plus-more-consul-news</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure-to-go-ga-plus-more-consul-news"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul is becoming generally available on Azure, Consul API Gateway version 0.3 is going GA, and Consul 1.13 is due later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IoT ExpressLink Now Generally Available – Quickly Develop Devices That Connect Securely to AWS Cloud]]></title>
        <id>487d07cf76d37f913a79c647cc30be56978e730d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-iot-expresslink-now-generally-available-quickly-develop-devices-that-connect-securely-to-aws-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T14:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2021, we introduced AWS IoT ExpressLink, software for partner-manufactured connectivity modules that makes it easier and faster for original equipment manufacturers to connect any type of product to the cloud, such as industrial sensors, small and large home appliances, irrigation systems, and medical devices. Today we announce the general availability of AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at CVPR 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/google-at-cvpr-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/google-at-cvpr-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T14:09:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shaina Mehta and Kristen Borg, Program Managers 
This week marks the beginning of the premier annual Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition conference (CVPR 2022), held both in-person in New Orleans, LA and virtually. As a leader in computer vision research and a Platinum Sponsor, Google will have a strong presence across CVPR 2022 with over 80 papers being presented at the main conference and active involvement in a number of conference workshops and tutorials. 
If you are attending CVPR this year, please stop by our booth and chat with our researchers who are actively exploring the latest machine learning techniques for application to various areas of machine perception. Our researchers will also be available to talk about and demo several recent efforts, including on-device M…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - June 21st, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/21/this-week-in-spring-june-21st-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/21/this-week-in-spring-june-21st-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you? It’s been a hot minute since we last chatted. I was in Germany this time last week. Now, I’m back in beautiful San Francisco. Today the weather will climb to a monumental 84 F! That’s very unusual, for any time of the year, here in San Francisco. Most places here in San Francisco don’t have air conditioning. Some have heating. I bought a brand new condo in 2014 and it didn’t have air conditioning. You just open the window. I am privileged enough that I have air conditioning today, of course. I mention all this to say that it’s hot here! I worry for the elderly! When it gets this hot, the YMCA and other organizations typically invite elderly people to come in and get some cool air and water. It’s dangerous. Some days it gets even hotter. Very rare, but it does happen. I hope you’re all doing well. Take care of yourselves and each other, my friends. 

And, speaking of being hot, let’s look at this week’s roundup of the latest-and-greatest that’s hot off the press! 


  
Bootiful Podcast: Spring Framework contributor Sébastien Deleuze on GraalVM, AOT, project Leyden, and WebAssembly

  
CVE report published for Spring Cloud Function

  
Debugging Collections, Streams and Watch Renderers

  
Difference Between Flux.create and Flux.generate

  
Handle Spring Security Exceptions With @ExceptionHandler

  
MongoDB Composite Key With Spring Data

  
Spring Authorization Server 0.3.1 available now

  
Monitoring Spring Boot applications using Spring Boot Admin

  
Spring Data 2021.2.1 and 2021.1.5 released

  
Spring Data JPA – Run an App Without a Database

  
Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression Injection Vulnerability (CVE-2022-22980)

  
Spring Framework 5.3.21 available now

  
Spring Security 5.7.2 and 5.6.6 available now

  
Spring Tools 4.15.0 released

  
Spring Tools 4.15.1 released

  
What are the Spring Boot Default Memory Settings?

  
A Guide to Docker Private Registry

  
Is There a Destructor in Java?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HashiCorp Developer Site is Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hashicorp-developer-site-is-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hashicorp-developer-site-is-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our new documentation platform makes it easy to learn from dozens of interactive lab environments, hundreds of tutorials, and thousands of reference docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Adds Drift Detection for Infrastructure Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-drift-detection-for-infrastructure-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-drift-detection-for-infrastructure-management"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drift Detection for Terraform Cloud continuously checks infrastructure state to detect and notify operators of any changes, minimizing risk, downtime, and costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the HCP Waypoint Private Beta Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcp-waypoint-private-beta-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hcp-waypoint-private-beta-program"/>
        <updated>2022-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HCP Waypoint Private Beta Program allows select early adopters to onboard applications and try out HCP Waypoint to develop a proof of concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.7.2 and 5.6.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-security-5-7-2-and-5-6-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-security-5-7-2-and-5-6-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Security 5.7.2 and 5.6.6 are available now.



You can find more details about the respective releases here and
 here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – High Volume Outbound Communication with Amazon Connect Outbound Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>a20b9048be0b3be3a34bbd843c36e4433e02d727</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-high-volume-outbound-communication-with-amazon-connect-outbound-campaigns/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T19:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new high volume outbound communication capability in Amazon Connect which was announced at Enterprise Connect last year, is now generally available to all. It is named Amazon Connect outbound campaigns. If you haven’t heard about Amazon Connect, it is an easy-to-use cloud contact center service that helps companies of any size deliver superior customer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo – UX/Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64531</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-ux-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T18:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I took the road less traveled, and that has made all the difference.
The post DevOps Dojo – UX/Accessibility appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – June 20, 2022]]></title>
        <id>a332bdf7b28369cb096731e12bebdd69553bacc1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-20-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T17:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Last Week’s Launches It’s been a quiet week on the AWS News Blog, however a glance at What’s New page shows the various service teams have been busy as usual. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Phases of Infrastructure Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-3-phases-of-infrastructure-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-3-phases-of-infrastructure-automation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From adoption to standardization to operating and optimizing at scale, the evolution of infrastructure automation is critical to modern hybrid and multi-cloud environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 0.3.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-authorization-server-0-3-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-authorization-server-0-3-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Authorization Server 0.3.1.



You can download it from Maven Central by using the module coordinates:




implementation 'org.springframework.security:spring-security-oauth2-authorization-server:0.3.1'




See the release notes for complete details.



This release includes downgrading to JDK 1.8 baseline along with some minor enhancements and bug fixes.



To get started using Spring Authorization Server, see the Getting Started chapter of the reference documentation and the samples to become familiar with setup and configuration.



We would love to gather your feedback as we strive to improve and build upon this release.



Project Page | GitHub Issues | ZenHub Board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Automation Controller for API Driven Workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/scaling-automation-controller-for-api-driven-workloads</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/scaling-automation-controller-for-api-driven-workloads"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When scaling automation controller in an enterprise organization, administrators are faced with more clients automating their interactions with its REST API. As with any web application, automation controller has a finite capacity to serve web requests, and  web clients can experience degraded service if that capacity is met or superseded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elijah Delee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.2.1 and 2021.1.5 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-2021-2-1-and-2021-1-5-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-2021-2-1-and-2021-1-5-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T12:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce Spring Data service releases 2021.2.1 and 2021.1.5.
Both releases ship with a fix for mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.
For your convenience, Spring Boot 2.7.1 respective 2.6.9 are going to pick up these releases in the upcoming days.

In addition, these releases include fixes for one vulnerability:


  
CVE-2022-22980
 “Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression Injection Vulnerability”
 SpEL injection attack in MongoDB applications through repository query methods annotated with @Query or @Aggregation using parametrized SpEL statements with non-sanitized input.
 Severity: High


These new versions are recommended upgrades for all Spring Data production scenarios.

To round things off, here are the links to the individual modules, chan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression Injection Vulnerability (CVE-2022-22980)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-mongodb-spel-expression-injection-vulnerability-cve-2022-22980</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/20/spring-data-mongodb-spel-expression-injection-vulnerability-cve-2022-22980"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T12:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates 


  
[06-20] CVE-2022-22980 is published

  
[06-20] Spring Data MongoDB 3.4.1 and 3.3.5 are available


Table of Contents


  
Overview

  
Vulnerability

  
Am I Impacted

  
Status

  
Suggested Workarounds


Overview

We would like to announce that we have released Spring Data MongoDB 3.4.1 and 3.3.5 to address the following CVE report:


  
CVE-2022-22980: Spring Data MongoDB SpEL Expression injection vulnerability through annotated repository query methods


This vulnerability was responsibly reported by Zewei Zhang from NSFOCUS TIANJI Lab on Monday, June 13 2022. The full report will be published to MITRE and as security advisory under tanzu.vmware.com/security in the upcoming days.
Vulnerability

The vulnerability affects Spring Data MongoDB applications u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.15.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/18/spring-tools-4-15-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/18/spring-tools-4-15-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.15.1 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: VScode incorrectly suggests removing @Autowired annotation from methods (#787)

  
(Spring Boot) fixed: VScode quick fix should not suggest removing @Autowired annotation from JUnit tests (#786)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Not able to extract the new version of spring-tool-suite-4-4.15.0.RELEASE-e4.24.0-win32.win32.x86_64.self-extracting.jar on windows 11 (#788)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: Cannot open Spring Boot Language Server Java Editor settings menu (#789)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-06-17-4151-release-incl-language-servers-version-1360

Spring Tools 4.15.2 is scheduled to be released in early August 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stores from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 17.06.2022]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64512</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stores-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-17-06-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T10:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last weekend was the Scottish Summit, while this event is local to the UK, people flew in globally to speak and attend one of the best Azure events around! There were so many great sessions from technical folks in the community and an amazing keynote from Dona Sarkar about accessibility.
The post Top Stores from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 17.06.2022 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Service Mesh Support for AWS Lambda Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul support for AWS Lambda is now available in public beta enabling services in the mesh to invoke AWS Lambda functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​HashiCorp Recognized as a Best Workplace in the Bay Area]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-recognized-as-a-best-workplace-in-the-bay-area</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-recognized-as-a-best-workplace-in-the-bay-area"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp was ranked 28 on the 2022 Great Place to Work and Fortune magazine Best Workplaces in the Bay Area list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Can’t I Delete a Process Definition in Camunda Platform 8?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57095</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/why-cant-i-delete-a-process-definition-in-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deleting process definitions in Camunda Platform 8 requires complex behavior across multiple components in the system.
The post Why Can’t I Delete a Process Definition in Camunda Platform 8? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bootiful Podcast: Spring Framework contributor Sébastien Deleuze on GraalVM, AOT, project Leyden, and WebAssembly]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/16/bootiful-podcast-spring-framework-contributor-s-bastien-deleuze-on-graalvm-aot-project-leyden-and-webassembly</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/16/bootiful-podcast-spring-framework-contributor-s-bastien-deleuze-on-graalvm-aot-project-leyden-and-webassembly"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Spring Framework contributor Sébastien Deleuze (@sdeleuze) on GraalVM, AOT, project Leyden, and WebAssembly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M3 (codename Kilburn) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m3-codename-kilburn-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m3-codename-kilburn-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T06:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Milestone 3 (M3) of the Spring Cloud 2022.0.0 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2022.0.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2022.0.0 Release Train

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.

Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M3 is compatible with Spring Boot 3.0.0-M3.
Spring Cloud Stream


  
Enhanced support for Kafka “tombstone” records via recently added support for BiFunction/BiConsumer

  
Added support for function-based error-handling, thus no longer requiring annotations


Spring Cloud Kubernetes


  
Load Config Maps and Secrets using spring.config.import removing the need to use B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE report published for Spring Cloud Function]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/cve-report-published-for-spring-cloud-function</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/cve-report-published-for-spring-cloud-function"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released Spring Cloud Function 3.2.6 to address the following CVE report.


  
CVE-2202-22979: Spring Cloud Function Dos Vulnerability 


Please review the information in the CVE report and upgrade immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.15.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-tools-4-15-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-tools-4-15-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.15.0 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
updated to Eclipse 2022-06 release (new and noteworthy)


fixes and improvements


  
(Spring Boot) fixed: vscode-sts: an edge case of workspace symbol for @PutMapping (#781)

  
(VSCode) fixed: Failed to refresh live data from process 12704 - com.xxxx.xx.xxx.BillingServiceApp after retries: 10 (#748)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: The Spring Boot Language Server is not immediately shutdown after closing the last open editor to avoid the need to restart the server when you open the next file (related to #568)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: When opening symbols, open the compilation unit from the relevant project (#769)

  
(Eclipse) fixed: The issue with the internal web browser not being able to open HTTP URLs on macOS got fixed. If you prefer to use the internal browser instead of an external one, you can make that switch in the preferences.

  
(Concourse) fixed: Update Concourse registry-image schema (#777)

  
(Concourse) fixed: Add registry_mirror & across as a known properties (#752)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-06-15-4150-release-incl-language-servers-version-1340

Spring Tools 4.15.1 is scheduled to be released in early August 2022.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​Terraform Cloud Run Tasks with Styra DAS Provides OPA Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-with-styra-das-provides-opa-validation</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-with-styra-das-provides-opa-validation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration of HashiCorp Terraform with OPA-founder Styra allows users to validate Terraform infrastructure as code with Open Policy Agent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Netflix Content Engineering makes a federated graph searchable (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/49348511c06c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/how-netflix-content-engineering-makes-a-federated-graph-searchable-part-2-49348511c06c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Alex Hutter, Falguni Jhaveri, and Senthil Sayeebaba]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure - Network Access - blog #2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you to Hicham Mourad and Scott Harwell for co-authoring this blog.
 
Introduction
 
In this blog series, we will continue discussing the deployment of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Harwell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.21 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-framework-5-3-21-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/06/15/spring-framework-5-3-21-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T09:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.21 is available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.21 includes 22 fixes and improvements.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe Is Back: Join Us in Amsterdam or Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years as a fully digital event, HashiConf Europe will once again return to Amsterdam on 20-22 June 2022. Here’s what you can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scanned Objects by Google Research: A Dataset of 3D-Scanned Common Household Items]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/scanned-objects-by-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/scanned-objects-by-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:06:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Laura Downs and Anthony Francis, Software Engineers, Robotics at Google  
Many recent advances in computer vision and robotics rely on deep learning, but training deep learning models requires a wide variety of data to generalize to new scenarios. Historically, deep learning for computer vision has relied on datasets with millions of items that were gathered by web scraping, examples of which include ImageNet, Open Images, YouTube-8M, and COCO. However, the process of creating these datasets can be labor-intensive, and can still exhibit labeling errors that can distort the perception of progress. Furthermore, this strategy does not readily generalize to arbitrary three-dimensional shapes or real-world robotic data.  
 

Real-world robotic data collection is very useful, but diffi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=57164</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1. Check out the latest improvements including the Management Dashboard, new reports, and Spring Boot migration. 
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56809</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/camunda-automation-platform-7180-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the second alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7.18. See what's new and learn how you can contribute. 
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – June 13, 2022]]></title>
        <id>f62346f0e4c3f5f23df31341fcd4572e7dafb8ca</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-june-13-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T19:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Last Week’s Launches I made a short trip to Austin, Texas last week in order to visit and learn from some customers. As is always the case, the days when […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure - Network Access - blog #1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-microsoft-azure-network-access-blog-1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you to Hicham Mourad and Scott Harwell for co-authoring this blog.
 
Introduction
 
In this blog series we will discuss the deployment of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure, specifically focusing on the deployment access types and what that means for accessing Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Azure after deployment completion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Harwell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Process and Task Events with Camunda Platform, AWS Kinesis, and Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56867</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/integrating-process-and-task-events-with-camunda-platform-aws-kinesis-and-elasticsearch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Camunda Community Summit 2022, Fidelity Investments Director of Architecture Harish Malavade shared a behind-the-scenes look at Fidelity’s digital automation platform that uses Camunda as its core workflow engine. Here are the technical details. 
The post Integrating Process and Task Events with Camunda Platform, AWS Kinesis, and Elasticsearch appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harish Malavade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 R6id Instances with NVMe Local Instance Storage of up to 7.6 TB]]></title>
        <id>a84adda0652b06fccf7c94df6d0eeed2bdeb3602</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-r6id-instances/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T21:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2021, we launched the memory-optimized Amazon EC2 R6i instances, our sixth-generation x86-based offering powered by 3rd Generation Intel Xeon Scalable processors (code named Ice Lake). Today I am excited to announce a disk variant of the R6i instance: the Amazon EC2 R6id instances with non-volatile memory express (NVMe) SSD local instance storage. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LIMoE: Learning Multiple Modalities with One Sparse Mixture-of-Experts Model]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/limoe-learning-multiple-modalities-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/limoe-learning-multiple-modalities-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:49:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Basil Mustafa, Research Software Engineer and Carlos Riquelme, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain team 
Sparse models stand out among the most promising approaches for the future of deep learning. Instead of every part of a model processing every input (“dense” modeling), sparse models employing conditional computation learn to route individual inputs to different “experts” in a potentially huge network. This has many benefits. First, model size can increase while keeping computational cost constant — an effective and environmentally friendlier way to scale models, which is often key to high performance. Sparsity also naturally compartmentalizes neural networks. Dense models that learn many different tasks simultaneously (multitask) or sequentially (continual learning) of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copy a work item type using Azure DevOps API’s]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64424</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/copy-a-work-item-type-using-azure-devops-apis-undocumented/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, we all love how we can manage engagements in Azure DevOps (ADO). We can create Epics, Features, User Stories and track our progress on Kanban boards. You can customize work item types to suit the needs of your business and project with ease.
The post Copy a work item type using Azure DevOps API’s appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Art Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pump-Up your ITIL with Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/pump-up-your-itil-with-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/pump-up-your-itil-with-automation"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of automation and agility, it seems that Information Technology Infrastructure Library (ITIL) doesn’t have a role to play anymore, being marked as an “old school” framework. Can it be the end of the methodology after it served numerous IT organizations for so long as a guideline and blueprint for their processes?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Lavarde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernize Your Mainframe Applications & Deploy Them In The Cloud]]></title>
        <id>6b1b29b8416988254d5bb4b9eb7bf37cc88ab414</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/modernize-your-mainframe-applications-deploy-them-in-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are launching AWS Mainframe Modernization service to help you modernize your mainframe applications and deploy them to AWS fully-managed runtime environments. This new service also provides tools and resources to help you plan and implement migration and modernization. Since the introduction of System/360 on April 7 1964, mainframe computers have enabled many industries […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at Cisco Live: Demos, Presentations, Experts, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-cisco-live-demos-presentations-experts-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-cisco-live-demos-presentations-experts-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re at Cisco Live, June 12-16. Find out more details in our pre-event blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo – OKRs (Objectives and Key Results)]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64394</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-okrs-objectives-and-key-results/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is vision?
The post DevOps Dojo – OKRs (Objectives and Key Results) appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Desktop App with React and Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=56716</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/06/building-a-desktop-app-with-react-and-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow along as Principal Developer Advocate David Simmons uses Camunda Platform 8 and React to build an app that requests, fetches, and saves data.
The post Building a Desktop App with React and Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS MGN Update – Configure DR, Convert CentOS Linux to Rocky Linux, and Convert SUSE Linux Subscription]]></title>
        <id>5d64e7849cb97cd88b049a203409a40516c031fb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-mgn-update-configure-dr-convert-centos-linux-to-rocky-linux-and-convert-suse-linux-subscription/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just about a year ago, Channy showed you How to Use the New AWS Application Migration Server for Lift-and-Shift Migrations. In his post, he introduced AWS Application Migration Service (AWS MGN) and said: With AWS MGN, you can minimize time-intensive, error-prone manual processes by automatically replicating entire servers and converting your source servers from physical, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第210話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270296674398611831</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270296674398611831"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 private automation hub features about automation execution environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/8-private-automation-hub-features-about-automation-execution-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/8-private-automation-hub-features-about-automation-execution-environments"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.1 introduced automation execution environments, which is a new way to package automation into a container runtime environment. In addition, private automation hub also joined the party by adding significant support for execution environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End-to-end Generative Pre-training for Multimodal Video Captioning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/end-to-end-generative-pre-training-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/06/end-to-end-generative-pre-training-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Paul Hongsuck Seo and Arsha Nagrani, Research Scientists, Google Research, Perception Team  
Multimodal video captioning systems utilize both the video frames and speech to generate natural language descriptions (captions) of videos. Such systems are stepping stones towards the longstanding goal of building multimodal conversational systems that effortlessly communicate with users while perceiving environments through multimodal input streams.  
 Unlike video understanding tasks (e.g., video classification and retrieval) where the key challenge lies in processing and understanding multimodal input videos, the task of multimodal video captioning includes the additional challenge of generating grounded captions. The most widely adopted approach for this task is to train an encoder-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Azure is Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-on-azure"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul on Microsoft Azure is now available in public beta. Get started today with a secure, resilient service mesh for connecting applications running in Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>