<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-08T01:16:03.274Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-08T01:16:03.274Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards ML-enabled cleaning robots]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/towards-ml-enabled-cleaning-robots.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/towards-ml-enabled-cleaning-robots.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T21:06:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Thomas Lew, Research Intern, and Montserrat Gonzalez Arenas, Research Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team


Over the past several years, the capabilities of robotic systems have improved dramatically. As the technology continues to improve and robotic agents are more routinely deployed in real-world environments, their capacity to assist in day-to-day activities will take on increasing importance. Repetitive tasks like wiping surfaces, folding clothes, and cleaning a room seem well-suited for robots, but remain challenging for robotic systems designed for structured environments like factories. Performing these types of tasks in more complex environments, like offices or homes, requires dealing with greater levels of environmental variability captured by high-dimensional sensor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Directing ML toward natural hazard mitigation through collaboration]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/directing-ml-toward-natural-hazard.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/directing-ml-toward-natural-hazard.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T16:09:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Oren Gilon, Software Engineer, and Grey Nearing, Research Scientist, Google Research




Floods are the most common type of natural disaster, affecting more than 250 million people globally each year. As part of Google's Crisis Response and our efforts to address the climate crisis, we are using machine learning (ML) models for Flood Forecasting to alert people in areas that are impacted before disaster strikes.


Collaboration between researchers in the industry and academia is essential for accelerating progress towards mutual goals in ML-related research. Indeed, Google's current ML-based flood forecasting approach was developed in collaboration with researchers (1, 2) at the Johannes Kepler University in Vienna, Austria, the University of Alabama, and the Hebrew University of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What developers need to know about generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-07-what-developers-need-to-know-about-generative-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-07-what-developers-need-to-know-about-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T15:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI has been dominating the news lately—but what exactly is it? Here’s what you need to know, and what it means for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · April 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-07-game-bytes-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-07-game-bytes-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T14:32:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two kinds of salad]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45535</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/734007668/0/sethsblog~Two-kinds-of-salad/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T10:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A useful metaphor for freelancers and small businesses. Every good restaurant should have two different salads on the menu. The boring salad is the regular kind. It’s there for people who know that they want a reliable, repeatable, unremarkable salad. It’s the safe part of a safe meal. It might remind them of their childhood […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Project Starline improves remote communication]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/how-project-starline-improves-remote.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/how-project-starline-improves-remote.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T19:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Greg Blascovich and Eric Gomez, User Researchers, Google




As companies settle into a new normal of hybrid and distributed work, remote communication technology remains critical for connecting and collaborating with colleagues. While this technology has improved, the core user experience often falls short: conversation can feel stilted, attention can be difficult to maintain, and usage can be fatiguing. 





Project Starline renders people at natural scale on a 3D display and enables natural eye contact.

Project Starline, a technology project that combines advances in hardware and software to create a remote communication experience that feels like you’re together, even when you’re thousands of miles apart. This perception of co-presence is created by representing users in 3D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building GitHub with Ruby and Rails]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-06-building-github-with-ruby-and-rails/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-06-building-github-with-ruby-and-rails/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T18:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the beginning, GitHub.com has been a Ruby on Rails monolith. Today, the application is nearly two million lines of code and more than 1,000 engineers collaborate on it daily. We deploy as often as 20 times a day, and nearly every week one of those deploys is a Rails upgrade. Upgrading Rails weekly Every [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-trained Gaussian processes for Bayesian optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/pre-trained-gaussian-processes-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/pre-trained-gaussian-processes-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T17:02:00.009Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zi Wang and Kevin Swersky, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 





Bayesian optimization (BayesOpt) is a powerful tool widely used for global optimization tasks, such as hyperparameter tuning, protein engineering, synthetic chemistry, robot learning, and even baking cookies. BayesOpt is a great strategy for these problems because they all involve optimizing black-box functions that are expensive to evaluate. A black-box function’s underlying mapping from inputs (configurations of the thing we want to optimize) to outputs (a measure of performance) is unknown. However, we can attempt to understand its internal workings by evaluating the function for different combinations of inputs. Because each evaluation can be computationally expensive, we need to find the best i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2.5 Is Out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=317305</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/04/webstorm-2022-2-5/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T16:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fifth bug-fix update for v2022.2 is now available. You can upgrade to the latest build using the Toolbox App or via our website. WebStorm 2022.2.5 brings the following fixes: We’ve added fixes to cover new cases with the screen flickering in full-screen mode on macOS Ventura (JBR-4959). We’ve fixed the issue causing blank popup […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwning Pixel 6 with a leftover patch]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-06-pwning-pixel-6-with-a-leftover-patch/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-06-pwning-pixel-6-with-a-leftover-patch/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T16:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, I’ll look at a security-related change in version r40p0 of the Arm Mali driver that was AWOL in the January update of the Pixel bulletin, where other patches from r40p0 was applied, and how these two lines of changes can be exploited to gain arbitrary kernel code execution and root from a malicious app. This highlights how treacherous it can be when backporting security changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy’s New Projects and Topics: April Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=341057</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/04/06/jetbrains-academys-new-projects-and-topics-april-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At JetBrains Academy, we believe that learning can be both educational and entertaining. Our latest projects let you build your own traffic light, create a hospital appointment booking system, and even a password hacker project – not coincidentally combining learning and fun. This month we’ve released 10 new projects and 36 topics across a variety […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasiia Pogorelova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.1.1 Bug-Fix Update: Critical Fixes for Rename, LLDB on Ubuntu, and QML!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=341025</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/04/clion-2023-1-1-bug-fix-update-critical-fixes-for-rename-lldb-on-ubuntu-and-qml/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T15:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.1 was released recently with the following key enhancements: Disassemble on demand, and other debugger enhancements. Integration with vcpkg. A new experimental Clangd-based indexer to speed up the Find Usages action. A huge update to the new UI. We found a few issues in the release, which we’ve addressed with this new bug-fix update, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | April 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=340407</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/04/06/net-annotated-monthly-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? JavaScript was released on December 4, 1995, after being quickly developed over 10 days, to work with the Netscape browser. It stuck around, became popular, and in 1997 folks finally recognized the need for formal structure and support, via ECMA. The rest is history as it has taken over the web. .NET […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding free and open Elastic APM as part of your Elastic Observability deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post, we showed you how to get started with the free and open tier of Elastic Observability. Below, we'll walk through what you need to do to expand your deployment so you can start gathering metrics from application performance monitoring (APM) or "tracing" data in your observability cluster, for free.
What is APM?
Application performance monitoring lets you see where your applications spend their time, what they are doing, what other applications or services they are calling, and what errors or exceptions they are encountering.

In addition, APM also lets you see history and trends for key performance indicators, such as latency and throughput, as well as transaction and dependency information:

Whether you're setting up alerts for SLA breaches, trying to gauge the impact of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding free and open Elastic APM as part of your Elastic Observability deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to gather application trace data and store it alongside the logs and metrics from your applications and infrastructure with Elastic Observability and Elastic APM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode 2023.1 Bug-Fix Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=340973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2023/04/appcode-2023-1-bug-fix-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T13:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, AppCode 2023.1 has just been released with fixes for Xcode 14.3 compatibility, Swift refactorings and intentions, the IDE’s UI, and Kotlin Multiplatform Mobile. On December 14, 2022, along with the AppCode 2022.3 release, we sunsetted the product and stopped sales. While we’ve refocused the team’s efforts in other directions, we’ve kept providing technical support […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Replacing bad systems with bad systems]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45575</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/733895525/0/sethsblog~Replacing-bad-systems-with-bad-systems/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A metaphor involving parking meters. Over the years, parking meters in town have evolved into a cumbersome, awkward system. Coins are heavy and you need to have them handy, meters need to be reinforced against theft and breakage, town employees have to empty the coins and securely deliver them to the bank, meter feeding allows […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugger Upskill: Variables, Evaluate Expression, and Watches]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=339251</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/04/debugger-upskill-variables-evaluate-expression-watches/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T06:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our previous article, you learned to move through your code with basic and advanced stepping actions. Now that you know how to navigate your code and control its execution step by step, we can look at the tools for analyzing your program’s state and testing scenarios for bug fixes.  In this Debugger Upskill blog, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Maryasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: José Paumard, Java Champion alumnus and Java legend, on Project Loom, Valhalla, and more, from Devnexus 2023!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/06/a-bootiful-podcast-jose-paumard-java-champion-alumnus-and-java-legend-on</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/06/a-bootiful-podcast-jose-paumard-java-champion-alumnus-and-java-legend-on"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Keeping Kubernetes Secure with Updated Go Versions]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/06/keeping-kubernetes-secure-with-updated-go-versions/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/06/keeping-kubernetes-secure-with-updated-go-versions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jordan Liggitt (Google)
The problem
Since v1.19 (released in 2020), the Kubernetes project provides 12-14 months of patch releases for each minor version.
This enables users to qualify and adopt Kubernetes versions in an annual upgrade cycle and receive security fixes for a year.
The Go project releases new minor versions twice a year,
and provides security fixes for the last two minor versions, resulting in about a year of support for each Go version.
Even though each new Kubernetes minor version is built with a supported Go version when it is first released,
that Go version falls out of support before the Kubernetes minor version does,
and the lengthened Kubernetes patch support since v1.19 only widened that gap.
At the time this was written, just over half of all Go patch releas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul Service (HCS) on Azure End of Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-consul-service-hcs-on-azure-end-of-life</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-consul-service-hcs-on-azure-end-of-life"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCS on Azure has been deprecated. HCP Consul on Azure is the preferred way to run your HashiCorp Consul clusters on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bring your enterprise together with enterprise accounts for all]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-05-bring-your-enterprise-together-with-enterprise-accounts-for-all/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-05-bring-your-enterprise-together-with-enterprise-accounts-for-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T17:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With enterprise accounts for all, your organization can take advantage of all that GitHub Enterprise has to offer, from GitHub Actions and GitHub Advanced Security, to Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: March 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-05-github-availability-report-march-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-05-github-availability-report-march-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T16:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In March, we experienced six incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. This report also sheds light into a February incident that resulted in degraded performance for GitHub Codespaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new Terraform Associate 003 Certification exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-new-terraform-associate-003-certification-exam</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-new-terraform-associate-003-certification-exam"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HashiCorp’s updated Terraform Associate certification impacts your current and future Terraform Associate credentials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building organization-wide governance and re-use for CI/CD and automation with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-05-building-organization-wide-governance-and-re-use-for-ci-cd-and-automation-with-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-05-building-organization-wide-governance-and-re-use-for-ci-cd-and-automation-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T15:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of us are aware of the benefits that a strong focus on automation can bring, particularly in our development workflow and DevOps lifecycle. But silos across businesses can lead to duplication of effort, and potential to lose out on best practices. In this post, we’ll explore how CI/CD can be shared across your entire organization alongside policies, for a well-governed experience with GitHub Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving Build Server Scalability Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=340634</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/04/solving-build-server-scalability-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few months, the TeamCity team has been busy boosting the performance and stability of our build server. In this post, I’ll explain what steps we took and share the issues we’ve faced. First, some numbers On a typical working day, the load on the build server increases after 14:00 CET and starts […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavel Sher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging Kibana Dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/debugging-kibana-dashboards</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/debugging-kibana-dashboards"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kibana dashboards allow you to build visualizations quickly and easily on top of data indexed within Elasticsearch. However, the UI abstraction over Elasticsearch can make it tricky to diagnose performance issues in individual panels — especially for developers used to diving into the detail of implementations using debuggers and other profiling tools.
This blog introduces four approaches to help investigate and diagnose performance issues with Kibana dashboards. Specifically, we'll cover the use of Elastic application performance monitoring (APM), debugging via Chrome Developer Tools and profiling, inspecting individual panels via the Inspector, and the Elasticsearch Slow Log to identify the cause of dashboard slowness.
APM
When faced with a slow dashboard, ruling out slow performance cau…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging Kibana Dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/debugging-kibana-dashboards</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/debugging-kibana-dashboards"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diagnosing Kibana dashboard performance issues is tricky. This blog introduces how Elastic APM, Kibana Inspector, Chrome Developer Tools and the Elasticsearch Slow Log can help investigate and diagnose performance issues in Kibana dashboards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Richmond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ 2023.1: Call Tracking, Macro Expansion Preview, and Support for C++23 Features]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rscpp&amp;p=340363</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rscpp/2023/04/05/resharper-cpp-2023-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T12:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just released ReSharper C++ 2023.1! This update brings support for new C++20 and C++23 features as well as improvements for C++20 modules, Call tracking, macro substitution previews, context actions for refactorings, and file templates for Unreal Engine tests. To learn about all of the improvements in this release, check out our What’s New page. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elvira Mustafina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dotCover, dotMemory, dotPeek, and dotTrace 2023.1 Release!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=339947</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/04/05/dottools-2023-1-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T12:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dotCover 2023.1, dotMemory 2023.1, dotPeek 2023.1, and dotTrace 2023.1 have been released and are ready for download!  Let’s take a look at the most important updates for these tools. dotTrace The standalone version of dotTrace is now available on Linux and macOS as Beta. You can perform the full profiling workflow on these operating systems, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2023.1 Comes With Enhanced C# Support, Exciting Updates for C++, and More!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=339633</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/04/05/resharper-2023-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T12:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, ReSharper 2023.1 and new versions of other JetBrains .NET tools have just been released. In this article, we’ll cover the highlights of this major update for ReSharper and touch on the features coming to ReSharper C++.  To learn more about our other .NET tools, including dotCover, dotMemory, dotPeek, and dotTrace, please check out […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2023.1: Enhanced C# Support, Best-in-class GameDev Features, and Much More!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=339804</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/04/05/rider-2023-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T12:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, The latest major Rider update has just been published! We invite you to explore the new features and improvements in the 2023.1 version of your favorite cross-platform .NET IDE.  C# support Reducing the number of lookups in collections Rider 2023.1 introduces a set of inspections with corresponding quick-fixes to optimize and speed up […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In and out]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44200</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/733792928/0/sethsblog~In-and-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T08:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lots of organizations (and individuals) have plans and processes for getting the word out. In fact, we spend trillions of dollars doing so. Do you have a plan for getting the word in? Is it simply random chance that some ideas get to you and your team, that cultural and technical awareness just happens? How […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Diana Zuniga on finding a job after graduation, being a Latina in tech, and her role as a sales development representative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-sales-development-representative</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-sales-development-representative"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Diana Zuniga graduated from college in 2022 she didn’t know what her next step was. She joined Elastic through Elastigrad in June 2022 as a sales development representative. Read more about her journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying Elastic Security for Cloud and its capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-elastic-security-for-cloud-capabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-elastic-security-for-cloud-capabilities"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are moving to the cloud to meet growing customer demands. Security in the cloud must go hand-in-hand with application development. Learn how Elastic Security's Cloud Security capabilities help organizations secure their AWS cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sneha Sachidananda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Diana Zuniga on finding a job after graduation, being a Latina in tech, and her role as a sales development representative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-sales-development-representative</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastigrad-sales-development-representative"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
When Diana Zuniga graduated from college in 2022 she didn’t know what her next step was. 

“I was lost,” she says. “As a first generation American, I don’t have anyone to look up to and ask questions to. I was trying to find myself.”
She earned a degree in psychology and was considering going back to school, but she had always had an interest in working for a tech company.


“I knew that tech was a booming industry, so I was interested to see how I could bring in my skills and my psych background,” Diana says. “Being a Latina, I was scared to go into this industry where people like me aren't really seen, so I wanted to become that representation for others like myself.”


As Diana searchedroles at tech companies on LinkedIn, she came across the ElastiGrad program and applied. 


ElastiGr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying Elastic Security for Cloud and its capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-elastic-security-for-cloud-capabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-elastic-security-for-cloud-capabilities"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Moving to the Cloud introduces unique security challenges 
It's no surprise that organizations are moving to the cloud to innovate — to meet the growing demands of their customers and digital transformation. Organizations want to build applications that are fast and scalable. They want to make use of the latest cloud-native capabilities like containers, orchestrators, microservices, APIs, and declarative infrastructure. 

However, this also means security in the cloud cannot be an afterthought. It needs to go hand-in-hand with application development in the cloud. When we talk to security teams, they face unique challenges when it comes to protecting the cloud, including:

Lack of visibility: What is present in my organization’s cloud infrastructure — services, repositories, code base, i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sneha Sachidananda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily Confused Acronyms]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2759/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2759/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/easily_confused_acronyms.png" title="'Lever' was originally an acronym for Load Emplification by the Vimulated Emission of Radiation." alt="'Lever' was originally an acronym for Load Emplification by the Vimulated Emission of Radiation." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new with GitHub Sponsors]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-04-whats-new-with-github-sponsors/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-04-whats-new-with-github-sponsors/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T16:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Sponsors is now generally available for organizations. Also, new tooling for bulk sponsorships and an update on how we’re ensuring sustainability for GitHub Sponsors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevEx improvements in HashiCorp Sentinel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/devex-improvements-in-hashicorp-sentinel</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/devex-improvements-in-hashicorp-sentinel"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent releases of Sentinel have targeted improvements to the developer experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Data Tools 2023.1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=big-data-tools&amp;p=340368</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/big-data-tools/2023/04/04/big-data-tools-2023-1-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T14:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our latest release includes several new features and improvements based on feedback from our users. In this release, we’ve added integration with Kafka Schema Registry, Kerberos authentication, and extended support for all cloud storages in Big Data Tools. Read on to learn about the most important changes in the Big Data Tools plugin or try […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Cloud Automation with amazon.cloud 0.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.cloud-0.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.cloud-0.3.0"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post we will go over what has changed and highlight what’s new in the 0.3.0 release of this Ansible Content Collection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Signs Your Business Processes Are Not Human-Centric]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78044&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78044</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/five-signs-business-processes-not-human-centric/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To avoid limiting the returns of your investment into automation, center your development approach around humans. Here's how.
The post 5 Signs Your Business Processes Are Not Human-Centric appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage is brittle]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43158</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/733695494/0/sethsblog~Leverage-is-brittle/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T08:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debt is a financial miracle. If you buy a property for 20% down, with the bank financing the rest, and it goes up in value by just 10%, your profit is 50%. (I’ll wait while you do the math.) If you have a factory and can buy a machine that increases productivity, the money you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 4th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/04/this-week-in-spring-april-4th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/04/this-week-in-spring-april-4th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Spring team at Devnexus 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/04/the-spring-team-at-devnexus-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/04/the-spring-team-at-devnexus-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks are leveraging modern cloud security tools to mitigate human error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-banks-modern-cloud-security-tools</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-banks-modern-cloud-security-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security enables financial services security teams to protect their cloud environments with new CNAPP capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we implemented frequent item set mining in Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/frequent-item-set-mining-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/frequent-item-set-mining-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frequent item sets implements one of the best known data mining methods. This aggregation discovers regularities in data and has many use cases, but the challenge is to implement it efficiently. Here, we'll show how we approached the implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hendrik Muhs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor OpenAI API and GPT models with OpenTelemetry and Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitor-openai-api-gpt-models-opentelemetry-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitor-openai-api-gpt-models-opentelemetry-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready to be blown away by this game-changing approach to monitoring cutting-edge ChatGPT applications! As the ChatGPT phenomenon takes the world by storm, it's time to supercharge your monitoring game with OpenTelemetry and Elastic Observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks are leveraging modern cloud security tools to mitigate human error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-banks-modern-cloud-security-tools</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-banks-modern-cloud-security-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The efficiency, security, and scalability of cloud operations are driving financial institutions’ adoption of the technology faster than ever before. The ability to meet customers where they want to transact, personalize solutions, and leverage new data and analytics solutions (including AI) on-demand is driving this growth. In fact, according to Accenture, the banking industry's workloads in the cloud more than doubled from 2021 to 2022.
However, despite the rapid pace of change, more than 85% of banking workloads still remain on-prem. Part of the apprehension to send more workloads to the cloud has to do with underlying cloud security concerns. Even with rapid security advancements made by cloud providers over the past decade, the risk of a data breach or failure to meet regulations is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we implemented frequent item set mining in Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/frequent-item-set-mining-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/frequent-item-set-mining-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elasticsearch is a distributed data store and analytics engine, giving you the ability to store and analyze huge amounts of data. With aggregations, you can group, summarize, create statistics, and get insights about your data. With 8.7, we make frequent_item_sets — an aggregation to discover frequent patterns in data — generally available.
Compared to other aggregations, frequent_item_sets is special in various aspects. This blog post shares some challenges and insights.
Frequent item set mining
Frequent item set mining is a data mining technique. Its task is to find frequent and relevant patterns in large data sets. A famous legend is the correlation between beer and diaper purchases by young males on Friday afternoons. It tells us that this non-obvious correlation has been found by an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hendrik Muhs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor OpenAI API and GPT models with OpenTelemetry and Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitor-openai-api-gpt-models-opentelemetry-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/monitor-openai-api-gpt-models-opentelemetry-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
ChatGPT is so hot right now, it broke the internet. As an avid user of ChatGPT and a developer of ChatGPT applications, I am incredibly excited by the possibilities of this technology. What I see happening is that there will be exponential growth of ChatGPT-based solutions, and people are going to need to monitor those solutions. 

Since this is a pretty new technology, we wouldn’t want to burden our shiny new code with proprietary technology, would we? No, we would not, and that is why we are going to use OpenTelemetry to monitor our ChatGPT code in this blog. This is particularly relevant for me as I recently created a service to generate meeting notes from Zoom calls. If I am to release this into the wild, how much is it going to cost me and how do I make sure it is available? 
OpenAI…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Self-Service Provisioning of Terraform Open-Source Configurations with AWS Service Catalog]]></title>
        <id>530d6f7f8f803392ad96d74df5af817333cf8e53</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-self-service-provisioning-of-terraform-open-source-configurations-with-aws-service-catalog/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T23:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With AWS Service Catalog, you can create, govern, and manage a catalog of infrastructure as code (IaC) templates that are approved for use on AWS. These IaC templates can include everything from virtual machine images, servers, software, and databases to complete multi-tier application architectures. You can control which IaC templates and versions are available, what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Supply Chain Now Generally Available – Mitigate Risks and Lower Costs with Increased Visibility and Actionable Insights]]></title>
        <id>0518cc890b6889b079032b7c396d9960a46ba20f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-supply-chain-now-generally-available-mitigate-risks-and-lower-costs-with-increased-visibility-and-actionable-insights/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T22:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many of you, I experienced the disrupting effects introduced by external forces such as weather, geopolitical instability, and the COVID-19 pandemic. To improve supply chain resilience, organizations need visibility across their supply chain so that they can quickly find and respond to risks. This is increasingly complex as their customers’ preferences are rapidly changing, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level up monitoring and reporting for your enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-03-level-up-monitoring-and-reporting-for-your-enterprise/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-03-level-up-monitoring-and-reporting-for-your-enterprise/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T19:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A high-quality audit log is an essential tool for enterprises to ensure compliance, maintain security, investigate issues, and promote accountability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review: Public Preview of Amazon DataZone and AWS DataSync Updates – April 3, 2023]]></title>
        <id>1bcba2697b78cec48e028ae83294a24a0ff643a2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-public-preview-of-amazon-datazone-and-aws-datasync-updates-april-3-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T16:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last weekend, I enjoyed the spring vibes at Seoul Forest, a large park in the middle of Seoul city, where cherry blossoms are in full bloom. Compared to last year, there were crowds of people, so I realized that it was really back to normal after the pandemic. I hope you all enjoy the season […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calling all open source maintainers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-03-calling-all-open-source-maintainers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-03-calling-all-open-source-maintainers/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T16:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are building a private space for maintainers to connect with peers, preview features, and learn from each other!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Automation Platform … You’re using it wrong.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-youre-using-it-wrong</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-youre-using-it-wrong"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5 things you didn’t know your Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform could do]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On being missed]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43433</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/733597595/0/sethsblog~On-being-missed/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some friends moved away, and the cake at the party read, “We’ll miss you.” Perhaps it would have been more accurate for it to say, “You’ll miss us.” Because, after all, what’s mostly being missed is the community of friends and neighbors. Even when someone moves away, the community remains. When a marketer serves a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to monitor Kafka and Confluent Cloud with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-monitor-kafka-confluent-cloud-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-monitor-kafka-confluent-cloud-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post will take you through best practices to observe Kafka-based solutions implemented on Confluent Cloud with Elastic Observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving information retrieval in the Elastic Stack: Benchmarking passage retrieval]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-information-retrieval-elastic-stack-benchmarking-passage-retrieval</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-information-retrieval-elastic-stack-benchmarking-passage-retrieval"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we'll examine benchmark solutions to compare retrieval methods. We use a collection of data sets to benchmark BM25 against two dense models and illustrate the potential gain using fine-tuning strategies with one of those models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grégoire Corbière,Quentin Herreros,Thomas Veasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to monitor Kafka and Confluent Cloud with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-monitor-kafka-confluent-cloud-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-monitor-kafka-confluent-cloud-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The blog will take you through best practices to observe Kafka-based solutions implemented on Confluent Cloud with Elastic Observability. (To monitor Kafka brokers that are not in Confluent Cloud, I recommend checking out this blog.) We will instrument Kafka applications with Elastic APM, use the Confluent Cloud metrics endpoint to get data about brokers, and pull it all together with a unified Kafka and Confluent Cloud monitoring dashboard in Elastic Observability. 
Using full-stack Elastic Observability to understand Kafka and Confluent performance
In the 2023 Dice Tech Salary Report, Elasticsearch and Kakfa are ranked #3 and #5 out of the top 12 most in demand skills at the moment, so it’s no surprise that we are seeing a large number of customers who are implementing data in motion w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving information retrieval in the Elastic Stack: Benchmarking passage retrieval]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-information-retrieval-elastic-stack-benchmarking-passage-retrieval</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-information-retrieval-elastic-stack-benchmarking-passage-retrieval"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In a previous blog post, we discussed common approaches to information retrieval and introduced the concepts of models and training stages. Here, we will examine benchmark solutions to compare various methods in a fair manner. Note that the task of benchmarking is not straightforward and can lead to misperceptions about how models perform in real-world scenarios.
Historically, comparisons between BM25 and learned retrieval models have been based on limited data sets, or even only on the training data set of these dense models: MSMARCO, which may not provide an accurate representation of the models' performance on your data. Despite this approach being useful for demonstrating how well a dense model performs against BM25 in a specific domain, it does not capture one of BM25's key strength…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grégoire Corbière,Quentin Herreros,Thomas Veasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Favorite Things]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2758/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2758/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/my_favorite_things.png" title="When an Ur guy / sells Nanni things / but the copper's bad, / He simply records his complaint for all time / &quot;I got a bad deal / I'm maaaaad&quot;" alt="When an Ur guy / sells Nanni things / but the copper's bad, / He simply records his complaint for all time / &quot;I got a bad deal / I'm maaaaad&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foibles]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43211</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/733515749/0/sethsblog~Foibles/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-02T08:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our habits, preferences and idiosyncrasies make perfect sense. We each know that we have great reasons to embrace our ways and stick with them. Other people’s habits, though, show that they are simply picky, weird or too sensitive. The difference between a preference and a foible seems to be mostly where we’re standing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fooled]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45407</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/733418738/0/sethsblog~Fooled/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now it’s a business model. People are regularly fooled by crypto scams, NFT hype, opioid felons, algorithmic spam at scale, health claims, illogical political arguments, fundraising pitches, overnight shortcuts on the road to riches or happiness and MLM hustle. Your account has been locked, click here… When it becomes the tactic of a scalable business, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling vision transformers to 22 billion parameters]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/scaling-vision-transformers-to-22.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/scaling-vision-transformers-to-22.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T20:48:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Piotr Padlewski and Josip Djolonga, Software Engineers, Google Research




Large Language Models (LLMs) like PaLM or GPT-3 showed that scaling transformers to hundreds of billions of parameters improves performance and unlocks emergent abilities. The biggest dense models for image understanding, however, have reached only 4 billion parameters, despite research indicating that promising multimodal models like PaLI continue to benefit from scaling vision models alongside their language counterparts. Motivated by this, and the results from scaling LLMs, we decided to undertake the next step in the journey of scaling the Vision Transformer.
 

In “Scaling Vision Transformers to 22 Billion Parameters”, we introduce the biggest dense vision model, ViT-22B. It is 5.5x larger than the p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Peters]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45569</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/733368746/0/sethsblog~Tom-Peters/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T19:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom announced his retirement today, at 80 years old, after 45 years of Excellence and perhaps 10,000,000 miles flown. I remember a photo of him sleeping on a bench in an airport in Siberia. I remember him holding my young son just before we went on stage in Florida together twenty-four years ago. I remember […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Ready-to-use Models and Support for Custom Text and Image Classification Models in Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>0650ce6ad58192632c6d222ad8d4b8d88bf47ff5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-ready-to-use-models-and-support-for-custom-text-and-image-classification-models-in-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T17:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today AWS announces new features in Amazon SageMaker Canvas that help business analysts generate insights from thousands of documents, images, and lines of text in minutes with machine learning (ML). Starting today, you can access ready-to-use models and create custom text and image classification models alongside previously supported custom models for tabular data, all without […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify Service-to-Service Connectivity, Security, and Monitoring with Amazon VPC Lattice – Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>9dcb9cc925a7f92a2551692c29ff45a63a4371fd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-service-to-service-connectivity-security-and-monitoring-with-amazon-vpc-lattice-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T15:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2022, we introduced in preview Amazon VPC Lattice, a new capability of Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) that gives you a consistent way to connect, secure, and monitor communication between your services. With VPC Lattice, you can define policies for network access, traffic management, and monitoring to connect compute services across […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tackling observability in financial services: Panel recap with Société Générale & Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/tackling-observability-in-financial-services-panel-recap-with-soci-t-g-n-rale-microsoft</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/tackling-observability-in-financial-services-panel-recap-with-soci-t-g-n-rale-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI and machine learning are hot topics across industries, but their value within financial services is still being recognized. Artificial intelligence can enable users to perform detections, improve forecasting, and make sense out of mounds of data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tackling observability in financial services: Panel recap with Société Générale & Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/tackling-observability-in-financial-services-panel-recap-with-soci-t-g-n-rale-microsoft</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/tackling-observability-in-financial-services-panel-recap-with-soci-t-g-n-rale-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Getting visibility across data silos is problematic for most financial institutions. The vast array of legacy systems, enormous data volumes, shifting regulatory requirements, and new technologies has made the practice of observability increasingly harder for organizations. So how should technology leaders think about prioritizing their investments to improve team productivity, lower costs, and drive greater intelligence into their decision making?

In our latest financial services webinar, we discussed this topic and more with an esteemed panel of technology and business executives in financial services. The panel featured:

Martin Moeller, Sr. Financial Services Industry Executive & Banking Lead Western Europe, Microsoft
Thibaut Barrault, Monitoring Application Manager, Société Général…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 500 ways]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45545</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/733317296/0/sethsblog~The-ways/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are thousands of ways to express encouragement and enthusiasm and support. Few of them require a blood oath or even much inconvenience. “I’m thrilled that you’re contributing.” “Can’t wait to see how this turns out.” “I know someone who really needs to hear about this.” “Go make a ruckus, it matters.” If we want […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.2 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/31/spring-cloud-2022-0-2-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/31/spring-cloud-2022-0-2-is-available"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Gibb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your co-workers with autistic children want you to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-what-your-coworkers-with-autistic-children-want-you-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-what-your-coworkers-with-autistic-children-want-you-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting our Elasticians that have children with special needs starts with understanding, empathy, and support.
Here are a few things to know in order to better understand and support your co-workers who are raising an autistic child.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your co-workers with autistic children want you to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-what-your-coworkers-with-autistic-children-want-you-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-what-your-coworkers-with-autistic-children-want-you-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Autism isn’t one size fits all
April 2 is World Autism Awareness Day, as deemed by the UN General Assembly. According to the World Health Organization, 1 in 100 children have autism. Supporting our Elasticians that have children with special needs starts with understanding, empathy, and support.

At Elastic we believe in flexibility. In fact, it’s part of our Source Code. We believe in our employees having the flexibility to work and care for their responsibilities at home. 
For those with a child with autism, those responsibilities outside of work might look a lot different (and more demanding) than yours. Here are a few things to know in order to better understand and support your co-workers who are raising an autistic child.
Things are constantly changing
While those on the autism spe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towed Message]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2757/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2757/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/towed_message.png" title="&quot;Hi, what you do is fly over a designated zone and detach the--&quot; &quot;WE'RE SORRY, THE MOBILE CUSTOMER YOU ARE TRYING TO REACH IS OUT OF SERVICE&quot;" alt="&quot;Hi, what you do is fly over a designated zone and detach the--&quot; &quot;WE'RE SORRY, THE MOBILE CUSTOMER YOU ARE TRYING TO REACH IS OUT OF SERVICE&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp earns Comparably awards for company and teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-earns-comparably-awards-for-company-and-teams</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-earns-comparably-awards-for-company-and-teams"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comparably recognizes HashiCorp with awards for Best Company Outlook, Best Marketing Team, Best Sales Team, and Best HR Team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty Now Supports Amazon EKS Runtime Monitoring]]></title>
        <id>33f430b15e8d3f92d0343a89bf2132bddc860868</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-guardduty-now-supports-amazon-eks-runtime-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T21:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Amazon GuardDuty launched in 2017, GuardDuty has been capable of analyzing tens of billions of events per minute across multiple AWS data sources, such as AWS CloudTrail event logs, Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Flow Logs, and DNS query logs, Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) data plane events, Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul cluster peering enhances multi-cloud connectivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-cluster-peering-enhances-multi-cloud-connectivity</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-cluster-peering-enhances-multi-cloud-connectivity"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cluster peering for HashiCorp-managed HCP Consul in AWS and Azure boosts multi-cloud and hybrid-cloud connectivity in the enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Service Principal and Managed Identity support on Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66657</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-service-principal-and-managed-identity-support-on-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T17:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are proud to announce that Service Principals and Managed Identities can now be used to authenticate with Azure DevOps. For those who have not heard of them before, these Azure Active Directory identities enable teams to gain access to your Azure DevOps organizations acting as their own application,
The post Introducing Service Principal and Managed Identity support on Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data-centric ML benchmarking: Announcing DataPerf’s 2023 challenges]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/data-centric-ml-benchmarking-announcing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/data-centric-ml-benchmarking-announcing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Peter Mattson, Senior Staff Engineer, ML Performance, and Praveen Paritosh, Senior Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team




Machine learning (ML) offers tremendous potential, from diagnosing cancer to engineering safe self-driving cars to amplifying human productivity. To realize this potential, however, organizations need ML solutions to be reliable with ML solution development that is predictable and tractable. The key to both is a deeper understanding of ML data — how to engineer training datasets that produce high quality models and test datasets that deliver accurate indicators of how close we are to solving the target problem. 



The process of creating high quality datasets is complicated and error-prone, from the initial selection and cleaning of raw data, to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renew your existing HashiCorp Certifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/renew-your-existing-hashicorp-certifications</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/renew-your-existing-hashicorp-certifications"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp certification holders can now renew their certifications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda’s Vision for Low-Code]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=77631&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=77631</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/camunda-vision-low-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T11:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explaining our vision for how Camunda embraces low-code to make you more productive.
The post Camunda’s Vision for Low-Code appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making change happen]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42221</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/733210520/0/sethsblog~Making-change-happen/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One way to do it is to get people to want what you want. The other way is to help them get what they want in a way that gets you what you want. They’re not the same. Changing what someone wants is very different from helping them see the story and the path that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast:  Spring Integration lead Artem Bilan on the latest in Spring Integration 6]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-integration-lead-artem-bilan-on-the-latest-in</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/30/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-integration-lead-artem-bilan-on-the-latest-in"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Web Flow 3.0 RC1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/30/spring-web-flow-3-0-rc1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/30/spring-web-flow-3-0-rc1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rossen Stoyanchev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Validating Admission Policies: A Practical Example]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/30/kubescape-validating-admission-policy-library/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/30/kubescape-validating-admission-policy-library/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Craig Box (ARMO), Ben Hirschberg (ARMO)
Admission control is an important part of the Kubernetes control plane, with several internal
features depending on the ability to approve or change an API object as it is submitted to the
server. It is also useful for an administrator to be able to define business logic, or policies,
regarding what objects can be admitted into a cluster. To better support that use case, Kubernetes
introduced external admission control in
v1.7.
In addition to countless custom, internal implementations, many open source projects and commercial
solutions implement admission controllers with user-specified policy, including
Kyverno and Open Policy Agent’s
Gatekeeper.
While admission controllers for policy have seen adoption, there are blockers for their widespr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault Secrets Operator: A new method for Kubernetes integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-secrets-operator-a-new-method-for-kubernetes-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-secrets-operator-a-new-method-for-kubernetes-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vault Secrets Operator implements a first-class Kubernetes Operator pattern for HashiCorp Vault along with a set of CRDs responsible for synchronizing Vault secrets to Kubernetes Secrets natively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Ecosystem passes 3,000 providers with over 250 partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-ecosystem-passes-3-000-providers-with-over-250-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-ecosystem-passes-3-000-providers-with-over-250-partners"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform integrations ecosystem has reached a new milestone, surpassing 3,000 providers in the registry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Context Propagation with Project Reactor 3 - Unified Bridging between Reactive and Imperative]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/30/context-propagation-with-project-reactor-3-unified-bridging-between-reactive</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/30/context-propagation-with-project-reactor-3-unified-bridging-between-reactive"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dariusz Jędrzejczyk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualifications]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2756/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2756/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/qualifications.png" title="'So how DID you go from working at the employment records office to becoming president of MIT and CEO of IBM?' 'I guess I just have an eye for opportunities.'" alt="'So how DID you go from working at the employment records office to becoming president of MIT and CEO of IBM?' 'I guess I just have an eye for opportunities.'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging transfer learning for large scale differentially private image classification]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/leveraging-transfer-learning-for-large.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/leveraging-transfer-learning-for-large.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T18:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Harsh Mehta, Software Engineer, and Walid Krichene, Research Scientist, Google Research




Large deep learning models are becoming the workhorse of a variety of critical machine learning (ML) tasks. However, it has been shown that without any protection it is plausible for bad actors to attack a variety of models, across modalities, to reveal information from individual training examples. As such, it’s essential to protect against this sort of information leakage.


Differential privacy (DP) provides formal protection against an attacker who aims to extract information about the training data. The most popular method for DP training in deep learning is differentially private stochastic gradient descent (DP-SGD). The core recipe implements a common theme in DP: “fuzzing” an algor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The producer-consumer infrastructure model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-producer-consumer-infrastructure-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-producer-consumer-infrastructure-model"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure producers and consumers require very different capabilities from their automation tools. Vendors need to provide a flexible infrastructure as code solution that meets users at their different levels of expertise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Context Propagation with Project Reactor 2 - The bumpy road of Spring Cloud Sleuth]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/29/context-propagation-with-project-reactor-2-the-bumpy-road-of-spring-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/29/context-propagation-with-project-reactor-2-the-bumpy-road-of-spring-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dariusz Jędrzejczyk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - March 28th, 202]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/28/this-week-in-spring-march-28th-202</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/28/this-week-in-spring-march-28th-202"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of Step-by-Step Guides for Amazon Connect Agent Workspace]]></title>
        <id>6042ead436a3e7e535833ae688a6be1bd85467e5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-general-availability-of-step-by-step-guides-for-amazon-connect-agent-workspace/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T20:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2022 we announced the availability of step-by-step guides for Amazon Connect agent workspace in preview. My colleagues who collaborated to write the announcement post wrote about some of the challenges that contact centers face with training new agents to get up to speed with their agent desktop. They also mentioned that until […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How French Broadcaster TF1 Used AWS Cloud Technology and Expertise to Bring the FIFA World Cup to Millions]]></title>
        <id>f6b8b5588b3c1c2f89dc45e1ebb462cb3a116aa7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-french-broadcaster-tf1-used-aws-cloud-technology-and-expertise-to-bring-the-fifa-world-cup-to-millions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T19:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three years before millions of viewers saw, arguably, one of the most thrilling World Cup Finals ever broadcast, TF1, the leading private TV channel in France, started a project to redefine the foundations of its broadcasting platform, including adopting a new cloud-based architecture. They, and all other broadcasters, have been observing diminishing audiences for traditional […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESTO – A multilingual dataset for parsing realistic task-oriented dialogues]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/presto-multilingual-dataset-for-parsing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/presto-multilingual-dataset-for-parsing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T17:02:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rahul Goel and Aditya Gupta, Software Engineers, Google Assistant




Virtual assistants are increasingly integrated into our daily routines. They can help with everything from setting alarms to giving map directions and can even assist people with disabilities to more easily manage their homes. As we use these assistants, we are also becoming more accustomed to using natural language to accomplish tasks that we once did by hand. 


 

One of the biggest challenges in building a robust virtual assistant is identifying what a user wants and what information is needed to perform the task at hand. In the natural language processing (NLP) literature, this is mainly framed as a task-oriented dialogue parsing task, where a given dialogue needs to be parsed by a system to understand the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise adds projects, drift detection, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-projects-drift-detection-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-projects-drift-detection-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent Terraform Enterprise releases include powerful new features such as projects, native OPA support, dynamic provider credentials, and drift detection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Validated Content: Introduction to infra.osbuild Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-introduction-to-infra.osbuild-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-introduction-to-infra.osbuild-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to the Image builder use case
 
During the last year we met with multiple edge customers, covering the automation needs for IT Linux infrastructure at scale across remote locations where there is often no IT staff on site. Think about retail stores, dark stores and warehouses where self-checkout, handhelds and POS devices hosting RHEL are distributed everywhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Santiago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service Major Updates: Import and Export Feature, Source Server Migration Metrics Dashboard, and Additional Post-Launch Actions]]></title>
        <id>fa10696bac0b9446bb6ac881cb730c11e3d02931</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-application-migration-service-major-updates-import-and-export-feature-source-server-migration-metrics-dashboard-and-additional-post-launch-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T15:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service (AWS MGN) can simplify and expedite your migration to AWS by automatically converting your source servers from physical, virtual, or cloud infrastructure to run natively on AWS. In the post, How to Use the New AWS Application Migration Server for Lift-and-Shift Migrations, Channy introduced us to Application Migration Service and how […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Chime SDK Call Analytics: Real-Time Voice Tone Analysis and Speaker Search]]></title>
        <id>b5892bef67fe0abef13300dedbfb49b1a69ff7fa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-chime-sdk-call-analytics-real-time-voice-tone-analysis-and-speaker-search/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T15:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am pleased to announce the availability of Amazon Chime SDK call analytics, a new set of capabilities that helps make it easier and cost effective to record and generate insights on real-time audio calls: transcription, voice tone analysis, and speaker search. We’ve also improved the Amazon Chime SDK section of the AWS Management […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 27, 2023]]></title>
        <id>36af7fde9b2b41d5310560b417ffc23471afa1e9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-27-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! In Finland, where I live, spring has arrived. The snow has melted, and the trees have grown their first buds. But I don’t get my hopes high, as usually around […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Context Propagation with Project Reactor 1 - The Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/28/context-propagation-with-project-reactor-1-the-basics</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/03/28/context-propagation-with-project-reactor-1-the-basics"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dariusz Jędrzejczyk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting novel systemic biomarkers in external eye photos]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/detecting-novel-systemic-biomarkers-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/detecting-novel-systemic-biomarkers-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T19:13:00.009Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Boris Babenko, Software Engineer, and Akib Uddin, Product Manager, Google Research






Last year we presented results demonstrating that a deep learning system (DLS) can be trained to analyze external eye photos and predict a person’s diabetic retinal disease status and elevated glycated hemoglobin (or HbA1c, a biomarker that indicates the three-month average level of blood glucose). It was previously unknown that external eye photos contained signals for these conditions. This exciting finding suggested the potential to reduce the need for specialized equipment since such photos can be captured using smartphones and other consumer devices. Encouraged by these findings, we set out to discover what other biomarkers can be found in this imaging modality.



In “A deep learning mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual language maps for robot navigation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/visual-language-maps-for-robot.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/visual-language-maps-for-robot.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T19:08:00.012Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Oier Mees, PhD Student, University of Freiburg, and Andy Zeng, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google





People are excellent navigators of the physical world, due in part to their remarkable ability to build cognitive maps that form the basis of spatial memory — from localizing landmarks at varying ontological levels (like a book on a shelf in the living room) to determining whether a layout permits navigation from point A to point B. Building robots that are proficient at navigation requires an interconnected understanding of (a) vision and natural language (to associate landmarks or follow instructions), and (b) spatial reasoning (to connect a map representing an environment to the true spatial distribution of objects). While there have been many recent advances in training …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running dynamic, ephemeral multi-hop workers for HCP Boundary: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-dynamic-ephemeral-multi-hop-workers-for-hcp-boundary-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-dynamic-ephemeral-multi-hop-workers-for-hcp-boundary-part-1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worker management is very dynamic in Boundary and HCP Boundary. With a new custom plugin, you can automate even more tasks, including worker cleanup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deeper Look: Red Hat Named a Leader in the Forrester Wave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/a-deeper-look-red-hat-named-a-leader-in-the-forrester-wave</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/a-deeper-look-red-hat-named-a-leader-in-the-forrester-wave"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we announced that Red Hat has been named a leader in The Forrester Wave™ Infrastructure Automation, Q1 2023. In an effort to help explain this result from our point of view, the following blog answers some of the most frequently asked questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andriusb@redhat.com (Andrius Benokraitis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test as You Go: Rapid Process Development and Continuous Improvement]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=76773&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=76773</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/rapid-process-development-continuous-improvement/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T14:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Alpha release of the new rapid process testing functionality which is now available in Camunda Platform 8.
The post Test as You Go: Rapid Process Development and Continuous Improvement appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Inozemtceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Federal Sales Director Kathy Hsu thinks authenticity is important in sales. Hear why.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My passion is to work with the federal government and see how I can be a part of the mission. That’s why I wanted to work at Elastic. 

I first discovered my passion for tech sales as a college graduate working in Silicon Valley. I worked at Apple as a Technical Consultant and got my start in channel sales and the network IP space at a large company that provided solutions for semiconductor and infrastructure software. Then I moved to a startup that gave me the opportunity to support Civilian agencies, the Department of Defense (DoD), and the Intelligence Community. In this role, I spent a lot of time flying between California and Washington D.C. and quickly realized that I had a great sense of fire and purpose when serving the federal government. 

These early experiences helped me find m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Hsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Federal Sales Director Kathy Hsu thinks authenticity is important in sales. Hear why.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Hsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 219]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66630</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-219/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T17:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sprint 219 was dedicated to fixing bugs. We continue to drive down the bug backlog as quickly as we can. We will also have a couple new preview features coming that will be announced in the 219 sprint notes.
Issue
Delivery plans tab name
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 219 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第227話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361072081927</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361072081927"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66621</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/march-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T20:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Addressed issue that required restarting tfsjobagent service and Azure DevOps Server application pool after updating SMTP-related setting in the Azure DevOps Server Management Console.
The post March patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Clean Rooms Now Generally Available — Collaborate with Your Partners without Sharing Raw Data]]></title>
        <id>7489dac1ba7077e7020fc13589c13c0455e7b4d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-clean-rooms-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T19:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies across multiple industries, such as advertising and marketing, retail, consumer packaged goods (CPG), travel and hospitality, media and entertainment, and financial services, increasingly look to supplement their data with data from business partners, to build a complete view of their business. Let’s take a marketing use case as an example. Brands, publishers, and their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Camunda 8 on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=76579&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=76579</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/running-camunda-8-on-openshift/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T18:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you use Red Hat OpenShift? We've greatly improved how Camunda Platform 8 runs on OpenShift. Learn what's new and see an installation step by step.
The post Running Camunda 8 on OpenShift appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 20, 2023]]></title>
        <id>d37a1df2b4b3f11486d8d054016088476bc57107</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-20-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T15:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! A new week starts, and Spring is almost here! If you’re curious about AWS news from the previous seven days, I got you covered. Last Week’s Launches Here are the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New reference architecture: Deploying Ansible Automation Platform 2 on Red Hat OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-deploying-ansible-automation-platform-2-on-red-hat-openshift</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/new-reference-architecture-deploying-ansible-automation-platform-2-on-red-hat-openshift"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest reference architecture showcasing the best practices for deploying Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 on Red Hat OpenShift!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Providing Terraform with that Ansible Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/providing-terraform-with-that-ansible-magic</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/providing-terraform-with-that-ansible-magic"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Late last year, we introduced a Red Hat Ansible Certified Collection Collection for Terraform. This was an important step in automation, as these two tools really are great together and leveraging Ansible's ability to orchestrate other tools in the enterprise made this a no-brainer. Terraform with its infrastructure as code (IaC) provisioning and Ansible’s strength in configuration as code are a synergy that cannot be ignored - we are better together! Organizations are now in the position to utilize their existing infrastructure as code manifests and extend their automation with Terraform and Ansible together.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vid2Seq: a pretrained visual language model for describing multi-event videos]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/vid2seq-pretrained-visual-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/vid2seq-pretrained-visual-language.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T17:52:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Antoine Yang, Student Researcher, and Arsha Nagrani, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception team






Videos have become an increasingly important part of our daily lives, spanning fields such as entertainment, education, and communication. Understanding the content of videos, however, is a challenging task as videos often contain multiple events occurring at different time scales. For example, a video of a musher hitching up dogs to a dog sled before they all race away involves a long event (the dogs pulling the sled) and a short event (the dogs being hitched to the sled). One way to spur research in video understanding is via the task of dense video captioning, which consists of temporally localizing and describing all events in a minutes-long video. This differs from…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Removals and Major Changes In v1.27]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/17/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-v1-27/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/17/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-v1-27/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Harshita Sao
As Kubernetes develops and matures, features may be deprecated, removed, or replaced
with better ones for the project's overall health. Based on the information available
at this point in the v1.27 release process, which is still ongoing and can introduce
additional changes, this article identifies and describes some of the planned changes
for the Kubernetes v1.27 release.
A note about the k8s.gcr.io redirect to registry.k8s.io
To host its container images, the Kubernetes project uses a community-owned image
registry called registry.k8s.io. On March 20th, all traffic from the out-of-date
k8s.gcr.io registry will be redirected
to registry.k8s.io. The deprecated
k8s.gcr.io registry will eventually be phased out.
What does this change mean?
If you are a subproject maintai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Chatbot Now Integrates With Microsoft Teams]]></title>
        <id>173381d3f83132268431d2b67f1614ae358dbea3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-chatbot-now-integrates-with-microsoft-teams/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T21:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that, starting today, you can use AWS Chatbot to troubleshoot and operate your AWS resources from Microsoft Teams. Communicating and collaborating on IT operation tasks through chat channels is known as ChatOps. It allows you to centralize the management of infrastructure and applications, as well as to automate and streamline […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: The Impact Lab]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T20:13:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jamila Smith-Loud, Human Rights & Social Impact Research Lead, Google Research, Responsible AI and Human-Centered Technology Team



    
Responsible AI Team, employs a range of interdisciplinary methodologies to ensure critical and rich analysis of the potential implications of technology development. The team’s mission is to examine socioeconomic and human rights impacts of AI,  publish foundational research, and incubate novel mitigations enabling machine learning (ML) practitioners to advance global equity. We study and develop scalable, rigorous, and evidence-based solutions using data analysis, human rights, and participatory frameworks. 


 


The uniqueness of the Impact Lab’s goals is its multidisciplinary approach and the diversity of experience, including both applied …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds new Sentinel policy review UI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-new-sentinel-policy-review-ui</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-new-sentinel-policy-review-ui"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a more efficient, streamlined way of managing policy as code workflows in Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Meets Event-Driven Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/kubernetes-meets-event-driven-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/kubernetes-meets-event-driven-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s fast paced world, every second counts and the ability to react to activities in a timely fashion can mean the difference between satisfying the needs of consumers and meeting Service-Level Agreements. Each are goals of Event-Driven Ansible, which seeks to further the reach of Ansible based automation by responding to events that meet certain criteria. These events can originate from a variety of sources, such as from an HTTP endpoint, messages on a queue or topic, or from public cloud resources. Kubernetes has become synonymous with managing infrastructure and applications in cloud native architectures and many organizations are reliant on these systems for running their business critical workloads. Automation and Kubernetes go hand in hand and Ansible already plays a role within this ecosystem. A new capability leveraging the Event-Driven Ansible framework is now available that extends the integration between both Ansible and Kubernetes so that Ansible automation activities can be triggered based on events and actions occurring within a Kubernetes cluster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ablock@redhat.com (Andrew Block)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RPA + BPMN = True End-to-End Business Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=76245&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=76245</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/rpa-bpmn-process-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T21:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BPMN is an ideal tool for visualizing and controlling end-to-end business processes, including those that invoke RPA bots. Learn how to use them together.
The post RPA + BPMN = True End-to-End Business Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Linux 2023, a Cloud-Optimized Linux Distribution with Long-Term Support]]></title>
        <id>222e76bc4fa032f0a04b7b011b60ef08bec89805</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-linux-2023-a-cloud-optimized-linux-distribution-with-long-term-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T20:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am excited to announce the general availability of Amazon Linux 2023 (AL2023). AWS has provided you with a cloud-optimized Linux distribution since 2010. This is the third generation of our Amazon Linux distributions. Every generation of Amazon Linux distribution is secured, optimized for the cloud, and receives long-term AWS support. We built Amazon Linux […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximum Process Flexibility with Inbound Webhook Connectors]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=75153&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=75153</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/inbound-webhook-connectors/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T18:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to share that an inbound HTTP Webhook Connector and an inbound GitHub Webhook Connector are now available in Camunda Platform 8.
The post Maximum Process Flexibility with Inbound Webhook Connectors appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Elastic’s EMEA Go-To-Market Sales Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-the-team-at-elastic-emea-go-to-market</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-the-team-at-elastic-emea-go-to-market"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Field Operations is an important team here at Elastic. They cover all go-to-market (GTM) functions related to customer acquisition, expansion, and retention. As a team, they think globally and act locally with teams covering every major international market.
Our Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) sales team is rapidly growing, so we wanted to take a moment to highlight some of our GTM Elasticians working in the region and hear a bit about the work they do and why they value Elastic as an employer.
Charlotte van Dijk, commercial account executive, north EMEA

I work in the commercial sector within the Benelux region as an Account Executive. I started my career at Elastic as a User Success Manager nearly 5 years ago. As a User Success Manager, I had the opportunity to work with a lot of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Elastic’s EMEA Go-To-Market Sales Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-the-team-at-elastic-emea-go-to-market</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-meet-the-team-at-elastic-emea-go-to-market"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you based in Europe and considering a role in sales? Hear from some of our EMEA sales team about their roles and the work they do that contributes to Elastic’s success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrate Amazon S3’s 17th birthday at AWS Pi Day 2023]]></title>
        <id>48daf1f1e1724b4a81e1785becca7b650d3031a9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/celebrate-amazon-s3s-17th-birthday-at-aws-pi-day-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T19:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Pi Day 2023 is live today starting at 13:00 PDT; join us on the AWS on Air channel on Twitch. On this day 17 years ago, we launched a very simple object storage service. It allowed developers to create, list, and delete private storage spaces (known as buckets), upload and download files, and manage […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning from deep learning: a case study of feature discovery and validation in pathology]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/learning-from-deep-learning-case-study.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/learning-from-deep-learning-case-study.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T18:16:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ellery Wulczyn and Yun Liu, Google Research




When a patient is diagnosed with cancer, one of the most important steps is examination of the tumor under a microscope by pathologists to determine the cancer stage and to characterize the tumor. This information is central to understanding clinical prognosis (i.e., likely patient outcomes) and for determining the most appropriate treatment, such as undergoing surgery alone versus surgery plus chemotherapy. Developing machine learning (ML) tools in pathology to assist with the microscopic review represents a compelling research area with many potential applications.


Previous studies have shown that ML can accurately identify and classify tumors in pathology images and can even predict patient prognosis using known pathology featu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Use Amazon S3 Object Lambda with Amazon CloudFront to Tailor Content for End Users]]></title>
        <id>bb8eafd170bc0a7a2a4f58cc640790b11357cb96</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-use-amazon-s3-object-lambda-with-amazon-cloudfront-to-tailor-content-for-end-users/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T17:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With S3 Object Lambda, you can use your own code to process data retrieved from Amazon S3 as it is returned to an application. Over time, we added new capabilities to S3 Object Lambda, like the ability to add your own code to S3 HEAD and LIST API requests, in addition to the support for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault client libraries for Go and .NET are now in public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-client-libraries-for-go-and-net-are-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-client-libraries-for-go-and-net-are-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp expands its client libraries to include Go & .NET. The Vault 1.13 release includes support for Go & .NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Media Understanding Platform for ML Innovations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9bef9962dcb7</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/building-a-media-understanding-platform-for-ml-innovations-9bef9962dcb7?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T15:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The media understanding platform serves as an abstraction layer between Machine Learning (ML) algos and various applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.10.0-alpha5 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=75110&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=75110</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/camunda-optimize-3-10-0-alpha5/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the latest release of Camunda Optimize. Optimize makes it possible to evaluate the success of your process automation initiative.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.10.0-alpha5 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.19.0-alpha4 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=75119&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=75119</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/camunda-automation-platform-7-19-0-alpha4/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth alpha release of Camunda Automation Runtime 7.19 features new job due date functionality, support for Quarkus 2.16.4 and more.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.19.0-alpha4 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 13, 2023]]></title>
        <id>cb1390189c6b6ce821906a8bb9260207f9ef1972</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-13-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T03:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems like only yesterday I was last writing the Week in Review post, at the end of January, and now here we are almost mid-way through March, almost into spring in the northern hemisphere, and close to a quarter way through 2023. Where does time fly?! Last Week’s LaunchesHere’s some of the launches and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing channel assignment history and rollback for HCP Packer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-channel-assignment-history-and-rollback-for-hcp-packer</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-channel-assignment-history-and-rollback-for-hcp-packer"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer’s new channel assignment history and rollback provide a complete record of artifacts in a channel and enable a simple, one-click rollback to previous iterations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing/Maximizing your Scaling capability with Automation Controller 2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/enhancing/maximizing-your-scaling-capability-with-automation-controller-2.3</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/enhancing/maximizing-your-scaling-capability-with-automation-controller-2.3"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2 is the next generation automation platform from Red Hat’s trusted enterprise technology experts. We are excited to announce that the Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 release includes automation controller 4.3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch Indexing Strategy in Asset Management Platform (AMP)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/99332231e541</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/elasticsearch-indexing-strategy-in-asset-management-platform-amp-99332231e541?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T22:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Burak Bacioglu, Meenakshi Jindal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Reprocessing Pipeline in Asset Management Platform @Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/46fe225c35c9</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/data-reprocessing-pipeline-in-asset-management-platform-netflix-46fe225c35c9?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T22:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Meenakshi Jindal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PaLM-E: An embodied multimodal language model]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/palm-e-embodied-multimodal-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/palm-e-embodied-multimodal-language.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T17:25:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Danny Driess, Student Researcher, and Pete Florence, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google




Recent years have seen tremendous advances across machine learning domains, from models that can explain jokes or answer visual questions in a variety of languages to those that can produce images based on text descriptions. Such innovations have been possible due to the increase in availability of large scale datasets along with novel advances that enable the training of models on these data. While scaling of robotics models has seen some success, it is outpaced by other domains due to a lack of datasets available on a scale comparable to large text corpora or image datasets. 





Today we introduce PaLM-E, a new generalist robotics model that overcomes these issues by transferring k…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: k8s.gcr.io Redirect to registry.k8s.io - What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/10/image-registry-redirect/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/10/image-registry-redirect/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Bob Killen (Google), Davanum Srinivas (AWS), Chris Short (AWS), Frederico Muñoz (SAS
Institute), Tim Bannister (The Scale Factory), Ricky Sadowski (AWS), Grace Nguyen (Expo), Mahamed
Ali (Rackspace Technology), Mars Toktonaliev (independent), Laura Santamaria (Dell), Kat Cosgrove
(Dell)
On Monday, March 20th, the k8s.gcr.io registry will be redirected to the community owned
registry,
registry.k8s.io .
TL;DR: What you need to know about this change
On Monday, March 20th, traffic from the older k8s.gcr.io registry will be redirected to
registry.k8s.io with the eventual goal of sunsetting k8s.gcr.io.
If you run in a restricted environment, and apply strict domain name or IP address access policies
limited to k8s.gcr.io, the image pulls will not function after k8s.gcr.io starts redire…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why SüdLeasing Chose Camunda Platform 8 SaaS]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=74641&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=74641</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/why-camunda-platform-8-suedleasing/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why SüdLeasing, a major German financial services institution, is setting up all their new processes in Camunda Platform 8 SaaS.
The post Why SüdLeasing Chose Camunda Platform 8 SaaS appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Schroth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five tips for growing your career in tech sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-five-tips-for-growing-your-career-in-tech-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-five-tips-for-growing-your-career-in-tech-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Rain Hu's favorite moments of the day is her early morning run. "I run six kilometers minimum daily, rain or shine," she says. "I enjoy the time alone because it allows me to have time for self-reflection and self-conversation." 
The discipline that it takes to maintain a healthy lifestyle is carried throughout her life. As a wife, mother of two young boys, and sales leader, Rain optimizes her time so that she can show up fully and authentically in all aspects of her life. 
We sat down with Rain, Area Vice President, ASEAN and Greater China  at Elastic, to learn how she has built a career she loves. Read on to learn about how she grew her career in tech sales and what advice she has for others looking to do the same. 


Launching a career in tech sales
Shortly after graduating with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mara Gates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five tips for growing your career in tech sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-five-tips-for-growing-your-career-in-tech-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-five-tips-for-growing-your-career-in-tech-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Mara Gates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Forensic container analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/10/forensic-container-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/10/forensic-container-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Adrian Reber (Red Hat)
In my previous article, Forensic container checkpointing in
Kubernetes, I introduced checkpointing in Kubernetes
and how it has to be setup and how it can be used. The name of the
feature is Forensic container checkpointing, but I did not go into
any details how to do the actual analysis of the checkpoint created by
Kubernetes. In this article I want to provide details how the
checkpoint can be analyzed.
Checkpointing is still an alpha feature in Kubernetes and this article
wants to provide a preview how the feature might work in the future.
Preparation
Details about how to configure Kubernetes and the underlying CRI implementation
to enable checkpointing support can be found in my Forensic container
checkpointing in Kubernetes article.
As an example I prepa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The BirdCLEF 2023 Challenge: Pushing the frontiers of biodiversity monitoring]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/the-birdclef-2023-challenge-pushing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/the-birdclef-2023-challenge-pushing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T19:27:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tom Denton, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team





Worldwide bird populations are declining at an alarming rate, with approximately 48% of existing bird species known or suspected to be experiencing population declines. For instance, the U.S. and Canada have reported 29% fewer birds since 1970.



Effective monitoring of bird populations is essential for the development of solutions that promote conservation. Monitoring allows researchers to better understand the severity of the problem for specific bird populations and evaluate whether existing interventions are working. To scale monitoring, bird researchers have started analyzing ecosystems remotely using bird sound recordings instead of physically in-person via passive acoustic monitoring. Researchers can gather t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the Newest AWS Heroes – March 2023]]></title>
        <id>23c2f55be52d9c2b3b30a239f3c22b95b0fc3586</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/meet-the-newest-aws-heroes-march-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T18:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Heroes are passionate AWS experts who are dedicated to sharing their in-depth knowledge within the community. They inspire, uplift, and motivate the global AWS community, and today, we’re excited to announce and recognize the newest Heroes in 2023! Aidan Steele – Melbourne, Australia Serverless Hero Aidan Steele is a Senior Engineer at Nightvision. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic provider credentials now generally available for Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dynamic-provider-credentials-now-ga-for-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dynamic-provider-credentials-now-ga-for-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform’s dynamic provider credentials enable secure, short-lived authentication for HashiCorp Vault and cloud providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>