<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-10-16T02:36:50.673Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-16T02:36:50.673Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We forgot to choose]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42252</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/715677944/0/sethsblog~We-forgot-to-choose/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T08:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When abundance showed up, first in manufactured goods, then in information, it all seemed like a simple win. More of what we want, thanks. But of course, more of too many things is too much. We are leaving the age of information and entering the age of choice. Not just choosing what we’ll consume, but […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn more about Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3 in these two great talks from Devoxx 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/15/learn-more-about-spring-framework-6-and-spring-boot-3-in-these-two-great-talks-from-devoxx-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/15/learn-more-about-spring-framework-6-and-spring-boot-3-in-these-two-great-talks-from-devoxx-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! I was just at Devoxx in Belgium, where hundreds of experts from across the Java ecosystem converged for the first time since 2019 to deliver their biggest and best. 

I could do a proper trip report, but I really just came here to point you to two talks from two of my amazing teammates, Stéphane Nicoll (@snicoll) and Brian Clozel (@bclozel), who have been very hard at work on both Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3, both of which will land by the end of November, 2022. These are brand new generations of the framework, implying huge new paradigms and new opportunities for developers. 

This first is a broader, whirlwind tour of the new features in Spring Framework 6 (which bubble up into Spring Boot 3).


This second one introduces the new ahead-of-time (AOT) support in Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3, which makes it trivial to build GraalVM native images.



NB: please ignore the metadata for the YouTube videos. Both talks feature both speakers, and there is no mention whatsoever of React and JavaScript and the like. I think that was a metadata issue with the publication of the videos on YouTube, which will hopefully be resolved. 

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode 2022.3 EAP: New Settings Sync Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=287314</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/10/appcode-2022-3-eap-new-settings-sync-solution/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T00:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, A new AppCode 2022.3 EAP build (223.6646.113) is available for download. Builds are available from our website and via the Toolbox App. You can also update from the 2022.3 EAP1 build via patch. DOWNLOAD APPCODE EAP New solution for synchronizing settings Synchronizing settings is essential when you use AppCode or other IntelliJ-based IDEs […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2022: Q&A with Bernd and Daniel]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=65420</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/camundacon-2022-qa-bernd-daniel/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T20:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn from Bernd Ruecker, Camunda Co-founder/Chief Technologist, and Daniel Meyer, Camunda CTO, as they tackle questions on connectors, modeling & more.
The post CamundaCon 2022: Q&A with Bernd and Daniel appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UL2 20B: An Open Source Unified Language Learner]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/ul2-20b-open-source-unified-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/ul2-20b-open-source-unified-language.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T18:47:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yi Tay and Mostafa Dehghani, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team
Building models that understand and generate natural language well is one the grand goals of machine learning (ML) research and has a direct impact on building smart systems for everyday applications. Improving the quality of language models is a key target for researchers to make progress toward such a goal.   
Most common paradigms to build and train language models use either autoregressive decoder-only architectures (e.g., PaLM or GPT-3), where the model is trained to predict the next word for a given prefix phrase, or span corruption-based encoder-decoder architectures (e.g., T5, ST-MoE), where the training objective is to recover the subset of words masked out of the input. On the one hand, T5-lik…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic continues to gain momentum in SIEM market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-continues-to-gain-momentum-in-siem-market</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-continues-to-gain-momentum-in-siem-market"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gartner SIEM MQ - Elastic has successfully delivered a leading Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) offering with only two years in the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols,Mike Paquette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic continues to gain momentum in SIEM market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-continues-to-gain-momentum-in-siem-market</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-continues-to-gain-momentum-in-siem-market"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic has successfully delivered a leading Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) offering with only two years in the market. According to IDC Worldwide Security Information and Event Management Market Shares, 2021: The Cardinal SIEMs report, Elastic is one of the fastest growing SIEMs (more than 80% year-over-year growth) — and had the fifth largest market share in 2021 of the 20+ SIEM vendors in the report. 
2021 worldwide SIEM revenue market share
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltbbcc5746c1499bd1/634979188473831f96bbd039/image1.png,image1.png,
Additionally, Gartner® has recognized Elastic as a Visionary in the 2022 Magic Quadrant™ for SIEM. We believe this recognition is a testament to Elastic’s ability to deliver value to customers quickly an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols,Mike Paquette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSI’s Deep Dive is an essential discussion on the future of AI and open source]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-14-osis-deep-dive-is-an-essential-discussion-on-the-future-of-ai-and-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-14-osis-deep-dive-is-an-essential-discussion-on-the-future-of-ai-and-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T16:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub is sponsoring Open Source Initiative’s Deep Dive: AI because we think it’s important for the community to unpack how open source software, process, and principles can help best deliver on the promise of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick-fix for Invalid Recursive Type, New Settings Synchronization Solution, and Improvements for Databases in GoLand EAP 2022.3 #3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=287057</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/10/14/quick-fix-for-invalid-recursive-type-new-settings-synchronization-solution-and-improvements-for-databases-in-goland-eap-2022-3-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T14:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third build of our current Early Access Program is out!  You can get the EAP build via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package (for Ubuntu), or from inside GoLand, select Check IDE updates for Early Access Program in Preferences / Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System Settings […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2022.3 EAP: New Settings Sync Solution, Linker Scripts, Azure RTOS]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=287260</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/10/clion-2022-3-eap-new-settings-sync-solution-linker-scripts-azure-rtos/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T14:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new CLion 2022.3 EAP build is available! Download build 223.6646.99 from our website via the Toolbox App or as a snap package (if you are using Ubuntu). If you are on macOS, there is a separate build for Apple Silicon (M1 chip). Update via patch if you are using EAP1 or EAP2 builds. DOWNLOAD […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.3 EAP 3: New Settings Sync Solution, Improvements for Java, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=284899</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/10/intellij-idea-2022-3-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T12:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.3 EAP 3 is now available! In this new EAP build, we introduce a reworked Settings Sync solution to help seamlessly synchronize your personal IDE settings, a range of new inspections and other improvements for Java, and experimental Maven import functionality that utilizes the new IntelliJ IDEA Workspace Model API. You can get […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCon Portugal 2022 trip report]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=286832</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/10/pycon-portugal-2022-trip-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T09:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year saw the premier of the first ever PyCon Portugal! With DjangoCon Europe being hosted in Porto this year, the organizers took the opportunity to piggyback off of this conference and set up a PyCon in this beautiful country. I was lucky enough to be selected as one of the speakers, and it was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jodie Burchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“America’s favorite pie”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43976</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/715566360/0/sethsblog~Americas-favorite-pie/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T08:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s what it said on the side of the tractor-trailer on the highway. Since 1924, they’re almost 100 years old. But it’s unlikely that it’s everyone’s favorite. Being everyone’s favorite is such an attractive goal, and almost impossible to achieve. Ask someone about their favorite pie and they’ll talk about the one they ate as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2045]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2685/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2685/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/2045.png" title="&quot;Sorry, doctor, I'm going to have to come in on a different day--I have another appointment that would be really hard to move, in terms of the kinetic energy requirements.&quot;" alt="&quot;Sorry, doctor, I'm going to have to come in on a different day--I have another appointment that would be really hard to move, in terms of the kinetic energy requirements.&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing GitHub Advanced Security SIEM integrations for security professionals]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-13-introducing-github-advanced-security-siem-integrations-for-security-professionals/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-13-introducing-github-advanced-security-siem-integrations-for-security-professionals/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T19:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about using GitHub Advanced Security (GHAS) alerts with Security Information and Events Management (SIEM) tools. Check out the integrations, and read more about getting started.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Two HashiCorp Employees Marked Latinx & Hispanic Heritage Month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-two-hashicorp-employees-marked-latinx-hispanic-heritage-month</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-two-hashicorp-employees-marked-latinx-hispanic-heritage-month"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Karla De La Garza and Abraham Martinez, from HashiCorp’s Unidos Employee Resource Group, share their experiences in Mexico during Latinx & Hispanic Heritage Month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crossmodal-3600 — Multilingual Reference Captions for Geographically Diverse Images]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/crossmodal-3600-multilingual-reference.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/crossmodal-3600-multilingual-reference.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:53:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ashish Thapliyal, Software Engineer, and Jordi Pont-Tuset, Research Scientist, Google Research
Image captioning is the machine learning task of automatically generating a fluent natural language description for a given image. This task is important for improving accessibility for visually impaired users and is a core task in multimodal research encompassing both vision and language modeling.  
 However, datasets for image captioning are primarily available in English. Beyond that, there are only a few datasets covering a limited number of languages that represent just a small fraction of the world’s population. Further, these datasets feature images that severely under-represent the richness and diversity of cultures from across the globe. These aspects have hindered research on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.12 Adds New Secrets Engines, ADP Updates, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-12</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-12"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new HashiCorp Vault 1.12 focuses on improving core workflows and making key features production-ready.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Story of Scalar]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-13-the-story-of-scalar/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-13-the-story-of-scalar/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New to Git v2.38, Scalar is a built-in repository manager for large repos. Here, we’ll tell the story of how Scalar went from a rough VFS for Git successor to a fully-integrated Git tool, with all of the engineering lessons learned in the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2022.3 EAP Is Open]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=286633</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2022/10/13/datagrip-2022-3-eap-is-open/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T12:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, DataGrip fans! As usual, we want to share our new functionality with you before the official release happens. Here’s what you will find in DataGrip 2022.3. Of course, you can already try all of this out by downloading our EAP build. Let’s go! Database explorer Quick filter A long-awaited feature is finally here! Now, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maksim Sobolevskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The small world questions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43984</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/715452174/0/sethsblog~The-small-world-questions/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T08:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without a doubt, the world has become more connected, noisier and more complex. But along the way, we’re still applying our instincts from a century ago, from a planet of villages and different expectations. Rhetorical questions worth considering as we think about what’s normal. Where does here end and there begin? Is there a line […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.0-M8 is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/13/spring-batch-5-0-0-m8-is-out</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/13/spring-batch-5-0-0-m8-is-out"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and all contributors, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M8 is now available from our milestone repository.

In this milestone, we introduced two main changes:


  
New default execution context serialization format

  
SystemCommandTasklet enhancements


This blog post walks through these two major changes in details. For the complete list of changes,
please check the release notes.
New default execution context serialization format

In this milestone release, the DefaultExecutionContextSerializer was updated to serialize/deserialize the context to/from Base64.

Moreover, the default ExecutionContextSerializer configured by @EnableBatchProcessing or DefaultBatchConfiguration was changed from JacksonExecutionContextStringSerializer to DefaultExecutionContextSerializer. The dependency to Jackson was made optional. In order to use the JacksonExecutionContextStringSerializer, jackson-core should be added to the classpath.
SystemCommandTasklet enhancements

The SystemCommandTasklet has been revisited in this release and was changed as follows:


  

  
A new strategy interface named CommandRunner was introduced in order to decouple the command execution from the tasklet execution. The default implementation is the JvmCommandRunner which uses the java.lang.Runtime#exec API to run system commands. This interface can be implemented to use any other API to run system commands.

  

  
The method that runs the command now accepts an array of Strings representing the command and its arguments. There is no need to tokenize the command or do any pre-processing anymore. This change makes the API more intuitive, and less prone to errors.


Feedback

I would like to thank all contributors who had a role in this release! As we continue
our work on Spring Batch 5, we look forward to your feedback on Github, Twitter and StackOverflow.


Spring Batch Home|Source on Github|Reference documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Google mad scientist Josh Suereth on Observability with OpenTelemetry, building better build tools, and so much more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/12/a-bootiful-podcast-google-mad-scientist-josh-suereth-on-observability-with-opentelemetry-building-better-build-tools-and-so-much-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/12/a-bootiful-podcast-google-mad-scientist-josh-suereth-on-observability-with-opentelemetry-building-better-build-tools-and-so-much-more"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment Josh Long (@starbuxman) looks at the latest and greatest in Spring Boot 3 AOT, then talks to Google’s Josh Suereth (@jsuereth) about observability with OpenTelemetry, building better build tools, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of the possible: Arming U.S. veterans with knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-art-of-the-possible-arming-us-veterans-with-knowledge</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-art-of-the-possible-arming-us-veterans-with-knowledge"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic can help us understand the data that impacts our daily lives and guides our decisions. Learn how one Elastic employee transformed data into something that provides invaluable insight and answers common questions in the veteran community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cami Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of the possible: Arming U.S. veterans with knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-art-of-the-possible-arming-us-veterans-with-knowledge</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-art-of-the-possible-arming-us-veterans-with-knowledge"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic can be used to help us understand the data that impacts our daily lives and guides our decisions, and the possibilities for individual use cases are endless. Our community is full of success stories about innovative ways Elastic empowers our users to make meaning out of data — and Isra Sunhachawi, senior solutions architect at Elastic recently did just that. Using the Elastic stack, Isra developed interactive maps and dashboards to depict the journey of a veteran from pre-enlistment to retirement. His tool distills otherwise meaningless data into useful information to help service members make informed decisions about housing, healthcare, and more.
,In 2022, Isra submitted his tool to the Academy Health DataJam Challenge and he won, successfully demonstrating the enormous potenti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cami Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observability with Spring Boot 3]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/12/observability-with-spring-boot-3</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/12/observability-with-spring-boot-3"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spring Observability Team has been working on adding observability support for Spring Applications for quite some time, and we are pleased to inform you that this feature will be generally available with Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3!



What is observability? In our understanding, it is "how well you can understand the internals of your system by examining its outputs". We believe that the interconnection between metrics, logging, and distributed tracing gives you the ability to reason about the state of your system in order to debug exceptions and latency in your applications. You can watch more about what we think observability is in this episode of Enlightning with Jonatan Ivanov.



The upcoming Spring Boot 3.0.0-RC1 release will contain numerous autoconfigurations fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Product Teams Can Build Empathy Through Experimentation]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6253603880a6</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/how-product-teams-can-build-empathy-through-experimentation-6253603880a6?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T20:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A conversation between Travis Brooks, Netflix Product Manager for Experimentation Platform, and George Khachatryan, OfferFit CEO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 4 Ways to Plot Data in Python Using Datalore]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=286377</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2022/10/12/top-4-ways-to-plot-data-in-python-using-datalore/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T15:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While tabular data works best for calculating descriptive statistics, you will need plotting to compare values and find complex insights. One of the easiest and most flexible ways to visualize and explore your data is by using Python charts. In this article, we will show you how to plot using Python libraries and Datalore. Plotting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Camunda 8 self-managed cluster and applications behind a directory]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=64638</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/securing-camunda-8-self-managed-cluster-and-applications-behind-a-directory/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Directory services are an effective way to manage an organization’s users, groups, printers, devices, and more. Most organizations accomplish this using Active Directory, Apache Directory, Oracle Internet Directory, or other similar tools. Recently I worked with a customer who wanted to see how he could secure the Camunda 8 Platform and process applications with such a directory. Their requirements consisted of: Allowing Directory users to access Camunda applications (Tasklist, Operate, Optimize) Accessing secured Tasklist & Operate APIs from our custom project Securing the custom project In this article, I’ll briefly explain the 3 easy steps taken to fulfill their requirements which include: Federate users from the Directory service into Keycloak Declare an application in Identity to access Camunda APIs Configure...
The post Securing Camunda 8 self-managed cluster and applications behind a directory appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christophe Dame</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate security into your developer workflow with GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65846</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/integrate-security-into-your-developer-workflow-with-github-advanced-security-for-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T12:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting things are in store for Azure DevOps in the coming year! We’re planning deep investments in security as well as broad investment across the product. Read on for more information, and then be sure to check out our updated roadmap at https://aka.ms/AzureDevOpsRoadmap.
The post Integrate security into your developer workflow with GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Hallberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0 goes RC1]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/12/spring-framework-6-0-goes-rc1</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/12/spring-framework-6-0-goes-rc1"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring community,

It is my pleasure to announce that a feature-complete Spring Framework 6.0 release candidate is available now! We are expecting a further release candidate in time for the first Spring Boot 3.0 release candidate next week, and then our final releases for general availability in November.

As a major revision of the core framework, 6.0 RC1 comes with a Java 17+ baseline, a move to Jakarta EE 9+ (in the jakarta namespace superseding the former javax based EE APIs), and a broader infrastructure revision. This provides access to the latest web containers such as Tomcat 10 / Jetty 11 and the latest persistence providers such as Hibernate ORM 6.1 - all of which are exclusively available with the jakarta-namespaced variants of the Servlet API and JPA. It also sets the st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Fleet Public Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=fleet&amp;p=285871</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/fleet/2022/10/introducing-the-fleet-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the initial announcement of Fleet, we have had an overwhelming amount of interest from all of you, with over 137,000 people signing up for the private preview. Our reason for starting with a closed preview was to be able to process the feedback in a gradual way. We want to thank each and every […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hadi Hariri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compose Multiplatform 1.2 Is Out: New Mouse and Keyboard APIs, ProGuard Support, Online Updates, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=285629</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2022/10/compose-multiplatform-1-2-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T08:42:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, Compose Multiplatform 1.2 is available for you to use! This latest version of the declarative UI framework for Kotlin brings compatibility with the latest Kotlin version and introduces several powerful features for the desktop target. Specifically, here are the highlights: The newly added ProGuard support allows you to minify and obfuscate your application […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Aigner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The uncanny valley of scale]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43932</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/715344454/0/sethsblog~The-uncanny-valley-of-scale/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T08:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big companies act like big companies. We don’t take them seriously when they say they care, because there is no “they.” When they send a holiday card or an email, we don’t really think it was from a person we could connect with. Individuals act like individuals. When they write us a note or show […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By the numbers: Public sector organizations quantify the benefits of Elastic solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/by-the-numbers-public-sector-organizations-quantify-the-benefits-of-elastic-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/by-the-numbers-public-sector-organizations-quantify-the-benefits-of-elastic-solutions"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help public sector organizations better understand how their peers are using Elastic and what results they’re seeing, we partnered with Socratic Technologies to manage and analyze a survey of our public sector and education customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The evolution of Discover in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-evolution-of-discover-in-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-evolution-of-discover-in-kibana"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover has been around for quite some time in Kibana. But recently, we've added a new document table, field statistics, and the ability to create threshold alert rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias Polman-Wilhelm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The automotive landscape is transforming — how can industry leaders stay ahead of the curve?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-automotive-landscape-is-transforming-how-can-industry-leaders-stay-ahead-of-the-curve</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-automotive-landscape-is-transforming-how-can-industry-leaders-stay-ahead-of-the-curve"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital transformation process in the automotive industry has already begun. With the current macroeconomic  headwinds, find out how automakers, OEMs, and suppliers can be successful in overcoming those speed bumps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By the numbers: Public sector organizations quantify the benefits of Elastic solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/by-the-numbers-public-sector-organizations-quantify-the-benefits-of-elastic-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/by-the-numbers-public-sector-organizations-quantify-the-benefits-of-elastic-solutions"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
When analyzing solution providers, it’s easy to get stuck in lists of product features and benefits, and harder to quantify what the actual results will be in your own environment. In some industries, like public sector, decision makers need to justify investments that will be put toward specialized use cases that apply only to their field, such as defense or public safety.

To help public sector organizations better understand how their peers are using Elastic and what results they’re seeing, we partnered with Socratic Technologies to manage and analyze a survey of our public sector and education customers. We wanted to know how — and how much — Elastic is helping them meet their missions, so that other organizations can understand how to best meet theirs. Respondents answered questions…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The evolution of Discover in Kibana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-evolution-of-discover-in-kibana</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-evolution-of-discover-in-kibana"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Discover has been around for quite some time. Still, it is one of the most used parts of Kibana, allowing you to search and view the atoms of Elasticsearch: the indexed documents. In 2015, it was released as part of Kibana 4. Let’s have a look at the early days of data discovery:
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt35ed3799b53db14f/6345c21b366c7610e0fbccc4/blog-elastic-evolution-1.png,blog-elastic-evolution-1.png,
In 5.6, the last significant change enabling users to view surrounding documents of a selected document was added (it was a separate plugin at that time). During 6.x and 7.x, we focused on removing technical debt, like moving from Angular 1 to React and migrating to Kibana’s new platform.

Now in 8.x, we’ve been adding big changes one after another. W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias Polman-Wilhelm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The automotive landscape is transforming — how can industry leaders stay ahead of the curve?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-automotive-landscape-is-transforming-how-can-industry-leaders-stay-ahead-of-the-curve</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/the-automotive-landscape-is-transforming-how-can-industry-leaders-stay-ahead-of-the-curve"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The automotive industry is on the cusp of a phase shift — thanks to changes in buyer behavior, mobility preferences, and technology advances in connectivity and AI. In fact, according to a Deloitte study,1 by 2035 revenues from “as-a-service” business models that leverage the economies of scale will grow by over 400%.

The digital transformation process has already begun. Leading car manufacturers have joined forces in various initiatives, such as the Mobility Open Blockchain Initiative (MOBI)2 and the MaaS Alliance,3 to simplify and protect financial operations, build transparency and agility in the supply chain, and design future-proof solutions that protect and accelerate the ability to achieve shared ownership and usage models at scale.

With the current macroeconomic conditions acti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Road Space Comparison]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2684/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2684/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/road_space_comparison.png" title="I wonder how hard it would be to ride an electric scooter in a hamster ball." alt="I wonder how hard it would be to ride an electric scooter in a hamster ball." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verifying distributed systems with Isabelle/HOL]]></title>
        <id>http://martin.kleppmann.com/2022/10/12/verifying-distributed-systems-isabelle.html</id>
        <link href="http://martin.kleppmann.com/2022/10/12/verifying-distributed-systems-isabelle.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post also appears on Larry Paulson’s blog. We use distributed systems every day in the form of internet services. These systems are very useful, but also challenging to implement because networks are unpredictable. Whenever you send a message over the network, it is likely to arrive quite quickly, but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Kleppmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Universe 2022 agenda is live]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-11-the-github-universe-2022-agenda-is-live/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-11-the-github-universe-2022-agenda-is-live/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T19:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore 80+ content sessions delivered by over 120 different speakers, across two days and four content tracks, all designed to level up your skills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View GitHub code scanning findings directly in VS Code and GitHub Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-11-view-github-code-scanning-findings-directly-in-vs-code-and-github-codespaces/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-11-view-github-code-scanning-findings-directly-in-vs-code-and-github-codespaces/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T19:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers can now view GitHub code scanning findings directly in VS Code and GitHub Codespaces. The new Microsoft SARIF Viewer extension gives developers direct access to their code scanning results, making remediating vulnerabilities easier than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State of Spring Survey 2022 Is Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/11/the-state-of-spring-survey-2022-is-here</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/11/the-state-of-spring-survey-2022-is-here"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The State of Spring survey is here! Please give us your feedback by going to spring.io/survey. Spread the word by sharing these posts on Twitter, LinkedIn, and any other social platform you use! 


Spring fans, our annual survey of the Spring community is back! Last year, we dived into the biggest projects and the most popular app patterns built with Spring, and a whole lot more! You told us your views about Spring Native, Data, and what matters to you when you start using a new Spring project.

The survey is back for 2022, and we’re really excited to learn again from you. What matters to you when you build with Spring? What types of apps are you building with Spring? What can we change, and what should remain the same?

Completing the survey should take about 15 minutes. If you want to be among the first to get the report, feel free to leave your email at the end of the survey.

Ok, if you’re ready, head over to spring.io/survey now!

One last thing - we’d really appreciate it if you share the survey with others in the Spring community. You can share the link spring.io/survey, or our Twitter and LinkedIn posts. Thank you!

The Spring Team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2022.2.3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=285867</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/10/pycharm-2022-2-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T16:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are releasing PyCharm 2022.2.3, which contains important fixes for workflows, including remote interpreters, and fixes for working with MicroPython plugin and the recent Matplotlib 3.6.0 package. You can update to this version from inside the IDE, by using the Toolbox App, or by using snaps for Ubuntu. You can also download it from our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode Bug-Fix Update 2022.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=285840</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/10/appcode-bug-fix-update-2022-2-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T16:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AppCode 2022.2.3 bug-fix update is now available! Build 222.4345.23 is available from our website, from the Toolbox App, or via an update patch from the IDE itself. DOWNLOAD APPCODE Here are the main highlights: Improved compatibility with Xcode 14.1 beta. The Create branch input field in the Open task window now has the correct […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the go with GitHub Projects on GitHub Mobile (public beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-11-on-the-go-with-github-projects-on-github-mobile-public-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-11-on-the-go-with-github-projects-on-github-mobile-public-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T16:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stay connected and up to date on your work with GitHub Projects on GitHub Mobile, now in public beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion Bug-Fix Update 2022.2.4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=285808</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/10/clion-bug-fix-update-2022-2-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T15:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CLion bug-fix update 2022.2.4 is now available! Download build 222.4345.21 from our website, through the Toolbox App, as a snap for Ubuntu, or via patch from the IDE. DOWNLOAD CLION The main highlights of this build include: We’ve fixed several bugs in code analysis: The Unreachable code warning is no longer triggered incorrectly in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8.1 Released – What’s New]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=64965</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/camunda-platform-8-1-released-whats-new/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re extremely excited to announce the release of Camunda Platform 8.1.  In this post, we will go into the highlights of this release including Web Modeler, Connectors, Zeebe, Operate, Optimize, and more. Here’s the highlights of what’s included in this release: Easier Installation and maintenance for Camunda Platform Self-managed Hot backups for Self-Managed Token-Based authentication Modeler updates Process Templates FEEL Expression Editor Inline Annotations Changes to Camunda forms Connectors updates Workflow engine updates Operate updates Optimize updates Let’s get started! Easier installation and maintenance for Camunda Platform Self-Managed Improved Guides and Support for OpenShift and Amazon EKS (AWS) With this release, we are introducing official support for deploying and running Camunda Platform 8 Self-Managed on OpenShift and Amazon EKS (AWS)....
The post Camunda Platform 8.1 Released – What’s New appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 7.18 Released – What’s New]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=65073</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/camunda-platform-7-18-released-whats-new/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re extremely excited to announce the release of Camunda Platform 7.18 Here are some of the highlights: Cockpit: Improved instance selection to avoid unintended batch operations Cockpit: Easier navigation of high batch operation volumes MDC logging features Camunda Forms in Tasklist: Populate select options via process data Exception error codes Filter and order tasks by last updated WebSphere Liberty New and retired supported environments You can download Camunda Platform or run it with Docker. For a complete list of the changes, please check out the release notes. For patched security vulnerabilities, see our security notices. If you want to dig deeper, check out the source code on GitHub. Cockpit: Improved instance selection to avoid unintended batch operations Previously, when performing...
The post Camunda Platform 7.18 Released – What’s New appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate Connectivity with Camunda Platform 8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=64182</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/10/accelerate-connectivity-with-camunda-platform-8-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re thrilled to announce Camunda Platform 8.1, the latest release of our process orchestration solution. This new version introduces features that accelerate connectivity to the many different systems and technologies that are required for true digital transformation, including: Create custom Connectors with our Integration Framework to accelerate connectivity New out-of-the-box Connectors for popular services Enhancements to Camunda Modeler that improve productivity Hot backups and official support for Amazon EKS and Red Hat OpenShift Plus, several upgrades requested by Camunda Platform 7 customers Organizations across all industries rely on complex technology stacks to adapt and enhance their operations in response to market dynamics, new disruptive companies, and increasing consumer expectations. Your technology stack likely includes everything from cutting-edge technologies to legacy...
The post Accelerate Connectivity with Camunda Platform 8.1 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Without reservations]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42982</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/715240176/0/sethsblog~Without-reservations/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not sure we have a common word for this. “Yes” can mean, “yes, I’m prepared to do the minimum” or it could mean, “yes, this commitment is something I wholeheartedly embrace and will devote myself to exceeding expectations at every turn.” Life’s way better if we find partnerships that are the second kind. “All […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing Virtual Threads]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/11/embracing-virtual-threads</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/11/embracing-virtual-threads"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project Loom has made it into the JDK through JEP 425. It’s available since Java 19 in September 2022 as a preview feature.
Its goal is to dramatically reduce the effort of writing, maintaining, and observing high-throughput concurrent applications.



Where Virtual Threads make sense



This makes lightweight Virtual Threads an exciting approach for application developers and the Spring Framework. Past years indicated a trend towards applications that communicate over the network with each other. Many applications make use of data stores, message brokers, and remote services. I/O-intensive applications are the primary ones that benefit from Virtual Threads if they were built to use blocking I/O facilities such as InputStream and synchronous HTTP, database, and message broker client…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - October 11th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/11/this-week-in-spring-october-11th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/11/this-week-in-spring-october-11th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! I write this installment as I pack and prepare for my trip to Antwerp, Belgium, for the always-amazing Devoxx show in Antwerp, Belgium. I’ve so missed this show over the pandemic and am so looking forward to returning. I hope to catch any and all of you there, too! I’ll be copresenting with my pal James Ward about some of the new and novel in Spring Boot 3 and Kotlin. It’s going to be awesome - join us and we’ll have some fun together! 

Now, we’ve got a ton to cover so let’s dive right into it!


  
Spring Tips: Spring Boot & Apache Kafka

  
Spring Batch 5.0.0-M7 available now!

  
Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M5 is now available

  
Spring Shell 2.1.2 and 3.0.0-M1 are now available

  
The State of Spring Survey

  
I put the updated code for my latest incarnation of Cloud Native Java - online in Github cloud-native-java-2022/e2e5

  
A Bootiful Podcast: Spring and Java community legend Marten Deinum

  
Difference Between Flux and Mono in Project Reactor

  
Hey - Baeldung.com (yes, that Baeldung.com!) is using Spring, and they’re looking for a Java Team Lead with Spring Experience (Remote) (Part Time)

  
Patterns for Iterating Over Large Result Sets With Spring Data JPA

  
JobRunr’s already been upgraded to Spring Boot 3 for the JRE - and perhaps Spring Boot 3 AOT support is on the way?

  
JMeter: Latency vs. Load Time


Want to learn more about Spring Boot and the wider ecosystem? SpringOne 2022 is almost here! If you want a chance to learn from the source, I hope you’ll join us 6-8 December 2022, right here in my hometown of San Francisco, my favorite west coast city in the USA. (Psst.: If you register now, there’s a $200 discount from the pass price with this code S1VM22_Advocate_200.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Google Cloud announce expanded and deeper partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-google-cloud-announce-expanded-and-deeper-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-google-cloud-announce-expanded-and-deeper-partnership"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to share that Elastic and Google Cloud are expanding and deepening our partnership to help organizations search, observe, and protect their data and workloads on Google Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin Richards,Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Google Cloud announce expanded and deeper partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-google-cloud-announce-expanded-and-deeper-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-google-cloud-announce-expanded-and-deeper-partnership"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We’re pleased to share that Elastic and Google Cloud are expanding and deepening our partnership to help organizations more easily search, observe, and protect their data and workloads. 

Today, we announce three new integrations we will be working on together: 

An integrated search experience with BigQuery and BigLake, allowing users to employ Elasticsearch to drive insights from data that reside in data lakes on Google Cloud.
Native integrations into a broader set of Google Cloud services for Elastic Observability and Elastic Security.
An integrated visualization experience for Looker to enable users to easily view Elastic analytical insights.

Our joint investments will make it easier for customers to monitor and secure Google Cloud workloads; build advanced search capabilities bring…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin Richards,Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 Trn1 Instances for High-Performance Model Training are Now Available]]></title>
        <id>71e7c11b2e368b46b3451452c13a32231a1453a3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-trn1-instances-for-high-performance-model-training-are-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T21:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deep learning (DL) models have been increasing in size and complexity over the last few years, pushing the time to train from days to weeks. Training large language models the size of GPT-3 can take months, leading to an exponential growth in training cost. To reduce model training times and enable machine learning (ML) practitioners […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – October 10, 2022]]></title>
        <id>7c008f7e8cef2812709e94fb9b2a1a09fcd48422</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-october-10-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T20:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I had an amazing start to the week last week as I was speaking at the AWS Community Day NL. This event had 500 attendees and over 70 speakers, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publishing extensions to Marketplace issue resolved]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65675</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/publishing-extensions-to-marketplace-issue-resolved/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T16:08:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have resolved a known issue regarding publishing extensions to the Visual Studio Marketplace. If you’ve run into the error message: “Your ability to create global personal access tokens (PATs) is restricted by your organization.”, this is likely because your administrator has enabled a policy to restrict the creation of global personal access tokens (PATs).
The post Publishing extensions to Marketplace issue resolved appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.13 Significantly Improves Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-13-significantly-improves-performance</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-13-significantly-improves-performance"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform (CDKTF) 0.13 vastly reduces synth time across all supported languages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add a store locator to your ecommerce storefront with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-add-a-store-locator-to-your-ecommerce-storefront-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-add-a-store-locator-to-your-ecommerce-storefront-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how to add a physical store locator, complete with maps, on your ecommerce storefront with Elastic Enterprise Search. This step-by-step post includes code samples and a code sandbox for you to try it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lionel Palacin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add a store locator to your ecommerce storefront with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-add-a-store-locator-to-your-ecommerce-storefront-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-add-a-store-locator-to-your-ecommerce-storefront-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
One thing that adds value to a business’s ecommerce presence is the ability for customers to easily find physical stores with an interactive map. Store locators can be built quite rapidly — all you need to place them on a map is geographic location in latitude and longitude.


In this post, I’ll outline the pieces needed to put together a proof-of-concept store locator that could later be added to an ecommerce website.


[Related article: Building personalized ecommerce search experiences with Elastic]
Indexing data and making it searchable
In this example, we’re going to make use of two datasets:

A list of stores with their location
A list of cities in the U.S. with their location 

Both datasets are provided in our sample repository as JSON files.


Here is an example of a store in JS…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lionel Palacin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compared to what]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42949</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/715130524/0/sethsblog~Compared-to-what/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T09:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satisfaction is often driven by the story we tell ourselves. How does this rank compared to what I expected? Compared to what I used to have? Compared to the person sitting next to me? The richest person in the world used to sleep on the floor and eat moldy food, but still felt great because […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: Spring Boot & Apache Kafka]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/10/spring-tips-spring-boot-apache-kafka</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/10/spring-tips-spring-boot-apache-kafka"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment of Spring Tips, I look at the venerable Apache Kafka broker and its integrations at various level of abstraction in the Spring Boot ecosystem.


Want to learn more about event driven architectures, AOT and GraalVM, Apache Kafka, and Spring Boot? SpringOne 2022 is almost here! If you want a chance to learn from the source, then I hope you’ll join us 6-8 December 2022, right here in my hometown of San Francisco, my favorite west coast city in the USA. (Psst.: If you register now, there’s a $200 discount from the pass price with this code S1VM22_Advocate_200.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Mental Health Day 2022: Supporting Elasticians and their families to Be.Well]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-world-mental-health-day-2021-supporting-elasticians-and-their-families-to-be-well</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-world-mental-health-day-2021-supporting-elasticians-and-their-families-to-be-well"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World Mental Health Day is October 10th and is a time to raise awareness around prioritizing our mental health and continuing the conversation in the workplace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leah Sutton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Mental Health Day 2022: Supporting Elasticians and their families to Be.Well]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-world-mental-health-day-2021-supporting-elasticians-and-their-families-to-be-well</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-world-mental-health-day-2021-supporting-elasticians-and-their-families-to-be-well"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
World Mental Health Day is on October 10, and Elastic remains committed to supporting Elasticians and their mental well-being through a range of support programs.
As a mom, wife, daughter, colleague and leader here at Elastic, I understand how we all play myriad roles outside of the one listed on our resume or LinkedIn profile. As I’ve struggled and have seen my friends, family, and colleagues struggle to show up for themselves and for each other, I’ve thought a great deal about how crucial it is to make yourself a priority. We can’t even begin to do our best work until we can bring our best self to all of the roles that make us who we are. 
This week is a reminder for all of us to acknowledge the importance of prioritizing our mental health and continuing the conversation in the workpla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leah Sutton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing data automation through hot, warm, cold, and frozen tiers — No coding needed!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/managing-data-automation-through-hot-warm-cold-and-frozen-tiers-no-coding-needed</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/managing-data-automation-through-hot-warm-cold-and-frozen-tiers-no-coding-needed"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post serves as a guide on how to use Kibana's “Stack Management” feature-set to automate the movement of your data through hot, warm, cold and frozen tiers, without the need to do any coding or execute command-line actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Quek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximizing the experience of Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes with Azure Kubernetes Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/maximizing-the-experience-of-elastic-cloud-on-kubernetes-with-azure-kubernetes-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/maximizing-the-experience-of-elastic-cloud-on-kubernetes-with-azure-kubernetes-service"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic on Azure allows you to harness your data to better understand customers, refine operations, and develop trusted long-term relationships.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemant Malik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing data automation through hot, warm, cold, and frozen tiers — No coding needed!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/managing-data-automation-through-hot-warm-cold-and-frozen-tiers-no-coding-needed</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/managing-data-automation-through-hot-warm-cold-and-frozen-tiers-no-coding-needed"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
If you are looking to do exactly what the title of this article suggests, look no further. This post intends to be a guide on how one can use the Kibana Dashboard’s “Stack Management” feature-set to automate the movement of your data through hot, warm, cold, and frozen tiers, without the need to do any coding or execute command-line actions.
Before we begin: Core concepts
Let’s take a step back to understand some core concepts of how data sits and moves within your Elasticsearch cluster before we go into how you can automate its movement. This is so we will be familiar with certain terms and patterns later on when we go into the hands-on step-by-step process in practice.

If your organization stores data, you will definitely need to consider a technical concept called “High Availability”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Quek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximizing the experience of Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes with Azure Kubernetes Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/maximizing-the-experience-of-elastic-cloud-on-kubernetes-with-azure-kubernetes-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/maximizing-the-experience-of-elastic-cloud-on-kubernetes-with-azure-kubernetes-service"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The world’s most iconic retailers leverage Elastic to streamline product development, perform smoother application monitoring, and close essential security gaps. With a tailored set of tools, you can create unique customer journeys that drive revenue and maximize your omnichannel strategy. Elastic on Azure allows you to harness your data to better understand customers, refine operations, and develop trusted long-term relationships.
Elastic and Azure Kubernetes Apps Marketplace 
Our partnership with Microsoft is focused on helping you get more out of both your data and your infrastructure. By combining the power of search and a future-ready cloud, it’s easier than ever to innovate and adapt to turn possibilities into results. With Elastic and Microsoft Azure, you can search faster, keep m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemant Malik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fan Theories]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2683/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2683/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/fan_theories.png" title="The universe fandom is great. Such sweet and enthusiastic people." alt="The universe fandom is great. Such sweet and enthusiastic people." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The invisibility paradox]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42023</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/715020458/0/sethsblog~The-invisibility-paradox/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T08:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The optic nerve dominates. It’s piped directly into our brains and uses a lot of processing power to help us discern the world through vision. As a result, it’s louder than our other senses and often outshouts the rest of our brain. That’s why it’s easy to be fooled by a magician. This focus on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Points of view]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=31895</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/714869252/0/sethsblog~Points-of-view/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The closer we look at what other people believe and do, the more clear it is that our view of the world doesn’t precisely match theirs. It never has, but now it’s magnified. The things we thought were a given, aren’t. No one believes what I believe, not exactly. How is it possible, we wonder, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 211 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65804</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-211-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T14:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sprint 211 was a busy one. We were able to complete a lot of bugs and yet introduce some new exciting features. We also enabled a “Try the New Boards Hub” banner and popup to the legacy boards experience on select organizations.
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 211 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A lot is a choice]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42926</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/714697006/0/sethsblog~A-lot-is-a-choice/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might want to make something that a lot of people want a little… Or you could make something that a few people want a lot. It’s usually neither. It’s rarely (very rarely) both. If you work hard and make intentional choices, though, you might end up with one or the other.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy or Hard]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2682/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2682/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/easy_or_hard.png" title="&quot;Friction-driven static electrification is familiar and fundamental in daily life, industry, and technology, but its basics have long been unknown and have continually perplexed scientists from ancient Greece to the high-tech era. [...] To date, no single theory can satisfactorily explain this mysterious but fundamental phenomenon.&quot; --Eui-Cheol Shin et. al. (2022)" alt="&quot;Friction-driven static electrification is familiar and fundamental in daily life, industry, and technology, but its basics have long been unknown and have continually perplexed scientists from ancient Greece to the high-tech era. [...] To date, no single theory can satisfactorily explain this mysterious but fundamental phenomenon.&quot; --Eui-Cheol Shin et. al. (2022)" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are now included in the WIPO Global Innovation Index]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-06-developers-are-now-included-in-the-wipo-global-innovation-index/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-06-developers-are-now-included-in-the-wipo-global-innovation-index/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T21:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited that the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO) has launched the 2022 edition of its Global Innovation Index (GII) with an indicator of developer creative outputs based on GitHub commits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-M5 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/06/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m5-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/06/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-m5-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T20:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Milestone 5 (M5) of the Spring Cloud 2022.0.0 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2022.0.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2022.00-M5 Release Train
Spring Cloud Netflix


  
Updated to Eureka 2.0.0-rc.3. Eureka 2.0.0 is a new branch of Eureka unrelated to the old 2.x-archive experiment from 7 years ago. The new 2.x branch is for compatibility with JakartaEE. This allows Spring Cloud Netflix to be compatible with Spring Framework 6.0 and Spring Boot 3.0. This is the first milestone that Spring Cloud Netflix has participated in the 2022.0 release train.


Spring Cloud Consul


  
Added runtime hints to enable native image s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AudioLM: a Language Modeling Approach to Audio Generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/audiolm-language-modeling-approach-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/audiolm-language-modeling-approach-to.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zalán Borsos, Research Software Engineer, and Neil Zeghidour, Research Scientist, Google Research 
Generating realistic audio requires modeling information represented at different scales. For example, just as music builds complex musical phrases from individual notes, speech combines temporally local structures, such as phonemes or syllables, into words and sentences. Creating well-structured and coherent audio sequences at all these scales is a challenge that has been addressed by coupling audio with transcriptions that can guide the generative process, be it text transcripts for speech synthesis or MIDI representations for piano. However, this approach breaks when trying to model untranscribed aspects of audio, such as speaker characteristics necessary to help people with spee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub’s supply chain security features now support Dart]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-06-githubs-supply-chain-security-features-now-support-dart/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-06-githubs-supply-chain-security-features-now-support-dart/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T18:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-platform apps built with the popular Flutter toolkit can now benefit from Dependabot alerts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.4 Adds Nomad Variables and Updates Service Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-4-adds-nomad-variables-and-updates-service-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-4-adds-nomad-variables-and-updates-service-discovery"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GA release of HashiCorp Nomad 1.4 enhances native service discovery support with health checks and introduces Nomad Variables, which lets users store configuration values.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Waypoint Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-waypoint-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-waypoint-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint — now available on the HashiCorp Cloud Platform in public beta — lets users standardize application delivery across platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Gains Visibility, Self-Service, and Compliance Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-gains-visibility-self-service-and-compliance-upgrades</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-gains-visibility-self-service-and-compliance-upgrades"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous validation, no-code provisioning, native OPA support for Terraform Cloud, and other new features are key upgrades to HashiCorp Terraform introduced at HashiConf Global 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For the upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=41946</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/714577306/0/sethsblog~For-the-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The phone in your pocket cost $600, but that was two years ago, so now, it seems to be free and fully paid for. The upgrade has a slightly better camera and a slightly faster processor. Here’s the question: “If you could have chosen between the phone you have now and the phone you want […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[js13kGames 2022 winners 🏆]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-06-js13k-2022-winners/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-06-js13k-2022-winners/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T07:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The eleventh annual js13kGames coding competition, challenging participants to create games in 13kB or less of JavaScript in a month, just wrapped up. This post highlights the top thirteen entries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring and Java community legend Marten Deinum]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/06/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-and-java-community-legend-marten-deinum</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/06/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-and-java-community-legend-marten-deinum"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to longtime Spring community member and legend Marten Deinum (@mdeinum) about scuba diving, software, Spring, community, and more. 

Also: I fixed the odd silence in the middle of the last few episodes! thanks for suffering through it with me. I have no idea what went wrong but I know now how to fix it


Want to meet more amazing people in our ecosystem, like Marten? SpringOne 2022 is almost here! I feel like it’s that anxious, exciting time before, sort of important holiday where you get given gifts! And with it, Spring Boot 3 and Spring Framework 6. We’re going to be announcing everything right here on the Spring blog, of course, but if you want a chance to learn from the source, then I hope you’ll join us 6-8 December 2022, right here in my hometown of San Francisco, my favorite west coast city in the USA, and my hometown. (Psst.: If you register now, there’s a $200 discount from the pass price with this code S1VM22_Advocate_200.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Local Zones Expansion: Taipei and Delhi]]></title>
        <id>4ed417884c91622d902ab22f2b9f806063ec1a09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-local-zones-expansion-taipei-and-delhi/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T21:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In late 2019 I told you about the AWS Local Zone in Los Angeles, California. In that post I described Local Zones as a new type of AWS infrastructure deployment that brings select AWS services very close to a particular geographic area. A year after that launch, I announced our plans to add 3 more […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect secrets in your code more accurately with dry runs for custom patterns now available in GitHub Advanced Security]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-10-05-detect-secrets-in-your-code-more-accurately-with-dry-runs-for-custom-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-10-05-detect-secrets-in-your-code-more-accurately-with-dry-runs-for-custom-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T18:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can seamlessly define trusted custom secret patterns to detect secrets unique to your organization with GitHub Advanced Security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Boundary — Now GA — Bolsters HashiCorp's Zero Trust Security Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-boundary-now-ga-bolsters-hashicorp-s-zero-trust-security-solution</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-boundary-now-ga-bolsters-hashicorp-s-zero-trust-security-solution"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of HCP Boundary lets developers access critical systems with fine-grained authorizations — without managing credentials or exposing your network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault on Microsoft Azure Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-on-microsoft-azure-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-on-microsoft-azure-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to its availability on AWS, HCP Vault can now be deployed on Microsoft Azure infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Developer: Your New Experience for Docs and Tutorials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-developer-your-new-experience-for-docs-and-tutorials</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-developer-your-new-experience-for-docs-and-tutorials"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Developer is your one-stop shop for interactive labs, sample code, videos, tutorials, and in-depth documentation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.14 Beta: Announcing Simplified Service Mesh Deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-14-beta-announcing-simplified-service-mesh-deployments</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-14-beta-announcing-simplified-service-mesh-deployments"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul 1.14 enhances traffic management and failover, and adds a new deployment method: Consul dataplane. AWS Lambda updates and beta Windows VM support were also added.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a New HCP-Based Management Plane for Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-a-new-hcp-based-management-plane-for-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-a-new-hcp-based-management-plane-for-consul"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Cloud Platform (HCP) adds new visibility and management controls for self-managed and HCP-managed Consul deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.2 and 3.0.0-M1 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/05/spring-shell-2-1-2-and-3-0-0-m1-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/05/spring-shell-2-1-2-and-3-0-0-m1-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T10:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.2 and 3.0.0-M1 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release, Maven Central and https://repo.spring.io/milestone respectively.

3.0.0-M1 is first milestone which builds on Spring Boot 3.x and requires JDK 17.

Please see the release notes 2.1.2 and release notes 3.0.0-M1 for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0.0-M7 available now!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/05/spring-batch-5-0-0-m7-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/05/spring-batch-5-0-0-m7-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and all contributors, I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 5.0.0-M7 is now available from our milestone repository.

The main theme of this milestone is the improvement of job parameters handling in Spring Batch. Two main changes were introduced in this release:


  
Add support to use any type as a job parameter

  
Improve job parameters conversion


This blog post walks through these two major changes in details. For the complete list of changes, please check the release notes.
Add support to use any type as a job parameter

Up to version 4, Spring Batch supported only 4 types that can be used as job parameters, which are long, double, String and Date. While this was convenient to simplify job parameters handling on the framework’s side, it turns out t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Current State: 2019 Third Party Security Audit of Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/05/current-state-2019-third-party-audit/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/05/current-state-2019-third-party-audit/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors (in alphabetical order): Cailyn Edwards (Shopify), Pushkar Joglekar (VMware), Rey Lejano (SUSE) and Rory McCune (DataDog)
We expect the brand new Third Party Security Audit of Kubernetes will be
published later this month (Oct 2022).
In preparation for that, let's look at the state of findings that were made
public as part of the last third party security audit of
2019
that was based on Kubernetes v1.13.4.
Motivation
Craig Ingram has graciously attempted over the years to keep track of the
status of the findings reported in the last audit in this issue:
kubernetes/kubernetes#81146.
This blog post will attempt to dive deeper into this, address any gaps
in tracking and become a point in time summary of the state of the
findings reported from 2019.
This article should also help reader…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2022 HashiCorp Technology Partner Award Winners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2022-hashicorp-technology-partner-award-winners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2022-hashicorp-technology-partner-award-winners"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 HashiCorp Technology Partner Awards have been announced. Find out who the winners are in our four categories this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large Motion Frame Interpolation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/large-motion-frame-interpolation.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/10/large-motion-frame-interpolation.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T18:43:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Fitsum Reda and Janne Kontkanen, Google Research 
Frame interpolation is the process of synthesizing in-between images from a given set of images. The technique is often used for temporal up-sampling to increase the refresh rate of videos or to create slow motion effects. Nowadays, with digital cameras and smartphones, we often take several photos within a few seconds to capture the best picture. Interpolating between these “near-duplicate” photos can lead to engaging videos that reveal scene motion, often delivering an even more pleasing sense of the moment than the original photos.  
  
Frame interpolation between consecutive video frames, which often have small motion, has been studied extensively. Unlike videos, however, the temporal spacing between near-duplicate photos can …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - October 4th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/04/this-week-in-spring-october-4th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/10/04/this-week-in-spring-october-4th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! It’s October 4th, 2022, and I’m in Austin, TX, for the new version of show formerly known as the Kafka Summit, here to talk to folks about the amazing opportunities for Spring Boot and Apache Kafka. On the 12th, I’ll be in Antwerp, Belgium, for the amazing Devoxx show. On October 17-20th, I’ll be in Las Vegas, for the new version of JavaOne. And, well, there’s more but I can’t say exactly. Stay tuned!

And as for now, well, I’m excited to be here! We’ve got a ton of cool stuff to cover this week, so let’s dive right into it!


  
A Bootiful Podcast: thought leader Chris Richardson (and no, I’m not using that title ironically!)

  
Getting a URL Attribute Value in Thymeleaf

  
RabbitMQ 3.11 Feature Preview: Super …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing Kueue]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/04/introducing-kueue/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/04/introducing-kueue/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Abdullah Gharaibeh (Google), Aldo Culquicondor (Google)
Whether on-premises or in the cloud, clusters face real constraints for resource usage, quota, and cost management reasons. Regardless of the autoscalling capabilities, clusters have finite capacity. As a result, users want an easy way to fairly and
efficiently share resources.
In this article, we introduce Kueue,
an open source job queueing controller designed to manage batch jobs as a single unit.
Kueue leaves pod-level orchestration to existing stable components of Kubernetes.
Kueue natively supports the Kubernetes Job
API and offers hooks for integrating other custom-built APIs for batch jobs.
Why Kueue?
Job queueing is a key feature to run batch workloads at scale in both on-premises and cloud environments. The main goal…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of Amazon Connect Cases]]></title>
        <id>b52baf93c46bb68d0030598dd7ae15d1a9913d72</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-general-availability-of-amazon-connect-cases/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T20:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June 2022 AWS announced a preview of Amazon Connect Cases, a feature of Amazon Connect that simplifies these customer interactions and reduces the average handle times of issues. Today I am excited to announce the general availability of Amazon Connect Cases. Cases, a feature of Amazon Connect, makes it easy for your contact center […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – October 3, 2022]]></title>
        <id>ae5d0488bf0646507a69e9e761f48098a248df55</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-october-3-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T18:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! A new week and a new month just started. Curious which were the most significant AWS news from the previous seven days? I got you covered with this post. Last […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hands-On Course for Business Analysts – Practical Decision Making using No-Code ML on AWS]]></title>
        <id>732ba82c2e85ba6a2394bf8a29ee95a5e73a4c90</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-hands-on-course-for-business-analysts-practical-decision-making-using-no-code-ml-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T16:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is all around us. AI sends certain emails to our spam folders. It powers autocorrect, which helps us fix typos when we text. And now we can use it to solve business problems. In business, data-driven insights have become increasingly valuable. These insights are often discovered with the help of machine learning […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Ansible and Packer, From Provisioning to Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-and-packer-why-they-are-better-together</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-and-packer-why-they-are-better-together"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform can help you orchestrate, operationalize and govern your hybrid cloud deployments.  In my last public cloud blog, I talked about Two Simple Ways Automation Can Save You Money on Your AWS Bill and similarly to Ashton’s blog Bringing Order to the Cloud: Day 2 Operations in AWS with Ansible, we both wanted to look outside the common public cloud use-case of provisioning and deprovisioning resources and instead look at automating common operational tasks.  For this blog post I want to cover how the Technical Marketing team for Ansible orchestrates a pipeline for demos and workshops with Ansible and how we integrate that with custom AMIs (Amazon Machine Images) created with Packer.  Packer is an open source tool that allows IT operators to standardize and automate the process of building system images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: alpha support for running Pods with user namespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/03/userns-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/03/userns-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Rodrigo Campos (Microsoft), Giuseppe Scrivano (Red Hat)
Kubernetes v1.25 introduces the support for user namespaces.
This is a major improvement for running secure workloads in
Kubernetes. Each pod will have access only to a limited subset of the
available UIDs and GIDs on the system, thus adding a new security
layer to protect from other pods running on the same system.
How does it work?
A process running on Linux can use up to 4294967296 different UIDs and
GIDs.
User namespaces is a Linux feature that allows mapping a set of users
in the container to different users in the host, thus restricting what
IDs a process can effectively use.
Furthermore, the capabilities granted in a new user namespace do not
apply in the host initial namespaces.
Why is it important?
There are mainly t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using FEEL with Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=64132</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/using-feel-with-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T16:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is FEEL As a part of the Decision Model and Notation (DMN) specification, the OMG also defined the Friendly Enough Expression Language (FEEL).  Since DMN is intended to be used by designers and business analysts who would like to build decision tables, FEEL needed to be designed as an uncomplicated and human-readable expression language that would help readers understand the logic being described or executed by the DMN table.  Expression languages are typically used by developers to evaluate data to produce a result based on query parameters or conditions. This means it’s syntactically closer to code than human-readable sentences. Since one of the goals of FEEL is to be “process analyst friendly,” it prioritizes readability more than other expression...
The post Using FEEL with Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon File Cache – A High Performance Cache On AWS For Your On-Premises File Systems]]></title>
        <id>5ab6ca4c7fbca6e707e93106cb015a859442a687</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-file-cache-a-high-performance-cache-on-aws-for-your-on-premises-file-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T14:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce today the availability of Amazon File Cache, a new high-speed cache service on AWS designed for processing file data stored in disparate locations—including on premises. File Cache accelerates and simplifies your most demanding cloud bursting and hybrid workflows by giving your applications access to files using a fast and familiar […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Camunda 8 supports process automation at enterprise scale]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63983</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/how-camunda-8-supports-process-automation-at-enterprise-scale/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling process automation across an enterprise naturally includes a wide array of challenges. To counter these challenges, more and more organizations are evolving their organizational structures accordingly, often creating Centers of Excellence (CoE) and/or communities of practice (CoP). Please note that during this post we will use the term CoE, but keep in mind your organization might call this very differently. That said, in Camunda Platform 8, we included new functionalities that will help companies to scale process automation successfully.  This blog post discusses different aspects of scaling process automation, the role of CoEs, and how new Camunda 8 features support those initiatives.  What does scaling mean? Organizations that want to create a competitive edge through digital transformation (and frankly: which...
The post How Camunda 8 supports process automation at enterprise scale appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon WorkSpaces Introduces Ubuntu Desktops]]></title>
        <id>f345653beefe2e326410b05edcca8bc0fdf98a41</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-workspaces-introduces-ubuntu-desktops/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T16:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS, we love to give our customers choices: the choice of infrastructure to deploy your workloads, to store your most important data, or the operating systems for your virtual desktops. Many of you choose Amazon Workspaces to provision and distribute virtual desktops securely and at scale to your workforce. Our customers choose Workspaces when […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dungeons & Dragons for Team Building]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dungeons-dragons-for-team-building</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dungeons-dragons-for-team-building"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Community team used a custom Dungeons & Dragons campaign as a team building exercise. Check out the highlights and then try it yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Programming Languages for Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63832</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/seven-best-programming-languages-for-microservices/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices are an architectural style that structures an application as a collection of services that are: Highly maintainable and testable Loosely coupled Independently deployable Organized around business capabilities Owned by a small team Conway’s Law states that “any organization that designs a system (defined broadly) will produce a design whose structure is a copy of the organization’s communication structure”. If your organization has multiple teams working on different parts of a larger system, then microservices can serve as a separation of concerns that map an independent, encapsulated service to a specific team. These teams have clear boundaries of responsibility and can deploy on their own schedule. These factors lend themselves to a polyglot approach. What this means is that because...
The post 7 Best Programming Languages for Microservices appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast:   thought leader Chris Richardson (and no, I'm not using that title ironically!)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/29/a-bootiful-podcast-thought-leader-chris-richardson-and-no-i-m-not-using-that-title-ironically</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/29/a-bootiful-podcast-thought-leader-chris-richardson-and-no-i-m-not-using-that-title-ironically"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to his friend Chris Richardson (@crichardson), who helped articulate and advance cloud computing, reactive programming, microservices, domain-driven design, event sourcing, and so much more years before the zeitgeist. Also, we used to work together! 


Want to meet more amazing people in our ecosystem, like Chris? SpringOne 2022 is almost here! I feel like it’s that anxious, exciting time before, sort of important holiday where you get given gifts! And with it, Spring Boot 3 and Spring Framework 6. We’re going to be announcing everything right here on the Spring blog, of course, but if you want a chance to learn from the source, then I hope you’ll join us 6-8 December 2022, right here in my hometown of San Francisco, my favorite west coast city in the USA, and my hometown. (Psst.: If you register now, there’s a $200 discount from the pass price with this code S1VM22_Advocate_200.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Enforce CRD Immutability with CEL Transition Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/29/enforce-immutability-using-cel/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/29/enforce-immutability-using-cel/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alexander Zielenski (Google)
Immutable fields can be found in a few places in the built-in Kubernetes types.
For example, you can't change the .metadata.name of an object. Specific objects
have fields where changes to existing objects are constrained; for example, the
.spec.selector of a Deployment.
Aside from simple immutability, there are other common design patterns such as
lists which are append-only, or a map with mutable values and immutable keys.
Until recently the best way to restrict field mutability for CustomResourceDefinitions
has been to create a validating
admission webhook:
this means a lot of complexity for the common case of making a field immutable.
Beta since Kubernetes 1.25, CEL Validation Rules allow CRD authors to express
validation constraints on their fields…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timestone: Netflix’s High-Throughput, Low-Latency Priority Queueing System with Built-in Support…]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1abf249ba95f</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/timestone-netflixs-high-throughput-low-latency-priority-queueing-system-with-built-in-support-1abf249ba95f?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T15:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Kostas Christidis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic inventory plugin collection for network device management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/dynamic-inventory-plugin-collection-for-network-device-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/dynamic-inventory-plugin-collection-for-network-device-management"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tackling the complexities of enterprise inventories
 
One common challenge our customers face is the need to track hosts from multiple sources: LDAP, cloud providers, and enterprise CMDB systems. Using a dynamic inventory allows users to integrate with these systems and update the Ansible inventory as it varies over time, with hosts spinning up and shutting down in response to business demands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric McLeroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zbchaos — A new fault injection tool for Zeebe]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63238</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/zbchaos-a-new-fault-injection-tool-for-zeebe/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During Summer Hackdays 2022, I worked on a project called “Zeebe chaos” (zbchaos), a fault injection command-line interface (CLI) tool. This allows us engineers to more easily run chaos experiments against Zeebe, build up confidence in the system’s capabilities, and discover potential weaknesses. Requirements To understand this blog post, it is useful to have a certain understanding of Kubernetes and Zeebe itself. Summer Hackdays: Hackdays are a regular event at Camunda, where people from different departments (engineering, consulting, DevRel, etc.) work together on new ideas, pet projects, and more. Check out previous Summer Hackdays here: Summer Hackdays 2020 Summer Hackdays 2019 Zeebe chaos CLI Working on the Zeebe project is not only about engineering a distributed system or a process...
The post Zbchaos — A new fault injection tool for Zeebe appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Zell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantization for Fast and Environmentally Sustainable Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/quantization-for-fast-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/quantization-for-fast-and.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T17:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Srivatsan Krishnan, Student Researcher, and Aleksandra Faust, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team   
Deep reinforcement learning (RL) continues to make great strides in solving real-world sequential decision-making problems such as balloon navigation, nuclear physics, robotics, and games. Despite its promise, one of its limiting factors is long training times. While the current approach to speed up RL training on complex and difficult tasks leverages distributed training scaling up to hundreds or even thousands of computing nodes, it still requires the use of significant hardware resources which makes RL training expensive, while increasing its environmental impact. However, recent work [1, 2] indicates that performance optimizations on existing hardware …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IoT FleetWise Now Generally Available – Easily Collect Vehicle Data and Send to the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>852c2e070c6cea86911d87c790881d8de55886cb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-iot-fleetwise-now-generally-available-easily-collect-vehicle-data-and-send-to-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T16:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we announce the general availability of AWS IoT FleetWise, a fully managed AWS service that makes it easier to collect, transform, and transfer vehicle data to the cloud. Last AWS re:Invent 2021, we previewed AWS IoT FleetWise, heard customer feedback, and improved features for various use cases of near-real-time vehicle data processing. With AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise Adds Run Metrics, Versioned Docs, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-run-metrics-versioned-docs-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-run-metrics-versioned-docs-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise enhances observability and cuts operational burden with improved run metrics, identity-based storage authentication, and versioned documentation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delete Passwords: Passwordless Connections for Spring Boot  Apps to Azure Services]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/27/delete-passwords-passwordless-connections-for-spring-boot-apps-to-azure-services</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/27/delete-passwords-passwordless-connections-for-spring-boot-apps-to-azure-services"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T09:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using username/password credentials to access one application from another presents a huge security risk for many
    reasons. Today, we are announcing the preview of passwordless connections for Java applications to Azure database
    and eventing services, letting you finally shift away from using passwords. 

Security Challenges with Passwords

Passwords should be used with caution, and developers must never place passwords in an unsecure location. Many Java
    applications connect to backend data, cache, messaging, and eventing services using usernames and passwords, or other sensitive credentials such as access tokens or connection strings.
    If exposed, the passwords could be used to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information such as a sales catalog
    that you…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 27th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/27/this-week-in-spring-september-27th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/27/this-week-in-spring-september-27th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring!

It’s the last week of September, already! The year’s more done than not. The days are receding into darkness earlier. And the Pumpkin Spice Lattes are upon us. The darker and colder days are kind of a bummer, but I’m stil excited and overjoyed this time of year. You know why?

SpringOne 2022 is almost here! I feel like it’s that anxious, exciting time before sort of important holiday where you get given gifts! And with it, Spring Boot 3 and Spring Framework 6. We’re going to be announcing everything right here on the Spring blog, of course, but if you want a chance to learn from the source, then I hope you’ll join us 6-8 December, 2022, right here in my hometown of San Francisco, my favorite west coast city in the U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week In Review — September 26, 2022]]></title>
        <id>7ba7c22c89a95d2ced12a3220867b6146d0a2db5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-september-26-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T23:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like my travel schedule is coupled with this Week In Review series of blog posts. This week, I am traveling to Fort-de-France in the French Caribbean islands to meet our customers and partners. I enjoy the travel time when I am offline. It gives me the opportunity to reflect on the past or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrate to Azure Monitor Agent on Azure Arc using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/migrate-to-azure-monitor-agent-on-azure-arc-using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/migrate-to-azure-monitor-agent-on-azure-arc-using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Arc is becoming the default Microsoft Azure service for connecting non-Azure infrastructure into Azure monitoring and administration.  Azure has also issued a deprecation notice for the Azure Log Analytics Agents; Microsoft Monitoring Agent and Log Analytics (OMS).  Azure Monitor Agent replaces these agents, introducing a simplified, flexible method of configuring collection configuration called Data Collection Rules. To leverage Azure Monitor Agent with their non-Azure servers, customers will need to onboard their machines to Azure Arc-enabled servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Harwell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Support in Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/26/native-support-in-spring-boot-3-0-0-m5</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/26/native-support-in-spring-boot-3-0-0-m5"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spring Team has been working on native image support for Spring Applications for quite some time. After 3+ years of incubation in the Spring Native experimental project with Spring Boot 2, native support is moving to General Availability with Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3!

Native images provide almost instant startup time and reduced memory consumption for Java applications. The recent Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5 release marks the first time we’re asking for broader community feedback on our native story. If you need to catch-up on the basics, please refer to the Ahead Of Time basics blog post from late March. You can also learn how to prepare your applications for Spring Boot 3.0.

A lot has happened since March! We’ve improved compatibility with a larger number of use cases and li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: Kubernetes In-Tree to CSI Volume Migration Status Update]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/26/storage-in-tree-to-csi-migration-status-update-1.25/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/26/storage-in-tree-to-csi-migration-status-update-1.25/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jiawei Wang (Google)
The Kubernetes in-tree storage plugin to Container Storage Interface (CSI) migration infrastructure has already been beta since v1.17. CSI migration was introduced as alpha in Kubernetes v1.14.
Since then, SIG Storage and other Kubernetes special interest groups are working to ensure feature stability and compatibility in preparation for CSI Migration feature to go GA.
SIG Storage is excited to announce that the core CSI Migration feature is generally available in Kubernetes v1.25 release!
SIG Storage wrote a blog post in v1.23 for CSI Migration status update which discussed the CSI migration status for each storage driver. It has been a while and this article is intended to give a latest status update on each storage driver for their CSI Migration status in Ku…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Process Orchestration be the “Glue” for the API Economy?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=63178</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/09/process-orchestration-api-economy/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The API economy is taking off, propelled by an explosion of activity across API tools and platforms. According to a 2021 report from Postman, developers reported spending nearly half of their time working on APIs, and 94% of companies planned to increase their investments in APIs in 2022. API-first development is also gaining traction, with an impressive 67% of companies embracing this methodology. Companies like Twilio and Stripe emerged as early winners in this new economy, with the promise of many more to come.  APIs offer organizations an opportunity to tap into best-of-breed software components without having to spend precious time or development resources creating them from scratch. With that said, an often-overlooked aspect of the API economy is how...
The post Could Process Orchestration be the “Glue” for the API Economy? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My SpringOne 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/23/my-springone-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/23/my-springone-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has taken me an embarrassingly long time to appreciate and understand that the devil is in the details regarding software development. Writing happy-path business logic isn’t the hard part! It’s the failure cases, observability, resilience, and process. It’s security and other so-called non-functional requirements. It’s architecting for agility. It’s production. Spring is unique because it sits at the crossroads of many exciting application development discussions. 

Spring’s community contains multitudes and is one of the key defining features. This diversity of discussion means that any conference that endeavors to cover the full sweep of ideas has its work cut out. I don’t know of any other show - and I’ve spoken at many thousands of shows and events in my life! - that completely co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: CustomResourceDefinition Validation Rules Graduate to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/23/crd-validation-rules-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/23/crd-validation-rules-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Joe Betz (Google), Cici Huang (Google), Kermit Alexander (Google)
In Kubernetes 1.25, Validation rules for CustomResourceDefinitions (CRDs) have graduated to Beta!
Validation rules make it possible to declare how custom resources are validated using the Common Expression Language (CEL). For example:
apiVersion: apiextensions.k8s.io/v1
kind: CustomResourceDefinition
 ...
 openAPIV3Schema:
 type: object
 properties:
 spec:
 type: object
 x-kubernetes-validations:
 - rule: "self.minReplicas <= self.replicas && self.replicas <= self.maxReplicas"
 message: "replicas should be in the range minReplicas..maxReplicas."
 properties:
 replicas:
 type: integer
 ...


Validation rules support a wide range of use cases. To get a sense of some of the capabilities, let's look at a few examples:
V…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/spring-boot-3-0-0-m5-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/09/22/spring-boot-3-0-0-m5-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T22:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 3.0.0-M5 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/milestone.

This release includes 153 enhancements, documentation improvements, dependency upgrades, and bug fixes. Notable new features include:


  
Improved Ahead-of-Time (AOT) processing and native image support

  
Improved actuator endpoints sanitization

  
Jersey support re-instated


Please see the release notes for more details and upgrade instructions.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TensorStore for High-Performance, Scalable Array Storage]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/tensorstore-for-high-performance.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/tensorstore-for-high-performance.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T21:33:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeremy Maitin-Shepard and Laramie Leavitt, Software Engineers, Connectomics at Google
Many exciting contemporary applications of computer science and machine learning (ML) manipulate multidimensional datasets that span a single large coordinate system, for example, weather modeling from atmospheric measurements over a spatial grid or medical imaging predictions from multi-channel image intensity values in a 2d or 3d scan. In these settings, even a single dataset may require terabytes or petabytes of data storage. Such datasets are also challenging to work with as users may read and write data at irregular intervals and varying scales, and are often interested in performing analyses using numerous machines working in parallel.  
Today we are introducing TensorStore, an open-source…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View Synthesis with Transformers]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/view-synthesis-with-transformers.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/view-synthesis-with-transformers.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T19:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Carlos Esteves and Ameesh Makadia, Research Scientists, Google Research 
A long-standing problem in the intersection of computer vision and computer graphics, view synthesis is the task of creating new views of a scene from multiple pictures of that scene. This has received increased attention [1, 2, 3] since the introduction of neural radiance fields (NeRF). The problem is challenging because to accurately synthesize new views of a scene, a model needs to capture many types of information — its detailed 3D structure, materials, and illumination —  from a small set of reference images.  
In this post, we present recently published deep learning models for view synthesis. In “Light Field Neural Rendering” (LFNR), presented at CVPR 2022, we address the challenge of accurately repro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.3 Improves Extensibility and Maintainability of Terraform Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-3-improves-extensibility-and-maintainability-of-terraform-modules</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-3-improves-extensibility-and-maintainability-of-terraform-modules"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now generally available, HashiCorp Terraform 1.3 introduces optional object type attributes with defaults, and enhancements to moved blocks, improving extensibility and maintainability of Terraform modules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第216話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316112896867289136</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316112896867289136"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Event-Driven Automation Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/why-event-driven-matters</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/why-event-driven-matters"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life comes down to moments. These events are often how we define our achievements, successes, and failures throughout life. Just like our daily lives, IT organizations and teams can also have these defining moments, where you will often hear phrases like the "great database crash of '98." Many of these memorable IT  moments occur from limiting ourselves to a reactive approach when it comes to managing our IT assets. This is where event-driven automation can help us move from reactive to proactive IT management – well before we have the next great issue or moment in our IT teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: Use Secrets for Node-Driven Expansion of CSI Volumes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/21/kubernetes-1-25-use-secrets-while-expanding-csi-volumes-on-node-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/21/kubernetes-1-25-use-secrets-while-expanding-csi-volumes-on-node-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Humble Chirammal (Red Hat), Louis Koo (deeproute.ai)
Kubernetes v1.25, released earlier this month, introduced a new feature
that lets your cluster expand storage volumes, even when access to those
volumes requires a secret (for example: a credential for accessing a SAN fabric)
to perform node expand operation. This new behavior is in alpha and you
must enable a feature gate (CSINodeExpandSecret) to make use of it.
You must also be using CSI
storage; this change isn't relevant to storage drivers that are built in to Kubernetes.
To turn on this new, alpha feature, you enable the CSINodeExpandSecret feature
gate for the kube-apiserver and kubelet, which turns on a mechanism to send secretRef
configuration as part of NodeExpansion by the CSI drivers thus make use of
the same to perfor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FindIt: Generalized Object Localization with Natural Language Queries]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/findit-generalized-object-localization.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/findit-generalized-object-localization.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T17:00:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Weicheng Kuo and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team  
Natural language enables flexible descriptive queries about images. The interaction between text queries and images grounds linguistic meaning in the visual world, facilitating a better understanding of object relationships, human intentions towards objects, and interactions with the environment. The research community has studied object-level visual grounding through a range of tasks, including referring expression comprehension, text-based localization, and more broadly object detection, each of which require different skills in a model. For example, object detection seeks to find all objects from a predefined set of classes, which requires accurate localization and classification, while referr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy your Amazon EKS Clusters Locally on AWS Outposts]]></title>
        <id>44f16a5754d845987d5a9cddff8e927e1897ca2b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/deploy-your-amazon-eks-clusters-locally-on-aws-outposts/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T16:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce the availability of local clusters for Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) on AWS Outposts. It means that starting today, you can deploy your Amazon EKS cluster entirely on Outposts: both the Kubernetes control plane and the nodes. Amazon EKS is a managed Kubernetes service that makes it easy for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – September 19, 2022]]></title>
        <id>c87835feafb2eecd408bc548fd91e06e13509083</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-september-19-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T19:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are heating up in Seattle, with preparation for AWS re:Invent 2022 well underway. Later this month the entire News Blog team will participate in our now-legendary “speed storming” event. Over the course of three or four days, each of the AWS service teams with a launch in the works for re:Invent will give us […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vagrant 2.3 Introduces Go Runtime]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vagrant-2-3-introduces-go-runtime</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vagrant-2-3-introduces-go-runtime"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vagrant 2.3 introduces a new Vagrant executable written in Golang, tying the Vagrant architecture more closely into the broader HashiCorp ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How network engineers can get more sleep using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform: Your guide to AnsibleFest 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-network-engineers-can-get-more-sleep-using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-your-guide-to-ansiblefest-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-network-engineers-can-get-more-sleep-using-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-your-guide-to-ansiblefest-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since connectivity is critical to all types of business applications including cloud apps, managing and maintaining the network often falls into the overnight hours. This is great for the business, but it puts a large wrinkle in your work-life balance. Luckily, AnsibleFest is here to help you get more sleep!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cindy Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: Local Storage Capacity Isolation Reaches GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/19/local-storage-capacity-isolation-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/09/19/local-storage-capacity-isolation-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jing Xu (Google)
Local ephemeral storage capacity isolation was introduced as a alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.7 and it went beta in 1.9. With Kubernetes 1.25 we are excited to announce general availability(GA) of this feature.
Pods use ephemeral local storage for scratch space, caching, and logs. The lifetime of local ephemeral storage does not extend beyond the life of the individual pod. It is exposed to pods using the container’s writable layer, logs directory, and EmptyDir volumes. Before this feature was introduced, there were issues related to the lack of local storage accounting and isolation, such as Pods not knowing how much local storage is available and being unable to request guaranteed local storage. Local storage is a best-effort resource and pods can be evicted due t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at Interspeech 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/google-at-interspeech-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/google-at-interspeech-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T02:00:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cat Armato, Program Manager, Google 
This week, the 23rd Annual Conference of the International Speech Communication Association (INTERSPEECH 2022) is being held in Incheon, South Korea, representing one of the world’s most extensive conferences on research and technology of spoken language understanding and processing. Over 2,000 experts in speech-related research fields gather to take part in oral presentations and poster sessions and to collaborate with streamed events across the globe. 
We are excited to be a Diamond Sponsor of INTERSPEECH 2022, where we will be showcasing nearly 50 research publications and supporting a number of workshops, special sessions and tutorials. We welcome in-person attendees to drop by the Google booth to meet our researchers and participate in Q&…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust Online Allocation with Dual Mirror Descent]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/robust-online-allocation-with-dual.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/09/robust-online-allocation-with-dual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Santiago Balseiro, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research, and Associate Professor at Columbia University, and Vahab Mirrokni, Distinguished Scientist, Google Research 
The emergence of digital technologies has transformed decision making across commercial sectors such as airlines, online retailing, and internet advertising. Today, real-time decisions need to be repeatedly made in highly uncertain and rapidly changing environments. Moreover, organizations usually have limited resources, which need to be efficiently allocated across decisions. Such problems are referred to as online allocation problems with resource constraints, and applications abound. Some examples include: 
 
Bidding with Budget Constraints: Advertisers increasingly purchase ad slots using auction-based mark…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Drift Detection Helps Maintain a Secure Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-drift-detection-helps-maintain-a-secure-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-drift-detection-helps-maintain-a-secure-infrastructure"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drift detection is essential to maintaining efficiency while minimizing risk and giving teams confidence in your infrastructure as code (IaC) provisioning workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>