<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-05T01:14:01.716Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-05T01:14:01.716Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Quality-of-Service for Memory Resources (alpha)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/05/qos-memory-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/05/qos-memory-resources/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Dixita Narang (Google)
Kubernetes v1.27, released in April 2023, introduced changes to
Memory QoS (alpha) to improve memory management capabilites in Linux nodes.
Support for Memory QoS was initially added in Kubernetes v1.22, and later some
limitations
around the formula for calculating memory.high were identified. These limitations are
addressed in Kubernetes v1.27.
Background
Kubernetes allows you to optionally specify how much of each resources a container needs
in the Pod specification. The most common resources to specify are CPU and Memory.
For example, a Pod manifest that defines container resource requirements could look like:
apiVersion: v1
kind: Pod
metadata:
name: example
spec:
containers:
- name: nginx
resources:
requests:
memory: "64Mi"
cpu: "250m"
limits:
memory: "6…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MaMMUT: A simple vision-encoder text-decoder architecture for multimodal tasks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/mammut-simple-vision-encoder-text.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/mammut-simple-vision-encoder-text.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T21:59:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by AJ Piergiovanni and Anelia Angelova, Research Scientists, Google Research




Vision-language foundational models are built on the premise of a single pre-training followed by subsequent adaptation to multiple downstream tasks. Two main and disjoint training scenarios are popular: a CLIP-style contrastive learning and next-token prediction. Contrastive learning trains the model to predict if image-text pairs correctly match, effectively building visual and text representations for the corresponding image and text inputs, whereas next-token prediction predicts the most likely next text token in a sequence, thus learning to generate text, according to the required task. Contrastive learning enables image-text and text-image retrieval tasks, such as finding the image that best match…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating Critical Traffic At Scale with No Downtime — Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ba1c7a1c7835</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/migrating-critical-traffic-at-scale-with-no-downtime-part-1-ba1c7a1c7835?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T21:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shyam Gala, Javier Fernandez-Ivern, Anup Rokkam Pratap, Devang Shah]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage your application security stack effectively with the tool status page]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-04-manage-your-application-security-stack-effectively-with-the-tool-status-page/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-04-manage-your-application-security-stack-effectively-with-the-tool-status-page/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T18:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning’s tool status gives you a bird's eye view of your application security stack, allowing you to quickly confirm everything is working, or troubleshoot any tool in your application security arsenal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All In for Students 2023 cohort: our biggest group of open source leaders yet!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-04-all-in-for-students-2023-cohort-our-biggest-group-of-open-source-leaders-yet/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-04-all-in-for-students-2023-cohort-our-biggest-group-of-open-source-leaders-yet/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T17:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second cohort of All In for Students has graduated! With a cohort 12 times as large as the pilot, learn about how this group of college students is leaning into the future of technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The price of salt]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45916</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/738657068/0/sethsblog~The-price-of-salt/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salt is essentially free. A bag of salted nuts is the same price (or less) as an unsalted one. But salt used to be expensive. Truly expensive, like gold. We keep seeing the deflation of things we were sure would remain expensive. Computer chips, disk storage and now, content. Once computers start illustrating, writing and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Java Champion Ken Kousen on Gradle, Java, Kotlin, Mockito, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/04/a-bootiful-podcast-java-champion-ken-koussen-on-gradle-java-kotlin-mockito</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/04/a-bootiful-podcast-java-champion-ken-koussen-on-gradle-java-kotlin-mockito"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial control systems security with Elastic Security and Zeek]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/industrial-control-systems-elastic-security-zeek</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/industrial-control-systems-elastic-security-zeek"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog walks through the security challenges associated with ICS and how Elastic Security and Zeek can help address them, in addition to the benefits of having integrated machine learning and threat intelligence within the ICS security program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdelwahhab Satta, Octodet,Samir Bennacer, Octodet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Elasticsearch and Time Series Data Streams for observability metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-time-series-data-streams-observability-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-time-series-data-streams-observability-metrics"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Time Series Data Streams (TSDS), Elasticsearch introduces optimized storage for metrics time series. Check out how we use it for Elastic Observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Ruflin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial control systems security with Elastic Security and Zeek]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/industrial-control-systems-elastic-security-zeek</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/industrial-control-systems-elastic-security-zeek"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Industrial control systems (ICS) have historically been isolated and less interconnected. Isolation was one of the things that kept these systems more secure behind air gaps, at the cost of lost coordination and collaboration. This is rapidly changing with the rise of Industry 4.0 with increased interconnectivity and integration of smart technologies like Industrial IoT (IIoT) and cloud computing in modern industrial processes.

This blog walks through the security challenges associated with ICS and how Elastic Security and Zeek can help address them, in addition to the benefits of having integrated machine learning and threat intelligence within the ICS security program.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt1e29f607dfe021f0/6453c12670a4470c7a8b2282/blog-elastic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdelwahhab Satta, Octodet,Samir Bennacer, Octodet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Elasticsearch and Time Series Data Streams for observability metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-time-series-data-streams-observability-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticsearch-time-series-data-streams-observability-metrics"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elasticsearch is used for a wide variety of data types — one of these is metrics. With the introduction of Metricbeat many years ago and later our APM Agents, the metric use case has become more popular. Over the years, Elasticsearch has made many improvements on how to handle things like metrics aggregations and sparse documents. At the same time, TSVB visualizations were introduced to make visualizing metrics easier. One concept that was missing that exists for most other metric solutions is the concept of time series with dimensions. 

Mid 2021, the Elasticsearch team embarked on making Elasticsearch a much better fit for metrics. The team created Time Series Data Streams (TSDS), which were released in 8.7 as generally available (GA). 

This blog post dives into how TSDS works and how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Ruflin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: StatefulSet PVC Auto-Deletion (beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/04/kubernetes-1-27-statefulset-pvc-auto-deletion-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/04/kubernetes-1-27-statefulset-pvc-auto-deletion-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Matthew Cary (Google)
Kubernetes v1.27 graduated to beta a new policy mechanism for
StatefulSets that controls the lifetime of
their PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs). The new PVC
retention policy lets users specify if the PVCs generated from the StatefulSet spec template should
be automatically deleted or retrained when the StatefulSet is deleted or replicas in the StatefulSet
are scaled down.
What problem does this solve?
A StatefulSet spec can include Pod and PVC templates. When a replica is first created, the
Kubernetes control plane creates a PVC for that replica if one does not already exist. The behavior
before the PVC retention policy was that the control plane never cleaned up the PVCs created for
StatefulSets - this was left up to the cluster administrator, or to some add-on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: April 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-03-github-availability-report-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-03-github-availability-report-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April, we experienced four incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. This report also sheds light into three March incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Bob’s Used Books—a New, Real-World, .NET Sample Application]]></title>
        <id>1c00c599af66e56a57ee408b24db5dd4f41dfeec</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-bobs-used-books-a-new-real-world-net-sample-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T20:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to announce that a new open-source sample application, a fictitious used books eCommerce store we call Bob’s Used Books, is available for .NET developers working with AWS. The .NET advocacy and development teams at AWS talk to customers regularly and, during those conversations, often receive requests for more in-depth samples. Customers tell […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Set Up Your AWS Notifications in One Place]]></title>
        <id>01ea65c02e7f25c9e84ec4d664b25ae3dc22c87a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-set-up-your-aws-notifications-in-one-place/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T17:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are launching AWS User Notifications, a single place in the AWS console to set up and view AWS notifications across multiple AWS accounts, Regions, and services. You can centrally set up and view notifications from over 100 AWS services, such as Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) objects events, Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IndoorSim-to-OutdoorReal: Learning to navigate outdoors without any outdoor experience]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/indoorsim-to-outdoorreal-learning-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/05/indoorsim-to-outdoorreal-learning-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Joanne Truong, Student Researcher, and Wenhao Yu, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google





Teaching mobile robots to navigate in complex outdoor environments is critical to real-world applications, such as delivery or search and rescue. However, this is also a challenging problem as the robot needs to perceive its surroundings, and then explore to identify feasible paths towards the goal. Another common challenge is that the robot needs to overcome uneven terrains, such as stairs, curbs, or rockbed on a trail, while avoiding obstacles and pedestrians. In our prior work, we investigated the second challenge by teaching a quadruped robot to tackle challenging uneven obstacles and various outdoor terrains. 



In “IndoorSim-to-OutdoorReal: Learning to Navigate Outdoors without an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More than meets the pull request: maintainers talk contributions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-03-more-than-meets-the-pull-request-maintainers-talk-contributions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-03-more-than-meets-the-pull-request-maintainers-talk-contributions/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T16:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an open source project can feel a bit like sending out an open invite to a party—will it be a roaring good time, or will you unbegrudginly dine on leftover junk food for the following week after nobody shows? When the first guest arrives, you breathe a sigh of relief. The party’s a success, [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging the gap between technology and FinOps with HashiCorp and Intel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/bridging-the-gap-between-technology-and-finops-with-hashicorp-and-intel</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/bridging-the-gap-between-technology-and-finops-with-hashicorp-and-intel"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Cloud Optimized Modules for Terraform and Sentinel standardize infrastructure deployment and increase performance with purpose-built policy as code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take Ansible validated content to the next level with Event-Driven Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-with-event-driven-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-with-event-driven-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing has become an essential factor in IT transformation and business innovation. The highly dynamic nature of cloud environments, where new resources are constantly being added and removed, poses new challenges. One of the main challenges organizations face is the lack of visibility into the cloud environment. As cloud computing continues to grow in complexity, it can be challenging to keep track of all the different resources and applications that make up the infrastructure. This lack of visibility can make it difficult to maintain security policies and configurations, making the infrastructure vulnerable to attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing Elastic to robotics developers: Integrating with ROS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-elastic-to-robotics-developers-integrating-with-ros</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-elastic-to-robotics-developers-integrating-with-ros"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Salgado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing Elastic to robotics developers: Integrating with ROS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-elastic-to-robotics-developers-integrating-with-ros</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/bringing-elastic-to-robotics-developers-integrating-with-ros"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The robotics industry has experienced significant growth in recent years, with the global robotics market size expected to reach US$230 billion by 2025. This growth is largely driven by the increasing adoption of automation and robotics in various industries, including manufacturing, healthcare, logistics, and more. The integration of automation and robotics with Industry 4.0 technologies has brought new challenges, including the management and analysis of large amounts of data generated by connected devices and sensors, which is estimated to generate around 4.4 zettabytes of data per year.

The Robot Operating System (ROS) is an open-source framework that provides a standardized way of developing robotic applications. ROS has become an essential component of the robotics industry, as it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Salgado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第229話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361192645271</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361192645271"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2023.2 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=348546</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/05/03/rider-2023-2-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T12:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we prepare for the start of the Early Access Program (EAP) for Rider 2023.2, now seems like the perfect time to share our plans for this upcoming release. Keep in mind that these plans are subject to change, and some features and improvements may need to be postponed to a future release. Also, be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2023.2 Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=348432</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/05/03/resharper-2023-2-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T12:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The upcoming Early Access Program (EAP) for ReSharper version 2023.2 is fast approaching, and we want to share the development roadmap we’ve set for the next release. Before we get into it, this roadmap is tentative and subject to change based on our priorities, available resources, and developments in the .NET sphere. Some features may […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – May 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=347022</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/05/java-annotated-monthly-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T12:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The May edition of Java Annotated Monthly is here! This issue comes with exciting news on the future Java release, including a sneak peek at the JEPs planned for implementation. Our hand-picked selection of Java tutorials will help you sharpen your skills and stay on top of the latest trends. In addition, we have curated […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Maryasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Bachelor’s Program With Neapolis University Paphos]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=347959</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/05/03/introducing-the-computer-science-and-artificial-intelligence-bachelor-s-program-with-neapolis-university-paphos/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T11:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Together with Neapolis University Pafos (NUP), our partner university in Cyprus, we are announcing the launch of the Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence bachelor’s program. NUP is a leading private university in Cyprus that was established in 2010. It reflects our core values, particularly in providing high-quality higher education, generating innovative applied knowledge, and serving […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Kulikov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The house painter and the architect]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45928</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/738459503/0/sethsblog~The-house-painter-and-the-architect/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T08:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t design a book until after it’s written. Or cast the movie until the screenplay is complete. The house painter has an important job, but it makes no sense to plan for the painting before the house is designed. This makes a lot of sense because some parts of a project have high variability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing an observability solution for public cloud and on-prem implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-public-cloud-on-prem-implementation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-public-cloud-on-prem-implementation"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the different components architects should consider when designing an observability solution for public cloud and on-premise implementations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calizo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing an observability solution for public cloud and on-prem implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-public-cloud-on-prem-implementation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-public-cloud-on-prem-implementation"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In my previous article, I talked about the importance of how a unified observability approach can augment the security posture of an organization. 
In this article, I’ll discuss the different components architects should consider when designing an observability solution for public cloud and on-premise implementations. 
Having a sound observability solution on both cloud and on-prem is essential. This is especially true due to the rise of microservices architecture adoption, which makes visibility, traceability, and correlation of different components a necessity to be at the forefront of what is happening in your environment via almost real-time insights.
These recommendations are based on many considerations and a number of factors to ensure that the solution provides effective monitori…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calizo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[College Knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2771/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2771/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/college_knowledge.png" title="'Your chitin armor is no match for our iron-tipped stingers! Better go hide in your jars!' --common playground taunt" alt="'Your chitin armor is no match for our iron-tipped stingers! Better go hide in your jars!' --common playground taunt" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot relieves alert fatigue from npm devDependencies]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-05-02-dependabot-relieves-alert-fatigue-from-npm-devdependencies/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-05-02-dependabot-relieves-alert-fatigue-from-npm-devdependencies/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T20:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new alert rules engine for Dependabot leverages alert metadata to identify and auto-dismiss up to 15% of alerts as false positives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Annotated Monthly | May 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=347873</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/05/02/net-annotated-monthly-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T14:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know? There is a difference between compilation and transpilation. The short explanation is that compilers use code from one language to produce output, usually binary. Transpilers are a type of compiler that produce source code but at the same level of abstraction, so the output is usually more source code. .NET news Featured […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet Preview Update 1.18 Is Out! With Prettier on Save, .NET Unit Testing, In-Tree Test Rerun, Safe Quitting, Updated Debug Console, Git Integration Improvements, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=fleet&amp;p=345225</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/fleet/2023/05/fleet-preview-update-1-18-is-out-with-prettier-on-save-net-unit-testing-in-tree-test-rerun-safe-quitting-updated-debug-console-git-integration-improvements-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T14:09:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the release of Fleet 1.18. This update brings numerous new features and improvements to the product. Keep reading to get a brief overview of the major changes in this release: For those with more than one target framework in a project, we’ve added a new selector that allows you to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Prokashev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Datalore Enterprise 2023.2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datalore&amp;p=343749</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datalore/2023/05/02/introducing-datalore-enterprise-2023-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T13:08:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Datalore Enterprise 2023.2 is out! This version brings native R package support for R users, and elevates your collaborative data science experience with notebook content search, environment variable management, and usability improvements for the Report builder.  Upgrade to the newest version and read on to discover what’s new in Datalore Enterprise 2023.2! Upgrade to 2023.2 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alena Guzharina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MPS 2022.3 Is Finally Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=mps&amp;p=347335</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/mps/2023/05/mps-2022-3-is-finally-here/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T12:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This version was supposed to be released last year, but we had to delay the release date because of some technical issues. MPS is built on top of the IntelliJ IDEA platform, so every release cycle, we have to migrate to the new version of the platform. Sometimes the migration is straightforward, other times not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oscar Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2023.1.1 is released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=347176</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2023/05/phpstorm-2023-1-1-is-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T08:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first bug-fix update for PhpStorm 2023.1 is now available. You can update to it using the Toolbox App or right from inside the IDE. You can also download PhpStorm 2023.1.1 from the website. Notable changes in this update: The full list of changes is available in the release notes. And as always, please feel […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Pronskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The list of compromises]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/738237575/0/sethsblog~The-list-of-compromises/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the no-compromise solutions have failed. If there was a way to solve our problem without giving something up, we would have done that already. So, if a persistent problem is important, the question is not: Should we compromise or not? The question is: Which changes are we going to make first?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: HorizontalPodAutoscaler ContainerResource type metric moves to beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/02/hpa-container-resource-metric/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/05/02/hpa-container-resource-metric/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Kensei Nakada (Mercari)
Kubernetes 1.20 introduced the ContainerResource type metric
in HorizontalPodAutoscaler (HPA).
In Kubernetes 1.27, this feature moves to beta and the corresponding feature gate (HPAContainerMetrics) gets enabled by default.
What is the ContainerResource type metric
The ContainerResource type metric allows us to configure the autoscaling based on resource usage of individual containers.
In the following example, the HPA controller scales the target
so that the average utilization of the cpu in the application container of all the pods is around 60%.
(See the algorithm details
to know how the desired replica number is calculated exactly)
type: ContainerResource
containerResource:
 name: cpu
 container: application
 target:
 type: Utilization
 averageUtilizatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Spring Cloud AWS 3.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/announcing-spring-cloud-aws-3-0-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/announcing-spring-cloud-aws-3-0-0"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Gibb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 0.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/spring-modulith-0-6-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/spring-modulith-0-6-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - May 2, 20223]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/this-week-in-spring-may-2-20223</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/05/02/this-week-in-spring-may-2-20223"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.7.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-7-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-7-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.7.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.7.1 over 8.7.0 and 8.6.x releases.
The 8.7.1 patch release contains fixes for potential security vulnerabilities. Please see our security advisory for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arpad Kiraly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.10 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-10-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-10-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.17.10 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.10 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrés Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.7.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-7-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-7-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arpad Kiraly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.10 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-10-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-10-released"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrés Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Review – AWS Verified Access, Java 17, Amplify Flutter, Conferences, and More – May 1, 2023]]></title>
        <id>ae3f62fcbec27e6f57598f0de24b8a0e4fcfbe7e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/week-in-review-aws-verified-access-java-17-amplify-flutter-conferences-and-more-may-1-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T22:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conference season has started and I was happy to meet and talk with iOS and Swift developers at the New York Swifty conference last week. I will travel again to Turino (Italy), Amsterdam (Netherlands), Frankfurt (Germany), and London (UK) in the coming weeks. Feel free to stop by and say hi if you are around. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Winning Process Orchestration Plays for Financial Services]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80223&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80223</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/05/process-orchestration-plays-financial-services/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To improve a business, improve its processes. But how? Here are some proven process orchestration patterns to follow for financial services. 
The post Four Winning Process Orchestration Plays for Financial Services appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason English</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 221]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66868</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-221/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our team remains dedicated to improving New Boards Hub by addressing any issues that may arise. We’re happy to report that the New Boards Hub has been steadily progressing with each sprint. Although it is not quite ready for general availability yet,
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 221 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you should run your platform team like a product team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/why-you-should-run-your-platform-team-like-a-product-team</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/why-you-should-run-your-platform-team-like-a-product-team"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like a product team, a successful platform team must understand the needs of its "customers" and stakeholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On to the next thing]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44372</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/738073769/0/sethsblog~On-to-the-next-thing/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T07:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vitally important, rarely taught, easily messed up. In order to go onto the next thing, which we all do (unless you’re still wearing pajamas with feet and taking ballet lessons), we need to walk away from the last thing. Wrap it up, learn from it, leave it in good hands. And we also need to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ICLR 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-iclr-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-iclr-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T06:37:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Catherine Armato, Program Manager, Google




The Eleventh International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR 2023) is being held this week as a hybrid event in Kigali, Rwanda. We are proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of ICLR 2023, a premier conference on deep learning, where Google researchers contribute at all levels. This year we are presenting over 100 papers and are actively involved in organizing and hosting a number of different events, including workshops and interactive sessions.

 

If you’re registered for ICLR 2023, we hope you’ll visit the Google booth to learn more about the exciting work we’re doing across topics spanning representation and reinforcement learning, theory and optimization, social impact, safety and privacy, and applications from generative AI to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet ElastAsians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Employee resource groups, or Elastician resource groups as we call them, are groups within Elastic that are aligned with shared identities, experiences, interests, affinities, and allyships.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logging for public sector: How to make the most of your mission-critical data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/logging-public-sector-mission-critical-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/logging-public-sector-mission-critical-data"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Log management is growing more complex and expensive, which is why it’s important for agencies to leverage logs for multiple purposes, such as for both cybersecurity and observability. Learn five tips for maximizing your logging data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Cox,Nathan Stacey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet ElastAsians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Employee resource groups, or Elastician resource groups as we call them, are groups within Elastic that are aligned with shared identities, experiences, and allyships. 

These groups were formalized in 2021, but they’ve been a part of Elastic’s culture since 2016. By formalizing them, we ensure they all have a structure, budget, and voice. This was an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy. 

Each ERG has their own mission and goals, but as a whole they create community and belonging around shared interests and experiences. 
Our Core ERGs
We have seven formal ERGs: The Accessibles, Blasticians, ElastAsians, Elasticians Unidos, Rainbow Stack, Mil-Asticians, and Women of Elastic. We’ll be spotlighting them over the next year as they relate to culture or comm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logging for public sector: How to make the most of your mission-critical data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/logging-public-sector-mission-critical-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/logging-public-sector-mission-critical-data"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
With governments doubling down on logging compliance, many public sector organizations have been focusing on optimizing their log management, especially to ensure they retain logs for required periods of time. 

Logs — though seemingly straightforward — are the backbone of many mission-based use cases and therefore have the potential to accelerate mission success when centrally organized and leveraged strategically. In public sector, logs are instrumental in:

Giving early warnings of mission-critical issues
Pinpointing what went wrong
Accelerating problem resolution based on mission priority
Complying with logging regulations such as M-21-31 in the US

But log management is growing exponentially more complex and expensive, which is why it’s important for agencies to leverage logs for mu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Cox,Nathan Stacey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tapetum Lucidum]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2770/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2770/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/tapetum_lucidum.png" title="Using a reflective wall in a game to give one shot two chances to hit is called a double-tapetum lucidum." alt="Using a reflective wall in a game to give one shot two chances to hit is called a double-tapetum lucidum." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An end to pop]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45897</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/737928578/0/sethsblog~An-end-to-pop/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pop culture depends on scarcity. When there are only a few TV stations or a dozen radio stations, it’s likely that many of us watch or hear the same thing at the same time. And so a popular TV show or song from fifty years ago probably reached twenty times as many people as a […]
Click the icon below to listen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.1.1 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=347010</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/04/2023-1-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T09:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With this build, we’ve introduced some highly requested bug fixes related to the debugger and remote interpreters. We also added support for PyScript’s new approach to application configuration. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the new version, but you can also manually download it from our website. Download PyCharm 2023.1.1 PyScript: code […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We probably can’t buy our way out of it]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45666</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/737784575/0/sethsblog~We-probably-cant-buy-our-way-out-of-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s what we usually try to do. When technology, comfort, convenience, efficiency and price line up, the market takes care of itself. On the other hand, seatbelts would never have happened if they weren’t required. But pizza grew to dominate our diets with no centralized action. They sell a lot of Tide laundry detergent. Billions […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Athena Provisioned Capacity]]></title>
        <id>17b4867be4eb5a35b07009ae78749bcc1c401801</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-athena-provisioned-capacity/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T19:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we launch the ability to provision capacity to run your Athena queries. Athena is a query service that makes it simple to analyze data in Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) data lakes and 30 different data sources, including on-premises data sources or other cloud systems, using standard SQL queries. Athena is serverless, so […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This month on The ReadME Podcast: exploring the fusion of technology and progress]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-28-this-month-on-the-readme-podcast-exploring-the-fusion-of-technology-and-progress/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-28-this-month-on-the-readme-podcast-exploring-the-fusion-of-technology-and-progress/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T16:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open source’s impact on nuclear fusion research, adapting to technological change, and mastering GitHub essentials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.1.2 Bug-Fix Update: Fix for Docker, CMake, Debugger, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=346989</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/04/clion-2023-1-2-bug-fix-update-fix-for-docker-cmake-debugger-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T15:29:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We hope you’ve already tried the new enhancements in the CLion 2023.1 release, like disassemble on demand, vcpkg integration, and the experimental Clangd-based indexer. We’re starting to plan the 2023.2 version now, and you can already check out the preliminary roadmap. CLion 2023.2 is planned as a quality-focused release, but in the meantime, we’re continuing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.1.1 Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=346559</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/04/webstorm-2023-1-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T14:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.1.1, the first bug-fix update for WebStorm 2023.1, is now available! It’s packed with improvements including a better New Vue Component action, various bug fixes for Angular, Astro, Tailwind CSS, and more. You can update to v2023.1.1 by using the Toolbox App, installing it right from the IDE, or downloading it from our website. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The magic of placebos]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43486</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/737641028/0/sethsblog~The-magic-of-placebos/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of two things is true: A placebo is a force beyond understanding, one that is capable of disappearing when we do the appropriate double-blind tests and has mechanisms that defy our knowledge of the laws of physics. Or… A placebo is a prompt for our subconscious to do the hard work of healing our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.7 (aka Jubilee) has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/28/spring-cloud-2021-0-7-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/28/spring-cloud-2021-0-7-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Maciaszek-Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Root cause analysis with logs: Elastic Observability's AIOps Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-logs-machine-learning-aiops</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-logs-machine-learning-aiops"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability provides more than just log aggregation, metrics analysis, APM, and distributed tracing. Elastic’s machine learning-based AIOps capabilities will help you analyze the root cause of issues allowing you to focus your time on the most important tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The power of effective log management in software development and operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-management-observability-operations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-management-observability-operations"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improve your development and operations processes with effective log management strategies. Our blog offers insights into the importance of log management, best practices, and tools for managing logs efficiently. From identifying errors to troubleshooting issues, learn how to leverage log management for enhanced performance and streamlined operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Wintergerst,David Hope,Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Root cause analysis with logs: Elastic Observability's AIOps Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-logs-machine-learning-aiops</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/observability-logs-machine-learning-aiops"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In the previous blog in our root cause analysis with logs series, we explored how to analyze logs in Elastic Observability with Elastic’s anomaly detection and log categorization capabilities. Elastic’s platform enables you to get started on machine learning (ML) quickly. You don’t need to have a data science team or design a system architecture. Additionally, there’s no need to move data to a third-party framework for model training. 

Preconfigured machine learning models for observability and security are available. If those don't work well enough on your data, in-tool wizards guide you through the few steps needed to configure custom anomaly detection and train your model with supervised learning. To get you started, there are several key features built into Elastic Observability to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The power of effective log management in software development and operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-management-observability-operations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/log-management-observability-operations"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The rapid software development process that exists today requires an expanding and complex infrastructure and application components, and the job of operations and development teams is ever growing and multifaceted. Observability, which helps manage and analyze telemetry data, is the key to ensuring the performance and reliability of your applications and infrastructure. In particular, logs are the main default signal developers enable, providing a significant amount of detail for debugging, performance analysis, security, and compliance management. So how do you define a strategy to get the most out of your logs?

In this blog post, we'll explore:

The logging journey, which reviews the collection, processing and enrichment, and analysis and rationalization of logs
The difference betwee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Wintergerst,David Hope,Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overlapping Circles]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2769/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2769/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/overlapping_circles.png" title="&quot;The Venn diagram of the sun and the moon is a circle.&quot; --someone being snarky at totality" alt="&quot;The Venn diagram of the sun and the moon is a circle.&quot; --someone being snarky at totality" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: StatefulSet Start Ordinal Simplifies Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/28/statefulset-start-ordinal/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/28/statefulset-start-ordinal/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Peter Schuurman (Google)
Kubernetes v1.26 introduced a new, alpha-level feature for
StatefulSets that controls
the ordinal numbering of Pod replicas. As of Kubernetes v1.27, this feature is
now beta. Ordinals can start from arbitrary
non-negative numbers. This blog post will discuss how this feature can be
used.
Background
StatefulSets ordinals provide sequential identities for pod replicas. When using
OrderedReady Pod management
Pods are created from ordinal index 0 up to N-1.
With Kubernetes today, orchestrating a StatefulSet migration across clusters is
challenging. Backup and restore solutions exist, but these require the
application to be scaled down to zero replicas prior to migration. In today's
fully connected world, even planned application downtime may not allow you to
me…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Alerting with Atlas Streaming Eval]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e691c60dc61e</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/improved-alerting-with-atlas-streaming-eval-e691c60dc61e?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ruchir Jha, Brian Harrington, Yingwu Zhao]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An ML-based approach to better characterize lung diseases]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/an-ml-based-approach-to-better.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/an-ml-based-approach-to-better.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:24:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Babak Behsaz, Software Engineer, and Andrew Carroll, Product Lead, Genomics




The combination of the environment an individual experiences and their genetic predispositions determines the majority of their risk for various diseases. Large national efforts, such as the UK Biobank, have created large, public resources to better understand the links between environment, genetics, and disease. This has the potential to help individuals better understand how to stay healthy, clinicians to treat illnesses, and scientists to develop new medicines.


One challenge in this process is how we make sense of the vast amount of clinical measurements — the UK Biobank has many petabytes of imaging, metabolic tests, and medical records spanning 500,000 individuals. To best use this data, we nee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CyberGRX cut ML processing time from 8 days to 56 minutes with AWS Step Functions Distributed Map]]></title>
        <id>6ca49d44c0bb9aa0d343f5673699f5a7fe73ca58</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-cybercrx-cut-ml-processing-time-from-8-days-to-56-minutes-with-aws-step-functions-distributed-map/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T19:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last December, Sébastien Stormacq wrote about the availability of a distributed map state for AWS Step Functions, a new feature that allows you to orchestrate large-scale parallel workloads in the cloud. That’s when Charles Burton, a data systems engineer for a company called CyberGRX, found out about it and refactored his workflow, reducing the processing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The braid out of balance]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45682</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/737491748/0/sethsblog~The-braid-out-of-balance/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are three strands, present for most everyone: Power (sometimes seen as status, or the appearance of status) Safety (survival and peace of mind) Meaning (hope and the path forward) The changes in our media structure, public health and economy have pushed some people to overdo one or the other and perhaps ignore a third. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Sebastien Deleuze and James Ward on a Bootiful Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/27/a-bootiful-podcast-sebastien-deleuze-and-james-ward-on-a-bootiful-podcast</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/27/a-bootiful-podcast-sebastien-deleuze-and-james-ward-on-a-bootiful-podcast"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robust and efficient medical imaging with self-supervision]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robust-and-efficient-medical-imaging.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robust-and-efficient-medical-imaging.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T20:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shekoofeh Azizi, Senior Research Scientist, and Laura Culp, Senior Research Engineer, Google Research
  
  
  
Despite recent progress in the field of medical artificial intelligence (AI), most existing models are narrow, single-task systems that require large quantities of labeled data to train. Moreover, these models cannot be easily reused in new clinical contexts as they often require the collection, de-identification and annotation of site-specific data for every new deployment environment, which is both laborious and expensive. This problem of data-efficient generalization (a model’s ability to generalize to new settings using minimal new data) continues to be a key translational challenge for medical machine learning (ML) models and has in turn, prevented their broad uptak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLI tricks every developer should know]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-26-cli-tricks-every-developer-should-know/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-26-cli-tricks-every-developer-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T16:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn some tips, tricks, and tools for mastering the command line from GitHub’s own developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud no-code provisioning is now GA with new features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-no-code-provisioning-is-now-ga-with-new-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-no-code-provisioning-is-now-ga-with-new-features"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No-code provisioning is now GA for Terraform Cloud Business, providing validated self-service infrastructure, additional security through more granular permissions, and ease of use with variable options as dropdowns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to call the Camunda Inbound Webhook from Postman]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=79381&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=79381</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/how-to-call-camunda-inbound-webhook-postman/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to create processes using the Camunda Webhook Connector and to start them via Postman both in unauthenticated and authenticated modes.
The post How to call the Camunda Inbound Webhook from Postman appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Pappas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explaining it to a kid]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42391</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/737344031/0/sethsblog~Explaining-it-to-a-kid/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It can be difficult. Explaining atoms or molecules, or decision making, or what you do at your job… The reason that it’s difficult is that in order to explain something, we need to really understand it first. Not simply be able to do the task or ace the test. But understand. And the reason we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Definition of e]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2768/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2768/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/definition_of_e.png" title="Yeah, my math teacher back in high school set up the system to try to teach us something or other, but the 100% rate was unbelievably good, so I engineered a hostile takeover of his bank and now use it to make extra cash on the side." alt="Yeah, my math teacher back in high school set up the system to try to teach us something or other, but the 100% rate was unbelievably good, so I engineered a hostile takeover of his bank and now use it to make extra cash on the side." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LayerNAS: Neural architecture search in polynomial complexity]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/layernas-neural-architecture-search-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/layernas-neural-architecture-search-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T17:20:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yicheng Fan and Dana Alon, Software Engineers, Google Research




Every byte and every operation matters when trying to build a faster model, especially if the model is to run on-device. Neural architecture search (NAS) algorithms design sophisticated model architectures by searching through a larger model-space than what is possible manually. Different NAS algorithms, such as MNasNet and TuNAS, have been proposed and have discovered several efficient model architectures, including MobileNetV3, EfficientNet. 

 


Here we present LayerNAS, an approach that reformulates the multi-objective NAS problem within the framework of combinatorial optimization to greatly reduce the complexity, which results in an order of magnitude reduction in the number of model candidates that must be …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git security vulnerabilities announced]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-25-git-security-vulnerabilities-announced-4/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-25-git-security-vulnerabilities-announced-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T17:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new set of Git releases were published to address a variety of security vulnerabilities. All users are encouraged to upgrade. Take a look at GitHub’s view of the latest round of releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gearing up for Maintainer Month this May!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-25-gearing-up-for-maintainer-month-this-may/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-25-gearing-up-for-maintainer-month-this-may/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T16:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for ways to support open source maintainers? Maintainer Month is the perfect opportunity!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sentinel and control groups now available in HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/sentinel-and-control-groups-now-available-in-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/sentinel-and-control-groups-now-available-in-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Plus Clusters add support for Sentinel policies and control groups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaping the GitHub of the future as COO]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-25-shaping-the-github-of-the-future-as-coo/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-25-shaping-the-github-of-the-future-as-coo/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T14:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub is driving the future of software development and, after 10 years as a Hubber, I’m more energized than ever as I take on the role of COO to help bring our vision to life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unwritten rules get written]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44328</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/737149847/0/sethsblog~The-unwritten-rules-get-written/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T08:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[…when someone decides to selfishly push. There’s an assumption of civility and fairness in all of our interactions. When a harsh competitor unilaterally breaks unwritten rules (because it’s “not technically against the rules”) the community then writes down a new rule. The best way for a market to be a free market is for the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security Kerberos 2.0.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/27/spring-security-kerberos-2-0-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/27/spring-security-kerberos-2-0-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 25th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/25/this-week-in-spring-april-25th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/25/this-week-in-spring-april-25th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Updates to the Auto-refreshing Official CVE Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/25/k8s-cve-feed-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/25/k8s-cve-feed-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Cailyn Edwards (Shopify), Mahé Tardy (Isovalent), Pushkar Joglekar
Since launching the Auto-refreshing Official CVE feed as an alpha
feature in the 1.25 release, we have made significant improvements and updates. We are excited to announce the release of the
beta version of the feed. This blog post will outline the feedback received, the changes made, and talk about how you can help
as we prepare to make this a stable feature in a future Kubernetes Release.
Feedback from end-users
SIG Security received some feedback from end-users:
The JSON CVE Feed did not comply
with the JSON Feed specification as its name would suggest.
The feed could also support RSS
in addition to JSON Feed format.
Some metadata could be added to indicate the freshness of
the feed overall, or specific CVEs. A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 24, 2023: Amazon CodeCatalyst, Amazon S3 on Snowball Edge, and More…]]></title>
        <id>f99637a00ba132ddbd2ab3f3ddf491e8cdcc7989</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-24-2023-amazon-codecatalyst-amazon-s3-on-snowball-edge-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T21:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As always, there’s plenty to share this week: Amazon CodeCatalyst is now generally available, Amazon S3 is now available on Snowball Edge devices, version 1.0.0 of AWS Amplify Flutter is here, and a lot more. Let’s dive in! Last Week’s Launches Here are some of the launches that caught my eye this past week: Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Power Automate to update Azure DevOps queries]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66806</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/use-power-automate-to-update-azure-devops-queries/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T21:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I’ll explain how to set up automation to automatically update Azure DevOps (ADO) queries. Using an automated Power Automate flow, you save time by not having to manually update your queries for each sprint. Everyone using your queries benefits by having data and details that are always current and accurate.
The post Use Power Automate to update Azure DevOps queries appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Reitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choose Korean in AWS Support as Your Preferred Language]]></title>
        <id>3fd49d6f464a65c650e1d14d5e7d7c56e29331bc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/choose-korean-in-aws-support-as-your-preferred-language/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T20:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the general availability of AWS Support in Korean as your preferred language, in addition to English, Japanese, and Chinese. As the number of customers speaking Korean grows, AWS Support is invested in providing the best support experience possible. You can now communicate with AWS Support engineers and agents in Korean when you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud adds Vault-backed dynamic credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-vault-backed-dynamic-credentials</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-vault-backed-dynamic-credentials"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic provider credentials in HashiCorp Terraform Cloud now supports Vault dynamic secrets engines to consolidate cloud access for Terraform runs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at CHI 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-chi-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/google-at-chi-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T02:26:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Malaya Jules, Program Manager, Google




This week, the Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI 2023) is being held in Hamburg, Germany. We are proud to be a Hero Sponsor of CHI 2023, a premier conference on human-computer interaction, where Google researchers contribute at all levels. This year we are presenting over 30 papers and are actively involved in organizing and hosting a number of different events across workshops, courses, and interactive sessions.


 


If you’re registered for CHI 2023, we hope you’ll visit the Google booth to learn more about the exciting work across various topics, including language interactions, causal inference, question answering and more. Take a look below to learn more about the Google research being presented at CHI 2023 (Goog…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Server Side Field Validation and OpenAPI V3 move to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/24/openapi-v3-field-validation-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/24/openapi-v3-field-validation-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jeffrey Ying (Google), Antoine Pelisse (Google)
Before Kubernetes v1.8 (!), typos, mis-indentations or minor errors in
YAMLs could have catastrophic consequences (e.g. a typo like
forgetting the trailing s in replica: 1000 could cause an outage,
because the value would be ignored and missing, forcing a reset of
replicas back to 1). This was solved back then by fetching the OpenAPI
v2 in kubectl and using it to verify that fields were correct and
present before applying. Unfortunately, at that time, Custom Resource
Definitions didn’t exist, and the code was written under that
assumption. When CRDs were later introduced, the lack of flexibility
in the validation code forced some hard decisions in the way CRDs
exposed their schema, leaving us in a cycle of bad validation causing
bad O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.0-RC1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/22/spring-boot-3-1-0-rc1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/22/spring-boot-3-1-0-rc1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Webb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Blocks for ML: Accelerating machine learning prototyping with interactive tools]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/visual-blocks-for-ml-accelerating.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/visual-blocks-for-ml-accelerating.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T19:01:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ruofei Du, Interactive Perception & Graphics Lead, Google Augmented Reality, and Na Li, Tech Lead Manager, Google CoreML

  


Recent deep learning advances have enabled a plethora of high-performance, real-time multimedia applications based on machine learning (ML), such as human body segmentation for video and teleconferencing, depth estimation for 3D reconstruction, hand and body tracking for interaction, and audio processing for remote communication.



However, developing and iterating on these ML-based multimedia prototypes can be challenging and costly. It usually involves a cross-functional team of ML practitioners who fine-tune the models, evaluate robustness, characterize strengths and weaknesses, inspect performance in the end-use context, and develop the applications.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Query Node Logs Using The Kubelet API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/21/node-log-query-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/21/node-log-query-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aravindh Puthiyaparambil (Red Hat)
Kubernetes 1.27 introduced a new feature called Node log query that allows
viewing logs of services running on the node.
What problem does it solve?
Cluster administrators face issues when debugging malfunctioning services
running on the node. They usually have to SSH or RDP into the node to view the
logs of the service to debug the issue. The Node log query feature helps with
this scenario by allowing the cluster administrator to view the logs using
kubectl. This is especially useful with Windows nodes where you run into the
issue of the node going to the ready state but containers not coming up due to
CNI misconfigurations and other issues that are not easily identifiable by
looking at the Pod status.
How does it work?
The kubelet already has a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep long-horizon forecasting]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/recent-advances-in-deep-long-horizon.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/recent-advances-in-deep-long-horizon.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T20:26:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rajat Sen and Abhimanyu Das, Research Scientists, Google Research




Time-series forecasting is an important research area that is critical to several scientific and industrial applications, like retail supply chain optimization, energy and traffic prediction, and weather forecasting. In retail use cases, for example, it has been observed that improving demand forecasting accuracy can meaningfully reduce inventory costs and increase revenue. 
 

Modern time-series applications can involve forecasting hundreds of thousands of correlated time-series (e.g., demands of different products for a retailer) over long horizons (e.g., a quarter or year away at daily granularity). As such, time-series forecasting models need to satisfy the following key criterias:



Ability to handle auxi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 Compatible Storage on AWS Snowball Edge Compute Optimized Devices Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>3a5f9a4909fe852e7ed6cc8ac314d50e62bf28b1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-compatible-storage-on-aws-snowball-edge-compute-optimized-devices-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T18:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have added a collection of purpose-built services to the AWS Snow Family for customers, such as Snowball Edge in 2016 and Snowcone in 2020. These services run compute intensive workloads and stores data in edge locations with denied, disrupted, intermittent, or limited network connectivity and for transferring large amounts of data from on-premises and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Human Approach to Process Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78911&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78911</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/human-approach-process-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chances of success are significantly higher when you put humans in the center of your orchestration projects.
The post A Human Approach to Process Automation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Gradle Developer Advocate, Java Champion, and legend Trisha Gee]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/20/a-bootiful-podcast-gradle-developer-advocate-java-champion-and-legend-trisha</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/20/a-bootiful-podcast-gradle-developer-advocate-java-champion-and-legend-trisha"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Single Pod Access Mode for PersistentVolumes Graduates to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/20/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/20/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chris Henzie (Google)
With the release of Kubernetes v1.27 the ReadWriteOncePod feature has graduated
to beta. In this blog post, we'll take a closer look at this feature, what it
does, and how it has evolved in the beta release.
What is ReadWriteOncePod?
ReadWriteOncePod is a new access mode for
PersistentVolumes (PVs)
and PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs)
introduced in Kubernetes v1.22. This access mode enables you to restrict volume
access to a single pod in the cluster, ensuring that only one pod can write to
the volume at a time. This can be particularly useful for stateful workloads
that require single-writer access to storage.
For more context on access modes and how ReadWriteOncePod works read
What are access modes and why are they important?
in the Introducing Single Pod Acces…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Building without Limits at AWS Developer Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>5642e5e26f54b4e2d613344cf7fb6a8727367ef7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/discover-building-without-limits-at-aws-developer-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T18:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We hope you can join us on Wednesday, April 26, for a free-to-attend online event, AWS Developer Innovation Day. AWS will stream the event simultaneously across multiple platforms, including LinkedIn Live, Twitter, YouTube, and Twitch. Developer Innovation Day is a brand-new event designed specifically for developers and development teams. In the event, sessions throughout the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Technology, AI, Society and Culture]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T18:12:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lauren Wilcox, Senior Staff Research Scientist, on behalf of the Technology, AI, Society, and Culture Team




Google sees AI as a foundational and transformational technology, with recent advances in generative AI technologies, such as LaMDA, PaLM, Imagen, Parti, MusicLM, and similar machine learning (ML) models, some of which are now being incorporated into our products. This transformative potential requires us to be responsible not only in how we advance our technology, but also in how we envision which technologies to build, and how we assess the social impact AI and ML-enabled technologies have on the world. This endeavor necessitates fundamental and applied research with an interdisciplinary lens that engages with — and accounts for — the social, cultural, economic, and ot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第228話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361158146336</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361158146336"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differentially private heatmaps]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/differentially-private-heatmaps.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/differentially-private-heatmaps.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T20:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Badih Ghazi, Staff Research Scientist, and Nachiappan Valliappan, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research






Recently, differential privacy (DP) has emerged as a mathematically robust notion of user privacy for data aggregation and machine learning (ML), with practical deployments including the 2022 US Census and in industry. Over the last few years, we have open-sourced libraries for privacy-preserving analytics and ML and have been constantly enhancing their capabilities. Meanwhile, new algorithms have been developed by the research community for several analytic tasks involving private aggregation of data. 
 

One such important data aggregation method is the heatmap. Heatmaps are popular for visualizing aggregated data in two or more dimensions. They are widely used in ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Efficient SELinux volume relabeling (Beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/18/kubernetes-1-27-efficient-selinux-relabeling-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/18/kubernetes-1-27-efficient-selinux-relabeling-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jan Šafránek (Red Hat)
The problem
On Linux with Security-Enhanced Linux (SELinux) enabled, it's traditionally
the container runtime that applies SELinux labels to a Pod and all its volumes.
Kubernetes only passes the SELinux label from a Pod's securityContext fields
to the container runtime.
The container runtime then recursively changes SELinux label on all files that
are visible to the Pod's containers. This can be time-consuming if there are
many files on the volume, especially when the volume is on a remote filesystem.
Note
subPath of a volume, only that subPath of the whole
volume is relabeled. This allows two pods that have two different SELinux labels
to use the same volume, as long as they use different subpaths of it.

If a Pod does not have any SELinux label assigned in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s happening at KubeCon Europe 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-s-happening-at-kubecon-europe-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-s-happening-at-kubecon-europe-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attending KubeCon EU, either in person or online? Check out what HashiCorp is doing and talking about at the event, and learn about recent Kubernetes-related product features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.16 improves automatic HCL conversion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-16-improves-automatic-hcl-conversion</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-16-improves-automatic-hcl-conversion"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform v0.16 improves automatic conversion of configuration code from HCL to supported languages by enabling type coercion and providing better support for iterators and functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate External Systems Effortlessly with Custom Connectors in Camunda Platform – No Java Coding Required!]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78910&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78910</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/create-custom-template-based-on-rest-connector/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, learn how to create a new custom Connector for Camunda Platform in just a few simple steps and start orchestrating faster.
The post Integrate External Systems Effortlessly with Custom Connectors in Camunda Platform – No Java Coding Required! appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bastian Koerber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review: New Service for Generative AI and Amazon EC2 Trn1n, Inf2, and CodeWhisperer now GA – April 17, 2023]]></title>
        <id>1276fde47550c891c0d47e730e2a5344912bf074</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-new-service-for-generative-ai-and-amazon-ec2-trn1n-inf2-and-codewhisperer-now-ga-april-17-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T19:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I could almost title this blog post the “AWS AI/ML Week in Review.” This past week, we announced several new innovations and tools for building with generative AI on AWS. Let’s dive right into it. Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my attention during the previous week: Announcing Amazon Bedrock and Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: More fine-grained pod topology spread policies reached beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/17/fine-grained-pod-topology-spread-features-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/17/fine-grained-pod-topology-spread-features-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Alex Wang (Shopee), Kante Yin (DaoCloud), Kensei Nakada (Mercari)
In Kubernetes v1.19, Pod topology spread constraints
went to general availability (GA).
As time passed, we - SIG Scheduling - received feedback from users,
and, as a result, we're actively working on improving the Topology Spread feature via three KEPs.
All of these features have reached beta in Kubernetes v1.27 and are enabled by default.
This blog post introduces each feature and the use case behind each of them.
KEP-3022: min domains in Pod Topology Spread
Pod Topology Spread has the maxSkew parameter to define the degree to which Pods may be unevenly distributed.
But, there wasn't a way to control the number of domains over which we should spread.
Some users want to force spreading Pods over a minimum number of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond automatic differentiation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/beyond-automatic-differentiation.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/beyond-automatic-differentiation.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Matthew Streeter, Software Engineer, Google Research




Derivatives play a central role in optimization and machine learning. By locally approximating a training loss, derivatives guide an optimizer toward lower values of the loss. Automatic differentiation frameworks such as TensorFlow, PyTorch, and JAX are an essential part of modern machine learning, making it feasible to use gradient-based optimizers to train very complex models.


 


But are derivatives all we need? By themselves, derivatives only tell us how a function behaves on an infinitesimal scale. To use derivatives effectively, we often need to know more than that. For example, to choose a learning rate for gradient descent, we need to know something about how the loss function behaves over a small but finite windo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 220]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66772</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-220/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sprint 220 was again dedicated to fixing bugs. We continue to drive down that bug backlog as quickly as we can.
Issue
Date and time shift between New Boards and old
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 220 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robotic deep RL at scale: Sorting waste and recyclables with a fleet of robots]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robotic-deep-rl-at-scale-sorting-waste.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robotic-deep-rl-at-scale-sorting-waste.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T19:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sergey Levine, Research Scientist, and Alexander Herzog, Staff Research Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team
  
  
Reinforcement learning (RL) can enable robots to learn complex behaviors through trial-and-error interaction, getting better and better over time. Several of our prior works explored how RL can enable intricate robotic skills, such as robotic grasping, multi-task learning, and even playing table tennis. Although robotic RL has come a long way, we still don't see RL-enabled robots in everyday settings. The real world is complex, diverse, and changes over time, presenting a major challenge for robotic systems. However, we believe that RL should offer us an excellent tool for tackling precisely these challenges: by continually practicing, getting better, and l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a secure Azure reference architecture with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-a-secure-azure-reference-architecture-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-a-secure-azure-reference-architecture-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use HashiCorp Terraform to deploy Azure resources using security best practices and policy as code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Service Connection guidance for AKS customers using Kubernetes tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66692</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/service-connection-guidance-for-aks-customers-using-kubernetes-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T13:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes tasks & Service Connections
AzureFunctionOnKubernetes
These tasks can be configured to target a Kubernetes cluster in a number of ways, using the connectionType property:
Connection Type
Azure Resource Manager
The post Service Connection guidance for AKS customers using Kubernetes tasks appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline Your Ansible Module Development with Content Builder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/streamline-your-ansible-module-development-with-content-builder</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/streamline-your-ansible-module-development-with-content-builder"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo byHush Naidoo Jade Photography onUnsplash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gomathi Selvi Srinivasan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 Inf2 Instances for Low-Cost, High-Performance Generative AI Inference are Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>eb18bd7117541f6c4b0788702c73681882dd3cc4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-inf2-instances-for-low-cost-high-performance-generative-ai-inference-are-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T12:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Innovations in deep learning (DL), especially the rapid growth of large language models (LLMs), have taken the industry by storm. DL models have grown from millions to billions of parameters and are demonstrating exciting new capabilities. They are fueling new applications such as generative AI or advanced research in healthcare and life sciences. AWS has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeWhisperer, Free for Individual Use, is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>449ba7d8898cd00282a5d25974f238fd40f0b703</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-codewhisperer-free-for-individual-use-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T12:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon CodeWhisperer, a real-time AI coding companion, is generally available and also includes a CodeWhisperer Individual tier that’s free to use for all developers. Originally launched in preview last year, CodeWhisperer keeps developers in the zone and productive, helping them write code quickly and securely and without needing to break their flow by leaving […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the SQL Connector to Streamline Trade Ops Processes]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78093&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78093</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/using-sql-connector-streamline-trade-ops-processes/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are new Connectors available for SQL databases. Here's how you can get them and a quick example of how you could use them today in financial services.
The post Using the SQL Connector to Streamline Trade Ops Processes appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UniPi: Learning universal policies via text-guided video generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/unipi-learning-universal-policies-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/unipi-learning-universal-policies-via.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sherry Yang, Research Scientist, and Yilun Du, Student Researcher, Google Research, Brain Team
Building models that solve a diverse set of tasks has become a dominant paradigm in the domains of vision and language. In natural language processing, large pre-trained models, such as PaLM, GPT-3 and Gopher, have demonstrated remarkable zero-shot learning of new language tasks. Similarly, in computer vision, models like CLIP and Flamingo have shown robust performance on zero-shot classification and object recognition. A natural next step is to use such tools to construct agents that can complete different decision-making tasks across many environments.



However, training such agents faces the inherent challenge of environmental diversity, since different environments operate with di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BGP Management with Ansible Validated Content using the network.bgp collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/bgp-management-with-ansible-validated-content-using-the-network.bgp-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/bgp-management-with-ansible-validated-content-using-the-network.bgp-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AnsibleFest 2022, we announced a new addition to the content ecosystem offered through the platform which is Ansible validated content. Ansible validated content is use cases-focused automation content that is packaged as Collections that contain Ansible plugins, roles and playbooks that you can use as an automation job through Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps 2023 Q2 Roadmap update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66701</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-2023-q2-roadmap-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T22:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday we published an updated list of features we plan to deliver in Q2. Each title includes a link where you can find details about each feature. We expect that this will help bring visibility into the key investments for the upcoming quarter.
The post Azure DevOps 2023 Q2 Roadmap update  appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing an aging clock using deep learning on retinal images]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/developing-aging-clock-using-deep.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/developing-aging-clock-using-deep.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:22:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Ahadi, Research Fellow, Applied Science, and Andrew Carroll, Product Lead, Genomics




Aging is a process that is characterized by physiological and molecular changes that increase an individual's risk of developing diseases and eventually dying. Being able to measure and estimate the biological signatures of aging can help researchers identify preventive measures to reduce disease risk and impact. Researchers have developed “aging clocks” based on markers such as blood proteins or DNA methylation to measure individuals’ biological age, which is distinct from one’s chronological age. These aging clocks help predict the risk of age-related diseases. But because protein and methylation markers require a blood draw, non-invasive ways to find similar measures could make aging i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66647</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/announcing-azure-devops-server-2022-0-1-rc/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T17:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are releasing Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC. This is a go-live release, meaning it is supported on production instances, and you will be able to upgrade to our final release.
The post Announcing Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Vault integration via Sidecar Agent Injector vs. Vault Secrets Operator vs. CSI provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-vault-integration-via-sidecar-agent-injector-vs-csi-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-vault-integration-via-sidecar-agent-injector-vs-csi-provider"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A detailed comparison of three HashiCorp-supported methods for HashiCorp Vault and Kubernetes integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.10 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78394&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78394</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/camunda-modeler-5-10/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T15:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the latest version of Camunda Desktop Modeler, including FEEL templating, a visual grid for diagrams and more. 
The post Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.10 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beatriz Mendes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8.2: The Key to Scaling Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78377&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78377</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/camunda-platform-8-2-key-to-scaling-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T13:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8.2 brings a suite of features that improve the process development lifecycle and helps you further scale automation. Read the latest.
The post Camunda Platform 8.2: The Key to Scaling Automation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.27: Chill Vibes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/11/kubernetes-v1-27-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/11/kubernetes-v1-27-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes v1.27 Release Team
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.27, the first release of 2023!
This release consist of 60 enhancements. 18 of those enhancements are entering Alpha, 29 are graduating to Beta, and 13 are graduating to Stable.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes v1.27: Chill Vibes
The theme for Kubernetes v1.27 is Chill Vibes.
It's a little silly, but there were some important shifts in this release that helped inspire the theme. Throughout a typical Kubernetes release cycle, there are several deadlines that features need to meet to remain included. If a feature misses any of these deadlines, there is an exception process they can go through. Handling these exceptions is a very normal part of the release. But v1.27 is the first release that anyone can remember wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Review: Terraform in Service Catalog, AWS Supply Chain, Streaming Response in Lambda, and Amplify Library for Swift – April 10, 2023]]></title>
        <id>a3c18e35b5c3d5c56d33482fd39b1c582a776641</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/week-in-review-terraform-in-service-catalog-aws-supply-chain-streaming-response-in-lambda-and-amplify-library-for-swift-april-10-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T21:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Summit season has started. AWS Summits are free technical and business conferences happening in large cities across the planet. This week, we were happy to welcome our customers and partners in Sydney and Paris. In France, 9,973 customers and partners joined us for the day to meet and exchange ideas but also to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Consul’s transparent proxy on virtual machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-consul-s-transparent-proxy-on-virtual-machines</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-consul-s-transparent-proxy-on-virtual-machines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure Consul’s transparent proxy on virtual machines to find and connect to services in the service mesh with DNS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards ML-enabled cleaning robots]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/towards-ml-enabled-cleaning-robots.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/towards-ml-enabled-cleaning-robots.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T21:06:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Thomas Lew, Research Intern, and Montserrat Gonzalez Arenas, Research Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team


Over the past several years, the capabilities of robotic systems have improved dramatically. As the technology continues to improve and robotic agents are more routinely deployed in real-world environments, their capacity to assist in day-to-day activities will take on increasing importance. Repetitive tasks like wiping surfaces, folding clothes, and cleaning a room seem well-suited for robots, but remain challenging for robotic systems designed for structured environments like factories. Performing these types of tasks in more complex environments, like offices or homes, requires dealing with greater levels of environmental variability captured by high-dimensional sensor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Directing ML toward natural hazard mitigation through collaboration]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/directing-ml-toward-natural-hazard.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/directing-ml-toward-natural-hazard.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T16:09:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Oren Gilon, Software Engineer, and Grey Nearing, Research Scientist, Google Research




Floods are the most common type of natural disaster, affecting more than 250 million people globally each year. As part of Google's Crisis Response and our efforts to address the climate crisis, we are using machine learning (ML) models for Flood Forecasting to alert people in areas that are impacted before disaster strikes.


Collaboration between researchers in the industry and academia is essential for accelerating progress towards mutual goals in ML-related research. Indeed, Google's current ML-based flood forecasting approach was developed in collaboration with researchers (1, 2) at the Johannes Kepler University in Vienna, Austria, the University of Alabama, and the Hebrew University of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Project Starline improves remote communication]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/how-project-starline-improves-remote.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/how-project-starline-improves-remote.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T19:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Greg Blascovich and Eric Gomez, User Researchers, Google




As companies settle into a new normal of hybrid and distributed work, remote communication technology remains critical for connecting and collaborating with colleagues. While this technology has improved, the core user experience often falls short: conversation can feel stilted, attention can be difficult to maintain, and usage can be fatiguing. 





Project Starline renders people at natural scale on a 3D display and enables natural eye contact.

Project Starline, a technology project that combines advances in hardware and software to create a remote communication experience that feels like you’re together, even when you’re thousands of miles apart. This perception of co-presence is created by representing users in 3D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-trained Gaussian processes for Bayesian optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/pre-trained-gaussian-processes-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/pre-trained-gaussian-processes-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T17:02:00.009Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zi Wang and Kevin Swersky, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 





Bayesian optimization (BayesOpt) is a powerful tool widely used for global optimization tasks, such as hyperparameter tuning, protein engineering, synthetic chemistry, robot learning, and even baking cookies. BayesOpt is a great strategy for these problems because they all involve optimizing black-box functions that are expensive to evaluate. A black-box function’s underlying mapping from inputs (configurations of the thing we want to optimize) to outputs (a measure of performance) is unknown. However, we can attempt to understand its internal workings by evaluating the function for different combinations of inputs. Because each evaluation can be computationally expensive, we need to find the best i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding free and open Elastic APM as part of your Elastic Observability deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post, we showed you how to get started with the free and open tier of Elastic Observability. Below, we'll walk through what you need to do to expand your deployment so you can start gathering metrics from application performance monitoring (APM) or "tracing" data in your observability cluster, for free.
What is APM?
Application performance monitoring lets you see where your applications spend their time, what they are doing, what other applications or services they are calling, and what errors or exceptions they are encountering.

In addition, APM also lets you see history and trends for key performance indicators, such as latency and throughput, as well as transaction and dependency information:

Whether you're setting up alerts for SLA breaches, trying to gauge the impact of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding free and open Elastic APM as part of your Elastic Observability deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to gather application trace data and store it alongside the logs and metrics from your applications and infrastructure with Elastic Observability and Elastic APM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Keeping Kubernetes Secure with Updated Go Versions]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/06/keeping-kubernetes-secure-with-updated-go-versions/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/06/keeping-kubernetes-secure-with-updated-go-versions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jordan Liggitt (Google)
The problem
Since v1.19 (released in 2020), the Kubernetes project provides 12-14 months of patch releases for each minor version.
This enables users to qualify and adopt Kubernetes versions in an annual upgrade cycle and receive security fixes for a year.
The Go project releases new minor versions twice a year,
and provides security fixes for the last two minor versions, resulting in about a year of support for each Go version.
Even though each new Kubernetes minor version is built with a supported Go version when it is first released,
that Go version falls out of support before the Kubernetes minor version does,
and the lengthened Kubernetes patch support since v1.19 only widened that gap.
At the time this was written, just over half of all Go patch releas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul Service (HCS) on Azure End of Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-consul-service-hcs-on-azure-end-of-life</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-consul-service-hcs-on-azure-end-of-life"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCS on Azure has been deprecated. HCP Consul on Azure is the preferred way to run your HashiCorp Consul clusters on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new Terraform Associate 003 Certification exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-new-terraform-associate-003-certification-exam</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-new-terraform-associate-003-certification-exam"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HashiCorp’s updated Terraform Associate certification impacts your current and future Terraform Associate credentials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>