<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-02-04T01:25:32.890Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-02-04T01:25:32.890Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real-time tracking of wildfire boundaries using satellite imagery]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/real-time-tracking-of-wildfire.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/real-time-tracking-of-wildfire.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T18:05:00.012Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zvika Ben-Haim and Omer Nevo, Software Engineers, Google Research   
   As global temperatures rise, wildfires around the world are becoming more frequent and more dangerous. Their effects are felt by many communities as people evacuate their homes or suffer harm even from proximity to the fire and smoke.  

As part of Google’s mission to help people access trusted information in critical moments, we use satellite imagery and machine learning (ML) to track wildfires and inform affected communities. Our wildfire tracker was recently expanded. It provides updated fire boundary information every 10–15 minutes, is more accurate than similar satellite products, and improves on our previous work. These boundaries are shown for large fires in the continental US, Mexico, and most of Cana…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Adds OpenID Connect (OIDC) Single Sign-On Functionality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-adds-openid-connect-oidc-single-sign-on-functionality</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-adds-openid-connect-oidc-single-sign-on-functionality"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how users of the HashiCorp Cloud Platform (HCP) can now leverage the popular OpenID Connect (OIDC) protocol for their single sign-on (SSO) integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 EAP 3: New UI Enhancements, Docker Improvements, and Kubernetes Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=318189</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/02/intellij-idea-2023-1-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T16:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1 Early Access Program is ongoing and the third build is now available! You can get the latest build from our website, through the free Toolbox App, or as a snap if you use Ubuntu.  To learn about the previously added features from the past two weeks, check out the blog posts […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customers using Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 6 should upgrade the OS on Self-hosted agents]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66368</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/customers-using-red-hat-enterprise-linux-rhel-6-should-upgrade-the-os-on-self-hosted-agents/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T15:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RHEL 6 & .NET Core 3.1
The post Customers using Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 6 should upgrade the OS on Self-hosted agents appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reproducible Kotlin Compiler Artifacts]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=320372</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/02/reproducible-kotlin-compiler-artifacts/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Kotlin team, security is always a priority. Being an open-source programming language inherently provides Kotlin with significant security guarantees and protection against potentially malicious code being added to our codebase. However, just being open source does not ensure that we are completely invulnerable to determined attackers who want to inject their malware. There […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikolay Krasko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ 2023.1 EAP: Call Tracking and C++23 Features]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rscpp&amp;p=320262</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rscpp/2023/02/03/resharper-cpp-2023-1-eap3-call-tracking/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T15:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Early Access build is here with the Incoming Calls hierarchy and support for the first set of C++23 features! Read on for more details and check out the full list of issues we’ve fixed in this update. You can download the EAP builds from our website or via the Toolbox App. DOWNLOAD RESHARPER […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elvira Mustafina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2023.1 EAP 3 is Available With Docker and Structure View Improvements and a Localization Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=320823</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/02/03/rider-2023-1-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T15:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third EAP build is available for download!  Let’s go over this build’s feature highlights:  Structure view Rider 2023.1 EAP 3 comes packed with improvements and fixes for code navigation. Rider now shows inherited members in the Structure view toolwindow, and we’ve restored Rider’s ability to display the class members of decompiled code in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2023.1 EAP 3 Is Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=320825</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/02/03/resharper-2023-1-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T14:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can download the latest ReSharper 2023.1 Early Access Program build from our website. Let’s take a look at what’s inside.  CSS support switched off by default With little demand for CSS in ReSharper, we found it increasingly hard to prioritize keeping up with the latest versions of the language. We therefore decided to put […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity 2022.10.2 Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=319460</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/02/teamcity-2022-10-2-is-here/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T14:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new bug-fix update, TeamCity 2022.10.2, is live and ready for download. This version addresses about 50 issues and contains several security and performance fixes, minor additions, and tweaks. With this version, you’ll take advantage of improved TeamCity HTTPS settings, AWS support, and Perforce integration. See our release notes for the full list of fixes. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Alexandrova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.1 EAP #3: Astro Support, New UI Enhancements, and Docker Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=320271</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/02/webstorm-2023-1-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T13:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re continuing to work on WebStorm 2023.1 with our third EAP build. To catch up on all of the new features WebStorm 2023.1 will bring, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP builds and keep both your stable and EAP versions up to date. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s chance to be a leader in the age of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-03-europes-chance-to-be-a-leader-in-the-age-of-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-03-europes-chance-to-be-a-leader-in-the-age-of-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T13:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Below are my prepared remarks delivered at the EU Open Source Policy Summit in Brussels on Feb 3rd.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compact Mode for the New UI, Better Performance With Windows Defender, and Docker and Kubernetes Updates in GoLand 2023.1 EAP #3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=320535</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2023/02/03/compact-mode-for-the-new-ui-better-performance-with-windows-defender-and-docker-and-kubernetes-updates-in-goland-2023-1-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T10:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third GoLand 2023.1 EAP build is now available!  You can get it via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package (for Ubuntu), or from inside GoLand, select Check IDE updates for: Early Access Program in Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System Settings | Updates. Download GoLand 2023.1 EAP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar – Aaron Stannard – .NET Systems Programming Learned the Hard Way]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=315104</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/02/03/webinar-aaron-stannard-dotnet-systems-programming-learned-the-hard-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T10:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us Thursday, February 23, 2023, 3:00 – 4:00 UTC (check other timezones) for our free live webinar, .NET Systems Programming Learned the Hard Way, with CEO and Petabridge founder Aaron Stannard. Register now and get a reminder, or join on YouTube What is a thread quantum, and why is it different on Windows Desktop […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confusion about performance]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42703</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726270131/0/sethsblog~Confusion-about-performance/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T09:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thing that your product or service delivers could be called performance, and it’s made of two components: –The story and expectations and cultural impact of what you do (the story). –The deliverables that are objectively measured (the spec). It helps to have both. Many hard-working freelancers are confused about their story. Either they insist […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Annotated Monthly – February 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=320011</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/02/java-annotated-monthly-february-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T05:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month – new stories! The February edition of Java Annotated Monthly is here, featuring industry news and trends, helpful tutorials, and step-by-step screencasts. This JAM offers several interesting forecasts about Java and other technologies for the upcoming year. Finally, the Culture and Community section includes a detailed, by-the-numbers analysis of 2023.  Let’s see what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Maryasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An ever green, ever great way to learn Spring]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/03/an-ever-green-ever-great-way-to-learn-spring</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/03/an-ever-green-ever-great-way-to-learn-spring"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 State of Spring Survey Report]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/03/the-state-of-spring-survey-2022-report</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/03/the-state-of-spring-survey-2022-report"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Instrumentation]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/02/03/sig-instrumentation-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/02/03/sig-instrumentation-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Imran Noor Mohamed (Delivery Hero)
Observability requires the right data at the right time for the right consumer (human or piece of software) to make the right decision. In the context of Kubernetes, having best practices for cluster observability across all Kubernetes components is crucial.
SIG Instrumentation helps to address this issue by providing best practices and tools that all other SIGs use to instrument Kubernetes components-like the API server, scheduler, kubelet and kube-controller-manager.
In this SIG Instrumentation spotlight, Imran Noor Mohamed, SIG ContribEx-Comms tech lead talked with Elana Hashman, and Han Kang, chairs of SIG Instrumentation, on how the SIG is organized, what are the current challenges and how anyone can get involved and contribute.
About SIG Ins…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research, 2022 & beyond: ML & computer systems]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/google-research-2022-beyond-ml-computer.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/google-research-2022-beyond-ml-computer.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T21:13:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Phitchaya Mangpo Phothilimthana, Staff Research Scientist, and Adam Paszke, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research    
    

(This is Part 3 in our series of posts covering different topical areas of research at Google. You can find other posts in the series here.)
   
  Great machine learning (ML) research requires great systems. With the increasing sophistication of the algorithms and hardware in use today and with the scale at which they run, the complexity of the software necessary to carry out day-to-day tasks only increases. In this post, we provide an overview of the numerous advances made across Google this past year in systems for ML that enable us to support the serving and training of complex models while easing the complexity of implementation for end users. This b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.1: EAP 2 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=320532</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/02/2023-1-eap-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T21:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second EAP build, we’re offering in-editor improvements and additions to TypeScript support. You can check out the previous EAP posts to see what else we’ve implemented in PyCharm 2023.1. You can download the new EAP build from our website, get it from the free Toolbox App, or update by using snaps if you’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the GitHub Docs team uses GitHub Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-02-how-the-github-docs-team-uses-github-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-02-how-the-github-docs-team-uses-github-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T19:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how the GitHub Docs team uses GitHub Projects for content coordination, reviews, and publishing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling branch deployments through IssueOps with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-02-enabling-branch-deployments-through-issueops-with-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-02-enabling-branch-deployments-through-issueops-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T18:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if developers want to leverage branch deployments but don't have a full ChatOps stack integrated with their repositories? We wanted to set out to find a way for all developers to be able to take advantage of branch deployments with ease, right from their GitHub repository, and so the branch-deploy Action was born!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Vizier: Towards reliable and flexible hyperparameter and blackbox optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/open-source-vizier-towards-reliable-and.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/open-source-vizier-towards-reliable-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T17:56:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xingyou (Richard) Song, Research Scientist, and Chansoo Lee, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team  
Google Vizier is the de-facto system for blackbox optimization over objective functions and hyperparameters across Google, having serviced some of Google’s largest research efforts and optimized a wide range of products (e.g., Search, Ads, YouTube). For research, it has not only reduced language model latency for users, designed computer architectures, accelerated hardware, assisted protein discovery, and enhanced robotics, but also provided a reliable backend interface for users to search for neural architectures and evolve reinforcement learning algorithms. To operate at the scale of optimizing thousands of users’ critical systems and tuning millions of machine learning…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Automation Platform Moving Towards Smarter Inventory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-moving-towards-smarter-inventory</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-moving-towards-smarter-inventory"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR What is this?
 
It has been a long term ask and our desire to make Smart Inventory, well, smarter. We’ve listened to feedback, and are now addressing not only direct customer asks but also presenting solutions to make it better overall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Profiling Go Code with GoLand]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=316519</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2023/02/02/profiling-go-code-with-goland/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T11:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was written by an external contributor. Modern software stacks contain many moving pieces. With each piece potentially relying on a different set of dependencies, it can be difficult to identify bottlenecks in your application’s performance. Profiling can provide insights into how the application is running and where improvements can be made. Profiling applications […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagining cities in a few simple questions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44832</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726170180/0/sethsblog~Reimagining-cities-in-a-few-simple-questions/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T09:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What would happen if public transportation were free? What if it were paid for by congestion pricing, digitally implemented? What if public toilets were safe, beautiful, well-appointed and consistently maintained? What if there were a tax on empty storefronts, payable after three months of vacancy? Shortly after the invention of the car, society made many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Moderne founder Jon Schneider on OpenRewrite, modernizing code bases en masse, freedom and responsibility, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/02/a-bootiful-podcast-moderne-founder-jon-schneider-on-openrewrite-modernizing</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/02/a-bootiful-podcast-moderne-founder-jon-schneider-on-openrewrite-modernizing"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Lateral Movement activity: A new Kibana integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-lateral-movement-activity-a-new-kibana-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-lateral-movement-activity-a-new-kibana-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber attacks are becoming more frequent, targeted, and complex. When it comes to sophisticated attacks, one of the most commonly seen tactics is Lateral Movement. During lateral movement, many attackers try impersonating a legitimate user by abusing admin tools (e.g., SMB, SAMBA, FTP, WMI, WinRM, and PowerShell Remoting) to move laterally from system to system in search of sensitive information. In addition, they may avoid using traditional malware to stay beneath the security radar, making detection more difficult.
This publication will discuss the newly available Lateral Movement Detection package under Kibana’s integrations app. Our new package includes anomaly detection jobs and security rules and takes advantage of the endpoint malware classifier to make finding Lateral Movement in y…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirti Sodhi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.9 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-9-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-9-released"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.17.9 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 7.17.9 over the previous patch versions in 7.17.x.
The 7.17.9 patch release contains a fix for a potential security vulnerability. Please see our security advisory for more details.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maha Alsayasneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Lateral Movement activity: A new Kibana integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-lateral-movement-activity-a-new-kibana-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detecting-lateral-movement-activity-a-new-kibana-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This publication will discuss the newly available Lateral Movement Detection package under Kibana’s integrations app. Our new package includes anomaly detection jobs and security rules and takes advantage of the endpoint malware classifier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirti Sodhi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.17.9 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-9-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-17-9-released"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maha Alsayasneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the launch of the All In for Maintainers DEI Resource Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-01-announcing-the-launch-of-the-all-in-for-maintainers-dei-resource-hub/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-01-announcing-the-launch-of-the-all-in-for-maintainers-dei-resource-hub/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T23:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DEI Resource Hub is a vetted collection of resources, tools, and best practices designed to help open source maintainers create and maintain inclusive and diverse open source communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestration vs Choreography]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=71907&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=71907</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/02/orchestration-vs-choreography/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T22:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the benefits and disadvantages of using Orchestration or Choreography for your microservice architecture.
The post Orchestration vs Choreography appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Flan Collection: Advancing open source methods for instruction tuning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/the-flan-collection-advancing-open.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/02/the-flan-collection-advancing-open.html"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T18:16:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shayne Longpre, Student Researcher, and Adam Roberts, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team  
Language models are now capable of performing many new natural language processing (NLP) tasks by reading instructions, often that they hadn’t seen before. The ability to reason on new tasks is mostly credited to training models on a wide variety of unique instructions, known as “instruction tuning”, which was introduced by FLAN and extended in T0, Super-Natural Instructions, MetaICL, and InstructGPT. However, much of the data that drives these advances remain unreleased to the broader research community. 
    
In “The Flan Collection: Designing Data and Methods for Effective Instruction Tuning”, we closely examine and release a newer and more extensive publicly ava…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source’s impact on the world’s 100 million developers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-01-open-sources-impact-on-the-worlds-100-million-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-01-open-sources-impact-on-the-worlds-100-million-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T18:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re taking a look at how open source software has evolved on GitHub, and how the role of a maintainer and contributor has changed alongside the massive growth in open source software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: January 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-02-01-github-availability-report-january-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-02-01-github-availability-report-january-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T16:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January, we experienced two incidents, one that resulted in degraded performance for Packages and Pages and another that impacted Git users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t know, don’t care]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42699</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/726076745/0/sethsblog~Dont-know-dont-care/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T09:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clients and customers can be frustrating. Perhaps they don’t know what you know. Perhaps they don’t care. It’s possible to educate and inspire. It might be more productive to find the few that want to go where you do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.17.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/01/spring-tools-4-17-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/02/01/spring-tools-4-17-2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lippert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Blasticians introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-blasticians-introduction</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-blasticians-introduction"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of our global DEI initiatives are our employee resource groups. These groups are aligned to shared identities and allow Elasticians to build a sense of community and belonging at work. Here, we discuss their origin and meet the Blasticians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Blasticians introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-blasticians-introduction</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-blasticians-introduction"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We formalized our employee resource groups, or as we like to call them Elastician resource groups, in 2021 but they’ve been a part of the culture at Elastic since 2016. They’ve since evolved into more than just their original Slack channels, and are formal groups focused on community, learning, and much more. 

Each ERG is ensured structure, budget, and ultimately, a voice based on any dimension of diversity, identity, allyship, and advocacy. We feel this was important in framing our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy.

The groups are aligned to shared identities, interests, affinities, or allyships with a goal to create a community of people with something in common and to encourage sharing, learning, and networking. They are also all working towards building a sense of co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bursa of Fabricius]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2732/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2732/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/bursa_of_fabricius.png" title="If an anatomical structure is named for a person, it means they were the only person to have it. Pierre Paul Broca had a special area of his brain that created powerful magnetic fields, enabling him to do 19th century fMRI research." alt="If an anatomical structure is named for a person, it means they were the only person to have it. Pierre Paul Broca had a special area of his brain that created powerful magnetic fields, enabling him to do 19th century fMRI research." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skilling for the future: How GitHub is advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion within open source communities]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-01-31-skilling-for-the-future-how-github-is-advancing-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-within-open-source-communities/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-01-31-skilling-for-the-future-how-github-is-advancing-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-within-open-source-communities/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T22:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the coming months, we’re scaling, expanding, and launching new programming to further DEI within open source communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native OPA Support in Terraform Cloud Is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/native-opa-support-in-terraform-cloud-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/native-opa-support-in-terraform-cloud-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Native Open Policy Agent (OPA) support allows customers who have standardized on OPA to bring their policies into Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS CloudTrail Lake Supports Ingesting Activity Events From Non-AWS Sources]]></title>
        <id>2cadae3dc824e2c665b70b1870d33db1a034c6c2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-cloudtrail-lake-supports-ingesting-activity-events-from-non-aws-sources/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T19:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2013, we announced AWS CloudTrail to track user activity and API usage. AWS CloudTrail enables auditing, security monitoring, and operational troubleshooting. CloudTrail records user activity and API calls across AWS services as events. CloudTrail events help you answer the questions of “who did what, where, and when?”. Recently we have improved the ability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Hermes, An Open Source Document Management System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-hermes-an-open-source-document-management-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-hermes-an-open-source-document-management-system"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about Hermes, an open source document management system created by HashiCorp to help streamline writing and document processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Helios, HashiCorp’s New Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-helios-hashicorp-s-new-design-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/introducing-helios-hashicorp-s-new-design-system"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helios, HashiCorp’s new open source design system, offers a peek into how we create our product UIs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 Configuration as Code Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-2.3-configuration-as-code-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-2.3-configuration-as-code-improvements"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 29, we launched Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.3, which included new and exciting features including improvements for Configuration as Code (CaC). Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 also includes improvements to automation controller as well as the introduction of Ansible validated content. This blog post will walk you through what CaC is and the benefits it can bring to your organization, including a UI and API walkthrough of automation controller and how to take a full Configuration as Code approach to your automation infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get/Want/Have To]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44842</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/725976722/0/sethsblog~GetWantHave-To/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T09:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get to, want to and have to are an endless braid. How much of our time do we spend on each? Have to is often up to someone else. The things we’re required to do by the system or the people in it. Get to is a matter of perspective. Trust and health and leverage […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - January 31st, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/31/this-week-in-spring-january-31st-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/31/this-week-in-spring-january-31st-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AIOps for automation and efficiency in observability and IT operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/aiops-use-cases-observability-operations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/aiops-use-cases-observability-operations"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Common use cases and scenarios for a successful AIOps deployment within observability. From monitoring to anomaly detection and root cause analysis, understand how you can improve your AIOps deployment and see success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinay Chandrasekhar,Tom Grabowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AIOps for automation and efficiency in observability and IT operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/aiops-use-cases-observability-operations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/aiops-use-cases-observability-operations"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Artificial intelligence for IT Operations (or AIOps) has been playing an expanding role in helping SREs, DevOps, and developers effectively navigate the challenges around application and infrastructure complexity, pace of change, and data volume that characterize the operations landscape. By improving efficiency and effectiveness of application and infrastructure monitoring by automating many of the tasks, AIOps can help to reduce the workload on observability teams and free up time to spend on more meaningful analysis.

In our first post, What is AIOps? A beginner’s guide, we dove into AIOps: what it is, why it matters, and establishing production readiness. We talked about why it’s important for an AIOps initiative to start simple with time tested and proven AIOps capabilities, and the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinay Chandrasekhar,Tom Grabowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Deployment Pipelines Reference Architecture and Reference Implementations]]></title>
        <id>dd2c157f3c72dd66393258908bba82d05d2db201</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new_deployment_pipelines_reference_architecture_and_-reference_implementations/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T20:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are launching a new reference architecture and a set of reference implementations for enterprise-grade deployment pipelines. A deployment pipeline automates the building, testing, and deploying of applications or infrastructures into your AWS environments. When you deploy your workloads to the cloud, having deployment pipelines is key to gaining agility and lowering time to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Adds Dynamic Provider Credentials for Vault and Official Cloud Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-dynamic-provider-credentials-vault-official-cloud-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-dynamic-provider-credentials-vault-official-cloud-providers"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic provider credentials for Terraform Cloud provide a simple and safe authentication workflow for Vault and official cloud providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – January 30, 2023]]></title>
        <id>7265ce28a89983515038362f8ac766030479bead</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-january-30-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T18:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s review post comes to you from the road, having just wrapped up sponsorship of NDC London. While there we got to speak to many .NET developers, both new and experienced with AWS, and all eager to learn more. Thanks to everyone who stopped by our expo booth to chat or ask questions to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Action needed for GitHub Desktop and Atom users]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-01-30-action-needed-for-github-desktop-and-atom-users/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-01-30-action-needed-for-github-desktop-and-atom-users/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T18:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update to the latest version of Desktop and previous version of Atom before February 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discovering Creative Insights in Promotional Artwork]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/295e4d788db5</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/discovering-creative-insights-in-promotional-artwork-295e4d788db5?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T16:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Grace Tang, Aneesh Vartakavi, Julija Bagdonaite, Cristina Segalin, and Vi Iyengar]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Population and big innovations]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44828</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/725885624/0/sethsblog~Population-and-big-innovations/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s tempting to embrace the meme that the best way for humans to solve the big problems in front of us is to increase the population, perhaps dramatically. The thinking goes that people are the ones who can solve problems, and more people give us more problem-solvers. This doesn’t hold up to a reductio ad […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get more out of Strava activity fields with runtime fields and transforms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/strava-activity-fields-runtime-fields-transforms</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/strava-activity-fields-runtime-fields-transforms"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the third blog post in a series of ones to follow. I will take you through a journey of data onboarding, manipulation, and visualization using Strava as a backdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoD + DevSecOps: A path toward speed and agility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/dod-devsecops-speed-agility</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/dod-devsecops-speed-agility"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the US Department of Defense moves to a software factory and DevSecOps approach, it's on a path to increase speed and agility. But to truly keep up with modern warfare, an observability solution is an essential investment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Keeney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get more out of Strava activity fields with runtime fields and transforms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/strava-activity-fields-runtime-fields-transforms</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/strava-activity-fields-runtime-fields-transforms"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
This is the third blog post in our Strava series (don’t forget to catch up on the first and second)! I will take you through a journey of data onboarding, manipulation, and visualization.

What is Strava and why is it the focus? Strava is a platform where athletes, from recreational to professional, can share their activities. All my fitness data from my Apple Watch, Garmin, and Zwift is automatically synced and saved there. It is safe to say that if I want to get an overview of my fitness, getting the data out of Strava is the first step.

Why do this with the Elastic Stack? I want to ask my data questions, and questions are just searches!

Have I ridden my bike more this year than last?
On average, is my heart rate reduced by doing more distance on my bike?
Am I running, hiking, and cy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoD + DevSecOps: A path toward speed and agility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/dod-devsecops-speed-agility</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/dod-devsecops-speed-agility"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As the US Department of Defense’s (DoD’s) Software Modernization Strategy is put into place, agility, cloud adoption, and the software-factory methodology are top of mind. But according to a new study from the Hudson Institute, the DoD’s current approach to software and software updates isn’t fast enough to keep pace with modern warfare. The authors write: “The DoD needs to act in a way that recognizes software, not legacy warfighting platforms, controls the speed and efficacy of the modern kill chain and military dilemma.”

While the study’s authors recognize that acquisitions reform is a necessary component to modern software strategy, a dynamic DevSecOps-style approach to leveraging data is also a key element to increasing agility and speed. Many DoD agencies are already pioneering th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Keeney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K-Means Clustering]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2731/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2731/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/k_means_clustering.png" title="According to my especially unsupervised K-means clustering algorithm, there are currently about 8 billion types of people in the world." alt="According to my especially unsupervised K-means clustering algorithm, there are currently about 8 billion types of people in the world." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The coming ubiquity]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44826</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/725810207/0/sethsblog~The-coming-ubiquity/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-29T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fuss about AI might be mis-focused. It’s easy to point to a computer-created essay, song or illustration and find the defects or errors. Given hard work by 1,000 trained people, it’s likely that a human could make something more useful or inspired than a computer could. But the real impact of AI isn’t going […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ways to codify purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44809</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/725735396/0/sethsblog~New-ways-to-codify-purpose/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-28T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And then what happens? Many small businesses start with generosity and good intent at their core. But it’s a rough ride, and especially when outside funding is involved, it’s easy to get seduced by the bright lights of Milton Friedman and an obsession with short-term profits. Over time, purpose starts to fade. The urgencies and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hobson’s choice]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43692</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/725734118/0/sethsblog~Hobsons-choice/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-28T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[…is no choice at all. The stable owner gets to pick which horse you get. Take it or leave it. Some people prefer this. It means that we’re off the hook and not responsible. It relieves us of the emotional labor of choice. Let someone else worry about it… And so we give up our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bypassing OGNL sandboxes for fun and charities]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-01-27-bypassing-ognl-sandboxes-for-fun-and-charities/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-01-27-bypassing-ognl-sandboxes-for-fun-and-charities/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T16:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object Graph Notation Language (OGNL) is a popular, Java-based, expression language used in popular frameworks and applications, such as Apache Struts and Atlassian Confluence. Learn more about bypassing certain OGNL injection protection mechanisms including those used by Struts and Atlassian Confluence, as well as different approaches to analyzing this form of protection so you can harden similar systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Azure DevOps from Zero to Hero]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66329</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/learn-azure-devops-from-zero-to-hero/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T12:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps is FULL of so many features! Myself and Nana from Techworld with Nana teamed up to bring you an Azure DevOps Zero to Hero video! Many of you reading this blog may already be very experienced with Azure DevOps,
The post Learn Azure DevOps from Zero to Hero appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pay what you want]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44800</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/725634233/0/sethsblog~Pay-what-you-want/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T08:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a fascinating payment model. For digital goods and other transactions where the marginal cost of one more sale approaches zero, “pay what you want” exposes how complicated the story we tell about money can be. When we add in the charity component, it becomes even more layered. The Best of Akimbo (volume 1) is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Lifespan]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2730/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2730/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/code_lifespan.png" title="Surely (no one/everyone) will (recognize how flexible and useful this architecture is/spend a huge amount of effort painstakingly preserving and updating this garbage I wrote in 20 minutes)" alt="Surely (no one/everyone) will (recognize how flexible and useful this architecture is/spend a huge amount of effort painstakingly preserving and updating this garbage I wrote in 20 minutes)" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting the foundations for compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-01-26-setting-the-foundations-for-compliance/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-01-26-setting-the-foundations-for-compliance/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T17:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laying the groundwork for developer-enabled compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Zen of Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-zen-of-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-zen-of-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[This blog post is based on my presentation at AnsibleFest 2022 in Chicago and virtually.]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tima@redhat.com (Timothy Appnel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grandiosity as a form of hiding]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43673</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/725539628/0/sethsblog~Grandiosity-as-a-form-of-hiding/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T09:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A business that says its mission is to, “reinvent local commerce to better serve our customers and neighborhoods,” can spend a lot of time doing not much of anything before they realize that they’re not actually creating value. A non-profit that seeks to create “fairness and equity” can also fall into a non-specific trap. Far […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scalable Annotation Service — Marken]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f5ba9266d428</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/scalable-annotation-service-marken-f5ba9266d428?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T03:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Marken (Scalable Annotation Service at Netflix), an annotation is a piece of metadata which can be attached to an object from any domain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: GraalVM advocate Alina Yurenko on a Bootiful Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/a-bootiful-podcast-graalvm-advocate-alina-yurenko-on-a-bootiful-podcast</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/a-bootiful-podcast-graalvm-advocate-alina-yurenko-on-a-bootiful-podcast"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Azure 5.0 is now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/spring-cloud-azure-5-0-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/spring-cloud-azure-5-0-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.1 (codename Kilburn) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/spring-cloud-2022-0-1-codename-kilburn-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/26/spring-cloud-2022-0-1-codename-kilburn-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Baxter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.6.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-6-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-6-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.6.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version over the 8.6.0 minor release.
The 8.6.1 release addresses a recent Elastic Cloud issue where a rolling restart would fail for some users.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, please refer to the release notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Duarte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.6.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-6-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-6-1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in the 8.6.1 release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Duarte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Atlassian uses Camunda within their hyperautomation tech stack]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=71896&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=71896</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/01/atlassian-camunda-hyperautomation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T20:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why Atlassian turned to process orchestration to hyperautomate their tech stack with Camunda and deliver improved customer and employee experiences.
The post How Atlassian uses Camunda within their hyperautomation tech stack appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning with queried hints]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/learning-with-queried-hints.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/learning-with-queried-hints.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T20:46:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sreenivas Gollapudi, Senior Staff Research Scientist, and Kostas Kollias, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research, Algorithms & Optimization Team  
In many computing applications the system needs to make decisions to serve requests that arrive in an online fashion. Consider, for instance, the example of a navigation app that responds to driver requests. In such settings there is inherent uncertainty about important aspects of the problem. For example, the preferences of the driver with respect to features of the route are often unknown and the delays of road segments can be uncertain. The field of online machine learning studies such settings and provides various techniques for decision-making problems under uncertainty. 
   


A navigation engine has to decide how to route thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary KMS (Key Management Service) Root Key Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-kms-key-management-service-root-key-migration</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-kms-key-management-service-root-key-migration"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to migrate HashiCorp Boundary from one KMS provider to another, and learn more about how its encryption works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第223話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190247133138894</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190247133138894"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disable creation of classic pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66312</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/disable-creation-of-classic-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T07:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YAML pipelines offer the best security for your Azure Pipelines. In contrast to classic build and release pipelines, YAML pipelines:
Can be code reviewed. YAML pipelines are no different from any other piece of code. You can prevent malicious actors from introducing malicious steps in your pipelines by enforcing the use of Pull Requests to merge changes.
The post Disable creation of classic pipelines appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silviu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Microservices Patterns with Spring Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/25/introducing-microservices-patterns-with-spring-integration</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/25/introducing-microservices-patterns-with-spring-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Bilan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.6 and 3.0.0 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/25/spring-shell-2-1-6-and-3-0-0-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/01/25/spring-shell-2-1-6-and-3-0-0-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planet Killer Comet Margarita]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2729/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2729/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/planet_killer_comet_margarita.png" title="I'll take mine on the rocks, no ice." alt="I'll take mine on the rocks, no ice." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deciphering clinical abbreviations with privacy protecting ML]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/deciphering-clinical-abbreviations-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/deciphering-clinical-abbreviations-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T22:19:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Posted by Alvin Rajkomar, Research Scientist, and Eric Loreaux, Software Engineer, Google Research  
Today many people have digital access to their medical records, including their doctor’s clinical notes. However, clinical notes are hard to understand because of the specialized language that clinicians use, which contains unfamiliar shorthand and abbreviations. In fact, there are thousands of such abbreviations, many of which are specific to certain medical specialities and locales or can mean multiple things in different contexts. For example, a doctor might write in their clinical notes, “pt referred to pt for lbp“, which is meant to convey the statement: “Patient referred to physical therapy for low back pain.”  Coming up with this translation is tough for laypeople and compu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research, 2022 & beyond: Responsible AI]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/google-research-2022-beyond-responsible.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/google-research-2022-beyond-responsible.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T19:51:00.014Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Marian Croak, VP, Google Research, Responsible AI and Human-Centered Technology    
    

(This is Part 2 in our series of posts covering different topical areas of research at Google. You can find other posts in the series here.)
 
The last year showed tremendous breakthroughs in artificial intelligence (AI), particularly in large language models (LLMs) and text-to-image models. These technological advances require that we are thoughtful and intentional in how they are developed and deployed. In this blogpost, we share ways we have approached Responsible AI across our research in the past year and where we’re headed in 2023. We highlight four primary themes covering foundational and socio-technical research, applied research, and product solutions, as part of our commitment to b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2022 Patch 1]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66315</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2022-patch-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T18:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact Azure DevOps Server 2022.
Test data was not being deleted, causing the database to grow. With this fix, we updated build retention to prevent creating new orphan test data.
The post Azure DevOps Server 2022 Patch 1 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundamentals of Network Automation with Ansible Validated Content using the network.base collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/based-validated-network-content</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/based-validated-network-content"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We introduced resource modules in Ansible 2.9, which provided a path for users to ease network management, especially across multiple different product vendors. This announcement was significant because these resource modules added a well structured representation of device configurations and made it easy to manage common network configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily analyze AWS VPC Flow Logs with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/vpc-flow-logs-monitoring-analytics-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/vpc-flow-logs-monitoring-analytics-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Observability can ingest and help analyze AWS VPC Flow Logs from your application’s VPC. Learn how to ingest AWS VPC Flow Logs through a step-by-step method into Elastic, then analyze it and apply OOTB machine learning for insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect data exfiltration activity with Kibana’s new integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-data-exfiltration-activity-with-kibanas-new-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-data-exfiltration-activity-with-kibanas-new-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Data Exfiltration Detection package can help you identify when critical enterprise data is being stolen and exfiltrated. In this blog, learn how to implement this package.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Apoorva Joshi,Susan Chang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily analyze AWS VPC Flow Logs with Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/vpc-flow-logs-monitoring-analytics-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/vpc-flow-logs-monitoring-analytics-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Observability provides a full-stack observability solution, by supporting metrics, traces, and logs for applications and infrastructure. In a previous blog, I showed you how to monitor your AWS infrastructure running a three-tier application. Specifically we reviewed metrics ingest and analysis on Elastic Observability for EC2, VPC, ELB, and RDS. In this blog, we will cover how to ingest logs from AWS, and more specifically, we will review how to get VPC Flow Logs into Elastic and what you can do with this data.

Logging is an important part of observability, for which we generally think of metrics and/or tracing. However, the amount of logs an application or the underlying infrastructure output can be significantly daunting. 

With Elastic Observability, there are three main mec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect data exfiltration activity with Kibana’s new integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-data-exfiltration-activity-with-kibanas-new-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detect-data-exfiltration-activity-with-kibanas-new-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Does your organization’s data include sensitive information, like intellectual property or personally identifiable information (PII)? Do you want to protect your data from being stolen and sent (i.e., exfiltrated) to external web services? If the answer to these questions is yes, then Elastic’s Data Exfiltration Detection package can help you identify when critical enterprise data is being stolen and exfiltrated.
What is data exfiltration?
Data exfiltration is the unauthorized transfer of data from a device or network. In simple terms, it is a type of data loss — and to enterprises, it may also mean risk exposure. Data exfiltration can be conducted by outsiders of an organization who compromise the network to steal company secrets or credentials. Another way data exfiltration can occur i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Apoorva Joshi,Susan Chang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Open — AWS Asia Pacific (Melbourne) Region in Australia]]></title>
        <id>afac5b6dd127ccc85ba88786f7834863c85ce956</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-aws-asia-pacific-melbourne-region-in-australia/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T23:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following up on Jeff’s post on the announcement of the Melbourne Region, today I’m pleased to share the general availability of the AWS Asia Pacific (Melbourne) Region with three Availability Zones and API name ap-southeast-4. The AWS Asia Pacific (Melbourne) Region is the second infrastructure Region in Australia, in addition to the Asia Pacific (Sydney) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-Driven Access Controls with HashiCorp Boundary and Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/event-driven-access-controls-with-hashicorp-boundary-and-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/event-driven-access-controls-with-hashicorp-boundary-and-vault"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s Rift proof-of-concept app automatically grants and revokes infrastructure access to on-call engineers when an incident is triggered and resolved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer Adds Ancestry to Track Image Relationships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-adds-ancestry-to-track-image-relationships</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-adds-ancestry-to-track-image-relationships"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ancestry tracking for HCP Packer provides visibility into image dependencies across your cloud environment for image lifecycle management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – January 23, 2023]]></title>
        <id>3730c1005965728eaa659a0cc8b3db0855b0fc7e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-january-23-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T18:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to my first AWS Week in Review of 2023. As usual, it has been a busy week, so let’s dive right in: Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that caught my eye last week: Amazon Connect – You can now deliver long lasting, persistent chat experiences for your customers, with the ability to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible and ChatGPT: Putting it to the test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-wisdom-and-chatgpt-putting-it-to-the-test</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-wisdom-and-chatgpt-putting-it-to-the-test"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image: DALL-E]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HashiCorp Employees Celebrate Lunar New Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-employees-celebrate-lunar-new-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-employees-celebrate-lunar-new-year"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp employees from around the world share how they’re celebrating Lunar New Year and the cultural traditions they practice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save space with byte-sized vectors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/save-space-with-byte-sized-vectors</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/save-space-with-byte-sized-vectors"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch is introducing a new type of vector that has 8-bit integer dimensions. This is 4x smaller than the current vector with 32-bit float dimensions, which can result in substantial space savings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Conradson,Benjamin Trent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save space with byte-sized vectors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/save-space-with-byte-sized-vectors</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/save-space-with-byte-sized-vectors"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elasticsearch is introducing a new type of vector in 8.6! This vector has 8-bit integer dimensions, where each dimension has a range of [-128, 127]. This is 4x smaller than the current vector with 32-bit float dimensions, which can result in substantial space savings.
You can start indexing these smaller, 8-bit vectors right now by adding the element_type parameter with the byte value to your vector mappings, similar to the example below.
{
    "mappings": {
        "properties": {
            "my_vector": {
                "type": "dense_vector",
                "element_type": "byte",
                "dims": 3,
                "index": true,
                "similarity": "dot_product"
            }
        }
    }
},
But what if your existing vectors' dimensions don't fit into this sma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Conradson,Benjamin Trent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 216 update]]></title>
        <id>https://localhost/devops/?p=66295</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-216-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T20:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because of the holidays, and our deployment schedule, this update includes our progress for both sprint 215 and 216. You will notice a lot of bugs being fixed in these sprints. Some of the issues being significant.
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 216 update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy production grade automation technology at scale with Red Hat and F5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/deploy-production-grade-automation-technology-at-scale-with-red-hat-and-f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/deploy-production-grade-automation-technology-at-scale-with-red-hat-and-f5"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You will learn how F5 and Red Hat assist network teams transitioning to a NetOps workflow, while reducing risk and increasing productivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George James</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Consider All Microservices Vulnerable — And Monitor Their Behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/20/security-behavior-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/20/security-behavior-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author:
David Hadas (IBM Research Labs)
This post warns Devops from a false sense of security. Following security best practices when developing and configuring microservices do not result in non-vulnerable microservices. The post shows that although all deployed microservices are vulnerable, there is much that can be done to ensure microservices are not exploited. It explains how analyzing the behavior of clients and services from a security standpoint, named here "Security-Behavior Analysis", can protect the deployed vulnerable microservices. It points to Guard, an open source project offering security-behavior monitoring and control of Kubernetes microservices presumed vulnerable.
As cyber attacks continue to intensify in sophistication, organizations deploying cloud services continue t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks, PagerDuty, ServiceNow, and VMware Highlight Continued Vault Ecosystem Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/palo-alto-networks-pagerduty-servicenow-vmware-highlight-vault-eco-growth</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/palo-alto-networks-pagerduty-servicenow-vmware-highlight-vault-eco-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Vault ecosystem continues to grow with the addition of 25 new integrations this past quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnsibleFest 2022 Quick Take: expanding to AWS, Event-Driven Automation and Project Wisdom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansiblefest-2022-quick-take-expanding-to-aws-event-driven-automation-and-project-wisdom</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansiblefest-2022-quick-take-expanding-to-aws-event-driven-automation-and-project-wisdom"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AnsibleFest 2022 was our first in-person event in a few years, and it delivered some exciting news that will impact the growth and expansion of automation for our customers in the months to come. We had more than 450 organizations represented in person in Chicago. Our keynotes featured Red Hat, IBM Research, and Rockwell Automation. During the two days, we announced several new features and capabilities to make adopting automation more accessible. In addition, IDC analyst Jevin Jensen recently published his opinions and insights on AnsibleFest 2022 that we break down below .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Universal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.15 Improves Integration with Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-15-improves-integration-with-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-15-improves-integration-with-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform (CDKTF) 0.15 improves on its ease of use with Terraform Cloud and Terraform Enterprise through automatic Terraform workspace creation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is hyperautomation?]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=71621&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=71621</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/01/what-is-hyperautomation/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T03:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about what hyperautomation is, why it's important and how you can think about applying it to your organization today.
The post What is hyperautomation? appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Research, 2022 & beyond: Language, vision and generative models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/google-research-2022-beyond-language.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/01/google-research-2022-beyond-language.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T19:01:00.019Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeff Dean, Senior Fellow and SVP of Google Research, on behalf of the Google Research community 
   
Today we kick off a series of blog posts about exciting new developments from Google Research. Please keep your eye on this space and look for the title “Google Research, 2022 & Beyond” for more articles in the series.
 
I’ve always been interested in computers because of their ability to help people better understand the world around them.  Over the last decade, much of the research done at Google has been in pursuit of a similar vision — to help people better understand the world around them and get things done. We want to build more capable machines that partner with people to accomplish a huge variety of tasks.  All kinds of tasks.  Complex, information-seeking tasks.  Creativ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Developer Advocate: Part 2, Building Empathy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-2-building-empathy</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-2-building-empathy"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second installment in a blog series on how to build the skills needed to become a developer advocate (or similar technical roles). This post focuses on building empathy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Adds ‘Projects’ to Organize Workspaces at Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-projects-to-organize-workspaces-at-scale</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-adds-projects-to-organize-workspaces-at-scale"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Projects in Terraform Cloud allow users to isolate particular subsets of workspaces and define permissions within a single organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AAP 2.3 Introducing Remote Execution Mesh Nodes for Openshift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/aap-2.3-introducing-remote-execution-mesh-nodes-for-openshift</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/aap-2.3-introducing-remote-execution-mesh-nodes-for-openshift"/>
        <updated>2023-01-17T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year Ansible Automation Platform (AAP) 2 introduced major changes around the mechanics on how automation is run. Learn about remote execution nodes for Openshift with these changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – January 16, 2023]]></title>
        <id>719a3a544137875e791a469a0df199b6819e71ca</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-january-16-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-16T19:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we celebrate Martin Luther King Jr. Day in the US to honor the late civil rights leader’s life, legacy, and achievements. In this article, Amazon employees share what MLK Day means to them and how diversity makes us stronger. Coming back to our AWS Week in Review—it’s been a busy week! Last Week’s Launches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build, preview, and test dynamic forms for user tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=71125&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=71125</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/01/build-preview-test-dynamic-forms-user-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T18:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the latest ways to build, preview and test forms to enable effective human workflow orchestration with Camunda Platform 8.
The post Build, preview, and test dynamic forms for user tasks appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Scale Test Report to Observe Gossip Stability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-scale-test-report-to-observe-gossip-stability</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-scale-test-report-to-observe-gossip-stability"/>
        <updated>2023-01-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our tests show Consul servers remain healthy under all test configurations and that splitting up a large LAN gossip pool cuts the risk of gossip instability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organization profile image]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66263</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/organization-profile-image/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T22:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, it’s hard to believe it’s already 2023! Here at Azure DevOps, we want to wish all of you a Happy New Year and share a small improvement we just added to the product roadmap.
The post Organization profile image appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brenner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing NetOps issues with Event-Driven Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/addressing-netops-issues-with-event-driven-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/addressing-netops-issues-with-event-driven-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A simple example - No Shut, No Problem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HCP-Based Global Management Plane for Consul Now in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-based-global-management-plane-for-consul-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-hcp-based-global-management-plane-for-consul-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new global management plane for Consul is now available as a free public beta. Try it out to gain full visibility for both self-managed and HCP Consul clusters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of Process Orchestration 2023 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=71037&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=71037</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/01/state-of-process-orchestration-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T01:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the challenges of process automation faced by IT leaders today, why process orchestration can help and how you can get started with it today.
The post State of Process Orchestration 2023 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Protect Your Mission-Critical Pods From Eviction With PriorityClass]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/12/protect-mission-critical-pods-priorityclass/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/12/protect-mission-critical-pods-priorityclass/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sunny Bhambhani (InfraCloud Technologies)
Kubernetes has been widely adopted, and many organizations use it as their de-facto orchestration engine for running workloads that need to be created and deleted frequently.
Therefore, proper scheduling of the pods is key to ensuring that application pods are up and running within the Kubernetes cluster without any issues. This article delves into the use cases around resource management by leveraging the PriorityClass object to protect mission-critical or high-priority pods from getting evicted and making sure that the application pods are up, running, and serving traffic.
Resource management in Kubernetes
The control plane consists of multiple components, out of which the scheduler (usually the built-in kube-scheduler) is one of the comp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Connect to Kubernetes Clusters Using Boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-connect-to-kubernetes-clusters-using-boundary</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-connect-to-kubernetes-clusters-using-boundary"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how to use HashiCorp Boundary to provide identity-based remote access and credential management for Kubernetes clusters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第222話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190247048704205</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190247048704205"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.7 released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=70858&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=70858</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/01/camunda-desktop-modeler-5-7/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T21:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the latest version of Camunda Desktop Modeler! Check out a preview of the new form features coming in the Camunda Platform 8.2 release.
The post Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.7 released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Fromme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.10.0-alpha3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=70843&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=70843</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/01/optimize-3-10-0-alpha3/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T20:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the latest release of Camunda Optimize! Camunda Optimize makes it possible to evaluate the success of your process automation initiative.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.10.0-alpha3 released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! AWS Week in Review – January 9, 2023]]></title>
        <id>29642ee7bf4126983375f8ea67a5256cd124b778</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-new-year-aws-week-in-review-january-9-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T17:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! As we kick off 2023, I wanted to take a moment to remind you of some 2023 predictions by AWS leaders for you to help prepare for the new year. Five Tech Predictions for 2023 and Beyond by Dr. Wener Vogels, CTO of Amazon.com – Read how these technologies and trends will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node runner update guidance for Azure Pipelines task authors]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66225</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/node-runner-update-guidance-for-azure-pipelines-task-authors/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T15:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
The post Node runner update guidance for Azure Pipelines task authors appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.26: Eviction policy for unhealthy pods guarded by PodDisruptionBudgets]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/06/unhealthy-pod-eviction-policy-for-pdbs/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/01/06/unhealthy-pod-eviction-policy-for-pdbs/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Filip Křepinský (Red Hat), Morten Torkildsen (Google), Ravi Gudimetla (Apple)
Ensuring the disruptions to your applications do not affect its availability isn't a simple
task. Last month's release of Kubernetes v1.26 lets you specify an unhealthy pod eviction policy
for PodDisruptionBudgets (PDBs)
to help you maintain that availability during node management operations.
In this article, we will dive deeper into what modifications were introduced for PDBs to
give application owners greater flexibility in managing disruptions.
What problems does this solve?
API-initiated eviction of pods respects PodDisruptionBudgets (PDBs). This means that a requested voluntary disruption
via an eviction to a Pod, should not disrupt a guarded application and .status.currentHealthy of a PDB should n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 Encrypts New Objects By Default]]></title>
        <id>6a490327f42a0b08871eb4843fc22e2b6a07f127</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-encrypts-new-objects-by-default/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T21:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS, security is the top priority. Starting today, Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) encrypts all new objects by default. Now, S3 automatically applies server-side encryption (SSE-S3) for each new object, unless you specify a different encryption option. SSE-S3 was first launched in 2011. As Jeff wrote at the time: “Amazon S3 server-side encryption […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>