<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-22T01:43:57.719Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-22T01:43:57.719Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Survey of Causal Inference Applications at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b62d25175e6f</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/a-survey-of-causal-inference-applications-at-netflix-b62d25175e6f?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T15:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Netflix, we want to entertain the world through creating engaging content and helping members discover the titles they will love. Key to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The department of bad behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog-production.mystagingwebsite.com/?p=29537</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/697139758/0/sethsblog~The-department-of-bad-behavior/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T08:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if organizations had a division that simply did the bad stuff? The people who were responsible for creating system updates that slow down old computers, that cover up bad behavior by employees, the people who dump pollution into the river when no one is watching… If all the folks who invent dark patterns, lobby […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auth0, Fortinet, and Vercel Among New Verified Terraform Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/auth0-fortinet-and-vercel-among-new-verified-terraform-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/auth0-fortinet-and-vercel-among-new-verified-terraform-providers"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the addition of 18 new verified providers to the growing HashiCorp Terraform ecosystem we hit a milestone with 200 verified Terraform providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · April 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-20-release-radar-apr-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-20-release-radar-apr-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T16:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each month, we highlight open source projects that have shipped major updates. These include everything from world-changing technology to developer tooling, and weekend projects. Here are our top staff picks on projects that shipped major version releases in April. Flyte 1.0 I was lucky enough to discover Flyte during Hacktoberfest last year. Now, Flyte has [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Action needed by GitHub Connect customers using GHES 3.1 and older to adopt new authentication token format updates]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-20-action-needed-by-github-connect-customers-using-ghes-3-1-and-older-to-adopt-new-authentication-token-format-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-20-action-needed-by-github-connect-customers-using-ghes-3-1-and-older-to-adopt-new-authentication-token-format-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade to GHES 3.2 or newer by June 3rd to continue using GitHub Connect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PhpStorm 2022.1.2 Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=phpstorm&amp;p=247909</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/phpstorm/2022/05/phpstorm-2022-1-2-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T14:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a new preview available of PhpStorm 2022.1.2, the upcoming minor release of PhpStorm. It brings a bunch of bug fixes and quality-of-life improvements. These are the most notable changes and bug fixes: Broken keyboard navigation in the create new class dialog has been fixed (WI-66414) Invalid suggestion to add a return type to destructors […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Roose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Data Tools 1.6 EAP: What’s New?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=big-data-tools&amp;p=246633</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/big-data-tools/2022/05/20/big-data-tools-1-6-eap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T13:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big Data Tools 1.6 EAP is now available. You can try the newly added features right away by installing the latest plugin version to the 2022.2 EAP of your IDE. Please note this is an Early Access Program build, meaning it’s not fully tested. Hive Metastore support Ability to create a Hive metastore connection from the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2022.2 Early Access Program Is Now Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=247925</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2022/05/20/goland-2022-2-early-access-program-is-now-open/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T12:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re starting our Early Access Program for the 2022.2 release. If you want to learn what we have planned for v2022.2, check out our roadmap. You can get this EAP build via the Toolbox App, download it from our website, use a snap package (for Ubuntu), or from inside GoLand, select Check IDE updates for: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Java Applications to Azure using Continuous Delivery]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64092</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploying-java-applications-to-azure-using-continuous-delivery/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T10:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 3 in our series DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions and continuous delivery!
April: [00:00:00] Tune in into this week’s episode of the DevOps lab,
The post Deploying Java Applications to Azure using Continuous Delivery appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2022.2 Early Access Program Is Now Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=246638</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2022/05/webstorm-2022-2-eap-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T10:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re ready to kick off WebStorm 2022.2 with a new Early Access Program (EAP). If you’re not familiar with how our EAP works, check out this blog post where we explain what it is and the benefits of participating. If you haven’t already seen what to expect in WebStorm 2022.2, have a look at our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 EAP Is Open!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=246220</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/05/intellij-idea-2022-2-eap-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T09:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re announcing the next Early Access Program and we invite you to take part in testing and validating new features that are expected to be included in the IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 release. The first IntelliJ IDEA 2022.2 EAP build brings a number of useful improvements to various parts of the product along with moving the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switch before perfect]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42044</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696990664/0/sethsblog~Switch-before-perfect/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T08:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1993, when I was raising investment for one of the first internet companies, there weren’t any firms that specialized in this sort of thing. They were VCs from a different era, looking for the next Fedex or pharma company. I pitched dozens of them, and the answer was consistent, “get back to us when […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a Java Application to Azure using Continuous Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64087</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-a-java-application-to-azure-using-continuous-integration/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T07:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 2 in our series for DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions and continuous integration.
April: We’re back this week with the dev ops lab and we’re continuing our series DevOps for Java shops.
The post Deploy a Java Application to Azure using Continuous Integration appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy natural language processing (NLP): Getting started]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-natural-language-processing-nlp-getting-started</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-natural-language-processing-nlp-getting-started"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog describes the process for getting up and running with deep learning models for natural language processing (NLP) in Elasticsearch using HuggingFace and PyTorch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy NLP: Sentiment Analysis Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-sentiment-analysis-example</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-sentiment-analysis-example"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking Sentiment Analysis as the example task, this blog describes the process for getting up and running using deep learning models for Natural Language Processing in Elasticsearch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy NLP: Text Embeddings and Vector Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-text-embeddings-and-vector-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-text-embeddings-and-vector-search"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking Sentiment Analysis as the example task, this blog describes the process for getting up and running using deep learning models for Natural Language Processing in Elasticsearch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayya Sharipova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy NLP: Named entity recognition (NER) example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-named-entity-recognition-ner-example</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-named-entity-recognition-ner-example"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using named entity recognition (NER) as an example, this blog describes the process for getting up and running using deep learning models for natural language processing (NLP) in Elasticsearch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VentureBeat: 'Once frenemies, Elastic and AWS are now besties’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/venturebeat-once-frenemies-elastic-and-aws-are-now-besties</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/venturebeat-once-frenemies-elastic-and-aws-are-now-besties"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An article recently published in VentureBeat details the transformation of the relationship between Elastic and AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Blog - Elasticsearch, Kibana, and ELK Stack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy natural language processing (NLP): Getting started]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-natural-language-processing-nlp-getting-started</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-natural-language-processing-nlp-getting-started"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The release of the Elastic Stack 8.0 introduced the ability to upload PyTorch machine learning models into Elasticsearch to provide modern natural language processing (NLP) in the Elastic Stack. NLP opens up opportunities to extract information, classify text, and provide better search relevance through dense vectors and approximate nearest neighbor search.
In this multi-part blog series, we will walk through end-to-end examples using a variety of PyTorch NLP models.
Part 1: How to deploy text embeddings and vector search
Part 2: Named entity recognition (NER)
Part 3: Sentiment analysis
In each example we will use a prebuilt NLP model from the Hugging Face model hub. Then we will follow the Elastic documented instructions for deploying an NLP model and adding NLP inference to an ingest pipeline.  Because it’s always a good idea to start with a defined use case and an understanding of the text data to process in the model, we’ll start by defining the objective for using NLP and a shared data set for anyone to try out.
To prepare for the NLP example, we will need an Elasticsearch cluster running at least version 8.0, an ML node with at least 2GB RAM, and for the named entity recognition (NER) example we’ll use the required mapper-annotated-text plugin. One of the easiest ways to get started is by following along with these NLP examples with your own free 14-day trial cluster on Elastic Cloud. Cloud trials are able to scale to a max of two 2GB ML nodes, which will allow you to deploy one or two of examples at any one time in this multi-part blog series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy NLP: Sentiment Analysis Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-sentiment-analysis-example</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-sentiment-analysis-example"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As part of our multi-blog series on natural language processing (NLP), we will walk through an example using a sentiment analysis NLP model to evaluate if comment (text) fields contain positive or negative sentiments. Using a publicly available model, we will show you how to deploy that model to Elasticsearch and use the model in an ingest pipeline to classify customer reviews as being either a positive or negative.
Sentiment analysis is a type of binary classification where the field is predicted to be either one value or the other. There is typically a probability score for that prediction between 0 and 1, with scores closer to 1 indicating more-confident predictions. This type of NLP analysis can be usefully applied to many data sets such as product reviews or customer feedback.
The c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy NLP: Text Embeddings and Vector Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-text-embeddings-and-vector-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-text-embeddings-and-vector-search"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As part of our natural language processing (NLP) blog series, we will walk through an example of using a text embedding model to generate vector representations of textual contents and demonstrating vector similarity search on generated vectors. We will deploy a publicly available model on Elasticsearch and use it in an ingest pipeline to generate embeddings from textual documents. We will then show how to use those embeddings in the vector similarity search to find semantically similar documents for a given query.
Vector similarity search or, as is commonly called semantic search, goes beyond the traditional keyword based search and allows users to find semantically similar documents that may not have any common keywords thus providing a wider range of results. Vector similarity search …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayya Sharipova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy NLP: Named entity recognition (NER) example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-named-entity-recognition-ner-example</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-deploy-nlp-named-entity-recognition-ner-example"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As part of our multi-blog series on natural language processing (NLP), we will walk through an example using a named entity recognition (NER) NLP model to locate and extract predefined categories of entities in unstructured text fields. Using a publicly available model, we will show you how to deploy that model to Elasticsearch, find named entities in text with the new _infer API, and use the NER model in an ingest pipeline to extract entities as documents are ingested into Elasticsearch.
NER models are useful for using natural language to extract entities like people, places, and organizations from full text fields.
In this example we will run the paragraphs of the book Les Misérables, through an NER model and use the model to extract the characters and locations from the text and visua…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VentureBeat: 'Once frenemies, Elastic and AWS are now besties’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/venturebeat-once-frenemies-elastic-and-aws-are-now-besties</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/venturebeat-once-frenemies-elastic-and-aws-are-now-besties"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
An article recently published in VentureBeat details the transformation of the relationship between Elastic and AWS.

Elastic announced that the company has expanded its collaboration with AWS, and that the companies are now working together to accelerate momentum and build, market, and deliver seamless access to Elastic Cloud on AWS for our shared customers, while also leveraging AWS’s global footprint and breadth of services.

“Our expanded collaboration includes streamlined signup and onboarding, more simplified data ingestion, new go-to-market initiatives, and expanded AWS competencies and validated qualifications.”

VentureBeat reporter, Paul Sawers, spoke with Elastic CEO, Ash Kulkarni, about the collaboration between the two companies and the path forward.

Read the full article at VentureBeat to learn more about this collaboration, which Kulkarni called a “win-win” for both companies.

Read more: Once frenemies, Elastic and AWS are now besties]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Blog - Elasticsearch, Kibana, and ELK Stack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Diameter Turnaround]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2622/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2622/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/angular_diameter_turnaround.png" title="Thank you to Katie Mack for teaching me about this effect, and to Janelle Shane for describing redshifts as 'like galaxies sinking into a pool of dilute blood,' which is how I'll see them from now on." alt="Thank you to Katie Mack for teaching me about this effect, and to Janelle Shane for describing redshifts as 'like galaxies sinking into a pool of dilute blood,' which is how I'll see them from now on." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power of Partners: How Camunda’s Partners are Making an Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=54712</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/the-power-of-partners-how-camundas-partners-are-making-an-impact/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard of our Camunda Connect program? Learn how it's enabling our partners to make process automation more accessible to our clients.
The post The Power of Partners: How Camunda’s Partners are Making an Impact appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation at the Edge - Summit 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-at-the-edge-summit-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-at-the-edge-summit-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As some of you may know, Red Hat Summit was back in person in Boston last week. For those who are not familiar, Red Hat Summit is the premier enterprise open source event for IT professionals to learn, collaborate, and innovate on technologies from the datacenter and public cloud to the edge and beyond. Red Hat made a lot of exciting announcements, with several that included Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. If you could not make the event or would like to revisit some of the content, you can access any session on demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elathram@redhat.com (Elle Lathram)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Math support in Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-19-math-support-in-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-19-math-support-in-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T17:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mathematical expressions are key to information sharing amongst engineers, scientists, data scientists, and mathematicians. Today we are pleased to announce that math expressions can be rendered in Markdown on GitHub using $$ as a delimiter for code blocks with math content or the $ delimiter for inline math expressions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we’re continuing to enable all developers to build]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-19-how-were-continuing-to-enable-all-developers-to-build/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-19-how-were-continuing-to-enable-all-developers-to-build/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T16:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about what GitHub is doing to make their products more inclusive, and what’s next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rider 2022.2 Early Access Program Has Started!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=246280</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/05/19/rider-2022-2-eap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first EAP build comes with updates to the main toolbar, an early preview of MAUI support, and the long-awaited move to .NET 6 runtime for the Rider backend on Windows. You can now download Rider 2022.2 EAP1 directly from www.jetbrains.com or install it via the JetBrains Toolbox App or from snapcraft.io. .NET 6 runtime […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Kurakin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppCode Starts the 2022.2 EAP with the UML Class Diagrams]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=appcode&amp;p=247566</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/appcode/2022/05/appcode-starts-the-2022-2-eap-with-the-uml-class-diagrams/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, Today we are starting the Early Access Program for AppCode 2022.2, and the first build is already available for download. Give the free EAP builds a try and let us know what you think about the changes! Share your feedback in the comments or submit it to our issue tracker. DOWNLOAD APPCODE 2022.2 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion Starts the 2022.2 EAP: Colorized Ninja output, Embedded GDB Server Wizard, Updated CMake Presets Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=247340</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2022/05/clion-starts-the-2022-2-eap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CLion 2022.2 Early Access Preview program starts today! Give the free EAP builds a try and let us know what you think about the changes! Share your feedback in the comments or submit it to our issue tracker. Build 222.2270.30 is available from our website via the Toolbox App or as a snap package […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ Starts the 2022.2 Early Access Program]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rscpp&amp;p=247551</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rscpp/2022/05/19/resharper-cpp-2022-2-eap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new 2022.2 development cycle follows the goals outlined in the roadmap for the first 2022.1 release and all of 2022: our main priorities are addressing quality issues and improving Unreal Engine support. We also never miss a chance to assist you with modern C++, so in this release we are working hard to introduce […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elvira Mustafina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2022.2 Starts the EAP]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=246305</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/05/19/resharper-2022-2-eap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve opened the Early Access Program for the ReSharper 2022.2 release cycle. You can download the ReSharper 2022.2 EAP1 build from www.jetbrains.com or via the JetBrains Toolbox App.  C# 11 We’ve added support for one more C# 11 feature – checked user-defined operators. This helps developers create user-defined operators that operate on types where arithmetic […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Kurakin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Do Accessible Design and Engineering at HashiCorp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-do-accessible-design-and-engineering-at-hashicorp</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-we-do-accessible-design-and-engineering-at-hashicorp"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two HashiCorp engineers discuss accessible design and engineering at HashiCorp, from overall principles to the tools we use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to Azure Pipelines Runtime Variables Settings [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63937</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/updates-to-azure-pipelines-runtime-variables-settings/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have gotten a lot of feedback on this change and after internal deliberation, we are now rolling back this change ASAP.
We have now fully rolled back the change that caused the issue.
The post Updates to Azure Pipelines Runtime Variables Settings [Updated] appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.8 Expands Health and Events Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-8-expands-health-and-events-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-boundary-0-8-expands-health-and-events-observability"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.8 adds key observability features and improvements to identity-based secure remote access for dynamic infrastructure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Space – Everything You Need to Start a New Software Development Project]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=246566</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2022/05/19/webinar-start-new-software-development-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T13:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us Thursday, June 2, 2022, 3:00 pm – 5:00 pm UTC (5:00 pm – 7:00 pm CEST or check other timezones) for our free live webinar, Space – everything you need to start a new software development project. In this live interactive webinar, your hosts Valerie Andrianova, Space Product Marketing Manager, and Mikhail Vink, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilia Afanasiev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in IntelliJ Rust for 2022.1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rust&amp;p=246967</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rust/2022/05/19/what-s-new-in-intellij-rust-for-2022-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T13:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this release cycle, we’ve improved our language support, code insight, run/debug support, and tool integrations, and added many enhancements and fixes.  Language Support Single-step macro expansion  We’ve significantly improved how macro expansion works. Previously the macro expansion process was implemented in multiple steps – up to 64. The indexing would start after every step. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Announces Expanded Collaboration with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-expanded-collaboration-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-expanded-collaboration-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T12:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Ariel Roop,Laurent Mechain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Announces Expanded Collaboration with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-expanded-collaboration-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-announces-expanded-collaboration-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T12:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,,
Today we announced an expansion to our collaboration with AWS. We’re working together to accelerate momentum and build, market and deliver seamless access to Elastic Cloud on AWS for our shared customers, while also leveraging AWS’s global footprint and breadth of services.

Our expanded collaboration includes streamlined signup and onboarding, more simplified data ingestion, new go-to-market initiatives, and expanded AWS competencies and validated qualifications.

Together, we’re helping our customers minimize risk and realize faster time to value. We’ve built a foundation to help customers search, analyze and protect their data across AWS and its services so they can transform their data into actionable insights.

“MISI deploys Elastic Cloud on AWS GovCloud (US) to operate a security …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ariel Roop,Laurent Mechain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[False metrics appearing real]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=40091</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696816552/0/sethsblog~False-metrics-appearing-real/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T09:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just because they’re easy to measure doesn’t mean they matter. If they appear in round numbers and are easily compared to those from others, we’re tempted to compare. But something that looks like a useful metric might not be. If you’re working with people who say they care about measurement, it might not pay to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Possibility is fragile]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42931</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696805598/0/sethsblog~Possibility-is-fragile/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T08:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And that’s the paradox, because the closer possibility gets to reality, the more it engages with the unforgiving edges of the real world. As we begin to imagine something better, it’s important to have some insulation, room to believe and a chance to fill in the missing pieces. But then we have to allow the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64084</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/deploy-a-java-application-to-azure-app-service-using-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T07:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for episode 1 in our series for DevOps for Java Shops! In this episode Brian Benz walks us through how to deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions. Brian also covers off feature flags!
April: Welcome to this week’s episode of the dev ops lab.
The post Deploy a Java application to Azure App Service using GitHub Actions appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic powers speed, security, and connectivity in capital markets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-speed-security-connectivity-capital-markets-finance</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-speed-security-connectivity-capital-markets-finance"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed is everything in capital markets. Success in the front and back office is dependent on the ability to provide accurate, fast responses to challenging questions. Over the past several decades, there has been a tremendous increase in the amount of information available to market participants, and trade transactions are now being carried out at a very rapid pace. In parallel, the technology which capital markets firms are developing is becoming increasingly complex. Especially as firms migrate workloads to the cloud and rely on more distributed architectures. Many business leaders need to ask themselves the burning question - how will this impact our ability to win in an increasingly competitive, democratized trading environment? 
Luckily, by delivering the right tools to enable their t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic powers speed, security, and connectivity in capital markets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-speed-security-connectivity-capital-markets-finance</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-speed-security-connectivity-capital-markets-finance"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed is everything in capital markets. By delivering the right tools, firms can set themselves up for success and take advantage of the opportunities available to them with digital and cloud transformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform 1.2 Improves Exception Handling and Updates to the CLI-driven Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-2-improves-exception-handling-and-updates-to-the-cli-driven-workflow</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-1-2-improves-exception-handling-and-updates-to-the-cli-driven-workflow"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now generally available, HashiCorp Terraform 1.2 introduces exception handling with pre- and post-conditions, support for non-interactive Terraform Cloud operations in a CI/CD pipeline, and CLI support for Run Tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Artifacts introduces new Upstreaming capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64079</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-artifacts-introduces-new-upstreaming-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T22:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Artifacts is announcing the long-desired feature of supporting Upstreams for Universal Packages across different ADO organizations.
The post Azure Artifacts introduces new Upstreaming capabilities appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing and delivering high-quality code with innersource metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-18-securing-and-delivering-high-quality-code-with-innersource-metrics/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-18-securing-and-delivering-high-quality-code-with-innersource-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T21:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With innersource, it’s important to measure both the amount of innersource activity and the quality of the code being created. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Backup Now Supports Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP]]></title>
        <id>4a4714ab05fe013a182547e67a8696dc9531dab4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-backup-now-supports-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T20:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a long-time reader of this blog, you know that I categorize some posts as “chocolate and peanut butter” in homage to an ancient (1970 or so) series of TV commercials for Reese’s Peanut Butter Cups. Today, I am happy to bring you the latest such post, combining AWS Backup and Amazon FSx […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector-Quantized Image Modeling with Improved VQGAN]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/vector-quantized-image-modeling-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/vector-quantized-image-modeling-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jiahui Yu, Senior Research Scientist, and Jing Yu Koh, Research Software Engineer, Google Research 
In recent years, natural language processing models have dramatically improved their ability to learn general-purpose representations, which has resulted in significant performance gains for a wide range of natural language generation and natural language understanding tasks. In large part, this has been accomplished through pre-training language models on extensive unlabeled text corpora.  
This pre-training formulation does not make assumptions about input signal modality, which can be language, vision, or audio, among others. Several recent papers have exploited this formulation to dramatically improve image generation results through pre-quantizing images into discrete integer …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The grandstanders]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42016</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696614138/0/sethsblog~The-grandstanders/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T08:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a common sort of feedback/criticism/brainstorming, and it deserves a name. Show up toward the end, when most of the work has been done and it’s almost time to ship… Make a suggestion that would require changing a great deal of what’s been done. It might even be a good suggestion on its face, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps for Java on Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64058</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-for-java-on-azure/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T08:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure loves Java, bring your favorite tools and frameworks to Azure!
The post DevOps for Java on Azure appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A peek behind the BPFDoor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-peek-behind-the-bpfdoor</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-peek-behind-the-bpfdoor"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this research piece, we explore BPFDoor — a backdoor payload specifically crafted for Linux in order to gain re-entry into a previously or actively compromised target environment, with insights on how evasion occurs within impacted systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A peek behind the BPFDoor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-peek-behind-the-bpfdoor</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-peek-behind-the-bpfdoor"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Threats knock on your door all the time. In this research piece, we explore BPFDoor — a backdoor payload specifically crafted for Linux in order to gain re-entry into a previously or actively compromised target environment. This payload has been observed across systems for five years, suggesting that the threat actors responsible for operating the malware have been around for some time and have likely operated undetected in many environments. 
The threat actors have leveraged a network of VPS servers to act as a controller and access these systems via compromised routers based out of Taiwan, acting as a VPN network for the adversarial group. In the Elastic Security Intelligence and Analytics team’s deep research, we explore the actual payload, the backdoor lifecycle, and the BPF filters that are leveraged to provide you with insights on how evasion occurs within impacted systems. 
It’s important to know how you can detect this payload threat and understand the sophistication of the loader. Both are covered in this research. The Elastic Security Intelligence and Analytics team also shares the actual indicators of compromise.
It’s critical to invest the time and resources into ensuring your organization’s workloads remain effectively monitored. Get started with a free 14-day trial of Elastic Cloud. Or download the self-managed version of the Elastic Stack for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can observability help telecom providers accelerate 5G monetization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-can-observability-help-telecom-providers-accelerate-5G-monetization</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-can-observability-help-telecom-providers-accelerate-5G-monetization"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The telecom industry is at an inflection point today where the endless possibilities of 5G meet the growing challenges of accelerating 5G monetization. In this blog post, we  take a broader look into some widely acknowledged 5G monetization opportunities and explore why unified observability is a prerequisite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can observability help telecom providers accelerate 5G monetization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-can-observability-help-telecom-providers-accelerate-5G-monetization</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-can-observability-help-telecom-providers-accelerate-5G-monetization"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The telecom industry is at an inflection point today, where the endless possibilities of 5G meet the growing challenges of accelerating 5G monetization. This is particularly true for telecom providers who have pumped billions of dollars in building 5G networks.
The telecom cloud market is expected to cross USD 74 billion by 2026. So, this presents telecom-as-a-service (TaaS) as an opportunity for telecom providers to monetize their network assets as well as decades of expertise in building and managing network infrastructure.
In this blog post, we  take a broader look into some widely acknowledged 5G monetization opportunities and explore why unified observability is a prerequisite.
New opportunities on the horizon
Network slicing in 5G arguably presents one of the biggest monetization o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mainly Known For]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2621/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2621/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/mainly_known_for.png" title="Oh sure, I know Keira Knightly, from the first movie in that series by The Land Before Time producer. You know, the franchise with the guy from Jurassic Park and Ghostwriter, and script work by Billie Lourd's mom?" alt="Oh sure, I know Keira Knightly, from the first movie in that series by The Land Before Time producer. You know, the franchise with the guy from Jurassic Park and Ghostwriter, and script work by Billie Lourd's mom?" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64002</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/may-patches-for-azure-devops-server-and-team-foundation-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T22:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact Azure DevOps Server 2019.0.1, as well as the following older Team Foundation Server (TFS) releases: TFS 2015.4.2, TFS 2017.3.1 and TFS 2018.3.2.
Revoke all personal access tokens after a user’s Active Directory account is disabled.
The post May patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contextual Rephrasing in Google Assistant]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/contextual-rephrasing-in-google.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/contextual-rephrasing-in-google.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T19:38:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Aurelien Boffy, Senior Staff Software Engineer, and Roberto Pieraccini, Engineering Director, Google Assistant 
When people converse with one another, context and references play a critical role in driving their conversation more efficiently. For instance, if one asks the question “Who wrote Romeo and Juliet?” and, after receiving an answer, asks “Where was he born?”, it is clear that ‘he’ is referring to William Shakespeare without the need to explicitly mention him. Or if someone mentions “python” in a sentence, one can use the context from the conversation to determine whether they are referring to a type of snake or a computer language. If a virtual assistant cannot robustly handle context and references, users would be required to adapt to the limitation of the technology by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2, 2020.0.2 and 2019.1.2 releases]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64015</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-server-2020-1-2-2020-0-2-and-2019-1-2-releases/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T18:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are releasing multiple versions of our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server. You can find the details of the fixes in the release notes for each version.
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2 ISO
Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2 Web Install
Release Notes
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2 ISO
Azure DevOps Server 2020.0.2 Web Install
Release Notes
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2 ISO
Azure DevOps Server 2019.1.2 Web Install
Release Notes
The post Azure DevOps Server 2020.1.2, 2020.0.2 and 2019.1.2 releases appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Helm and Kubernetes to deploy Camunda 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=53853</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/using-helm-and-kubernetes-to-deploy-camunda-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know to install, configure, and run Camunda Platform 8 Helm charts. 
The post Using Helm and Kubernetes to deploy Camunda 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please share the extra with a friend]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42939</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696445464/0/sethsblog~Please-share-the-extra-with-a-friend/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Krispy Kreme grew to become a doughnut behemoth in the US. The formula was simple: Scarce supply, high short-term taste satisfaction, and a dozen priced almost the same as just four. As a result, most people bought a dozen. But few could eat a dozen, and you can’t really save them, so you realized that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Maps now supports the Machine Learning Anomalies Layer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-maps-now-supports-the-machine-learning-anomalies-layer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-maps-now-supports-the-machine-learning-anomalies-layer"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Results from machine learning (ML) anomaly detection jobs that use geographical functions can now be viewed in Elastic Maps. The 8.1.0 release of Elastic Maps can generate a map of the anomalies by location and help you explore new trends in your data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Alvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Maps now supports the Machine Learning Anomalies Layer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-maps-now-supports-the-machine-learning-anomalies-layer</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-maps-now-supports-the-machine-learning-anomalies-layer"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Results from Machine Learning (ML) anomaly detection jobs that use geographical functions can now be viewed in Elastic Maps. The 8.1.0 release of Elastic Maps can generate a map of the anomalies by location and help you explore new trends in your data.
Elastic Maps is available on Elastic Cloud. You can also download the Elastic Stack and our cloud orchestration products, Elastic Cloud Enterprise (ECE) and Elastic Cloud for Kubernetes (ECK), for a self-managed experience.
In this example, we will use General Transit Feed Specification (GTFS) data. GTFS defines a common format for public transportation schedules and associated geographic information.
About the data
This data is a collection of approximately 2 months of gtfs-realtime data streamed from San Antonio, TX. This data consists s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Alvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to measure innersource across your organization]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-16-how-to-measure-innersource-across-your-organization/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-16-how-to-measure-innersource-across-your-organization/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T22:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The innersource contribution percentage is the rate of contributions from people outside the team that originally authored the software. Let’s dive into what it can look like for your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – May 16, 2022]]></title>
        <id>188f6fbb789cd4b216b2e97a6340bddf3499db79</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-16-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T19:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! I had been on the road for the last five weeks and attended many of the AWS Summits in Europe. It was great to talk to so many of you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we’re using projects to build projects]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-16-how-were-using-projects-to-build-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-16-how-were-using-projects-to-build-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At GitHub we use GitHub to build our own products, and the new projects experience is no different. Check out how our team uses projects to build powerful project planning for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Achieves ISO/IEC 27001:2013 Certification!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-16-github-achieves-iso-iec-270012013-certification/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-16-github-achieves-iso-iec-270012013-certification/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub’s Information Security Management System (ISMS) has been certified against ISO 27001:2013, an internationally recognized standard for security program best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask me Anything Recap - April]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ask-me-anything-recap-april</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ask-me-anything-recap-april"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For this webinar, we had an awesome group of individuals with a diverse talent range across multiple skill sets from Product Management, Technical Marketing and Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newbies welcome]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42020</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696281996/0/sethsblog~Newbies-welcome/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T08:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The paradox of most tightly-knit communities is that they have an internal culture. And that culture often makes it difficult for a new person to join. It’s hard to have insiders if you don’t have outsiders. This is true for guilds of copy editors, fans of anime or branches of science. The key transition point […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Health Data]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2620/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2620/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/health_data.png" title="Donate now to help us find a cure for causality. No one should have to suffer through events because of other events." alt="Donate now to help us find a cure for causality. No one should have to suffer through events because of other events." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone else is]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42013</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/696132578/0/sethsblog~Everyone-else-is/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T08:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, not everyone. Just most people. When you do something that everyone else is doing, you’re likely to get what everyone else is getting. But in almost every population, “everyone” leaves out the people who go first, who change things, who are weird and who challenge the status quo. That’s an option, even when it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data, information and decisions]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42924</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/695972622/0/sethsblog~Data-information-and-decisions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T08:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is everywhere, but turning it into information isn’t free. It takes focus, effort, consultation and time. More information is only useful if it helps you make a decision. Knowing the temperature on Saturn isn’t useful. Knowing it to even more accuracy is less useful. That’s because we’re not making any decisions that involve the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 13.05.2022]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=64029</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-06-13-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T12:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back this week for another top stories from the #AzureDevOps #Community!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 13.05.2022 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five beats]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=42921</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/695799348/0/sethsblog~Five-beats/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T08:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we’re close to an answer, there are two easy paths–name it, right now, and move on. Or avoid the answer and the responsibility that comes with it and stall. The best path is the third one. Wait for five beats. Kneejerk is not an admirable trait. A few breaths before we rip into someone. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crêpe]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2619/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2619/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/crepe.png" title="A medicine that makes you put two dots over your letters more often is a diäretic." alt="A medicine that makes you put two dots over your letters more often is a diäretic." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenges in Multi-objective Optimization for Automatic Wireless Network Planning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/challenges-in-multi-objective.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/challenges-in-multi-objective.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Ahmadian and Matthew Fahrbach, Research Scientists, Google Research, Large-Scale Optimization Team 
Economics, combinatorics, physics, and signal processing conspire to make it difficult to design, build, and operate high-quality, cost-effective wireless networks. The radio transceivers that communicate with our mobile phones, the equipment that supports them (such as power and wired networking), and the physical space they occupy are all expensive, so it’s important to be judicious in choosing sites for new transceivers. Even when the set of available sites is limited, there are exponentially many possible networks that can be built. For example, given only 50 sites, there are 250 (over a million billion) possibilities!  
Further complicating things, for every location wher…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 Adds Native Service Discovery and Edge Workload Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-3-adds-native-service-discovery-and-edge-workload-support"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.3 includes built-in service discovery, improved edge compute support, Container Storage Interface (CSI) general availability, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graduation is here! Celebrate the Class of 2022, and join GitHub on June 11 🎓]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-11-graduation-is-here-celebrate-the-class-of-2022-and-join-github-on-june-11/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-11-graduation-is-here-celebrate-the-class-of-2022-and-join-github-on-june-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, thousands of students from around the world came together and redefined the world we live in, how we learn, and how we move forward. We are honored to be part of the experience and eager to celebrate this milestone. So on June 11 we celebrate the Class of 2022 and welcome them to [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Language Models Perform Reasoning via Chain of Thought]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/language-models-perform-reasoning-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/language-models-perform-reasoning-via.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jason Wei and Denny Zhou, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain team 
In recent years, scaling up the size of language models has been shown to be a reliable way to improve performance on a range of natural language processing (NLP) tasks. Today’s language models at the scale of 100B or more parameters achieve strong performance on tasks like sentiment analysis and machine translation, even with little or no training examples. Even the largest language models, however, can still struggle with certain multi-step reasoning tasks, such as math word problems and commonsense reasoning. How might we enable language models to perform such reasoning tasks? 
In “Chain of Thought Prompting Elicits Reasoning in Large Language Models,” we explore a prompting method for improving the re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Zero-Resource Machine Translation to Support New Languages in Google Translate]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/24-new-languages-google-translate.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/24-new-languages-google-translate.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:07:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Isaac Caswell and Ankur Bapna, Research Scientists, Google Translate  
Machine translation (MT) technology has made significant advances in recent years, as deep learning has been integrated with natural language processing (NLP). Performance on research benchmarks like WMT have soared, and translation services have improved in quality and expanded to include new languages. Nevertheless, while existing translation services cover languages spoken by the majority of people world wide, they only include around 100 languages in total, just over 1% of those actively spoken globally. Moreover, the languages that are currently represented are overwhelmingly European, largely overlooking regions of high linguistic diversity, like Africa and the Americas. 
 There are two key bottlenecks t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 Now Supports NitroTPM and UEFI Secure Boot]]></title>
        <id>43dd6308bbff890b8b4acc020ae36428fe8fba36</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-now-supports-nitrotpm-and-uefi-secure-boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In computing, Trusted Platform Module (TPM) technology is designed to provide hardware-based, security-related functions. A TPM chip is a secure crypto-processor that is designed to carry out cryptographic operations. There are three key advantages of using TPM technology. First, you can generate, store, and control access to encryption keys outside of the operating system. Second, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Monthly &#8211; May 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-05-11-open-source-monthly-may-2022-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-05-11-open-source-monthly-may-2022-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Open Sauced, GitHub&#8217;s Explore page, Hacktoberfest, and First Timers Only help folks discover open source projects. This monthly series–Open Source Monthly—will add to these efforts by helping: First-time contributors find the right project to contribute to Corporations and individuals find a new project to sponsor Open source maintainers gain more consistent contributors and sponsors [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第209話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3270296674344129439</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3270296674344129439"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Cool Features of Camunda Platform 8]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=53306</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/10-cool-features-of-camunda-platform-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T12:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how these features support better IT and business collaboration, more efficient process execution, and instant troubleshooting. 
The post 10 Cool Features of Camunda Platform 8 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiConf Europe Is Back: Join Us in Amsterdam or Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashiconf-europe-is-back-join-us-in-amsterdam-or-online"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years as a fully digital event, HashiConf Europe will once again return to Amsterdam on 20-22 June 2022. Here’s what you can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a brand new way to automate your Azure cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-a-brand-new-way-to-automate-your-azure-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/introducing-a-brand-new-way-to-automate-your-azure-cloud"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T13:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December of 2021, Red Hat and Microsoft announced Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hicham Mourad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=53158</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-optimize-3-9-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1. Check out the latest improvements and bug fixes with this release.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.9.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52734</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-automation-platform-7-18-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're pleased to announce the first alpha release of Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0. Learn about the improvements made in this release. 
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.18.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the HashiCorp Releases API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hashicorp-releases-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-hashicorp-releases-api"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Releases API is now available. This API is your one-stop shop for finding and viewing extended metadata about HashiCorp product releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – May 9, 2022]]></title>
        <id>8339454c5a5172e1abc7a324ae07df48c5db2a14</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-9-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Another week starts, and here’s a collection of the most significant AWS news from the previous seven days. This week is also the one-year anniversary of CloudFront Functions. It’s exciting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Applications at the Edge with HashiCorp Nomad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-applications-at-the-edge-with-hashicorp-nomad</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-applications-at-the-edge-with-hashicorp-nomad"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Nomad users in the gaming, farming, and biotech industries are orchestrating applications and devices at the edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting You Around the Globe]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52992</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/supporting-you-around-the-globe/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We now offer follow-the-sun support. Pick your preferred time zone and get expert help to resolve any issue.
The post Supporting You Around the Globe appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous Detection and Mitigation (CDM)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/continuous-detection-and-mitigation-cdm</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/continuous-detection-and-mitigation-cdm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>achenamp@redhat.com (Ajay Chenampara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Observability with OpenTelemetry and Consul Service Mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/improve-observability-with-opentelemetry-and-consul-service-mesh</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/improve-observability-with-opentelemetry-and-consul-service-mesh"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Add OpenTelemetry to your Java or .NET applications on Kubernetes and combine them with Consul service mesh metrics and traces for use with Prometheus and Jaeger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.06.05]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=63983</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2022-06-05/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2022.06.05 are here!
I am April Edwards and every week I try to bring you the latest updates from around the DevOps on Azure community.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2022.06.05 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 Highlights from  #CamundaSummit]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52738</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/camunda-platform-8-highlights-from-camundasummit/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 only just arrived, and there’s already a lot of excitement around this new release. Early adopters share their highlights.
The post Camunda Platform 8 Highlights from  #CamundaSummit appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dorothy Tso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Locomotion Skills Safely in the Real World]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/learning-locomotion-skills-safely-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/learning-locomotion-skills-safely-in.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:05:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jimmy (Tsung-Yen) Yang, Student Researcher, Robotics at Google 
The promise of deep reinforcement learning (RL) in solving complex, high-dimensional problems autonomously has attracted much interest in areas such as robotics, game playing, and self-driving cars. However, effectively training an RL policy requires exploring a large set of robot states and actions, including many that are not safe for the robot. This is a considerable risk, for example, when training a legged robot. Because such robots are inherently unstable, there is a high likelihood of the robot falling during learning, which could cause damage. 
The risk of damage can be mitigated to some extent by learning the control policy in computer simulation and then deploying it in the real world. However, this approac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable Self-Service Amazon EKS Deploys with CDK for Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/enable-self-service-aws-eks-deployments-with-cdk-for-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/enable-self-service-aws-eks-deployments-with-cdk-for-terraform"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how platform and developer teams can collaborate effectively using CDK for Terraform, Terraform Cloud, and Sentinel to safely deploy EKS workloads to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphWorld: Advances in Graph Benchmarking]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/graphworld-advances-in-graph.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/graphworld-advances-in-graph.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T21:24:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Palowitch and Anton Tsitsulin, Research Scientists, Google Research, Graph Mining team 
Graphs are very common representations of natural systems that have connected relational components, such as social networks, traffic infrastructure, molecules, and the internet. Graph neural networks (GNNs) are powerful machine learning (ML) models for graphs that leverage their inherent connections to incorporate context into predictions about items within the graph or the graph as a whole. GNNs have been effectively used to discover new drugs, help mathematicians prove theorems, detect misinformation, and improve the accuracy of arrival time predictions in Google Maps. 
A surge of interest in GNNs during the last decade has produced thousands of GNN variants, with hundreds introduced each year. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Run Tasks are Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-are-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-are-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate security, compliance, and cost management into the Terraform Cloud workflow using Run Tasks. Now generally available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Camunda Platform 8’s GraphQL API]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52506</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/getting-started-with-camunda-platform-8s-graphql-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting familiar with Camunda Platform 8? Learn why GraphQL is replacing REST API as the interface technology and how it works.
The post Getting Started with Camunda Platform 8’s GraphQL API appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpa: Automated Model-Parallel Deep Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/alpa-automated-model-parallel-deep.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/05/alpa-automated-model-parallel-deep.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T21:30:00.058Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zhuohan Li, Student Researcher, Google Research, and Yu Emma Wang, Senior Software Engineer, Google Core  
  Update — 2022/05/06: This post has been updated to provide additional details about the collaboration with external research partners in the development of Alpa.     
  
Over the last several years, the rapidly growing size of deep learning models has quickly exceeded the memory capacity of single accelerators. Earlier models like BERT (with a parameter size of < 1GB) can efficiently scale across accelerators by leveraging data parallelism in which model weights are duplicated across accelerators while only partitioning and distributing the training data. However, recent large models like GPT-3 (with a parameter size of 175GB) can only scale using model parallel training, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Applications and Servers at the Edge with Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-applications-and-servers-at-the-edge-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-applications-and-servers-at-the-edge-with-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous blog, Why 2022 will be the year for edge automation, we discussed the objective of edge solutions to bring resources closer to the end user or data source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – May 2, 2022]]></title>
        <id>650b6b46711677bb46ba175a4d35a12387ae3f6a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-may-2-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! Wow, May already! Here in the Pacific Northwest, spring is in full bloom and nature has emerged completely from her winter slumbers. It feels that way here at AWS, too, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Benchmark Your Camunda Platform 8 Cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=52174</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/05/how-to-benchmark-your-camunda-platform-8-cluster/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about our interesting journey with benchmarking and how to run a benchmark to figure out what your Zeebe cluster can do.
The post How to Benchmark Your Camunda Platform 8 Cluster appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extracting Skill-Centric State Abstractions from Value Functions]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/extracting-skill-centric-state.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/extracting-skill-centric-state.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T17:02:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dhruv Shah, Intern, and Brian Ichter, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google 
Advances in reinforcement learning (RL) for robotics have enabled robotic agents to perform increasingly complex tasks in challenging environments. Recent results show that robots can learn to fold clothes, dexterously manipulate a rubik’s cube, sort objects by color, navigate complex environments and walk on difficult, uneven terrain. But "short-horizon" tasks such as these, which require very little long-term planning and provide immediate failure feedback, are relatively easy to train compared to many tasks that may confront a robot in a real-world setting. Unfortunately, scaling such short-horizon skills to the abstract, long horizons of real-world tasks is difficult. For example, how would one trai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon MSK Serverless Now Generally Available–No More Capacity Planning for Your Managed Kafka Clusters]]></title>
        <id>305f11c2d5084adabac03bcf0422320fe63911fe</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-msk-serverless-now-generally-available-no-more-capacity-planning-for-your-managed-kafka-clusters/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T18:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are making Amazon MSK Serverless generally available to help you reduce even more the operational overhead of managing an Apache Kafka cluster by offloading the capacity planning and scaling to AWS. In May 2019, we launched Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka to help our customers stream data using Apache Kafka. Apache Kafka […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Storage-Optimized Amazon EC2 Instances (I4i) Powered by Intel Xeon Scalable (Ice Lake) Processors]]></title>
        <id>6d11b906558df90e167a43676ae4febc00ab2a71</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-storage-optimized-amazon-ec2-instances-i4i-powered-by-intel-xeon-scalable-ice-lake-processors/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years we have released multiple generations of storage-optimized Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances including the HS1 (2012) , D2 (2015), I2 (2013) , I3 (2017), I3en (2019), D3/D3en (2020), and Im4gn/Is4gen (2021). These instances are used to host high-performance real-time relational databases, distributed file systems, data warehouses, key-value stores, and more. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.2 Brings New Cross-Namespace Controls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-2-brings-new-cross-namespace-controls</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-api-gateway-0-2-brings-new-cross-namespace-controls"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul API Gateway 0.2, now generally available, enhances the gateway’s traffic management capabilities by adding cross-namespace reference policy enforcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2022 HashiCorp SI & Reseller Partner Network Award Winners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2022-hashicorp-si-reseller-partner-network-award-winners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-2022-hashicorp-si-reseller-partner-network-award-winners"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 HashiCorp Partner Network Awards for Systems Integrators and Resellers have been announced. Find out who the winners are in our five categories this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第208話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496898209741</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496898209741"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Conversations: Uwe Koch, HDI Insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=51911</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/04/community-conversations-uwe-koch-hdi-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the first installment of our Community Conversations blog series with Uwe Koch, a Camunda Champion and enterprise architect.
The post Community Conversations: Uwe Koch, HDI Insurance appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolution of ML Fact Store]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5941d3231762</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/evolution-of-ml-fact-store-5941d3231762?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T20:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Vivek Kaushal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Wavelength Zone in Toronto – The First in Canada]]></title>
        <id>0536fdf5007395f77dfe25feb6e76bd15622ea6a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-wavelength-zone-in-toronto-the-first-in-canada/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T15:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless communication has put us closer to each other. 5G networks increase the reach of what we can achieve to new use cases that need end-to-end low latency. With AWS Wavelength, you can deploy AWS compute and storage services within telecommunications providers’ data centers at the edge of the 5G networks. Your applications can then […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ICLR 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/google-at-iclr-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/google-at-iclr-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T19:46:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cat Armato and Callan Hajosy, Program Managers 
The 10th International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR 2022) kicks off this week, bringing together researchers, entrepreneurs, engineers and students alike to discuss and explore the rapidly advancing field of deep learning. Entirely virtual this year, ICLR 2022 offers conference and workshop tracks that present some of the latest research in deep learning and its applications to areas ranging from computer vision, speech recognition and text understanding to robotics, computational biology, and more. 
 As a Platinum Sponsor of ICLR 2022 and Champion DEI Action Fund contributor, Google will have a robust presence with nearly 100 accepted publications and extensive participation on organizing committees and in workshops…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – April 25, 2022]]></title>
        <id>0fb329a009aafc65690dcbba4bb516553ed47289</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-april-25-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! The first in this year’s series of AWS Summits took place in San Francisco this past week and we had a bunch of great announcements. Let’s take a closer look… […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Cloud Search to Streamline Workspace Search and Switching]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-cloud-search-to-streamline-workspace-search-and-switching</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-terraform-cloud-search-to-streamline-workspace-search-and-switching"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new search capability available for all tiers in Terraform Cloud will allow you to easily switch between workspaces and organizations in the UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-driven remediation with systemd and Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-remediation-with-systemd-and-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/event-driven-remediation-with-systemd-and-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform can assist you here with not only keeping your infrastructure in check, but also giving your teams the peace of mind that systems are running as they should.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pix2Seq: A New Language Interface for Object Detection]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pix2seq-new-language-interface-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/04/pix2seq-new-language-interface-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T20:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ting Chen and David Fleet, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
Object detection is a long-standing computer vision task that attempts to recognize and localize all objects of interest in an image. The complexity arises when trying to identify or localize all object instances while also avoiding duplication. Existing approaches, like Faster R-CNN and DETR, are carefully designed and highly customized in the choice of architecture and loss function. This specialization of existing systems has created two major barriers: (1) it adds complexity in tuning and training the different parts of the system (e.g., region proposal network, graph matching with GIOU loss, etc.), and (2), it can reduce the ability of a model to generalize, necessitating a redesign of the model for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.12 Hardens Security on Kubernetes with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-12-hardens-security-on-kubernetes-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-12-hardens-security-on-kubernetes-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This release strengthens zero trust security architecture by leveraging HashiCorp Vault to reduce secrets sprawl and automate server TLS certificate rotation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>