<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-19T00:39:43.978Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-19T00:39:43.978Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Permutation-Invariant Neural Networks for Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/permutation-invariant-neural-networks.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/permutation-invariant-neural-networks.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:07:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by David Ha, Staff Research Scientist and Yujin Tang, Research Software Engineer, Google Research, Tokyo      “The brain is able to use information coming from the skin as if it were coming from the eyes. We don’t see with the eyes or hear with the ears, these are just the receptors, seeing and hearing in fact goes on in the brain.”
— Paul Bach-y-Rita1
-->  

  
“The brain is able to use information coming from the skin as if it were coming from the eyes. We don’t see with the eyes or hear with the ears, these are just the receptors, seeing and hearing in fact goes on in the brain.”
  
— Paul Bach-y-Rita1
  
 People have the amazing ability to use one sensory modality (e.g., touch) to supply environmental information normally gathered by another sense (e.g., vision). This adaptive a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PagerDuty, Palo Alto Networks, and Splunk Among New Verified Terraform Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pagerduty-palo-alto-networks-and-splunk-among-new-verified-terraform-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/pagerduty-palo-alto-networks-and-splunk-among-new-verified-terraform-providers"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We welcome 17 new verified providers to the growing HashiCorp Terraform ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 advanced workflow automation features with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-18-7-advanced-workflow-automation-features-with-github-actions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-18-7-advanced-workflow-automation-features-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T17:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out some advanced automation and CI/CD capabilities you can use today with GitHub Actions on any GitHub account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic puts employee safety first with COVID-19 vaccine mandate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastic-puts-employee-safety-first-with-covid-19-vaccine-mandate</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastic-puts-employee-safety-first-with-covid-19-vaccine-mandate"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic CEO Shay Banon explains how the company decided on a vaccine mandate for in-office employees and why: “We’re putting the safety and comfort of our employees first.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shay Banon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic puts employee safety first with COVID-19 vaccine mandate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastic-puts-employee-safety-first-with-covid-19-vaccine-mandate</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-elastic-puts-employee-safety-first-with-covid-19-vaccine-mandate"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
This is an internal email I sent that outlines our approach to vaccine mandates and we are sharing a version here to let everyone know the actions we are taking to ensure the safety and well-being of our employees and community.
We've thought long and hard about our approach to vaccine mandates. Like most of our decisions on managing COVID-19 to date, we're putting the safety and comfort of our employees first. At the same time,  we did not want to be the first out of the gate and rush into decisions. 
We can all agree that while things are improving globally, we're still seeing concerning developments with new and mutant variants that we feel a strong need to support vaccination programs. After a lot of work by our workplace safety, legal, and HR teams, who carried out very detailed due…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shay Banon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: The One with the SSO Implementation in Camunda]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=37324</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/qa-the-one-with-the-sso-implementation-in-camunda/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering how to make a SSO implementation work in Camunda? Have no fear. The answer you've been waiting for is here! 
The post Q&A: The One with the SSO Implementation in Camunda appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation for the cloud: Cloud Field Day 12 recap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-for-the-cloud-cloud-field-day-12-recap</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-for-the-cloud-cloud-field-day-12-recap"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently had the opportunity to present our Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform cloud strategy at Cloud Field Day 12. 
Cloud Field Day 12 was a three day event that focused on the impact of cloud on enterprise IT. As a presenter, you can use any combination of slides and live demos to foster a discussion with a group of thought leaders. This roundtable included people from many different companies, skill sets, backgrounds and favorite tools. Check out the Cloud Field Day website to see the delegate panel, their backgrounds and Twitter handles. I quite enjoyed, and preferred, the conversational tone of Cloud Field Day, and the delegates who asked questions during the demo made it a lot more interactive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic on Microsoft Azure adds the power of search for accelerated data insights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-on-microsoft-azure-adds-the-power-of-search-for-accelerated-data-insights</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-on-microsoft-azure-adds-the-power-of-search-for-accelerated-data-insights"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn more about deploying Elastic on Microsoft Azure to quickly turn data into valuable insights with end-to-end visibility to monitor and secure your environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Nairn,Osman Ishaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic on Microsoft Azure adds the power of search for accelerated data insights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-on-microsoft-azure-adds-the-power-of-search-for-accelerated-data-insights</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-on-microsoft-azure-adds-the-power-of-search-for-accelerated-data-insights"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
With Elastic Cloud and Microsoft Azure, you can remove data silos and uncover insights across your Microsoft Azure and on-premises environments. DevOps and IT practitioners can get the most out of their Azure infrastructure and data with Elastic, which adds the power of search to help teams monitor, manage, and protect environments. With Elastic on Azure, practitioners can analyze data logs and events to obtain insights, while DevSecOps and other security engineers can protect against threats by layering endpoint security and security event monitoring.
In this blog, we will review how to leverage end-to-end visibility across your Azure environment. We will also cover new enhancements to the Elasticsearch native integration on Azure offering, and subscription options. 
Adding value to you…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Nairn,Osman Ishaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.5.7 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/18/spring-boot-2-5-7-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/18/spring-boot-2-5-7-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T11:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.5.7 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 35 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.4.13 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/18/spring-boot-2-4-13-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/18/spring-boot-2-4-13-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.4.13 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 26 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
End of OSS Support

2.4.x has now reached the end of its OSS support period and regular releases will no longer be made. If you are still on this version, please consider upgrading at your earliest convenience. If you cannot upgrade at this time, commercial support is available.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predicting Text Readability from Scrolling Interactions]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/predicting-text-readability-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/predicting-text-readability-from.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T22:31:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sian Gooding, Intern, Google Research  
Illiteracy affects at least 773 million people globally, both young and old. For these individuals, reading information from unfamiliar sources or on unfamiliar topics can be extremely difficult. Unfortunately, these inequalities have been further magnified by the global pandemic as a result of unequal access to education in reading and writing. In fact, UNESCO reports that over 100 million children are falling behind the minimum proficiency level in reading due to COVID-related school closures.  
 With increasing world-wide access to technology, reading on a device, such as a tablet or phone, has largely taken the place of traditional formats. This provides a unique opportunity to observe reading interactions, e.g., how a reader scrolls th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scalable, Cost-Effective Disaster Recovery in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>111da60866f9a347924784f64e58e320956b900b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/scalable-cost-effective-disaster-recovery-in-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T20:39:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should disaster strike, business continuity can require more than just periodic data backups. A full recovery that meets the business’s recovery time objectives (RTOs) must also include the infrastructure, operating systems, applications, and configurations used to process their data. The growing threats of ransomware highlight the need to be able to perform a full point-in-time […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 4.3.4 and 4.2.8 available now!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/17/spring-batch-4-3-4-and-4-2-8-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/17/spring-batch-4-3-4-and-4-2-8-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that Spring Batch 4.2.8 and 4.3.4 have been released and are available now from Maven Central repository. These patch releases come with a number of bug fixes and dependency updates. You can find the complete change logs here: 4.2.8 and 4.3.4.

I would like to thank all contributors who had a role in these releases!

Spring Batch Home | Source on GitHub | Reference Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RLiable: Towards Reliable Evaluation & Reporting in Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/rliable-towards-reliable-evaluation.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/rliable-towards-reliable-evaluation.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T18:32:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rishabh Agarwal, Research Scientist and Pablo Samuel Castro, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team   
 Reinforcement learning (RL) is an area of machine learning that focuses on learning from experiences to solve decision making tasks. While the field of RL has made great progress, resulting in impressive empirical results on complex tasks, such as playing video games, flying stratospheric balloons and designing hardware chips, it is becoming increasingly apparent that the current standards for empirical evaluation might give a false sense of fast scientific progress while slowing it down. 
  To that end, in “Deep RL at the Edge of the Statistical Precipice”, accepted as an oral presentation at NeurIPS 2021, we discuss how statistical uncertainty of results needs t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub’s developer-first approach to content moderation]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-17-githubs-developer-first-approach-to-content-moderation/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-17-githubs-developer-first-approach-to-content-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T17:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub puts the needs of developers at the core of our content moderation policies. Learn more about our approach and how you can contribute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Vault 1.9]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-9</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-9"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.9 can act as an OIDC provider, includes general availability of a key management secrets engine for Google Cloud, and updates to Transform, Namespaces, and the UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Service Mesh on Amazon ECS Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-on-amazon-ecs-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-on-amazon-ecs-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul service mesh on Amazon ECS is now generally available and ready for production environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Netflix version 2.2.10.RELEASE is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/17/spring-cloud-netflix-version-2-2-10-release-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/17/spring-cloud-netflix-version-2-2-10-release-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that Spring Cloud Netflix version 2.2.10.RELEASE has been released.

This is primarily a security release that fixes the CVE-2021-22053. 

Applications using both spring-cloud-netflix-hystrix-dashboard and spring-boot-starter-thymeleaf exposed a way to execute code submitted within the request URI path during the resolution of view templates. When a request was made at /hystrix/monitor;[user-provided-data], the path elements following hystrix/monitor were being evaluated as SpringEL expressions, which could lead to code execution.

This release fixes the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How two Elastic Community Contributor award winners became amazing Elasticians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-two-elastic-community-contributor-award-winners-became-amazing-elasticians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-two-elastic-community-contributor-award-winners-became-amazing-elasticians"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We created the Elastic Contributor Program to recognize and reward folks for sharing code, organizing and presenting at community events, and for writing about Elastic. Two Elastic Contributor winners are now Elasticians. This is their journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How two Elastic Community Contributor award winners became amazing Elasticians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-two-elastic-community-contributor-award-winners-became-amazing-elasticians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-how-two-elastic-community-contributor-award-winners-became-amazing-elasticians"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Every year Elastic recognizes exceptional community members from across the globe with the Elastic Contributor Program. These Elastic champions have earned points for organizing events, delivering presentations, contributing code, writing or translating articles, and creating video tutorials -- all to advance in their careers. 
Two of our recent Elastic Contributor Program winners took their love of Elastic and our technology to the next level by becoming full-time Elasticians. We couldn’t be prouder to share the journeys of Peter Steenbergen and Philipp Kahr, from contributor to Elastician.
Peter Steenbergen, Senior Solutions Architect, Netherlands 
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt47808c58035e16ae/618c608700783f138785de70/elastic-blog-Peter-Steenbergen.jpg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: @Controllers: WebSockets]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/17/spring-tips-controllers-websockets</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/17/spring-tips-controllers-websockets"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment of Spring Tips, we’re going to resume our series on Spring’s @Controller annotation, this time diving into Spring’s WebSocket support.

The code is here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Never Told Anyone]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2543/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2543/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/never_told_anyone.png" title="Even if you said you were an employee of the website, if you asked for my password, I'd tell you." alt="Even if you said you were an employee of the website, if you asked for my password, I'd tell you." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL global ID migration update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-16-graphql-global-id-migration-update/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-16-graphql-global-id-migration-update/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T21:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All newly created GraphQL objects now have IDs that conform to a new format, which we refer to as "next IDs." Learn how to migrate older IDs to the new format and why we're making the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blue-teaming for Exiv2: adding custom CodeQL queries to code scanning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-16-adding-custom-codeql-queries-code-scanning/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-16-adding-custom-codeql-queries-code-scanning/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T18:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Exiv2 team tightened our security by enabling GitHub’s code scanning feature and adding custom queries tailored to the Exiv2 code base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of HashiCorp Nomad 1.2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-nomad-1-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-nomad-1-2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.2 introduces Nomad Pack, which simplifies application deployment and lifecycle management on Nomad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - November 16th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/16/this-week-in-spring-november-16th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/16/this-week-in-spring-november-16th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Can you believe it’s nearly December 2021? I’m still getting used to the idea that we’re already in 2021 and now the year’s nearly behind us! Stop the world, I want off! Time’s flying. 

I’ve been up to my eyeballs in Spring Tips video production. I can’t wait for you to see tomorrow’s installment (@SpringTipsLive)!

We’ve also got some great podcast interviews lined up. As always, new episodes drop on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, etc., every Thursday night (California time)/Friday (for most of the world). Don’t miss it (@BootifulPodcast)!

You could also just check out my blog (joshlong.com) for the upcoming appearances, podcasts, Spring Tips videos, etc. The trouble is that the blog is otherwise pretty boring. My boring content notwithstanding, it’s a plain l’il page on t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.6.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/16/spring-security-5-6-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/16/spring-security-5-6-0-released"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, it is my pleasure to announce the general availability of Spring Security 5.6. This release is the result of the work that went into 5.6.0-M1, 5.6.0-M2, 5.6.0-M3, 5.6.0-RC1, and 5.6.0.



You can find the highlights of 5.6 in the What’s new section of the Spring Security reference.



As always, we look forward to hearing your feedback!



Project Site |
Reference
| Help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2021 State of the Octoverse]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-16-the-2021-state-of-the-octoverse/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-16-the-2021-state-of-the-octoverse/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T14:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The State of the Octoverse analyzes data from millions of developers &#038; repos to share trends across working habits, productivity, and career satisfaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily share Kibana assets with elastic-package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/easily-share-kibana-assets-with-elastic-package</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/easily-share-kibana-assets-with-elastic-package"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic-package is the official developer tool, used to create your own integrations that will be run by Elastic Agent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily share Kibana assets with elastic-package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/easily-share-kibana-assets-with-elastic-package</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/easily-share-kibana-assets-with-elastic-package"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
An invaluable way to share best practices across your company, teams, and network is by sharing assets. We will present the export option of the elastic-package tool that will make your asset sharing as easy as ABC. In this guide you will walk through the elastic-package export option and learn about sharing and spreading useful dashboards.
Instead of reinventing the wheel, try to repurpose the work that has already been done. Some Kibana dashboards have already been created for you, but why not share yours as well.
Dashboard creation and export with elastic-package
To begin we will need to locally start a full elastic stack in order to access Kibana UI.
julienlind@MacBook-Pro elastic-package % elastic-package stack up -d -v,
“stack up” will start all needed containers, the -d option wil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Intuit Managed 19M Processes During Peak Tax, Accounting Seasons]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=36771</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/how-intuit-managed-19m-processes-during-peak-tax-accounting-seasons/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dig into how Intuit used workflow automation to manage 396 transactions per second during its most demanding months.
The post How Intuit Managed 19M Processes During Peak Tax, Accounting Seasons appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Connors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub&#8217;s commitment to npm ecosystem security]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-15-githubs-commitment-to-npm-ecosystem-security/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-15-githubs-commitment-to-npm-ecosystem-security/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T23:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're sharing details of recent incidents on the npm registry, our investigations, and how we’re continuing to invest in the security of npm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic brings speed, scale, and ease to real-time situational awareness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/elastic-speed-scale-ease-to-real-time-situational-awareness-rtsa-command-control</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/elastic-speed-scale-ease-to-real-time-situational-awareness-rtsa-command-control"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T22:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Q&A, find out how real-time situational awareness played a significant role in a former Air Operations Center operator’s daily workflow, and how technology speeds up the OODA loop in mission critical scenarios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzzanna Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Elastic brings speed, scale, and ease to real-time situational awareness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/elastic-speed-scale-ease-to-real-time-situational-awareness-rtsa-command-control</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/elastic-speed-scale-ease-to-real-time-situational-awareness-rtsa-command-control"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T22:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Real-time situational awareness (RTSA) done right provides complete, actionable information about what is going on around the operating environment at the moment and enables accurate decision making and data sharing easily, rapidly, and securely. RTSA has real world impact on a number of use cases, including network management and cybersecurity, supply chain management, military operations, public safety and emergency response, port of entry and logistics security, and campus or facility security.
In this blog, we explore what RTSA done right means to someone who has had boots on the digital ground – a former command and control (C2) system operator.
RTSA from the C2 operator’s perspective
Q: As a former operator in an Air Operations Center (AOC) environment, what are the essential thing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzzanna Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetNet-2: Deep Learning for 12-Hour Precipitation Forecasting]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/metnet-2-deep-learning-for-12-hour.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/metnet-2-deep-learning-for-12-hour.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T21:56:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nal Kalchbrenner and Lasse Espeholt, Google Research  
Deep learning has successfully been applied to a wide range of important challenges, such as cancer prevention and increasing accessibility. The application of deep learning models to weather forecasts can be relevant to people on a day-to-day basis, from helping people plan their day to managing food production, transportation systems, or the energy grid. Weather forecasts typically rely on traditional physics-based techniques powered by the world’s largest supercomputers. Such methods are constrained by high computational requirements and are sensitive to approximations of the physical laws on which they are based.  
 Deep learning offers a new approach to computing forecasts. Rather than incorporating explicit physical law…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from Git 2.34]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-15-highlights-from-git-2-34/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-15-highlights-from-git-2-34/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To celebrate this most recent release, here's GitHub's look at some of the most interesting features and changes introduced since last time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building confidence in a decision]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8705834e6fd8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/building-confidence-in-a-decision-8705834e6fd8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T16:20:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Tingley with Wenjing Zheng, Simon Ejdemyr, Stephanie Lane, Michael Lindon, and Colin McFarland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation controller workflow deployment as code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-controller-workflow-deployment-as-code</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automation-controller-workflow-deployment-as-code"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background: The Automation Controller Collection
 
The Automation Controller Collection allows Ansible Playbooks to automate the interaction with automation controller. For example, manually interacting via the Web-based UI or the API can now be automated just as the targets it manages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daylight Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2542/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2542/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/daylight_calendar.png" title="Could be worse. In some towns north of here, it's already December, and the 21st will last for nearly a week." alt="Could be worse. In some towns north of here, it's already December, and the 21st will last for nearly a week." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · October 2021 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-12-release-radar-oct-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-12-release-radar-oct-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T22:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What an incredible month it&#8217;s been for GitHub and our communities. Whilst we&#8217;ve been busy with GitHub Universe, our communities have been busy coding. It&#8217;s been a successful year for Hacktoberfest, with many first-time contributors]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the latest AWS Heroes – November 2021]]></title>
        <id>97d2f389c7c961dc211c93272540ec3cec3578c2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/meet-the-latest-aws-heroes-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T21:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is an exciting time of year, with AWS re:Invent right around the corner. As we reflect back on 2021, we continue to be impressed by the way AWS communities support one-another across intersecting journeys to expand technical skills. At the center of these communities are impactful leaders who go above and beyond to create […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Open Source Vibrotactile Haptics Platform for On-Body Applications]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/an-open-source-vibrotactile-haptics.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/an-open-source-vibrotactile-haptics.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T19:07:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Artem Dementyev, Hardware Engineer, Google Research 
Most wearable smart devices and mobile phones have the means to communicate with the user through tactile feedback, enabling applications from simple notifications to sensory substitution for accessibility. Typically, they accomplish this using vibrotactile actuators, which are small electric vibration motors. However, designing a haptic system that is well-targeted and effective for a given task requires experimentation with the number of actuators and their locations in the device, yet most practical applications require standalone on-body devices and integration into small form factors. This combination of factors can be difficult to address outside of a laboratory as integrating these systems can be quite time-consuming and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from GitHub&#8217;s security roadmap at Universe 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-12-highlights-github-security-roadmap-universe-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-12-highlights-github-security-roadmap-universe-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T17:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During Universe, we received a number of security questions ranging from our strategy to our advisories. Here's what we've got planned!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第197話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496597544962</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496597544962"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.1.0 goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/12/spring-data-2021-1-0-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/12/spring-data-2021-1-0-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data 2021.1.0.

These are the most important changes:


  
Upgrade to Querydsl 5.0

  
Support jMolecules’ @Identity Annotation for Identifiers

  
Fluent Query API for Querydsl and Query-by-Example

  
Deprecated RxJava 2 Support

  
MongoDB @DocumentReference, schema derivation for encrypted fields, and MongoDB 5.0 Time Series support

  
Redis 6.2 support

  
Support for streaming large result sets in Spring Data JDBC, Projections, and SQL Builder refinements around conditions, JOINs, and SELECT projections

  
Support for Impersonation and support for Querydsl in Neo4j


You can find a more detailed description in the Release Notes.
This is the first time we offer release notes in this format, so …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.0.7 and 2020.0.15 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/12/spring-data-2021-0-7-and-2020-0-15-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/12/spring-data-2021-0-7-and-2020-0-15-released"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data 2021.0.7 and 2020.0.15 service releases.

Both releases are built on top of Spring Framework 5.3.13. For your convenience, you can consume Spring Data 2021.0.7 and 2020.0.15 through the upcoming Spring Boot releases, 2.5.7 and 2.4.13, respectively. 

2020.0.x reached its end of life and will no longer be part of regular OSS releases. If you are still on this version, please consider upgrading at your earliest convenience.

Both service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.

To round things off, here are the links to the artifacts, change logs, and documentation:
2021.0.7


  
Spring Data Commons 2.5.7 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.2.7 -…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic introduces the new Customer Success website to accelerate user success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-introduces-the-new-customer-success-website-to-accelerate-user-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-introduces-the-new-customer-success-website-to-accelerate-user-success"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customer success is at the foundation of the Elastic journey. Our new Customer Success website brings together technical resources, best practices, expert knowledge, and a predefined Customer Success approach to guide users on their journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen Ndlovu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic introduces the new Customer Success website to accelerate user success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-introduces-the-new-customer-success-website-to-accelerate-user-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-introduces-the-new-customer-success-website-to-accelerate-user-success"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic introduces our new Customer Success website that brings together technical resources, best practices, expert knowledge, and a predefined Customer Success approach to guide users on their onboarding journey.
We love to hear how customers are using Elastic to solve business challenges and innovate. Ensuring our users' success with our products starts with providing a carefully curated hub of resources from getting started basics to migration how-to guides. 
Our commitment to your success
The new Customer Success website is designed to give all Elastic users the technical resources they need to start using Elastic solutions to simplify and expedite work and understand how to accelerate their use-cases. The hub is divided into four key areas: 

Data Ingestion Leading Practices Does y…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen Ndlovu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.11.12]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62801</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-11-12/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T10:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back! I am Jay Gordon and every week I try to bring you the latest updates from around the DevOps on Azure community. If you have a post you’d like to have me include, I am always listening. You can reach out on Twitter or LinkedIn and I will be sure to share your latest post with the community.
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.11.12 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – EC2 Instances (G5) with NVIDIA A10G Tensor Core GPUs]]></title>
        <id>11ddd41744e4e62813603bd93b2207ce7d47f95a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-ec2-instances-g5-with-nvidia-a10g-tensor-core-gpus/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T01:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two years ago I told you about the then-new G4 instances, which featured up to eight NVIDIA T4 Tensor Core GPUs. These instances were designed to give you cost-effective GPU power for machine learning inference and graphics-intensive applications. Today I am happy to tell you about the new G5 instances, which feature up to eight […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Occam]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2541/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2541/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/occam.png" title="Oh no, Murphy just picked up the razor." alt="Oh no, Murphy just picked up the razor." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Better Future Predictions by Watching Unlabeled Videos]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/making-better-future-predictions-by.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/making-better-future-predictions-by.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T20:26:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dave Epstein, Student Researcher and Chen Sun, Staff Research Scientist, Google Research   
Machine learning (ML) agents are increasingly deployed in the real world to make decisions and assist people in their daily lives. Making reasonable predictions about the future at varying timescales is one of the most important capabilities for such agents because it enables them to predict changes in the world around them, including other agents’ behaviors, and plan how to act next. Importantly, successful future prediction requires both capturing meaningful transitions in the environment (e.g., dough transforming into bread) and adapting to how transitions unfold over time in order to make decisions.  
  
Previous work in future prediction from visual observations has largely been const…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: JMS and Messaging legend, HornetQ and Artemis cofounder, Clebert Suconic]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/11/a-bootiful-podcast-jms-and-messaging-legend-hornetq-and-artemis-cofounder-clebert-suconic</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/11/a-bootiful-podcast-jms-and-messaging-legend-hornetq-and-artemis-cofounder-clebert-suconic"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Apache Artemis and messaging legend Clebert Suconic (@clebertsuconic). Check out ArtemisCloud.io for easy Kubernetes deployments of Apache Artemis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Variable Sets Beta Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-variable-sets-beta-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-variable-sets-beta-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud variable sets let you simplify the management of reusable variables across an entire organization. This feature is now available in public beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Elastic, Veterans Day is a family affair]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/category/culture-veterans-day-at-elastic-is-a-family-affair</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/category/culture-veterans-day-at-elastic-is-a-family-affair"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the United States celebrates Veterans Day and honors those who’ve served, we caught up with Elasticians with strong ties to military life. Read on to learn more about their lives, work, and how Elastic supports their families.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Elastic, Veterans Day is a family affair]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/category/culture-veterans-day-at-elastic-is-a-family-affair</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/category/culture-veterans-day-at-elastic-is-a-family-affair"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic is proud to employ veterans and their families around the world. As the United States celebrates Veterans Day and honors those who’ve served, we caught up with some of our team members who have strong familial ties to military members. Read on to learn more about their lives, how they got involved in the tech world, and how Elastic supports their families and those like them with benefits like military leave and training opportunities.
Finding a new career
“It’s amazing to see how many people at Elastic have a connection to the military,” says Hilary Arnwine, Training Ops Coordinator at Elastic. 
Hilary started her career in healthcare management and administration. “My focus was on long-term assisted living and Alzheimer's communities. When I had twins, I became a stay at home m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating execution environment image builds with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-execution-environment-image-builds-with-github-actions</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/automating-execution-environment-image-builds-with-github-actions"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Automation Platform 2 leverages containers dubbed automation execution environments which bundle in collection, python and platform dependencies to provide predictable, self-contained automation spaces that can be easily distributed across an organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmcnaugh@redhat.com (Colin McNaughton)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.13 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/11/spring-framework-5-3-13-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/11/spring-framework-5-3-13-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T08:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.13 is available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.13 includes 16 fixes and improvements.

Stay tuned for follow-up Spring Boot releases next week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Amazing Camunda Champions Loading…]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=36489</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/more-amazing-camunda-champions-loading/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our next cohort of Camunda Champions are about to begin. Take a look at our new recruits and learn how to join the program.
The post More Amazing Camunda Champions Loading… appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Buchholz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measure and Improve Your Application Resilience with AWS Resilience Hub]]></title>
        <id>4e23000e82db393ac49e2bb44751515e88eb75a6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/monitor-and-improve-your-application-resiliency-with-resilience-hub/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T23:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am excited to announce the immediate availability of AWS Resilience Hub, a new AWS service designed to help you define, track, and manage the resilience of your applications. You are building and managing resilient applications to serve your customers. Building distributed systems is hard; maintaining them in an operational state is even harder. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: My Reactive Summit 2021 Day 2 Keynote with James Ward]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/10/spring-tips-my-reactive-summit-2021-day-2-keynote-with-james-ward</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/10/spring-tips-my-reactive-summit-2021-day-2-keynote-with-james-ward"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of Spring Tips! In this installment, I wanted to share with you the keynote that Google’s James Ward (@_JamesWard) and I put together for the recent Reactive Summit 2021 event, titled: “Reactive, Here and There.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model Ensembles Are Faster Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/model-ensembles-are-faster-than-you.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/model-ensembles-are-faster-than-you.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:03:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Xiaofang Wang, Intern and Yair Alon (prev. Movshovitz-Attias), Software Engineer, Google Research    
When building a deep model for a new machine learning application, researchers often begin with existing network architectures, such as ResNets or EfficientNets. If the initial model’s accuracy isn’t high enough, a larger model may be a tempting alternative, but may not actually be the best solution for the task at hand. Instead, better performance potentially could be achieved by designing a new model that is optimized for the task. However, such efforts can be challenging and usually require considerable resources.  
In “Wisdom of Committees: An Overlooked Approach to Faster and More Accurate Models”,  we discuss model ensembles and a subset called model cascades, both of which…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 unique software collaboration features in GitHub Discussions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2021-11-10-7-unique-software-collaboration-features-in-github-discussions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-11-10-7-unique-software-collaboration-features-in-github-discussions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are a few ways our teams use GitHub Discussions internally to build community, simplify workflows, and get key insights into our work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud Wins 2021 CRN Tech Innovator Award]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-cloud-wins-2021-crn-tech-innovator-award</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-cloud-wins-2021-crn-tech-innovator-award"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud takes home the prize in the DevOps Platforms category of the 2021 CRN Tech Innovator Awards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.15.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-15-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-15-2-released"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.15.2 has been released. Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in Elasticsearch, Kibana, Logstash, Beats, APM, Elastic Enterprise Search, Elastic Security, and ECK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Bavey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.15.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-15-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-15-2-released"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 7.15.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
The 7.15.2 patch contains fixes and small enhancements for the stack
For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
7.15.2 release notes
Elastic Stack

Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash

Elastic Enterprise Search

Enterprise Search

Elastic Observability

APM

Elastic Security

Elastic Security solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Bavey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to increase website engagement with search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-increase-website-engagement-with-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-increase-website-engagement-with-search"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Website visitors have high expectations for search. Make sure your search experiences meet (and beat) those expectations, boosting engagement, conversion, and user satisfaction along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Meiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to increase website engagement with search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-increase-website-engagement-with-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-increase-website-engagement-with-search"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The search experience on your website is often the key driver of visitor satisfaction. Even on well-designed, well-organized websites, visitors frequently resort to search to find the exact products, services, content, and information they need. In fact, many visitors go immediately to the search box. The quality of search results they get back, and the ease with which they can customize and filter those results, can play an outsized role in engagement, conversion, and customer loyalty. 

Why “good enough” search usually isn’t good enough
It’s just a search box, right? How important could it really be? Turns out, pretty important.
According to a recent study, nearly a third of website visitors start with search. Customers are also willing to pay a 16% premium on products and services for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Meiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why developers are putting customer experience first]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-developers-are-putting-customer-experience-first</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-developers-are-putting-customer-experience-first"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital experiences have lifted expectations around service delivery for everyone. Devs are now front and center to the customer experience (CX). Embrace being CX-first, because being closer to the customer makes you more important to the business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Wen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why developers are putting customer experience first]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-developers-are-putting-customer-experience-first</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/why-developers-are-putting-customer-experience-first"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
User digital experience has transformed expectations around how technology and services are delivered, further bringing developers front and center into the customer experience (CX) realm.
More recently, the inability to meet in person has forced us to rely more heavily on technology to assist with our basic household and business needs: ordering groceries online and food delivery, scheduling appointments, streaming entertainment services, and hosting virtual meetings and events. As a result, developers are in a position to directly impact and improve the day-to-day digital experience that customers expect. And developers that proactively move toward a customer-first approach and embrace that responsibility for CX will emerge as leaders in their field.
Customer expectations raise the bar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Wen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TTSLTSWBD]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2540/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2540/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/ttsltswbd.png" title="Tomorrow's sessions will be entirely devoted to sewing machine rotary hooks." alt="Tomorrow's sessions will be entirely devoted to sewing machine rotary hooks." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - November 9th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/09/this-week-in-spring-november-9th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/09/this-week-in-spring-november-9th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How’re you doin’? I’m doing alright! It’s been raining cats and dogs here in San Francisco. California, the state where I live, dearly needs the rain, so it’s a positive, I suppose. But it still feels miserable. Between the daylights savings time shortening the daylight significantly and the rain, it’s a gloomy kind of day. At least there’s a lot of good stuff to read! Let’s dive right into it! 


  
Bootiful Podcast: Legend, Dutchess founder, Devoxx4Kids contributor, and fellow Java Champion Linda van der Pal

  
Full Stack Java with React, Spring Boot, and JHipster

  
Hello, Coherence — Bootiful Spring  by Oracle’s Gunnar Hillert, a legend.

  
Check out the videos from the recent Reactive Summit. I was the emcee and the day two keynoter, along with my friend and Google’s James Ward.

  
Running Spring Boot Apps? Start Tracing with OpenTelemetry in Minutes!

  
Spring Cloud 2021.0.0-RC1 (codename Jubilee) Has Been Released

  
Spring Cloud Data Flow 2.8.4 and 2.9.1 Released

  
Spring Cloud Gateway versions 2.2.10.RELEASE and 3.0.5 are now available

  
Spring Tips: @Controllers: Give HTTP a REST

  
The power of component scanning in Spring

  
Update on EOL for Spring Security OAuth

  
I’ll be speaking at the upcoming YOW! Conferences. Join us!

  
This is an interesting, optimized-for-certain-usecases alternative to @MockBean: antoinemeyer/mock-in-bean: Surgically Inject Mockito Mock/Spy in Spring Beans

  
Michael Coté thinks 2022 will be year of figuring out kubernetes for developers, “DevX” or whatever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing AV1 Streaming to Netflix Members’ TVs]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b7fc88e42320</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/bringing-av1-streaming-to-netflix-members-tvs-b7fc88e42320?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T19:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Liwei Guo, Ashwin Kumar Gopi Valliammal, Raymond Tam, Chris Pham, Agata Opalach, Weibo Ni]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Known issue with publishing extensions: “Your ability to create global personal access tokens (PATs) is restricted by your organization.”]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62780</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/issue-with-extension-publishing/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T19:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve run into trouble while trying to publish an Azure DevOps or Visual Studio extension to the Visual Studio Marketplace, please ask your administrator if they have enabled the new policy to restrict the creation of global personal access tokens (PATs).
The post Known issue with publishing extensions: “Your ability to create global personal access tokens (PATs) is restricted by your organization.” appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pazand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.3.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=36369</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/camunda-cloud-1-3-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T15:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with Camunda Cloud 1.3.0-alpha1 now! The alpha includes bug fixes and the preparations for the next 1.3.0 release. 
The post Camunda Cloud 1.3.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Cloud Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced Sleep Sensing in Nest Hub]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/enhanced-sleep-sensing-in-nest-hub.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/enhanced-sleep-sensing-in-nest-hub.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T14:40:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Michael Dixon, Software Engineer and Reena Singhal Lee, Product Manager, Google Health 
Earlier this year, we launched Contactless Sleep Sensing in Nest Hub, an opt-in feature that can help users better understand their sleep patterns and nighttime wellness. While some of the most critical sleep insights can be derived from a person’s overall schedule and duration of sleep, that alone does not tell the complete story. The human brain has special neurocircuitry to coordinate sleep cycles — transitions between deep, light, and rapid eye movement (REM) stages of sleep — vital not only for physical and emotional wellbeing, but also for optimal physical and cognitive performance. Combining such sleep staging information with disturbance events can help you better understand what’s hap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 61 – Deploying to @Azure is one “git push” away with @juliendubois]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62700</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-61-deploying-to-azure-is-one-git-push-away-with-juliendubois/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T13:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 61 – Deploying to @Azure is one “git push” away with @juliendubois appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.7.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=36192</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/camunda-optimize-3-7-0-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.7.0-alpha1. Get started by downloading the release or signing up for a free trial.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.7.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Optimize Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0-alpha1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=35939</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/camunda-automation-platform-7170-alpha1-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're pleased to announce the next alpha release of Camunda Platform Runtime 7.17.0. Download Camunda for free or run it with Dock.
The post Camunda Automation Platform 7.17.0-alpha1 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Platform Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at EMNLP 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/google-at-emnlp-2021.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/google-at-emnlp-2021.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T23:47:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Catherine Armato, Google Research  
This week, the annual conference on Empirical Methods in Natural Language Processing (EMNLP 2021) will be held both virtually and in Punta Cana, Dominican Republic. As a Diamond Level sponsor of EMNLP 2021, Google will contribute research on a diverse set of topics, including language interactions, causal inference, and question answering, additionally serving in various levels of organization in the conference.  
Below is a full list of Google’s involvement and publications being presented at EMNLP 2021. We congratulate these authors, and all other researchers who are presenting their work at the conference (Google affiliations presented in bold). 
 Organizing Committee
Ethics Committee includes: Nyalleng Moorosi   
Publications
MATE: Multi-vi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auditing Coming to General Availability (GA) Early 2022!]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62765</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/auditing-coming-to-general-availability-ga-early-2022/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T22:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past couple of years, we’ve been gradually working on building out the Auditing features within Azure DevOps, from adding new billing and token events to the logs to releasing the ability to send auditing data downstream into a Security Incident and Event Management (SIEM) tool.
The post Auditing Coming to General Availability (GA) Early 2022! appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved On-Device ML on Pixel 6, with Neural Architecture Search]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/improved-on-device-ml-on-pixel-6-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/improved-on-device-ml-on-pixel-6-with.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T20:02:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Suyog Gupta and Marie White, Software Engineers, Google Research   
This fall Pixel 6 phones launched with Google Tensor, Google’s first mobile system-on-chip (SoC), bringing together various processing components (such as central/graphic/tensor processing units, image processors, etc.) onto a single chip, custom-built to deliver state-of-the-art innovations in machine learning (ML) to Pixel users. In fact, every aspect of Google Tensor was designed and optimized to run Google’s ML models, in alignment with our AI Principles. That starts with the custom-made TPU integrated in Google Tensor that allows us to fulfill our vision of what should be possible on a Pixel phone.  
Today, we share the improvements in on-device machine learning made possible by designing the ML models for G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update on EOL for Spring Security OAuth]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/08/update-on-eol-for-spring-security-oauth</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/08/update-on-eol-for-spring-security-oauth"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May 2020, we announced that the Spring Security OAuth (legacy) project will reach end-of-life in May 2022. The same end-of-life timeline applies to the Spring Boot 2 auto-configuration project.



We are now 6 months away from the EOL date, and the currently supported version branch is 2.5.x, which is limited to security fixes only.



We recently announced the release of Spring Authorization Server 0.2.0, which is the first officially supported production-ready version backed by our new support policy.



We encourage users to migrate their applications to Spring Authorization Server 0.2.0, as it is a direct replacement for the OAuth 2.0 Authorization Server support provided by Spring Security OAuth (legacy).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In The Works – AWS Canada West (Calgary) Region]]></title>
        <id>d5d1134efbb6200be9cd3965d02342492c6032b1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/in-the-works-aws-canada-west-calgary-region/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T16:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched the Canada (Central) Region in 2016 and added a third Availability Zone in 2020. Since that launch, tens of thousands of AWS customers have used AWS services in Canada to accelerate innovation, increase agility, and to drive cost savings. This includes enterprises such as Air Canada, BMO Financial Group, NHL, Porter Airlines, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Step Towards Breakeven Fusion]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/another-step-towards-breakeven-fusion.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/another-step-towards-breakeven-fusion.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T19:03:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ted Baltz, Senior Staff Software Engineer, Google Research  
For more than 70 years, plasma physicists have dreamed of controlled “breakeven” fusion, where a system is capable of releasing more energy in a fusion reaction than it takes to initiate and sustain those reactions. The challenge is that the reactor must create a plasma at a temperature of tens of millions of degrees, which requires a highly complex, finely tuned system to confine and sustain. Further, creating the plasma and maintaining it, requires substantial amounts of energy, which, to date, have exceeded that released in the fusion reaction itself. Nevertheless, if a “breakeven” system could be achieved, it could provide ample zero-carbon electricity, the potential impact of which has driven interest by government…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dojo – Customers & Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62736</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/devops-dojo-customers-trust/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T17:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In DevOps Dojo first blog, we explained what trust really is—competency and character. In our conversations with customers, there are two surprising facts that top the list of trust. The 1st one is that we act with the customers’ best interests in mind,
The post DevOps Dojo – Customers & Trust appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevOps Dojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plans to Archive Unmaintained Packer Provisioner Plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/plans-to-archive-unmaintained-packer-provisioner-plugins</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/plans-to-archive-unmaintained-packer-provisioner-plugins"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We plan to archive some unmaintained HashiCorp Packer provisioner plugins. Here’s what that means for practitioners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Factors Impacting Your Business Process Management]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=35871</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/how-process-automation-can-ignite-your-business-process-management/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why companies are ditching BPMS and applying process modeling and automation practices to their customer-facing processes instead. 
The post 5 Factors Impacting Your Business Process Management appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Data Flow 2.8.4 and 2.9.1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/05/spring-cloud-data-flow-2-8-4-and-2-9-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/05/spring-cloud-data-flow-2-8-4-and-2-9-1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T10:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Data Flow team is pleased to announce the release of 2.8.4 and 2.9.1

Releases 2.9.1 and 2.8.4 contains a quick bug fix and more changes were made in 2.9.0 and 2.8.3. For complete list of changes for 2.9.x you can see its milestone and rc notes in releases.
Stay in touch…

As always, we welcome feedback and contributions, so please reach out to us on Stackoverflow or GitHub or via Gitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.11.05]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62695</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-11-05/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T09:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.11.05 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.11.05 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bootiful Podcast: Legend, Dutchess founder, Devoxx4Kids contributor, and fellow Java Champion Linda van der Pal]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/04/bootiful-podcast-legend-dutchess-founder-devoxx4kids-contributor-and-fellow-java-champion-linda-van-der-pal</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/04/bootiful-podcast-legend-dutchess-founder-devoxx4kids-contributor-and-fellow-java-champion-linda-van-der-pal"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this episode Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Dutchess founder, Devoxx4Kids Netherlands (@Devoxx4KidsNL) leader, inspiring person, and fellow Java Champion Linda van der Pal (@DuchessFounder).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud Gateway versions 2.2.10.RELEASE and 3.0.5 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/04/spring-cloud-gateway-versions-2-2-10-release-and-3-0-5-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/04/spring-cloud-gateway-versions-2-2-10-release-and-3-0-5-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T19:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that Spring Cloud Gateway versions 2.2.10.RELEASE and 3.0.5.

These are primarily security releases with fixes for the CVE-2021-22051. 

These versions will be picked up later by the 2020.0.x and 2021.0.x release trains, however, we recommend you upgrade Spring Cloud Gateway in your projects to these most recent versions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: The One with the Non-existent Variable]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=35654</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/11/qa-the-one-with-the-non-existent-variable/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having trouble setting your variable sometimes? Find out how to check if your variable is set and why it can occasionally appear non-existent.
The post Q&A: The One with the Non-existent Variable appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power of AI and the Science of Operations (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-power-of-ai-and-the-science-of-operations-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/the-power-of-ai-and-the-science-of-operations-part-1"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A variety of industry experts cite Artificial Intelligence and Automation as key emerging trends.  But if you look around your organizations, you will see the evidence of AI projects and also an increasing focus on using automation in a variety of ways.  IBM and Red Hat together can help you build on and apply these trends to your IT operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Lin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2021.0.0-RC1 (codename Jubilee) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/03/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-rc1-codename-jubilee-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/03/spring-cloud-2021-0-0-rc1-codename-jubilee-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T23:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Release Candidate 1 (RC1) of the Spring Cloud 2021.0 Release Train, codename Jubilee, is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2021.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2021.0 Release Train

RC1 is compatible with Spring Boot 2.6.0-RC1

See the project page for all the issues and pull requests included in this release.
Spring Cloud Commons


  
Adds support for per LoadBalancer client properties. (issue)

  
Adds X-Forwarded-* headers when using load-balanced RestTemplate. (issue)


Spring Cloud Kubernetes


  
Adds support for disabling Discovery when spring.cloud.kubernetes.enabled=false. (issue)

  
Better failure handling when a Config…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: @Controllers: Give HTTP a REST]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/03/spring-tips-controllers-give-http-a-rest</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/03/spring-tips-controllers-give-http-a-rest"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, we’ll continue our exploration of @Controllers, and look at HTTP APIs and SSE with Spring. This time, we’ll use Spring Webflux. 

The code is here: github.com/spring-tips/controllers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-Supervised Reversibility-Aware Reinforcement Learning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/self-supervised-reversibility-aware.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/11/self-supervised-reversibility-aware.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T18:11:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Johan Ferret, Student Researcher, Google Research, Brain Team    
An approach commonly used to train agents for a range of applications from robotics to chip design is reinforcement learning (RL). While RL excels at discovering how to solve tasks from scratch, it can struggle in training an agent to understand the reversibility of its actions, which can be crucial to ensure that agents behave in a safe manner within their environment. For instance, robots are generally costly and require maintenance, so one wants to avoid taking actions that might lead to broken components. Estimating if an action is reversible or not (or better, how easily it can be reversed) requires a working knowledge of the physics of the environment in which the agent is operating. However, in the standard …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Use the Vault Agent for Secrets Management?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/why-use-the-vault-agent-for-secrets-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/why-use-the-vault-agent-for-secrets-management"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HashiCorp’s Vault Agent can help you achieve zero trust security in a simple manner, consistently across all application teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Fully Managed RStudio on Amazon SageMaker for Data Scientists]]></title>
        <id>0ddead23befe1433cf15ad8e1e4a4ea58038b1c6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-fully-managed-rstudio-on-amazon-sagemaker-for-data-scientists/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T19:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two years ago, we introduced Amazon SageMaker Studio, the industry’s first fully integrated development environment (IDE) for machine learning (ML). Amazon SageMaker Studio provides a single, web-based visual interface where you can perform all ML development steps, improving data science team productivity by up to 10 times Many data scientists love the R project, an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - November 2nd, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/02/this-week-in-spring-november-2nd-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/11/02/this-week-in-spring-november-2nd-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How’re you doin’? I’ve been busy as all get out emceeing the Reactive Summit 2021 event (it’s free and it’s online!). The event has been awe-inspiring because there are so many amazing speakers from all walks of life present and speaking. Today, the conference welcomed professor Carl Hewitt, the creator of the Actor Paradigm, as its keynote. Then, figuring there was no topping that and figuring they could go for broke, they foolishly ( muahahah! ) asked me to do the day two keynote. So, I’ll be doing tomorrow’s keynote with my friend and Google Developer Advocate James Ward. Join us! It’ll be super fun! 

We’ve got a ton of stuff to get to this week though, so let’s dive right into it! 


  
Bootiful Podcast: Daniel Mikusa on Buildpacks, Paketo, UPX, Tilt, GraalVM Native Images, Docker Containers and more

  
Want to run the most modern incarnation of what used to be ActiveMQ? On the cloud? Check out the ArtemisCloud Operator which lets you easily stand up an Artemis instance on Kubernetes.

  
Cool! Check this out: Google announced Kotlin support for Google protocol buffers

  
A nice tutorial: how to set the logging level with application.properties in Spring Boot 

  
How to update an entity using Spring Data JPA? 

  
Spring GraphQL 1.0.0-M3 Released

  
Spring Tips: @Controllers (pt. 1): the “C” in Model 2 MVC

  
Spring Tools 4.12.1 released

  
We’re hiring! Join us: Staff-Software-Engineer - Cloud-Native-Runtimes–Streaming 

  
The new VMware Tanzu for developers hands-on lab is out!

  
Join me for this year’s YOW! Conference!

  
AppDynamics - 1 step to activate and monitor Spring Boot apps on Azure Spring Cloud 

  
One cool way to remove developer toil and improve security in Kubernetes, the VMWare Tanzu build service. Check out more and down]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Video Quality at Scale with Cosmos Microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/552be631c113</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/netflix-video-quality-at-scale-with-cosmos-microservices-552be631c113?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T17:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Christos G. Bampis, Chao Chen, Anush K. Moorthy and Zhi Li]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Adds 3 New Observability Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-adds-3-new-observability-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-vault-adds-3-new-observability-integrations"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New integrations with Datadog, Grafana Cloud, and Splunk offer pre-built dashboards for usage and performance monitoring in HCP Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnisbleFest 2021 - What it means for Partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/anisblefest-2021-what-means-for-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/anisblefest-2021-what-means-for-partners"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the weather turns to Fall, the seasons seem to parallel that of the technology cycles. Over the past couple of decades, we have seen various transformations within the high-tech area:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nelson Hsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start and Step Through a Process with REST (feat. SwaggerUI)]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=35255</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/start-and-step-through-a-process-with-rest-feat-swaggerui/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T08:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re going to be communicating with the Camunda engine from any kind of third-party system, you’re going to need to know a little bit about what Camunda’s REST API can do out of the box.
The post Start and Step Through a Process with REST (feat. SwaggerUI) appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights From HashiConf Global 2021 for Enterprises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/highlights-from-hashiconf-global-2021-for-enterprises</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/highlights-from-hashiconf-global-2021-for-enterprises"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recap of key announcements and presentations from HashiConf Global 2021 — focused on the needs and interests of enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第196話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496572306855</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496572306855"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 7.16 Webinar Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=35220</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/10/camunda-platform-7-16-webinar-recap/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get the bonus insight and answers we didn't have time to share during our recent Camunda Platform 7.16 release webinar.
The post Camunda Platform 7.16 Webinar Recap appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.10.29]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62647</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-10-29/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T08:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.10.29 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.10.29 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 C6i Instances Powered by the Latest Generation Intel Xeon Scalable Processors]]></title>
        <id>58ff26983ab74e9116e26ec67e44852d5ab372ce</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c6i-instances-powered-by-the-latest-generation-intel-xeon-scalable-processors/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T22:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently introduced Amazon EC2 M6i instances powered by the latest generation Intel® Xeon® Scalable processors with an all-core turbo frequency of 3.5 GHz, which offer customers up to 15% improvement in price performance compared to M5 instances. Today, I am happy to announce the availability of the new compute-optimized Amazon EC2 C6i instances, which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye Microsoft SQL Server, Hello Babelfish]]></title>
        <id>c49cbf1a684657d2d6c1cb4fa064a78b2ab04c08</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/goodbye-microsoft-sql-server-hello-babelfish/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T20:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of our customers are telling us they want to move away from proprietary database vendors to avoid expensive costs and burdensome licensing terms. But migrating away from commercial and legacy databases can be time-consuming and resource-intensive. When migrating your databases, you can automate the migration of your database schema and data using the AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoEmotions: A Dataset for Fine-Grained Emotion Classification]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/10/goemotions-dataset-for-fine-grained.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/10/goemotions-dataset-for-fine-grained.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T18:14:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Dana Alon and Jeongwoo Ko, Software Engineers, Google Research 
Emotions are a key aspect of social interactions, influencing the way people behave and shaping relationships. This is especially true with language — with only a few words, we're able to express a wide variety of subtle and complex emotions. As such, it’s been a long-term goal among the research community to enable machines to understand context and emotion, which would, in turn, enable a variety of applications, including empathetic chatbots, models to detect harmful online behavior, and improved customer support interactions. 
In the past decade, the NLP research community has made available several datasets for language-based emotion classification. The majority of those are constructed manually and cover targete…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul Updates: New Terraform Module for EKS and EC2, and an ECS Learn Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-updates-new-terraform-module-for-eks-and-ec2-ecs-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-updates-new-terraform-module-for-eks-and-ec2-ecs-guide"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New quickstart video demos walk you through our new Terraform module for Amazon EKS and EC2, and show how to test managing Consul features on Amazon ECS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Engineers of Netflix — Interview with Pallavi Phadnis]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/a1fcc5f64906</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/data-engineers-of-netflix-interview-with-pallavi-phadnis-a1fcc5f64906?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T17:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of our “Data Engineers of Netflix” series, Pallavi Phadnis shares her journey to Data Engineering at Netflix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copy Dashboard – Public Preview Phase 2]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62636</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/copy-dashboard-public-preview-phase-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T15:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copy Dashboard Phase 2
The post Copy Dashboard – Public Preview Phase 2 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost your cloud-native deployments with Red Hat OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/boost-your-cloud-native-deployments-with-red-hat-openshift</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/boost-your-cloud-native-deployments-with-red-hat-openshift"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud-native deployments are becoming the new normal. Being able to keep full control of the application lifecycle (deployment, updates, and integrations) is a strategic advantage. This article will explain how the latest release of the Ansible Content Collection for Red Hat OpenShift takes the redhat.openshift Collection to the next level, improving the performance of large automation tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open-Sourcing a Monitoring GUI for Metaflow]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/75ff465f0d60</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/open-sourcing-a-monitoring-gui-for-metaflow-75ff465f0d60?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T21:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix’s ML Platform has made a new addition to Open Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Attribute-Based Instance Type Selection for EC2 Auto Scaling and EC2 Fleet]]></title>
        <id>3d39d9ceb38f954d93ed92346f5c37e06ee363fe</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-attribute-based-instance-type-selection-for-ec2-auto-scaling-and-ec2-fleet/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T21:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first AWS service I used, more than ten years ago, was Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2). Over time, EC2 has added a wide selection of instance types optimized to fit different use cases, with a varying combination of CPU/GPU, memory, storage, and networking capacity to give you the flexibility to choose the appropriate […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grammar Correction as You Type, on Pixel 6]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/10/grammar-correction-as-you-type-on-pixel.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/10/grammar-correction-as-you-type-on-pixel.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T20:31:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tony Mak, Software Engineer, Google Research and Simon Tong, Principal Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
Despite the success and widespread adoption of smartphones, using them to compose longer pieces of text is still quite cumbersome. As one writes, grammatical errors can often creep into the text (especially undesirable in formal situations), and correcting these errors can be time consuming on a small display with limited controls. 
  
To address some of these challenges, we are launching a grammar correction feature that is directly built into Gboard on Pixel 6 that works entirely on-device to preserve privacy, detecting and suggesting corrections for grammatical errors while the user is typing. Building such functionality required addressing a few key obstacles: memory …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing CDK for Terraform 0.7]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-cdk-for-terraform-0-7</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-cdk-for-terraform-0-7"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform 0.7 introduces a tech preview for compatibility with AWS CDK constructs, a simplified provider API, and improved documentation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible for AWS: Introduction to Spot Instance Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-for-aws-introduction-to-spot-instance-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-for-aws-introduction-to-spot-instance-automation"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Spot Instance and Spot Instance Requests?
 
A Spot Instance is an instance that uses spare AWS EC2 capacity that is available for less than the On-Demand price. Because Spot Instances provide the ability to request unused EC2 instances at steep discounts, it can lower your Amazon EC2 costs significantly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mandar Vijay Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – EC2 Instances Powered by Gaudi Accelerators for Training Deep Learning Models]]></title>
        <id>1286bfacea703cc5f6cf0a6ec9ec02e8da004157</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-ec2-instances-powered-by-gaudi-accelerators-for-training-deep-learning-models/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T20:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are more applications today for deep learning than ever before. Natural language processing, recommendation systems, image recognition, video recognition, and more can all benefit from high-quality, well-trained models. The process of building such a model is iterative: construct an initial model, train it on the ground truth data, do some test inferences, refine the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Local Zones Are Now Open in Las Vegas, New York City, and Portland]]></title>
        <id>08e94bdba33ee3a9bde2a667e0c729331ea1712a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-local-zones-are-now-open-in-las-vegas-new-york-city-and-portland/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T19:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are opening three new AWS Local Zones in Las Vegas, New York City (located in New Jersey), and Portland metro areas. We are now at a total of 14 Local Zones in 13 cities since Jeff Barr announced the first Local Zone in Los Angeles in December 2019. These three new Local Zones […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62630</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/october-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T18:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Previously, Azure DevOps Server could only create connections to GitHub Enterprise Server. With this patch, project administrators can create connections between Azure DevOps Server and repositories on GitHub.com.
The post October patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon RDS Custom for Oracle – New Control Capabilities in Database Environment]]></title>
        <id>3b4cda05885324e5d32490bd1276e5a6555d06a9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-rds-custom-for-oracle-new-control-capabilities-in-database-environment/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T17:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing databases in self-managed environments such as on premises or Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) requires customers to spend time and resources doing database administration tasks such as provisioning, scaling, patching, backups, and configuring for high availability. So, hundreds of thousands of AWS customers use Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) because it automates […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interpreting A/B test results: false negatives and power]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6943995cf3a8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/interpreting-a-b-test-results-false-negatives-and-power-6943995cf3a8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T15:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Tingley with Wenjing Zheng, Simon Ejdemyr, Stephanie Lane, and Colin McFarland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 60 – DevOps Solutions on @Azure with @TheAprilEdwards]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62622</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-60-devops-solutions-on-azure-with-theapriledwards/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T14:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 60 – DevOps Solutions on @Azure with @TheAprilEdwards appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help Make BugBusting History at AWS re:Invent 2021]]></title>
        <id>77fab76e6d668a7c6a06a9119500629ac4ff9ade</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/help-make-bugbusting-history-at-aws-reinvent-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T20:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, we launched the AWS BugBust Challenge, the world’s first global competition to fix one million code bugs and reduce technical debt by over $100 million. As part of this endeavor, we are launching the first AWS BugBust re:Invent Challenge at this year’s AWS re:Invent conference, from 10 a.m. (PST) November 29 to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean M. Tracey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Strategy Recommendations Service Helps Streamline AWS Cloud Migration and Modernization]]></title>
        <id>285a4222bec560f367b41ec232d51291e601b373</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-strategy-recommendations-service-helps-streamline-aws-cloud-migration-and-modernization/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T20:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Determining viable strategies for successful application migration and modernization to the cloud takes time. It can also require significant effort, depending on the size and complexity of the application portfolio to analyze. To date, the analysis process has been largely manual and nonstandard in nature, making it difficult to apply at scale on large portfolios. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deciding Which Tasks Should Train Together in Multi-Task Neural Networks]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/10/deciding-which-tasks-should-train.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/10/deciding-which-tasks-should-train.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Christopher Fifty, Research Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team 
Many machine learning (ML) models typically focus on learning one task at a time. For example, language models predict the probability of a next word given a context of past words, and object detection models identify the object(s) that are present in an image. However, there may be instances when learning from many related tasks at the same time would lead to better modeling performance. This is addressed in the domain of multi-task learning, a subfield of ML in which multiple objectives are trained within the same model at the same time. 
Consider a real-world example: the game of ping-pong. When playing ping-pong, it is often advantageous to judge the distance, spin, and imminent trajectory of the ping-pong bal…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volunteer for HashiCorp Certified: Vault Operations Professional Beta Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/volunteer-for-hashicorp-certified-vault-operations-professional-beta-exam</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/volunteer-for-hashicorp-certified-vault-operations-professional-beta-exam"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take the beta exam for the newest level of Vault certification — for free — and you’ll have a chance to be one of the first certified Vault Ops Pros.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's New: The Ansible AWS Collection 2.0 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-the-ansible-aws-collection-2.0-release</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-the-ansible-aws-collection-2.0-release"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to Amazon Web Services (AWS) infrastructure automation, the latest release of the Ansible amazon.aws Collection brings a set of fresh features to build, manage and govern various public and hybrid cloud use cases while accelerating the process from development to production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Global 2021 Delivers Deep Learning for Practitioners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-global-2021-delivers-deep-learning-for-practitioners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-global-2021-delivers-deep-learning-for-practitioners"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch the keynotes and some of the most informative sessions for practitioners from HashiConf Global 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Differentially Private Clustering]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/10/practical-differentially-private.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/10/practical-differentially-private.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T20:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alisa Chang, Software Engineer, Google Cloud and Pritish Kamath, Research Scientist, Google Research 
Over the last several years, progress has been made on privacy-safe approaches for handling sensitive data, for example, while discovering insights into human mobility and through use of federated analytics such as RAPPOR. In 2019, we released an open source library to enable developers and organizations to use techniques that provide differential privacy, a strong and widely accepted mathematical notion of privacy. Differentially-private data analysis is a principled approach that enables organizations to learn and release insights from the bulk of their data while simultaneously providing a mathematical guarantee that those results do not allow any individual user's data to be …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predicting Spreadsheet Formulas from Semi-structured Contexts]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/10/predicting-spreadsheet-formulas-from.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2021/10/predicting-spreadsheet-formulas-from.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T20:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rishabh Singh, Research Scientist and Max Lin, Software Engineer, Google Research 
Hundreds of millions of people use spreadsheets, and formulas in those spreadsheets allow users to perform sophisticated analyses and transformations on their data. Although formula languages are simpler than general-purpose programming languages, writing these formulas can still be tedious and error-prone, especially for end-users. We've previously developed tools to understand patterns in spreadsheet data to automatically fill missing values in a column, but they were not built to support the process of writing formulas. 
In "SpreadsheetCoder: Formula Prediction from Semi-structured Context", published at ICML 2021, we describe a new model that learns to automatically generate formulas based on t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Vision at the Edge with AWS Panorama]]></title>
        <id>bb64b081a33e0e139a0be82e2486b897d168e908</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/computer-vision-at-the-edge-with-aws-panorama/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T17:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the AWS Panorama Appliance is generally available to all of you. The AWS Panorama Appliance is a computer vision (CV) appliance designed to be deployed on your network to analyze images provided by your on-premises cameras. Every week, I read about new and innovative use cases for computer vision. Some customers are using CV […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Consul API Gateway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-consul-api-gateway</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-consul-api-gateway"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Consul API Gateway is a dedicated ingress solution for intelligently routing traffic to applications running on the HashiCorp Consul service mesh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Consul 1.11 Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-consul-1-11</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-consul-1-11"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul 1.11 adds important new features: multi-tenancy with administrative partitions and a new installation-and-management Consul Kubernetes CLI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>