<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-16T01:59:45.836Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-16T01:59:45.836Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The good news]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45094</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/754267037/0/sethsblog~The-good-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if there were a pipeline into your day, a series of emails or posts or feeds that had nothing but nice things, positive feedback and encouragement coming your way? Amazingly, you could build something like that in just a few minutes and have it forever. If the bad news (comments, drama and controversy) is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Django Apps on Google Cloud With PyCharm and Cloud Code]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=372421</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/07/build-django-apps-on-google-cloud-with-pycharm-and-cloud-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T15:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you’ll learn how to build and run your applications both in a local Kubernetes cluster (Docker Desktop or Minikube) and remotely in Google Kubernetes Engine using Cloud Code and PyCharm. This will allow you to focus on coding, with the Google Cloud Code plugin taking care of the rest. The tutorial will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mukul Mantosh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extended C# Support in ReSharper and Rider 2023.2 EAP 9]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=371615</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/07/14/rsrp-rider-2023-2-eap9/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T13:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve just published new EAP builds for both ReSharper 2023.2 and Rider 2023.2. Both contain updates to C# support. Let’s dive in!  C#12 preview support  Primary constructors  In the 2023.2 version, we introduced primary constructor support for non-record classes and structs from the C# 12 preview. Unlike primary constructors in records, primary constructors in classes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subscription and Host Metric Changes in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/subscription-and-host-metric-changes-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.4</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/subscription-and-host-metric-changes-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.4"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What and Why?
 
Our customers use Ansible Automation Platform across a multitude of platforms, in a plethora of ways. Providing an accurate accounting and reporting capability is sometimes difficult across the various types of use cases we encounter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MPS 2021.3.3 Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=mps&amp;p=367983</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/mps/2023/07/mps-2021-3-3-has-been-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s never too late to improve old software! We’ve just backported two useful features from the latest MPS version all the way back to version 2021.3.3, which has just been released. MPS 2021.3.3 adopts one improvement that enhances the functionality of the overrides flag in the type system inference rules and makes them more powerful. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaclav Pech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.1.4 Is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=webstorm&amp;p=372149</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/webstorm/2023/07/webstorm-2023-1-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T09:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebStorm 2023.1.4, the fourth bug-fix update for WebStorm 2023.1, is now available! You can update to v2023.1.4 by using the Toolbox App, installing it right from the IDE, or downloading it from our website. WebStorm 2023.1.4 brings the following important fixes: We fixed the issue with missing custom code style settings and they are now […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raising the bar]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46676</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/753934388/0/sethsblog~Raising-the-bar/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s not the same as raising the average. With the advent of the high jump, the idiom raising the bar became well understood: If you can’t jump over the bar that the current leader cleared, you don’t win. But most of the innovations that change our culture don’t actually increase the simple linear measurements of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The RubyMine 2023.2 Beta: Updated AI Assistant, LSP API for Plugin Developers, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=370276</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2023/07/the-rubymine-2023-2-beta-updated-ai-assistant-lsp-api-for-plugin-developers-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T08:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RubyMine 2023.2 Early Access Program has reached Beta! Below are some of the new features in the upcoming release that we haven’t yet mentioned.  Please try it out and share your feedback either in the comments or through our issue tracker. Documentation generation with AI Assistant If you’re looking to generate documentation for a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iryna Pisklyarova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · Spring 2023 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-13-release-radar-spring-23/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-13-release-radar-spring-23/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T00:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It&#8217;s been a while since we&#8217;ve published our Release Radar. You can blame IRL conferences coming back, getting influenza, and being struck down by the weather. But those are just me problems. While I&#8217;ve been down or travelling, the community has been hard at work shipping new releases and new projects. So, we thought we&#8217;d [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2023.1.0-M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/14/spring-data-2023-1-0-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/14/spring-data-2023-1-0-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring HATEOAS 1.5.5, 2.0.5, 2.1.1 and 2.2 M1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/14/spring-hateoas-1-5-5-2-0-5-2-1-1-and-2-2-m1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/14/spring-hateoas-1-5-5-2-0-5-2-1-1-and-2-2-m1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Drotbohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2023.0.2, 2022.0.8, and 2021.2.14 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/14/spring-data-2023-0-2-2022-0-8-and-2021-2-14-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/14/spring-data-2023-0-2-2022-0-8-and-2021-2-14-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Paluch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hidden data challenges CIOs face on their quest to accelerate business outcomes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-challenges-cios-accelerate-business-outcomes</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-challenges-cios-accelerate-business-outcomes"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CIOs are on a quest to boost resilience, mitigate risks, and improve customer experiences. Hidden beneath the surface are data challenges that can impede progress. Once you can identify these challenges, you can turn them into opportunities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hidden data challenges CIOs face on their quest to accelerate business outcomes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-challenges-cios-accelerate-business-outcomes</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/data-challenges-cios-accelerate-business-outcomes"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Navigating the complex terrain of IT systems, operational issues, and security breaches is no easy job, even for the seasoned CIO. And when tasked with the lofty goals of improving operational resilience, mitigating security risk, and enhancing customer experiences, dealing with the day-to-day operations is all the more challenging. 

Achieving these goals can often feel overwhelming, with no end to the journey in sight. On top of that, hidden beneath these goals are the unseen challenges of harnessing the untapped potential of your data that can disrupt your efforts in achieving these goals. As a CIO, acknowledging and conquering these concealed challenges — and turning them into opportunities — is crucial to your organization's success. 

So, what are these hidden data challenges?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fermi Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fireflies]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2802/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2802/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/fireflies.png" title="I feel bad for Earth 2 and their shadowflies." alt="I feel bad for Earth 2 and their shadowflies." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Symbol tuning improves in-context learning in language models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/symbol-tuning-improves-in-context.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/symbol-tuning-improves-in-context.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T21:01:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jerry Wei, Student Researcher, and Denny Zhou, Principal Scientist, Google Research





A key feature of human intelligence is that humans can learn to perform new tasks by reasoning using only a few examples. Scaling up language models has unlocked a range of new applications and paradigms in machine learning, including the ability to perform challenging reasoning tasks via in-context learning. Language models, however, are still sensitive to the way that prompts are given, indicating that they are not reasoning in a robust manner. For instance, language models often require heavy prompt engineering or phrasing tasks as instructions, and they exhibit unexpected behaviors such as performance on tasks being unaffected even when shown incorrect labels.


In “Symbol tuning improves…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMMN Patterns Made Easily with BPMN]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=85842&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=85842</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/cmmn-patterns-bpmn/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T19:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the fundamental features of CMMN and how BPMN can easily match CMMN in dynamism. 
The post CMMN Patterns Made Easily with BPMN appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP Now Supports WORM Protection for Regulatory Compliance and Ransomware Protection]]></title>
        <id>43c4ca9ff2b7e7f88801eafbcd41be6544d74974</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap-now-supports-worm-protection-for-regulatory-compliance-and-ransomware-protection/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T19:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP was launched in late 2021. With FSx for ONTAP you get the popular features, performance, and APIs of ONTAP file systems, with the agility, scalability, security, and resilience of AWS, all as a fully managed service. Today we are adding support for SnapLock, an ONTAP feature that gives you the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(De)coding conventions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-13-decoding-conventions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-13-decoding-conventions/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating the ebb and flow of programming paradigms–from the shifts in the JavaScript ecosystem and TypeScript's rise, to AI's role in advancing accessibility, and strategies for encouraging non-code contributions–tune in to the latest episode of The ReadME Podcast for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps 2023 Q3 Roadmap update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67268</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-2023-q3-roadmap-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, we published updates to our product roadmap. It outlines our plans for the next two quarters, and future investments. The features listed below are a few highlights of what we plan to deliver in Q3. Visit our product roadmap for a complete look at the list of features for Q4.
The post Azure DevOps 2023 Q3 Roadmap update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.2 EAP 5: Black Formatter Integration, Endpoints Tool Window for Django REST Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=371614</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/07/2023-2-eap-5/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This EAP build includes the Black formatter integration, a new Endpoints tool window for Django REST framework, the Run Anything tool to quickly run anything or create a new run configuration, support for installing dependencies from pyproject.toml, inlay parameter name hints, and much more. To catch up on all of the new features PyCharm 2023.2 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey 2023: The financial services perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-the-financial-services-perspective</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-the-financial-services-perspective"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Financial services firms are using multi-cloud to improve their business outcomes in many ways, from boosting reliability to dealing with skills shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debug Source Generators in JetBrains Rider]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=348596</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/07/13/debug-source-generators-in-jetbrains-rider/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T13:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Source generators help developers rethink approaches that use reflection and instead use compile-time techniques to avoid the runtime expense of costly operations. The .NET team introduced the community to Source Generators on April 29th, 2020, as a new approach to inspect a project’s code using Roslyn and generate new C# source files that add new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving from a product to a service mindset]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-13-moving-from-a-product-to-a-service-mindset/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-13-moving-from-a-product-to-a-service-mindset/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T13:44:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to DevOps, cloud computing and other industry trends, many organizations are shifting from a product mindset to a service mindset. Here’s how you can implement a service-led strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.2 Goes Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=371907</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/07/clion-2023-2-goes-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T12:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Beta version of CLion 2023.2 is now available with the key improvements and changes that are expected in the upcoming release. Download build 232.8660.49 from our website, via the Toolbox App, or as a snap package (for Ubuntu). DOWNLOAD CLION 2023.2 BETA Text search in Search Everywhere Search Everywhere (Double Shift) is primarily used […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2023.2 Reaches Beta!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=370641</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2023/07/13/goland-2023-2-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T10:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first Beta of GoLand 2023.2 is available! You can get the Beta build via the Toolbox App, from our website, by using a snap package (for Ubuntu), or right from inside GoLand by selecting Check IDE updates for: Early Access Program in Settings | Appearance & Behavior | System Settings | Updates. Download GoLand […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remarkable pronouncements]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44887</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/753563984/0/sethsblog~Remarkable-pronouncements/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T08:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The scientific rule of thumb is simple: When you make a bold claim, you need significant research to back it up. Telling us that eating vegetables is healthy can be justified by a fairly simple high school science paper. But if you want to claim that the moon is made of celery and Elmer’s Glue, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliJ IDEA 2023.2 Goes Beta!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=369353</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/07/intellij-idea-2023-2-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T07:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Beta version of IntelliJ IDEA 2023.2 is now available! You can get the latest build from our website, through the free Toolbox App, or via snaps for Ubuntu. This build comes with all of the notable changes that were introduced throughout the Early Access Program and covered in our previous blog posts. Here are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Kosukhina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in Spring 6.1: RestClient]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/13/new-in-spring-6-1-restclient</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/13/new-in-spring-6-1-restclient"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjen Poutsma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.1 M2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/13/spring-framework-6-1-m2-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/13/spring-framework-6-1-m2-released"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.2.25.RELEASE, 5.3.29 and 6.0.11 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/13/spring-framework-5-2-25-release-5-3-29-and-6-0-11-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/13/spring-framework-5-2-25-release-5-3-29-and-6-0-11-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Web Flow 3.0.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/13/spring-web-flow-3-0-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/13/spring-web-flow-3-0-0-released"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rossen Stoyanchev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Framework and Spring Boot legend Stéphane Nicoll on a Bootiful Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/13/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-framework-and-spring-boot-legend-stephane-nicoll</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/13/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-framework-and-spring-boot-legend-stephane-nicoll"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving information retrieval in the Elastic Stack: Hybrid retrieval]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-information-retrieval-elastic-stack-hybrid</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-information-retrieval-elastic-stack-hybrid"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog we introduce hybrid retrieval and explore two concrete implementations in Elasticsearch. We explore improving Elastic Learned Sparse Encoder’s performance by combining it with BM25 using Reciprocal Rank Fusion and Weighted Sum of Scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quentin Herreros,Thomas Veasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Moose Stevens believes you should show up exactly who you are]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-moose-stevens-show-up-as-you-are</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-moose-stevens-show-up-as-you-are"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“My experience as being queer at Elastic has been super positive,” Moose says. “Come as YOU, are is acted out. I’m quirky and can be myself, nobody cares.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moose Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to combine OpenTelemetry instrumentation with Elastic APM Agent features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-instrumentation-elastic-apm-agent-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-instrumentation-elastic-apm-agent-features"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post shows you how you can combine the OpenTelemetry tracing APIs with Elastic APM Agents. You'll learn how OpenTelemetry spans became part of a trace that Elastic APM Agents report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Kalapos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving information retrieval in the Elastic Stack: Hybrid retrieval]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-information-retrieval-elastic-stack-hybrid</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/improving-information-retrieval-elastic-stack-hybrid"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In our last blog post, we introduced Elastic Learned Sparse Encoder, a model trained for effective zero-shot text retrieval. Elasticsearch® also has great lexical retrieval capabilities and rich tools for combining the results of different queries. In this blog, we introduce the concept of hybrid retrieval and explore two concrete implementations available in Elasticsearch. In particular, we explore how to improve the performance of Elastic Learned Sparse Encoder by combining it with BM25 using Reciprocal Rank Fusion and Weighted Sum of Scores.
We also discuss experiments we undertook to explore some general research questions. These include how best to parameterize Reciprocal Rank Fusion and how to calibrate Weighted Sum of Scores.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quentin Herreros,Thomas Veasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Like Me: Moose Stevens believes you should show up exactly who you are]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-moose-stevens-show-up-as-you-are</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-moose-stevens-show-up-as-you-are"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
I’m a Senior Engineering Manager for Elastic’s Security Solution who identifies as a nerdy Gender Queer who loves managing the people! I’ve been in tech for over 25 years, starting out as a junior programmer back in the day. Now I have the privilege of leading a group of exceptional Engineering Productivity wizzes who do fantastic work. 

My experience being queer at Elastic has been super positive. Come as YOU, are is acted out. I’m quirky and can be myself, nobody cares.

‘As YOU, Are’ is a company-wide value at Elastic. It means we celebrate the person you are and we know (and love) that everyone is different. It also means that we recognize and encourage individual differences as a variety of perspectives brings life to a project and the team. 

An example of ‘As YOU, Are’ put into a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moose Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to combine OpenTelemetry instrumentation with Elastic APM Agent features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-instrumentation-elastic-apm-agent-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-instrumentation-elastic-apm-agent-features"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic APM supports OpenTelemetry on multiple levels. One easy-to understand scenario, which we previously blogged about, is the direct OpenTelemetry Protocol (OTLP) support in APM Server. This means that you can connect any OpenTelemetry agent to an Elastic APM Server and the APM Server will happily take that data, ingest it into Elasticsearch®, and you can view that OpenTelemetry data in the APM app in Kibana®.

This blog post will showcase a different use-case: within Elastic APM, we have our own APM Agents. Some of these have download numbers in the tens of millions, and some of them predate OpenTelemetry. Of course we realize OpenTelemetry is very important and it’s here to stay, so we wanted to make these agents OpenTelemetry compatible.

Most of our Elastic APM Agents today are a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Kalapos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating Settlements Beyond T+1 with Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=85599&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=85599</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/accelerating-settlements-beyond-t1-process-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T20:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banks must strategically optimize processes beyond T+1 to achieve a high degree of straight-through processing. Process orchestration can help.
The post Accelerating Settlements Beyond T+1 with Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: June 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-12-github-availability-report-june-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-12-github-availability-report-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T20:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June, we experienced two incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services.  June 7 16:11 UTC (lasting 2 hours 28 minutes) On June 7 at 16:11 UTC, GitHub started experiencing increasing delays in an internal job queue used to process Git pushes. Our monitoring systems alerted our first responders after 19 minutes. During [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2023.2 EAP 3 Is Out!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=371322</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2023/07/2023-2-eap-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T19:41:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third EAP build for DataSpell 2023.2 brings you faster table data exploration, the new AI Assistant, and the ability to configure managed Jupyter servers. To catch up on all of the new features DataSpell 2023.2 brings, check out our previous EAP blog posts. The Toolbox App is the easiest way to get the EAP […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanislav Garkusha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No cyber resilience without open source sustainability]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-12-no-cyber-resilience-without-open-source-sustainability/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-12-no-cyber-resilience-without-open-source-sustainability/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T18:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have your say to protect open source in the EU.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary LDAP authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-ldap-authentication</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-ldap-authentication"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to set up Boundary’s new LDAP auth method and get a deep dive into how the feature can help you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub merge queue is generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-12-github-merge-queue-is-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-12-github-merge-queue-is-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supercharge pull request merges on your busiest branches by enabling your team to queue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing passwordless authentication on GitHub.com]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-12-introducing-passwordless-authentication-on-github-com/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-12-introducing-passwordless-authentication-on-github-com/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys are now available in public beta. Opting in lets you upgrade security keys to passkeys, and use those in place of both your password and your 2FA method.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第233話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361511369675</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361511369675"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Automated DevOps in .NET and Azure Using JetBrains TeamCity Cloud, July 20, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=371420</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/07/webinar-clearmeasure-july2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T14:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would you like to learn more about how to set up a DevOps continuous delivery pipeline for .NET? Make sure to join the webinar Automated DevOps in .NET and Azure Using TeamCity Cloud, conducted by our partner Clear Measure. Here’s what the webinar will cover: The webinar will be hosted by Jeffrey Palermo, who serves […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Bedrina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenShift and Ansible: Bridging the Automation Gap for 5G and Beyond Networks - Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/openshift-and-ansible-bridging-the-automation-gap-for-5g-and-beyond-networks-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/openshift-and-ansible-bridging-the-automation-gap-for-5g-and-beyond-networks-part-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post is co-authored with Ian Miller.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leonardo Ochoa-Aday</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Big Fat Greek Wedding]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44883</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/753214190/0/sethsblog~My-Big-Fat-Greek-Wedding/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among the top 500 grossing Hollywood movies of all time, this movie is the most profitable in return on investment. And among all Hollywood movies in the top 1,500 at the box office, Paranormal Activity is far and away the highest return, outperforming almost any investment the stock market has ever offered. The return on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Nginx metrics with Elastic time series data streams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/nginx-metrics-elastic-time-series-data-streams</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/nginx-metrics-elastic-time-series-data-streams"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch recently released time series metrics as GA. In this blog, we dive into details of what a time series metric document is and the mapping used for enabling time series by using an existing OOTB Nginx integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lalit Satapathy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 stand-out retail use cases for generative AI + Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/retail-use-cases-generative-ai-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/retail-use-cases-generative-ai-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With ESRE, retailers can enhance their search capabilities to deliver more accurate and relevant results to their customers and employees, while ensuring sensitive data remains protected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Nginx metrics with Elastic time series data streams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/nginx-metrics-elastic-time-series-data-streams</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/nginx-metrics-elastic-time-series-data-streams"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elasticsearch® recently released time series data streams for metrics. This not only provides better metrics support in Elastic Observability, but it also helps reduce storage costs. We discussed this in a previous blog. 

In this blog, we dive into how to enable and use time series data streams by reviewing what a time series metrics document is and the mapping used for enabling time series. In particular, we will showcase this by using Elastic Observability’s Nginx integration. As Elastic® time series data stream (TSDS) metrics capabilities evolve, some of the scenarios below will change.
Elastic TSDS stores metrics in indices optimized for a time series database (TSDB), which is used to store time series metrics. Elastic’s TSDB also got a significant optimization in 8.7 by reducing st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lalit Satapathy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 stand-out retail use cases for generative AI + Elasticsearch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/retail-use-cases-generative-ai-elasticsearch</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/retail-use-cases-generative-ai-elasticsearch"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Generative AI (GAI), powered by models like OpenAI’s ChatGPT, is rapidly gaining attention in the retail industry for its potential to revolutionize customer experience and drive innovation. The technology has the ability to improve every corner of the retail industry, from tailored ecommerce search and modernized customer support to omnichannel marketing and even predictive maintenance in supply chains. In fact, the many promising retail use cases for generative AI, which executives previously predicted would take years to achieve, might ultimately be delivered in the very near future.

However, retailers are understandably cautious in their approach to this technology due to the notable limitations of GAI. In a previous blog post, we discussed both the benefits and the risks retailers …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contact Merge]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2801/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2801/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/contact_merge.png" title="I actually kind of feel like John and Surf King wouldn't like each other, which is a lot to unpack." alt="I actually kind of feel like John and Surf King wouldn't like each other, which is a lot to unpack." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub CLI project command is now generally available!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-11-github-cli-project-command-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-11-github-cli-project-command-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:52:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your use of GitHub Projects on the command line and in GitHub Actions with the new project CLI command.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing the Future of Automation with Camunda Platform 8’s Headless Workflow Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=85359&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=85359</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/camunda-platform-8-headless-workflow-engine/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8's API-first design makes it a capable solution for headless automation.
The post Embracing the Future of Automation with Camunda Platform 8’s Headless Workflow Engine appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wulf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 224]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67277</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-224/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T17:14:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another sprint has come to an end, accompanied by a wave of bug fixes 🌊🪲. Our team’s hard work has allowed us to eliminate over 40 New Boards Hub bugs last sprint. With sprint 225, we are ready to activate the “Try the New Boards Hub”
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 224 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An open-source gymnasium for machine learning assisted computer architecture design]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/an-open-source-gymnasium-for-computer.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/an-open-source-gymnasium-for-computer.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T17:00:00.010Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Amir Yazdanbakhsh, Research Scientist, and Vijay Janapa Reddi, Visiting Researcher, Google Research




Computer Architecture research has a long history of developing simulators and tools to evaluate and shape the design of computer systems. For example, the SimpleScalar simulator was introduced in the late 1990s and allowed researchers to explore various microarchitectural ideas. Computer architecture simulators and tools, such as gem5, DRAMSys, and many more have played a significant role in advancing computer architecture research. Since then, these shared resources and infrastructure have benefited industry and academia and have enabled researchers to systematically build on each other's work, leading to significant advances in the field. 



Nonetheless, computer architectu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demonstrating end-to-end traceability with pull requests]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-11-demonstrating-end-to-end-traceability-with-pull-requests/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-11-demonstrating-end-to-end-traceability-with-pull-requests/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce developer and auditor friction involved in demonstrating compliance and maintaining end-to-end traceability by focusing your efforts around the pull request.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to become a developer advocate: Part 4, submitting to a call for papers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-4-submitting-to-a-call-for-papers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-4-submitting-to-a-call-for-papers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four steps toward writing a great abstract to submit to a conference call for papers (CFP).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform Alpha Release July 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=85318&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=85318</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/camunda-platform-alpha-release-july-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to announce the July 2023 alpha release of Camunda Platform. Check out what's new.
The post Camunda Platform Alpha Release July 2023 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know the Elastic Community series: meet Sagar Patel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/get-to-know-the-elastic-community-series-meet-sagar-patel</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/get-to-know-the-elastic-community-series-meet-sagar-patel"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this get to know the Elastic Community series, meet Sagar Patel. Sagar started his IT career in 2016 is an Elastic Certified Engineer with 6+ years of experience in developing cognitive search and log monitoring applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ully Sampaio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know the Elastic Community series: meet Sagar Patel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/get-to-know-the-elastic-community-series-meet-sagar-patel</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/get-to-know-the-elastic-community-series-meet-sagar-patel"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Sagar Patel started his IT career in 2016 and started working on enterprise search tools. He is an Elastic Certified Engineer with 6+ years of experience in the development of cognitive search and log monitoring applications. Sagar has hands-on expertise with various search technologies, including Elasticsearch, and a track record of creating enterprise search projects to assist content processing, including document classification and relevance optimization. He worked on extracting content from scanned files or images using the optical character recognition (OCR) process and has experience with extracting structured and unstructured content using machine learning (ML)/natural language processing (NLP).
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltb525e1075f51fa1d/64a85…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ully Sampaio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sanding off all the edges]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46653</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/752863358/0/sethsblog~Sanding-off-all-the-edges/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T08:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easier than ever. Solvents, power tools, market research, AI, committee meetings, online reviews and ennui are all aligned in one direction. To fit all the way in. Of course, once you sand off all the edges, it’s hard to get traction. Hard to find the texture or anything worth talking about. Smooth might not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Initializr 0.20.0 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/11/spring-initializr-0-20-0-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/11/spring-initializr-0-20-0-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stéphane Nicoll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Spring Apps Enterprise – More Power, Scalability & Extended Spring Boot Support]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/11/azure-spring-apps-enterprise-more-power-scalability-and-extended-spring-boot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/11/azure-spring-apps-enterprise-more-power-scalability-and-extended-spring-boot"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to capture custom metrics without app code changes using the Java Agent Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/custom-metrics-app-code-java-agent-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/custom-metrics-app-code-java-agent-plugin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the application you're monitoring doesn't emit the custom metrics you'd like, and you can't directly change the app code, you can use a Java Agent Plugin to automatically instrument the application and emit the custom metrics you desire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Shirazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to capture custom metrics without app code changes using the Java Agent Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/custom-metrics-app-code-java-agent-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/custom-metrics-app-code-java-agent-plugin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The Elastic APM Java Agent automatically tracks many metrics, including those that are generated through Micrometer or the OpenTelemetry Metrics API. So if your application (or the libraries it includes) already exposes metrics from one of those APIs, installing the Elastic APM Java Agent is the only step required to capture them. You'll be able to visualize and configure thresholds, alerts, and anomaly detection — and anything else you want to use them for!

The next simplest option is to generate custom metrics directly from your code (e.g., by adding code using the OpenTelemetry Metrics API directly into the application). The major downside of that approach is that it requires modifying the application, so if you can't or don't want to do that, you can easily produce the desired custo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Shirazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Kiwi.com chose Camunda Platform 8 for Their Customer Booking Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=80543&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=80543</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/why-camunda-platform-8-kiwi/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why Camunda Platform 8? Learn how leading travel-tech company Kiwi.com utilizes Camunda 8 to overcome challenges using process orchestration.
The post Why Kiwi.com chose Camunda Platform 8 for Their Customer Booking Journey appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – AWS Glue Crawlers Now Supports Apache Iceberg, Amazon RDS Updates, and More – July 10, 2023]]></title>
        <id>701f6bc4cf015f1b7cea2cae9e08dc24699d81af</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-aws-glue-crawlers-now-supports-apache-iceberg-amazon-rds-updates-and-more-july-10-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US celebrated Independence Day last week on July 4 with fireworks and barbecues across the country. But fireworks weren’t the only thing that launched last week. Let’s have a look! Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my attention: AWS Glue – AWS Glue Crawlers now supports Apache Iceberg tables. Apache Iceberg […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The commonweal]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46640</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/752647118/0/sethsblog~The-commonweal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who has read, talked about and taken action around my new book, The Song of Signficance. If you have a chance to post a review, that would be great. And you can find the podcasts here. The first step in making things better is talking about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform apply as code: The multispace pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-apply-as-code-the-multispace-pattern</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-apply-as-code-the-multispace-pattern"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use the Terraform Cloud/Enterprise provider to coordinate apply and destroy commands on downstream workspaces in Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ACL 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/google-at-acl-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/google-at-acl-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:02:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Malaya Jules, Program Manager, Google




  This week, the 61st annual meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics (ACL), a premier conference covering a broad spectrum of research areas that are concerned with computational approaches to natural language, is taking place online.


  As a leader in natural language processing and understanding, and a Diamond Level sponsor of ACL 2023, Google will showcase the latest research in the field with over 50 publications, and active involvement in a variety of workshops and tutorials.
bold).
 

Board and Organizing Committee
Dan Garrette

Workshop chairs include: Annie Louis

Publication chairs include: Lei Shu

Program Committee includes: Vinodkumar Prabhakaran, Najoung Kim, Markus Freitag


 

Spotlight papers
NusaCrowd: O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discernment in creativity]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44872</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/752488826/0/sethsblog~Discernment-in-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hard part isn’t good ideas. It never has been. The hard part is choosing. Ask GPT for ten subtitles for your book, or sixteen ways to hold a surprise party, and you’ll be delighted at how useful they are. Ask Dreamstudio or Kittl for some logo designs, same thing. There is creativity in discernment. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized as a Visionary in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for APM and Observability for the third consecutive year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-critical-capabilities-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-critical-capabilities-apm"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why Elastic was recognized as a visionary in the latest 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for APM and Observability! From Completeness of Vision to Ability to Execute, this new report covers all the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic recognized as a Visionary in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for APM and Observability for the third consecutive year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-critical-capabilities-apm</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-observability-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-critical-capabilities-apm"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are excited to announce that Elastic® has been recognized as a Visionary in the 2023 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Application Performance Monitoring (APM) and Observability for the third year in a row. In addition, Elastic scored among the three highest scoring vendors for three out of six Use Cases in the 2023 Gartner® Critical Capabilities for Application Performance Monitoring and Observability.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt5ce6662686913bce/64ac1dfd873fa3aa8c02fb57/APM_MQ_2023.png,APM_MQ_2023.pngElastic also scores among the three highest scoring vendors for three Use Cases in Critical Capabilities report,
While the Magic Quadrant considers Completeness of Vision and Ability to Execute, the Critical Capabilities report for APM and Observability focus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Down]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2800/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2800/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/down.png" title="It's just that I get nervous about heights." alt="It's just that I get nervous about heights." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it a skill?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44867</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/752185088/0/sethsblog~Is-it-a-skill/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If so, it might be worth learning. If so, it might pay to let someone who has learned it take care of it. Coding is a skill. But it’s not clear that the person who knows how to code should be doing your design. Teaching is a skill. But simply because someone is good at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sufficient resolution]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46627</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/751865942/0/sethsblog~Sufficient-resolution/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T09:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Johnson is known as the king of the Delta blues. One reason is that his small output was brilliant. The other, bigger reason is that the recordings that remain of his short life are among the earliest that sound good… most audio recordings from before 1936 sound antique and scratchy. The Wizard of Oz […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why External Script Task Users will Love the Camunda Platform 8 Integration Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84827&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=84827</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/external-script-task-connector-integration-framework/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Integration Framework is a significant upgrade over external script tasks, with improved reusability, user-friendliness, and customization.
The post Why External Script Task Users will Love the Camunda Platform 8 Integration Framework appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modular visual question answering via code generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/modular-visual-question-answering-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/modular-visual-question-answering-via.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:01:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sanjay Subramanian, PhD student, UC Berkeley, and Arsha Nagrani, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception Team




Visual question answering (VQA) is a machine learning task that requires a model to answer a question about an image or a set of images. Conventional VQA approaches need a large amount of labeled training data consisting of thousands of human-annotated question-answer pairs associated with images. In recent years, advances in large-scale pre-training have led to the development of VQA methods that perform well with fewer than fifty training examples (few-shot) and without any human-annotated VQA training data (zero-shot). However, there is still a significant performance gap between these methods and state-of-the-art fully supervised VQA methods, such as MaMMU…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Solution – Clickstream Analytics on AWS for Mobile and Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>711a0f0b733911d5daecaf567086b254c8f14f24</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-solution-clickstream-analytics-on-aws-for-mobile-and-web-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T16:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can deploy on your AWS account an end-to-end solution to capture, ingest, store, analyze, and visualize your customers’ clickstreams inside your web and mobile applications (both for Android and iOS). The solution is built on top of standard AWS services. This new solution Clickstream Analytics on AWS allows you to keep your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small doses]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44849</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/751494770/0/sethsblog~Small-doses/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you go to a health food store and buy some pills with selenium, colloidal silver or other mysterious substances in them, it’s possible that they’ll make you feel a bit better. On the other hand, if you take a large dose, you’ll get sick or possibly die. In very small doses, all you’re getting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating R&D in pharma with Elasticsearch, ESRE, LLMs, and LangChain — Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-development-pharma-elasticsearch-esre-llms-langchain-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-development-pharma-elasticsearch-esre-llms-langchain-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to leverage ESRE and generative AI in order to enable R&D organizations to interact with data effectively and make better decisions in the drug discovery process. The challenges with privacy and missing context will also be addressed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerio Arvizzigno,Dimitri Marx,Francesco Di Stefano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating R&D in pharma with Elasticsearch, ESRE, LLMs, and LangChain — Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-development-pharma-elasticsearch-esre-llms-langchain-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/research-development-pharma-elasticsearch-esre-llms-langchain-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Faster drug discovery leading to promising drug candidates is the main objective of the pharmaceutical industry. To support that goal, the industry has to find better ways to utilize both public and proprietary data — at speed and in a safe way.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltc027a3db22757b8a/64a83a20d60b85339768c415/elastic-blog-1-blockbusters.png,elastic-blog-1-blockbusters.png,
According to WIPO, R&D patent analytics can help researchers and innovators to assist to:

Avoid duplicating research and development effort 
Determine the patentability of their inventions 
Avoid infringing other inventors’ patents 
Estimate the value of their or other inventors’ patents
Exploit technology from patent applications that have never been granted, are not valid in c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerio Arvizzigno,Dimitri Marx,Francesco Di Stefano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frankenstein Claim Permutations]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2799/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2799/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/frankenstein_claim_permutations.png" title="When I began trying to form a new claim by stitching together these parts in such an unnatural way, some called me mad." alt="When I began trying to form a new claim by stitching together these parts in such an unnatural way, some called me mad." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seamless Integration with Message Queue Technology through Inbound Subscription Connectors]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84716&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=84716</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/inbound-subscription-connectors-message-queue-integration/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T20:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With new inbound subscription Connectors, you can achieve a seamless and full-featured integration with message queue systems like Kafka, RabbitMQ and more.
The post Seamless Integration with Message Queue Technology through Inbound Subscription Connectors appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pic2Word: Mapping pictures to words for zero-shot composed image retrieval]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/pic2word-mapping-pictures-to-words-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/pic2word-mapping-pictures-to-words-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kuniaki Saito, Student Researcher, Google Research, Cloud AI Team, and Kihyuk Sohn, Research Scientist, Google Research





Image retrieval plays a crucial role in search engines. Typically, their users rely on either image or text as a query to retrieve a desired target image. However, text-based retrieval has its limitations, as describing the target image accurately using words can be challenging. For instance, when searching for a fashion item, users may want an item whose specific attribute, e.g., the color of a logo or the logo itself, is different from what they find in a website. Yet searching for the item in an existing search engine is not trivial since precisely describing the fashion item by text can be challenging. To address this fact, composed image retrieval (CIR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility considerations behind code search and code view]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-06-accessibility-considerations-behind-code-search-and-code-view/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-06-accessibility-considerations-behind-code-search-and-code-view/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at how we improved the readability of code on GitHub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Confidential Kubernetes: Use Confidential Virtual Machines and Enclaves to improve your cluster security]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/07/06/confidential-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/07/06/confidential-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Fabian Kammel (Edgeless Systems), Mikko Ylinen (Intel), Tobin Feldman-Fitzthum (IBM)
In this blog post, we will introduce the concept of Confidential Computing (CC) to improve any computing environment's security and privacy properties. Further, we will show how
the Cloud-Native ecosystem, particularly Kubernetes, can benefit from the new compute paradigm.
Confidential Computing is a concept that has been introduced previously in the cloud-native world. The
Confidential Computing Consortium (CCC) is a project community in the Linux Foundation
that already worked on
Defining and Enabling Confidential Computing.
In the Whitepaper,
they provide a great motivation for the use of Confidential Computing:
Data exists in three states: in transit, at rest, and in use. …Protecting sensitive…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service Major Updates: Global View, Import and Export from Local Disk, and Additional Post-launch Actions]]></title>
        <id>14172370fc6fd2b9a6a7a63a8138f20ba11f6302</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-application-migration-service-major-updates-global-view-import-and-export-from-local-disk-and-additional-post-launch-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T17:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service simplifies, expedites, and reduces the cost of migrating your applications to AWS. It allows you to lift and shift many physical, virtual, or cloud servers without compatibility issues, performance disruption, or long cutover windows. You can minimize time-intensive, error-prone manual processes by automating replication and conversion of your source servers from physical, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Consul cluster peering locally with Minikube]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploy-consul-cluster-peering-locally-with-minikube</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploy-consul-cluster-peering-locally-with-minikube"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use Minikube to create multiple Kubernetes clusters with Consul and test cluster peering configurations in your local development environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Google Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-google-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-google-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is co-authored by Zack Kayyali and Hicham (he-sham) Mourad]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary Kayyali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey 2023: Inside the maturity model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-inside-the-maturity-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-inside-the-maturity-model"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s 2023 State of Cloud Strategy Survey debuts a new cloud-maturity model, which reveals how more-mature organizations enjoy better business outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Generative AI with LLM Hands-on Course, Amazon SageMaker Data Wrangler Updates, and More – July 3, 2023]]></title>
        <id>3fb74ddd0280e06d6387d7abc8383d64678fa7dc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-generative-ai-with-llm-hands-on-course-amazon-sagemaker-data-wrangler-updates-and-more-july-3-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T18:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In last week’s AWS Week in Review post, Danilo mentioned that it’s summer in London. Well, I’m based in Singapore, and it’s mostly summer here. But, June is a special month here as it marks the start of durian season. Starting next week, I’ll be travelling to Thailand, Malaysia, and the Philippines. But before I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.16 enhances service mesh reliability, user experience, and security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-16-enhances-service-mesh-reliability-user-experience-and-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-16-enhances-service-mesh-reliability-user-experience-and-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.16 adds new reliability, scalability, security, service mesh UX, extensibility, and service discovery capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the first Machine Unlearning Challenge]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/announcing-first-machine-unlearning.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/announcing-first-machine-unlearning.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T21:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Fabian Pedregosa and Eleni Triantafillou, Research Scientists, Google





Deep learning has recently driven tremendous progress in a wide array of applications, ranging from realistic image generation and impressive retrieval systems to language models that can hold human-like conversations. While this progress is very exciting, the widespread use of deep neural network models requires caution: as guided by Google’s AI Principles, we seek to develop AI technologies responsibly by understanding and mitigating potential risks, such as the propagation and amplification of unfair biases and protecting user privacy.
 

Fully erasing the influence of the data requested to be deleted is challenging since, aside from simply deleting it from databases where it’s stored, it also requires …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-device diffusion plugins for conditioned text-to-image generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/on-device-diffusion-plugins-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/on-device-diffusion-plugins-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:10:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yang Zhao and Tingbo Hou, Software Engineers, Core ML




In recent years, diffusion models have shown great success in text-to-image generation, achieving high image quality, improved inference performance, and expanding our creative inspiration. Nevertheless, it is still challenging to efficiently control the generation, especially with conditions that are difficult to describe with text.



Today, we announce MediaPipe diffusion plugins, which enable controllable text-to-image generation to be run on-device. Expanding upon our prior work on GPU inference for on-device large generative models, we introduce new low-cost solutions for controllable text-to-image generation that can be plugged into existing diffusion models and their Low-Rank Adaptation (LoRA) variants. 




Text-t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Migrating to Camunda Platform 8 Accelerates Existing Process Automation Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84254&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=84254</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/migration-camunda-platform-8-accelerates-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how you can gain a competitive advantage by unlocking the unparalleled capabilities of the latest version of Camunda technology.
The post How Migrating to Camunda Platform 8 Accelerates Existing Process Automation Projects appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Liberadzki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HCP Consul management plane with  cloud-based observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-consul-management-plane-with-cloud-based-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hcp-consul-management-plane-with-cloud-based-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HCP Consul management plane now offers deeper insights to your Consul deployments via cloud-based observability and seamlessly links new and existing self-managed Consul clusters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use the new Constructed Inventory Feature in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-use-the-new-constructed-inventory-feature-in-aap-2.4</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-use-the-new-constructed-inventory-feature-in-aap-2.4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New Constructed Inventory Feature
 
In this blog we introduced the idea for a new smarter way of handling inventory based on the Ansible constructed plugin. Now in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4, we have introduced this as a fully supported feature and this blog aims to introduce you to it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Rominger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Verifying Container Image Signatures Within CRI Runtimes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/06/29/container-image-signature-verification/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/06/29/container-image-signature-verification/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
The Kubernetes community has been signing their container image-based artifacts
since release v1.24. While the graduation of the corresponding enhancement
from alpha to beta in v1.26 introduced signatures for the binary artifacts,
other projects followed the approach by providing image signatures for their
releases, too. This means that they either create the signatures within their
own CI/CD pipelines, for example by using GitHub actions, or rely on the
Kubernetes image promotion process to automatically sign the images by
proposing pull requests to the k/k8s.io repository. A requirement for
using this process is that the project is part of the kubernetes or
kubernetes-sigs GitHub organization, so that they can utilize the community
infrastructure for pushing images…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI with Large Language Models — New Hands-on Course by DeepLearning.AI and AWS]]></title>
        <id>54f117b5accead3dc22e75b2f9aa923036b2bdb2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/generative-ai-with-large-language-models-new-hands-on-course-by-deeplearning-ai-and-aws/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T15:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI has taken the world by storm, and we’re starting to see the next wave of widespread adoption of AI with the potential for every customer experience and application to be reinvented with generative AI. Generative AI lets you to create new content and ideas including conversations, stories, images, videos, and music. Generative AI […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第232話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361388410249</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361388410249"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why transentis consulting Chose Camunda Platform 8 SaaS for Their Vacation Request Process]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84053</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/why-camunda-platform-8-transentis/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T01:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why transentis consulting chose Camunda Platform 8 SaaS to digitize their vacation request process.
The post Why transentis consulting Chose Camunda Platform 8 SaaS for Their Vacation Request Process appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Ashworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unifying image-caption and image-classification datasets with prefix conditioning]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/unifying-image-caption-and-image.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/unifying-image-caption-and-image.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T21:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kuniaki Saito, Student Researcher, Cloud AI Team, and Kihyuk Sohn, Research Scientist, Perception Team




Pre-training visual language (VL) models on web-scale image-caption datasets has recently emerged as a powerful alternative to traditional pre-training on image classification data. Image-caption datasets are considered to be more “open-domain” because they contain broader scene types and vocabulary words, which result in models with strong performance in few- and zero-shot recognition tasks. However, images with fine-grained class descriptions can be rare, and the class distribution can be imbalanced since image-caption datasets do not go through manual curation. By contrast, large-scale classification datasets, such as ImageNet, are often curated and can thus provide fine-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS AppFabric Improves Application Observability for SaaS Applications]]></title>
        <id>219ecb75a7af29bfa01f68ada61052b158a23ec8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-appfabric-improves-application-observability-for-saas-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T17:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s business landscape, companies strive to equip their employees with the most suitable and efficient tools to perform their jobs effectively. To achieve this goal, many companies turn to Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) applications. This approach allows companies to optimize their workflows, enhance employee productivity, and focus their resources on core business activities rather than software […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp acquires BluBracket to add secrets scanning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-acquisition-of-blubracket</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-acquisition-of-blubracket"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BluBracket’s secrets-scanning functionality will complement HashiCorp Vault’s secrets management to help prevent accidental leaks and fight secret sprawl.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.6 beta adds node pools, UX updates, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-6-adds-node-pools-ux-updates-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-6-adds-node-pools-ux-updates-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.6 introduces node pools to help manage multi-tenant Nomad clusters, along with a redesigned job UI, Nomad Pack improvements, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.4</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T13:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of new features found in the Ansible Automation Platform 2.4 release]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choose an image for your organization]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67205</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/choose-an-image-for-your-organization/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T12:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to announce that you can now choose an image for your Azure DevOps organization and replace the automatically generated image. Learn how to change your organization’s image
BEFORE
The ability to change an organization’s image has been a long standing feature request in the Developer Community with over 150 votes.
The post Choose an image for your organization appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brenner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Step Functions Versions and Aliases, EC2 Instances with Graviton3E Processors, and More – June 26, 2023]]></title>
        <id>b5f480df9c754ac5d9a62c25e2a998f30d088412</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-step-functions-versions-and-aliases-ec2-instances-with-graviton3e-processors-and-more-june-26-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s now summer in the northern hemisphere, and you can feel it in London where I live. But let’s not get distracted by the nice weather and go through your AWS updates from the previous seven days. Last Week’s Launches Another interesting week with many announcements! Here are some that got more of my attention: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Terraform continuous validation use cases for AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/8-terraform-continuous-validation-use-cases-for-aws-google-cloud-and-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/8-terraform-continuous-validation-use-cases-for-aws-google-cloud-and-azure"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how you can use Terraform check blocks and continuous validation with AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on AWS to AWS GovCloud in the United States]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-aws-to-aws-govcloud-in-the-us</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-aws-to-aws-govcloud-in-the-us"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is co-authored by Zack Kayyali and Hicham (he-sham) Mourad
 
Deploying Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform Foundation
 
The steps below detail how to install Ansible Automation Platform on AWS United States GovCloud from the AWS Marketplace. The steps to deploy into AWS GovCloud and AWS Commercial cloud are nearly identical. Before starting your deployment process, please ensure the AWS account you are using to deploy has the following IAM roles. These IAM roles are required to deploy the AWS foundation stack offering. The foundation stack offering here refers to the base Ansible Automation Platform 2 deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary Kayyali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Ansible Lightspeed with IBM Watson Code Assistant Technical Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/welcome-to-the-ansible-lightspeed-technical-preview</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/welcome-to-the-ansible-lightspeed-technical-preview"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T12:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of what to expect with the technology preview of Ansible Lightspeed with IBM Watson Code Assistant, a new generative AI service available now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Open Source Software Gives You Access to Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=84019</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/06/how-open-source-software-gives-you-access-to-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open source software provides access to innovations and latest technologies. Check out this post to explore some of the ways that open source software gives companies access to innovation.
The post How Open Source Software Gives You Access to Innovation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preference learning with automated feedback for cache eviction]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/preference-learning-with-automated.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/preference-learning-with-automated.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T19:24:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ramki Gummadi, Software Engineer, Google and Kevin Chen, Software Engineer, YouTube





Caching is a ubiquitous idea in computer science that significantly improves the performance of storage and retrieval systems by storing a subset of popular items closer to the client based on request patterns. An important algorithmic piece of cache management is the decision policy used for dynamically updating the set of items being stored, which has been extensively optimized over several decades, resulting in several efficient and robust heuristics. While applying machine learning to cache policies has shown promising results in recent years (e.g., LRB, LHD, storage applications), it remains a challenge to outperform robust heuristics in a way that can generalize reliably beyond benchmar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A HashiCorp Ambassador at HashiDays London]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-hashicorp-ambassador-at-hashidays-london</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/a-hashicorp-ambassador-at-hashidays-london"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Ambassador Chris van Meer shares his experiences at HashiDays London.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoundStorm: Efficient parallel audio generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/soundstorm-efficient-parallel-audio.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/soundstorm-efficient-parallel-audio.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T18:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zalán Borsos, Research Software Engineer, and Marco Tagliasacchi, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Research







The recent progress in generative AI unlocked the possibility of creating new content in several different domains, including text, vision and audio. These models often rely on the fact that raw data is first converted to a compressed format as a sequence of tokens. In the case of audio, neural audio codecs (e.g., SoundStream or EnCodec) can efficiently compress waveforms to a compact representation, which can be inverted to reconstruct an approximation of the original audio signal. Such a representation consists of a sequence of discrete audio tokens, capturing the local properties of sounds (e.g., phonemes) and their temporal structure (e.g., prosody). By re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault 1.14 brings ACME for PKI, AWS roles, and more improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-14-brings-acme-for-pki-aws-roles-and-more-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-1-14-brings-acme-for-pki-aws-roles-and-more-improvements"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault 1.14 includes the Vault Secrets Operator GA, ACME PKI, and a new OpenLDAP secrets engine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Cloud Automation with amazon.aws 6.0.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-6.0.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.aws-6.0.0"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to Amazon Web Services (AWS) infrastructure automation, the latest release of the certified amazon.aws Collection for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform brings a number of enhancements to improve the overall user experience and speed up the process from development to production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: AI for Social Good]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/responsible-ai-at-google-research-ai.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/responsible-ai-at-google-research-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T20:57:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jimmy Tobin and Katrin Tomanek, Software Engineers, Google Research, AI for Social Good


Google’s AI for Social Good team consists of researchers, engineers, volunteers, and others with a shared focus on positive social impact. Our mission is to demonstrate AI’s societal benefit by enabling real-world value, with projects spanning work in public health, accessibility, crisis response, climate and energy, and nature and society. We believe that the best way to drive positive change in underserved communities is by partnering with change-makers and the organizations they serve.


 


In this blog post we discuss work done by Project Euphonia, a team within AI for Social Good, that aims to improve automatic speech recognition (ASR) for people with disordered speech. For people with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s first braiding of non-Abelian anyons]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/the-worlds-first-braiding-of-non.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/the-worlds-first-braiding-of-non.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T17:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Trond Andersen and Yuri Lensky, Research Scientists, Google Quantum AI Team  






Imagine you’re shown two identical objects and then asked to close your eyes. When you open your eyes, you see the same two objects in the same position. How can you determine if they have been swapped back and forth? Intuition and the laws of quantum mechanics agree: If the objects are truly identical, there is no way to tell. 



While this sounds like common sense, it only applies to our familiar three-dimensional world. Researchers have predicted that for a special type of particle, called an anyon, that is restricted to move only in a two-dimensional (2D) plane, quantum mechanics allows for something quite different. Anyons are indistinguishable from one another and some, non-Abelian anyons, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 Hpc7g Instances Powered by AWS Graviton3E Processors Optimized for High Performance Computing Workloads]]></title>
        <id>5ea979c45bdfa8e4b408386066d2c67700c1c40d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-hpc7g-instances-powered-by-aws-graviton3e-processors-optimized-for-high-performance-computing-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T20:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2022, Adam Selipsky, CEO of AWS, explained high performance computing (HPC) workloads typically can either be compute-intensive, compute- and networking-intensive, or data- and memory-intensive in his keynote. Compute workloads include weather forecasting, computational fluid dynamics, and financial options pricing. To help with this, you have Amazon EC2 Hpc6a instances, which deliver up […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon EC2 C7gn Instances: Graviton3E Processors and Up To 200 Gbps Network Bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>4b5a7a85829664e1b14fef7adcba05a5d8436262</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c7gn-instances-graviton3e-processors-and-up-to-200-gbps-network-bandwidth/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T20:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The C7gn instances that we previewed last year are now available and you can start using them today. The instances are designed for your most demanding network-intensive workloads (firewalls, virtual routers, load balancers, and so forth), data analytics, and tightly-coupled cluster computing jobs. They are powered by AWS Graviton3E processors and support up to 200 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to streamline and secure your SaaS applications at AWS Applications Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>5dc3826279a8cfb6eabd79bfa44f3c629827141f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/learn-how-to-streamline-and-secure-your-saas-applications-at-aws-applications-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T18:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies continue to adopt software as a service (SaaS) applications at a rapid clip, with recent research showing that the average SaaS portfolio now has at least 200 applications. While organizations purchase these purpose-built tools to make their employees more productive, they now must contend with growing security complexities, context switching, and data silos. If […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Goldstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Scene Changes in Audiovisual Content]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/77a61d3eaad6</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/detecting-scene-changes-in-audiovisual-content-77a61d3eaad6?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T16:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avneesh Saluja, Andy Yao, Hossein Taghavi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking the 2023 HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey [Video]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/unpacking-the-2023-hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-video</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/unpacking-the-2023-hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-video"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch this 10-minute video for an insightful overview of the survey’s key findings and how HashiCorp can help your organization make the most of the cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Amazon EC2 Instance Connect Endpoint, Detective, Amazon S3 Dual Layer Encryption, Amazon Verified Permission – June 19, 2023]]></title>
        <id>3652b5bcb9a6bda391b1dd7ad03ab1fb81ac3d06</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-amazon-ec2-instance-connect-endpoint-detective-amazon-s3-dual-layer-encryption-amazon-verified-permission-june-19-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T19:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I’ll meet you at AWS partner’s Jamf Nation Live in Amsterdam where we’re showing how to use Amazon EC2 Mac to deploy your remote developer workstations or configure your iOS CI/CD pipelines in the cloud. Last Week’s Launches While I was traveling last week, I kept an eye on the AWS News. Here […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 223]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67177</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-223/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T18:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the risk of sounding repetitive, sprint 223 was dedicated to resolving bugs. Looks like sprint 224 will be much of the same. We continue to make great progress, but we have a little way to go before the New Boards Hub is ready for general availability.
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 223 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at CVPR 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/google-at-cvpr-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/06/google-at-cvpr-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T18:00:00.018Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shaina Mehta, Program Manager, Google




This week marks the beginning of the premier annual Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition conference (CVPR 2023), held in-person in Vancouver, BC (with additional virtual content). As a leader in computer vision research and a Platinum Sponsor, Google Research will have a strong presence across CVPR 2023 with ~90 papers being presented at the main conference and active involvement in over 40 conference workshops and tutorials.




If you are attending CVPR this year, please stop by our booth to chat with our researchers who are actively exploring the latest techniques for application to various areas of machine perception. Our researchers will also be available to talk about and demo several recent efforts, including on-device ML applic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GoDaddy Implemented a Multi-Region Event-Driven Platform at Scale]]></title>
        <id>a98489d395f0c435cc777fcf89a3a9ff10dd4933</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-godaddy-implemented-a-multi-region-event-driven-platform-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T17:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoDaddy, a leading global provider of domain registration and web hosting services, has served over 84 million domains and 22 million customers since its establishment in 1997. Among its various internal systems, the Customer Signal Platform provides tooling to capture, analyze, and act on customer and product data to drive better business outcomes. With this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>