<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-20T01:18:00.308Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-20T01:18:00.308Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Single Pod Access Mode for PersistentVolumes Graduates to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/20/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/20/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chris Henzie (Google)
With the release of Kubernetes v1.27 the ReadWriteOncePod feature has graduated
to beta. In this blog post, we'll take a closer look at this feature, what it
does, and how it has evolved in the beta release.
What is ReadWriteOncePod?
ReadWriteOncePod is a new access mode for
PersistentVolumes (PVs)
and PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs)
introduced in Kubernetes v1.22. This access mode enables you to restrict volume
access to a single pod in the cluster, ensuring that only one pod can write to
the volume at a time. This can be particularly useful for stateful workloads
that require single-writer access to storage.
For more context on access modes and how ReadWriteOncePod works read
What are access modes and why are they important?
in the Introducing Single Pod Acces…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Building without Limits at AWS Developer Innovation Day]]></title>
        <id>5642e5e26f54b4e2d613344cf7fb6a8727367ef7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/discover-building-without-limits-at-aws-developer-innovation-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T18:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We hope you can join us on Wednesday, April 26, for a free-to-attend online event, AWS Developer Innovation Day. AWS will stream the event simultaneously across multiple platforms, including LinkedIn Live, Twitter, YouTube, and Twitch. Developer Innovation Day is a brand-new event designed specifically for developers and development teams. In the event, sessions throughout the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI at Google Research: Technology, AI, Society and Culture]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/responsible-ai-at-google-research.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T18:12:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lauren Wilcox, Senior Staff Research Scientist, on behalf of the Technology, AI, Society, and Culture Team




Google sees AI as a foundational and transformational technology, with recent advances in generative AI technologies, such as LaMDA, PaLM, Imagen, Parti, MusicLM, and similar machine learning (ML) models, some of which are now being incorporated into our products. This transformative potential requires us to be responsible not only in how we advance our technology, but also in how we envision which technologies to build, and how we assess the social impact AI and ML-enabled technologies have on the world. This endeavor necessitates fundamental and applied research with an interdisciplinary lens that engages with — and accounts for — the social, cultural, economic, and ot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private vulnerability reporting now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-19-private-vulnerability-reporting-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-19-private-vulnerability-reporting-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T16:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open source maintainers and security researchers embrace a new best practice to report and fix vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing npm package provenance]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-19-introducing-npm-package-provenance/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-19-introducing-npm-package-provenance/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T16:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to verifiably link npm packages to their source repository and build instructions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The natural size]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44231</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/736222769/0/sethsblog~The-natural-size/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how many people come over for dinner, you’re only going to be able to engage with a few. And no matter how big the crowd in the arena, the musicians can only see the faces of a few hundred. An investor can only be engaged and smart about a very small number of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.2.0-RC1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/19/spring-for-graphql-1-2-0-rc1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/19/spring-for-graphql-1-2-0-rc1-released"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rossen Stoyanchev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond the build: Why runtime security is critical for container protection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-runtime-security-container-protection</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-runtime-security-container-protection"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers and microservices have changed the game — and at Elastic we believe implementing container runtime security is essential. We’ve taken a novel approach to simplify container security in our release of Container Workload Protection features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Rohan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT and Elasticsearch: OpenAI meets private data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatgpt-elasticsearch-openai-meets-private-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatgpt-elasticsearch-openai-meets-private-data"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the integration of Elasticsearch's search relevance capability with ChatGPT's question-answering capability to enhance your domain-specific knowledge base. Learn how to harness ChatGPT to enrich your information repository like never before!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Vestal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond the build: Why runtime security is critical for container protection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-runtime-security-container-protection</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/march-2023-launch-runtime-security-container-protection"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Containers and microservices have changed the game: They allow organizations to ship apps faster and make better use of hardware. They encourage modular software design. And containers help teams embrace the cloud-native paradigms of scalability, mobility, and resilience. It’s safe to say that containers have shaken things up. 
Why is it hard to protect containers?
Securing containers isn’t easy, and most companies are failing to protect their containerized applications. The Cloud Native Computing Foundation reported that more than half of its surveyed organizations suffered a security incident involving containers in the last 12 months.* The Cloud Security Alliance said that containers continue to be a “prime target for attackers because organizations lack sufficient security control me…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Rohan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT and Elasticsearch: OpenAI meets private data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatgpt-elasticsearch-openai-meets-private-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/chatgpt-elasticsearch-openai-meets-private-data"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Combine Elasticsearch's search relevance with OpenAI's ChatGPT's question-answering capabilities to query your data. In this blog, you'll learn how to connect ChatGPT to proprietary data stores using Elasticsearch and build question/answer capabilities for your data.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltfefb79796adf0e48/643ffcc2762f385962b0f7f6/blog-elastic-elasticdocs-gpt-list-the-steps-free-trial.png,blog-elastic-elasticdocs-gpt-list-the-steps-free-trial.pngWhat is ChatGPT?,
In recent months, there has been a surge of excitement around ChatGPT, a groundbreaking AI model created by OpenAI. But what exactly is ChatGPT? 

Based on the powerful GPT architecture, ChatGPT is designed to understand and generate human-like responses to text inputs. GPT stands for "Gen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Vestal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differentially private heatmaps]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/differentially-private-heatmaps.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/differentially-private-heatmaps.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T20:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Badih Ghazi, Staff Research Scientist, and Nachiappan Valliappan, Staff Software Engineer, Google Research






Recently, differential privacy (DP) has emerged as a mathematically robust notion of user privacy for data aggregation and machine learning (ML), with practical deployments including the 2022 US Census and in industry. Over the last few years, we have open-sourced libraries for privacy-preserving analytics and ML and have been constantly enhancing their capabilities. Meanwhile, new algorithms have been developed by the research community for several analytic tasks involving private aggregation of data. 
 

One such important data aggregation method is the heatmap. Heatmaps are popular for visualizing aggregated data in two or more dimensions. They are widely used in ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: Efficient SELinux volume relabeling (Beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/18/kubernetes-1-27-efficient-selinux-relabeling-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/18/kubernetes-1-27-efficient-selinux-relabeling-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jan Šafránek (Red Hat)
The problem
On Linux with Security-Enhanced Linux (SELinux) enabled, it's traditionally
the container runtime that applies SELinux labels to a Pod and all its volumes.
Kubernetes only passes the SELinux label from a Pod's securityContext fields
to the container runtime.
The container runtime then recursively changes SELinux label on all files that
are visible to the Pod's containers. This can be time-consuming if there are
many files on the volume, especially when the volume is on a remote filesystem.
Note
subPath of a volume, only that subPath of the whole
volume is relabeled. This allows two pods that have two different SELinux labels
to use the same volume, as long as they use different subpaths of it.

If a Pod does not have any SELinux label assigned in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s happening at KubeCon Europe 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-s-happening-at-kubecon-europe-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/what-s-happening-at-kubecon-europe-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attending KubeCon EU, either in person or online? Check out what HashiCorp is doing and talking about at the event, and learn about recent Kubernetes-related product features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub joins industry commitment to curb cyber mercenaries]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-18-github-joins-industry-commitment-to-curb-cyber-mercenaries/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-18-github-joins-industry-commitment-to-curb-cyber-mercenaries/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:26:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub is proud to join 40 companies endorsing the Cybersecurity Tech Accord principles limiting offensive operations in cyberspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.16 improves automatic HCL conversion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-16-improves-automatic-hcl-conversion</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-16-improves-automatic-hcl-conversion"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform v0.16 improves automatic conversion of configuration code from HCL to supported languages by enabling type coercion and providing better support for iterators and functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce Lookups in HashSet, Dictionary and Other Collections With ReSharper]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=341154</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/04/18/reduce-lookups-in-hashset-dictionary-and-other-collections-with-resharper/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T13:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many C# projects contain numerous places where developers add items to collections like HashSet and Dictionary. Quite often, there’s a check to verify whether the item is already in the collection. However, this may be quite wasteful, as the Add() and TryAdd() methods on these collections already do that check for you – occupying the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maarten Balliauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate External Systems Effortlessly with Custom Connectors in Camunda Platform – No Java Coding Required!]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78910&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78910</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/create-custom-template-based-on-rest-connector/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, learn how to create a new custom Connector for Camunda Platform in just a few simple steps and start orchestrating faster.
The post Integrate External Systems Effortlessly with Custom Connectors in Camunda Platform – No Java Coding Required! appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bastian Koerber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Space Git Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=space&amp;p=342596</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/space/2023/04/18/space-git-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T09:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you strive to deliver quality code smoothly and steadily? For development teams that practice a continuous release cycle, establishing a delivery flow can require significant effort when it comes to coordinating team members, setting up processes, and integrating multiple tools. To reduce this burden, we’re introducing the JetBrains Space Git flow, a complete process […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgenia Verbina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The empathy device]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44269</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/736050983/0/sethsblog~The-empathy-device/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s interesting to realize that mirrors weren’t perfected until a few hundred years ago. Human beings spend a lot of time considering our own appearance and our own feelings and most of all, our own needs. The market produces a shift. When it’s a fair and open exchange, the customer gains in power. As a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 18th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/18/this-week-in-spring-april-18th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/18/this-week-in-spring-april-18th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 1.1.0-RC1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/18/spring-authorization-server-1-1-0-rc1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/18/spring-authorization-server-1-1-0-rc1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Grandja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Authorization Server 1.0.2 and 0.4.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/18/spring-authorization-server-1-0-2-and-0-4-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/18/spring-authorization-server-1-0-2-and-0-4-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Grandja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Common Schema and OpenTelemetry — A path to better observability and security with no vendor lock-in]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecs-elastic-common-schema-otel-opentelemetry-faq</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecs-elastic-common-schema-otel-opentelemetry-faq"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how the convergence of Elastic Common Schema (ECS) and OpenTelemetry Semantic Conventions will benefit both observability and security practitioners through an industry-wide common schema.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Observability and Security Teams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic contributes Elastic Common Schema (ECS) to OpenTelemetry (OTel), helping accelerate adoption of OTel-based observability and security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecs-elastic-common-schema-otel-opentelemetry-announcement</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecs-elastic-common-schema-otel-opentelemetry-announcement"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Common Schema (ECS), an open source specification, has been accepted by the OpenTelemetry project supporting a common schema for metrics, logs, traces, and events data. Learn how this contribution and OpenTelemetry can help with your observability and security efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Exner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Common Schema and OpenTelemetry — A path to better observability and security with no vendor lock-in]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecs-elastic-common-schema-otel-opentelemetry-faq</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecs-elastic-common-schema-otel-opentelemetry-faq"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
At KubeCon Europe, it was announced that Elastic Common Schema (ECS) has been accepted by OpenTelemetry (OTel) as a contribution to the project. The goal is to achieve convergence of ECS and OpenTelemetry’s Semantic Conventions (SemConv) into a single open schema that is maintained by OpenTelemetry. This FAQ details Elastic’s contribution of Elastic Common Schema to OpenTelemetry, how it will help drive the industry to a common schema, and its impact on observability and security.
What is being announced? 
Elastic is contributing its open source project, Elastic Common Schema (ECS), to the OpenTelemetry project under the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) to help converge toward a common schema for observability and security data. A common schema helps normalize data to enable bett…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Observability and Security Teams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic contributes Elastic Common Schema (ECS) to OpenTelemetry (OTel), helping accelerate adoption of OTel-based observability and security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecs-elastic-common-schema-otel-opentelemetry-announcement</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ecs-elastic-common-schema-otel-opentelemetry-announcement"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today, data from multiple sources with schemas makes it difficult to pinpoint software issues and understand the root cause of a problem. A common schema helps normalize data to enable improved analysis, visualization, and correlation of data across observability and security solutions, accelerating root cause analysis. To ensure that our customers and the broader community can benefit from standardization, Elastic is committed to developing a common schema for metrics, logs, traces, and security events based on the Elastic Common Schema (ECS) and OpenTelemetry (OTel).  
Elastic is contributing ECS to OTel and committing to joint development of a common schema. OTel is the second highest velocity project in the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), and provides a collection of tools,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Exner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review: New Service for Generative AI and Amazon EC2 Trn1n, Inf2, and CodeWhisperer now GA – April 17, 2023]]></title>
        <id>1276fde47550c891c0d47e730e2a5344912bf074</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-new-service-for-generative-ai-and-amazon-ec2-trn1n-inf2-and-codewhisperer-now-ga-april-17-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T19:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I could almost title this blog post the “AWS AI/ML Week in Review.” This past week, we announced several new innovations and tools for building with generative AI on AWS. Let’s dive right into it. Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my attention during the previous week: Announcing Amazon Bedrock and Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-repository enablement: effortlessly scale code scanning across your repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-17-multi-repository-enablement-effortlessly-scale-code-scanning-across-your-repositories/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-17-multi-repository-enablement-effortlessly-scale-code-scanning-across-your-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T18:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve gotten great feedback on default setup, a simple way to set up code scanning on your repository. Now, you have the ability to use default setup across your organization's repositories, in just one click.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital prepwork]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44266</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/735929600/0/sethsblog~Digital-prepwork/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T08:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s so tempting to simply begin painting a wall. After all, it’s pretty easy to lay down paint. But it turns out that masking and dropcloths, painstakingly put into place, save many hours compared to cleaning up a mess afterward. The same is true for what happens when we have a new hard drive or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar – Stefan Pölz – How to test C# unit tests with mutation testing]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=330339</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/04/17/webinar-stefan-polz-how-to-test-csharp-unit-tests-with-mutation-testing/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T07:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us Thursday, May 4, 2023, 3:00 – 4:00 PM UTC (check other timezones) for our free live webinar, How to test C# unit tests with mutation testing, with Clean C# Coder, Stefan Pölz. Register now and get a reminder, or join on YouTube Executing the very short development cycle of test-driven development requires discipline […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Abuhakmeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 6.1.0-RC1, 6.0.3, 5.8.3 and 5.7.8 released, fix CVE-2023-20862]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/17/spring-security-6-1-0-rc1-6-0-3-5-8-3-and-5-7-8-released-fix-cve-2023-20862</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/17/spring-security-6-1-0-rc1-6-0-3-5-8-3-and-5-7-8-released-fix-cve-2023-20862"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcus Hert Da Coregio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.8, 3.0.2 and 3.1.0-M2 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/17/spring-shell-2-1-8-3-0-2-and-3-1-0-m2-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/17/spring-shell-2-1-8-3-0-2-and-3-1-0-m2-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving intelligence analysis through a transparent and collaborative approach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/intelligence-analysis-transparent-collaborative-approach</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/intelligence-analysis-transparent-collaborative-approach"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, the prevailing approach to public sector intelligence analysis has been to operate in secrecy. But an approach rooted in transparency, flexibility, and collaboration can offer agencies benefits that are more aligned with their missions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Teas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flightwatching helps carriers reduce CO2 emissions and save over $100K per aircraft per year, with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/flightwatching-helps-carriers-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/flightwatching-helps-carriers-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flightwatching monitors data from 600+ aircrafts on its platform, requiring a solution for storing, searching, analyzing, and creating customer dashboards that have helped boost operational efficiency for its customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Olivier Hodac, Flightwatching</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to migrate from OpenSearch to Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-migrate-from-opensearch-to-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-migrate-from-opensearch-to-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating to Elastic Cloud can eliminate the need for organizations to manage their own infrastructure, reducing maintenance costs and increasing uptime. This blog takes you through the pre-requirements and tasks required to perform a migration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Kernutt,Udayasimha Theepireddy,Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Independence with OpenTelemetry on Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTelemetry has become a key component for observability given its open standards and developer-friendly tools. See how easily Elastic Observability integrates with OTel to provide a platform that minimizes vendor lock-in and maximizes flexibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving intelligence analysis through a transparent and collaborative approach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/intelligence-analysis-transparent-collaborative-approach</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/intelligence-analysis-transparent-collaborative-approach"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
For years, the prevailing approach to intelligence analysis has been to operate in utmost secrecy — using proprietary data platforms, large external teams, and a walled-off strategy.  
In some instances it makes sense to look at intelligence platforms this way, especially for government agencies responsible for critical operations such as national intelligence, defense, fraud detection, and classified investigations. 
But in most instances, taking a different approach — one rooted in transparency, flexibility, and collaboration — can offer agencies a variety of benefits that are more aligned with the freedoms that their missions are designed to safeguard.
A proprietary, closed approach takes control out of your hands
Relying on closed software for intelligence analysis (even if those com…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Teas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flightwatching helps carriers reduce CO2 emissions and save over $100K per aircraft per year, with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/flightwatching-helps-carriers-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/flightwatching-helps-carriers-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Flightwatching is a France-based technology company enabling aircraft carriers to optimize operational maintenance costs and environmental impact with a unique real-time connected digital platform. Its proven industrial-grade software platform drives real-time connectivity via data visualization and analytics, resulting in benefits such as greater fuel savings, CO2 reduction, and improved predictive fleet maintenance. Flightwatching has been quietly growing as one of the frontrunners in the space through partnerships with leading carriers.
Wrangling data across the fleet 
The solution designed by Flightwatching is currently monitoring (on average) data from 600 aircrafts (and growing) at any given time. This is an enormous amount of information that needs to be injected into the platform…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,Olivier Hodac, Flightwatching</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to migrate from OpenSearch to Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-migrate-from-opensearch-to-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-migrate-from-opensearch-to-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
As you may know, Amazon OpenSearch Service was formerly called Amazon Elasticsearch Service and was based on the Elasticsearch open source project. In early 2021, through a fork in the code development from Elasticsearch 7.10.2, the OpenSearch project was founded with the 1.0 release.

Since this time, both code bases have gone through a lot of change with the offerings diverging further and further apart. Today, both AWS and Elastic have managed service offerings available for users to consume — Amazon OpenSearch Service (based on OpenSearch) and Elastic Cloud (leveraging the Elastic project). Elastic also provides self-managed offerings for server- or Kubernetes-based deployments.

Recently, organizations are finding it increasingly important to gain efficiencies as well as competitive…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Kernutt,Udayasimha Theepireddy,Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Independence with OpenTelemetry on Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/opentelemetry-observability"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The drive for faster, more scalable services is on the rise. Our day-to-day lives depend on apps, from a food delivery app to have your favorite meal delivered, to your banking app to manage your accounts, to even apps to schedule doctor’s appointments. These apps need to be able to grow from not only a features standpoint but also in terms of user capacity. The scale and need for global reach drives increasing complexity for these high-demand cloud applications.
In order to keep pace with demand, most of these online apps and services (for example, mobile applications, web pages, SaaS) are moving to a distributed microservice-based architecture and Kubernetes. Once you’ve migrated your app to the cloud, how do you manage and monitor production, scale, and availability of the service? Op…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmological Nostalgia Content]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2764/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2764/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/cosmological_nostalgia_content.png" title="Later renouncing clickbait, Einstein called his inclusion of cosmological content in general relativity the biggest blunder of his career." alt="Later renouncing clickbait, Einstein called his inclusion of cosmological content in general relativity the biggest blunder of his career." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.27: More fine-grained pod topology spread policies reached beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/17/fine-grained-pod-topology-spread-features-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/17/fine-grained-pod-topology-spread-features-beta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Alex Wang (Shopee), Kante Yin (DaoCloud), Kensei Nakada (Mercari)
In Kubernetes v1.19, Pod topology spread constraints
went to general availability (GA).
As time passed, we - SIG Scheduling - received feedback from users,
and, as a result, we're actively working on improving the Topology Spread feature via three KEPs.
All of these features have reached beta in Kubernetes v1.27 and are enabled by default.
This blog post introduces each feature and the use case behind each of them.
KEP-3022: min domains in Pod Topology Spread
Pod Topology Spread has the maxSkew parameter to define the degree to which Pods may be unevenly distributed.
But, there wasn't a way to control the number of domains over which we should spread.
Some users want to force spreading Pods over a minimum number of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A treaty]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44263</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/735818594/0/sethsblog~A-treaty/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-16T08:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful treaties calm things down and let us get back to what’s really important. Sometimes, the fight becomes the entire point. Not surprisingly, when we’re busy fighting a war in our head about a previous injustice or slight, we can effectively consummate a treaty without the other person even knowing about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The explosion]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45645</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/735702977/0/sethsblog~The-explosion/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-15T08:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We spend much of our worrying time on crises. Our media is filled with warnings, coverage and fear of cataclysms. The big boom, the sudden end, the crash. In fact, rot is far more common. Things decay unless we persistently work to support them. Organizations, reputations, systems, health, investments… even our teeth. For every hockey […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 benefits of migrating and consolidating your source code]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-14-3-benefits-of-migrating-and-consolidating-your-source-code/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-14-3-benefits-of-migrating-and-consolidating-your-source-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T17:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how migrating your source code and collaboration history to GitHub can lead to some surprising benefits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How generative AI is changing the way developers work]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-14-how-generative-ai-is-changing-the-way-developers-work/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-14-how-generative-ai-is-changing-the-way-developers-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid advancements in generative AI coding tools like GitHub Copilot are accelerating the next wave of software development. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond automatic differentiation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/beyond-automatic-differentiation.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/beyond-automatic-differentiation.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Matthew Streeter, Software Engineer, Google Research




Derivatives play a central role in optimization and machine learning. By locally approximating a training loss, derivatives guide an optimizer toward lower values of the loss. Automatic differentiation frameworks such as TensorFlow, PyTorch, and JAX are an essential part of modern machine learning, making it feasible to use gradient-based optimizers to train very complex models.


 


But are derivatives all we need? By themselves, derivatives only tell us how a function behaves on an infinitesimal scale. To use derivatives effectively, we often need to know more than that. For example, to choose a learning rate for gradient descent, we need to know something about how the loss function behaves over a small but finite windo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 220]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66772</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-220/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sprint 220 was again dedicated to fixing bugs. We continue to drive down that bug backlog as quickly as we can.
Issue
Date and time shift between New Boards and old
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 220 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unfettered]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44256</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/735583004/0/sethsblog~Unfettered/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s unlikely. You’re rarely going to get the freedom and resources to do your best work unfettered. The hard part (and the opportunity) is to figure out how to get comfortable with fettered. Because fettered is what’s on offer. Boundaries and scarcity aren’t simply impediments. They’re leverage points and opportunities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2023.0-RC1 and Service Releases 2022.0.5 & 2021.2.11 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/14/spring-data-2023-0-rc1-and-service-releases-2022-0-5-and-2021-2-11-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/14/spring-data-2023-0-rc1-and-service-releases-2022-0-5-and-2021-2-11-released"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg L. Turnquist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linguistics Gossip]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2763/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2763/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/linguistics_gossip.png" title="The E's wedding invitation definitely used the word LOVE more times than was strictly necessary." alt="The E's wedding invitation definitely used the word LOVE more times than was strictly necessary." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robotic deep RL at scale: Sorting waste and recyclables with a fleet of robots]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robotic-deep-rl-at-scale-sorting-waste.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/robotic-deep-rl-at-scale-sorting-waste.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T19:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sergey Levine, Research Scientist, and Alexander Herzog, Staff Research Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team
  
  
Reinforcement learning (RL) can enable robots to learn complex behaviors through trial-and-error interaction, getting better and better over time. Several of our prior works explored how RL can enable intricate robotic skills, such as robotic grasping, multi-task learning, and even playing table tennis. Although robotic RL has come a long way, we still don't see RL-enabled robots in everyday settings. The real world is complex, diverse, and changes over time, presenting a major challenge for robotic systems. However, we believe that RL should offer us an excellent tool for tackling precisely these challenges: by continually practicing, getting better, and l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring compliance in developer workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-13-ensuring-compliance-in-developer-workflows/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-13-ensuring-compliance-in-developer-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T16:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub Enterprise ensures secure and compliant developer workflows for highly regulated industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a secure Azure reference architecture with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-a-secure-azure-reference-architecture-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/building-a-secure-azure-reference-architecture-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use HashiCorp Terraform to deploy Azure resources using security best practices and policy as code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RubyMine Roadmap 2023.1–2023.2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ruby&amp;p=342539</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ruby/2023/04/rubymine-roadmap-2023-1-2023-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T15:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, we released RubyMine 2023.1, our first major update for the year 2023. We would like to express our gratitude to those who are already using it and providing us with feedback. Your responses have been incredible, with the new user interface being the most frequently mentioned aspect. We are permanently in the process […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iryna Pisklyarova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Service Connection guidance for AKS customers using Kubernetes tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66692</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/service-connection-guidance-for-aks-customers-using-kubernetes-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T13:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes tasks & Service Connections
AzureFunctionOnKubernetes
These tasks can be configured to target a Kubernetes cluster in a number of ways, using the connectionType property:
Connection Type
Azure Resource Manager
The post Service Connection guidance for AKS customers using Kubernetes tasks appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric van Wijk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline Your Ansible Module Development with Content Builder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/streamline-your-ansible-module-development-with-content-builder</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/streamline-your-ansible-module-development-with-content-builder"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo byHush Naidoo Jade Photography onUnsplash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gomathi Selvi Srinivasan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 Inf2 Instances for Low-Cost, High-Performance Generative AI Inference are Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>eb18bd7117541f6c4b0788702c73681882dd3cc4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-inf2-instances-for-low-cost-high-performance-generative-ai-inference-are-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T12:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Innovations in deep learning (DL), especially the rapid growth of large language models (LLMs), have taken the industry by storm. DL models have grown from millions to billions of parameters and are demonstrating exciting new capabilities. They are fueling new applications such as generative AI or advanced research in healthcare and life sciences. AWS has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeWhisperer, Free for Individual Use, is Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>449ba7d8898cd00282a5d25974f238fd40f0b703</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-codewhisperer-free-for-individual-use-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T12:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon CodeWhisperer, a real-time AI coding companion, is generally available and also includes a CodeWhisperer Individual tier that’s free to use for all developers. Originally launched in preview last year, CodeWhisperer keeps developers in the zone and productive, helping them write code quickly and securely and without needing to break their flow by leaving […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the SQL Connector to Streamline Trade Ops Processes]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78093&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78093</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/using-sql-connector-streamline-trade-ops-processes/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are new Connectors available for SQL databases. Here's how you can get them and a quick example of how you could use them today in financial services.
The post Using the SQL Connector to Streamline Trade Ops Processes appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataGrip 2023.1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=datagrip&amp;p=342456</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/datagrip/2023/04/13/datagrip-2023-1-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T11:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first update for DataGrip 2023.1 introduces some important fixes: DBE-17815 The delay in showing database object tooltips is back. DBE-13830 External schemas are now shown correctly in the Database Explorer. DBE-17380 We’ve fixed an issue with the unresponsive Сancel button in the Modify dialog. DBE-16138 Autocompletion in the data editor filter field functions properly.  […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa Lukonina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real and apparent risk]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43267</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/735413921/0/sethsblog~Real-and-apparent-risk/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T09:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roller coasters are one of the safest ways to travel (they end up where they begin, but that’s a different story). People pay to ride on them because they feel risky, even if they’re not. Air travel is really safe, and the airlines work overtime to reduce the perception of risk as well. That’s why […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KotlinConf 2023: A Look at the Opening Keynote]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=341654</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/04/kotlinconf-2023-opening-keynote/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T08:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the KotlinConf 2023 opening keynote, Roman Elizarov, Svetlana Isakova, and Egor Tolstoy made several exciting announcements regarding JetBrains’ recent work on the Kotlin language, while Grace Kloba shared the latest news from Google: Watch the keynote or read on for the main announcements. The conference has just started in Amsterdam and is set to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Dolgikh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin DSL Is Now the Default for New Gradle Builds]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=kotlin&amp;p=338798</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/kotlin/2023/04/kotlin-dsl-is-the-default-for-new-gradle-builds/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T08:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We always strive to help developers write better-structured and more maintainable builds. Given this aim, applying Kotlin to writing Gradle build scripts and plugins seems only natural. Kotlin provides many powerful features that make it an excellent choice for creating a DSL and significantly improve the developer experience. We have done a lot of work […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Yalyshev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.8, 5.3.27 and 5.2.24.RELEASE fix cve-2023-20863]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/13/spring-framework-6-0-8-5-3-27-and-5-2-24-release-fix-cve-2023-20863</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/13/spring-framework-6-0-8-5-3-27-and-5-2-24-release-fix-cve-2023-20863"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Clozel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Sonatype's Steve Poole and Gradle's Justin Reock on Improving Developer Productivity without compromising on things like security]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/13/a-bootiful-podcast-sonatypes-steve-poole-and-gradles-justin-reock-on</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/13/a-bootiful-podcast-sonatypes-steve-poole-and-gradles-justin-reock-on"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic wins 2023 Data Breakthrough Award for DataOps Platform of the Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/2023-data-breakthrough-award-dataops-platform-of-the-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/2023-data-breakthrough-award-dataops-platform-of-the-year"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that Elastic has been honored with the 2023 Data Breakthrough Award for DataOps Platform of the Year, recognizing the comprehensive capabilities of the Elasticsearch Platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Courcy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The importance of a unified observability solution in security implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/unified-observability-solution-security-implementation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/unified-observability-solution-security-implementation"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A unified observability solution allows organizations to consolidate data sources into a single platform. Learn how it can help security teams view and correlate data from across the entire infrastructure and more quickly respond to incidents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calizo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic wins 2023 Data Breakthrough Award for DataOps Platform of the Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/2023-data-breakthrough-award-dataops-platform-of-the-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/2023-data-breakthrough-award-dataops-platform-of-the-year"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are excited to announce that Elastic has been honored with the 2023 Data Breakthrough Award for DataOps Platform of the Year, recognizing the comprehensive capabilities of the Elasticsearch Platform.

Designed to address the complete data lifecycle, for any type of data, and to run anywhere — from on-premises to hybrid-cloud and multi-cloud environments — the Elasticsearch Platform enables organizations to continuously surface relevant insights from petabytes of data in real-time.
The common denominator = data
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/bltb3e62d03f7f34bfb/6436e9decbf47d113c0b26dc/blog-elastic-exponential-data-growth-increasing-complexities.png,blog-elastic-exponential-data-growth-increasing-complexities.png,
As organizations navigate today’s always-on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Courcy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The importance of a unified observability solution in security implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/unified-observability-solution-security-implementation</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/unified-observability-solution-security-implementation"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Observability is critical for effective security implementation. It allows organizations to monitor their systems, applications, and networks in real-time; detect and investigate security incidents; and quickly respond to them. But having multiple tools and solutions for observability can create a fragmented view of the environment, making it difficult to gain a comprehensive understanding of the security posture and respond to threats effectively.
This is where a unified observability solution becomes essential for organizations. It consolidates all data sources into a single platform, allowing security teams to view and correlate data from across the entire infrastructure. This provides a complete picture of the environment and enables security teams to quickly identify and respond to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Calizo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UniPi: Learning universal policies via text-guided video generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/unipi-learning-universal-policies-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/unipi-learning-universal-policies-via.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sherry Yang, Research Scientist, and Yilun Du, Student Researcher, Google Research, Brain Team
Building models that solve a diverse set of tasks has become a dominant paradigm in the domains of vision and language. In natural language processing, large pre-trained models, such as PaLM, GPT-3 and Gopher, have demonstrated remarkable zero-shot learning of new language tasks. Similarly, in computer vision, models like CLIP and Flamingo have shown robust performance on zero-shot classification and object recognition. A natural next step is to use such tools to construct agents that can complete different decision-making tasks across many environments.



However, training such agents faces the inherent challenge of environmental diversity, since different environments operate with di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Accelerator: our first cohort and what&#8217;s next]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-12-github-accelerator-our-first-cohort-and-whats-next/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-12-github-accelerator-our-first-cohort-and-whats-next/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T16:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the projects that make up the first GitHub Accelerator cohort and learn about how GitHub is helping bring their visions to reality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BGP Management with Ansible Validated Content using the network.bgp collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/bgp-management-with-ansible-validated-content-using-the-network.bgp-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/bgp-management-with-ansible-validated-content-using-the-network.bgp-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AnsibleFest 2022, we announced a new addition to the content ecosystem offered through the platform which is Ansible validated content. Ansible validated content is use cases-focused automation content that is packaged as Collections that contain Ansible plugins, roles and playbooks that you can use as an automation job through Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Try RiderFlow and Share Your Experience With Us]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=341730</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/04/12/try-riderflow-and-share-your-experience-with-us/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To ensure that RiderFlow is an essential plugin for Unity developers working on 3D scenes, we’re striving to understand their evolving needs and use cases. We are conducting a study to get a better sense of your experience with the plugin and learn how we can improve it. If you would like to participate, read […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Ruban</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Debug C++ Code Efficiently: Disassemble On Demand]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=342075</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/04/how-to-debug-c-code-efficiently-disassemble-on-demand/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T09:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.1 brought the ability to explore assembly code even when the source code is available. A new Disassemble action has been added to improve your debugging experience, help you catch issues, and eliminate inefficiencies in the code. When debugging C or C++ code in CLion, you can explore the underlying assembly code. To open […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design has a language]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45625</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/735050105/0/sethsblog~Design-has-a-language/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T08:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And it changes over time. You and I know what to do when we see a revolving door, or to speak quietly in a library. We have expectations of how the world works and what designers are saying with their work. Here’s a photo of a device with two controls. We’ve been taught our whole […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCon US will open its doors in a week!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=342210</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/04/pycon-us-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T08:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to be a part of this major Python conference and have the chance to connect with Pythonistas from all over the world. Visit JetBrains at booth 324 in the Expo Hall or attend one of our talks. Talks       Other activities  If you’re participating in PyCon US, we’re happy to chat. Come visit […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your JetBrains All Products Pack Tools Are Ready To Be Updated to 2023.1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=blog&amp;p=341597</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/blog/2023/04/12/your-jetbrains-all-products-pack-tools-are-ready-to-be-updated-to-2023-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T07:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have released the first annual update, 2023.1, for all of the JetBrains IDEs and .NET tools. IntelliJ-based IDEs You will find the following new features available across most of the IDEs: The new UI has been updated to provide you with a more polished and seamless experience. It is still in Beta and is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Toporov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diffraction Spikes]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2762/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2762/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/diffraction_spikes.png" title="Even if a planet is lucky enough to have a stable orbit that weaves between the spikes, the seasons get weird whenever it passes close to them." alt="Even if a planet is lucky enough to have a stable orbit that weaves between the spikes, the seasons get weird whenever it passes close to them." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps 2023 Q2 Roadmap update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66701</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-2023-q2-roadmap-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T22:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday we published an updated list of features we plan to deliver in Q2. Each title includes a link where you can find details about each feature. We expect that this will help bring visibility into the key investments for the upcoming quarter.
The post Azure DevOps 2023 Q2 Roadmap update  appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the newest GitHub Shop collection]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-11-introducing-the-newest-github-shop-collection/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-11-introducing-the-newest-github-shop-collection/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T19:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From dog bowl bottles to fanny packs, explore the latest and greatest GitHub merchandise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing an aging clock using deep learning on retinal images]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/developing-aging-clock-using-deep.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/developing-aging-clock-using-deep.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sara Ahadi, Research Fellow, Applied Science, and Andrew Carroll, Product Lead, Genomics




Aging is a process that is characterized by physiological and molecular changes that increase an individual's risk of developing diseases and eventually dying. Being able to measure and estimate the biological signatures of aging can help researchers identify preventive measures to reduce disease risk and impact. Researchers have developed “aging clocks” based on markers such as blood proteins or DNA methylation to measure individuals’ biological age, which is distinct from one’s chronological age. These aging clocks help predict the risk of age-related diseases. But because protein and methylation markers require a blood draw, non-invasive ways to find similar measures could make aging i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66647</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/announcing-azure-devops-server-2022-0-1-rc/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T17:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are releasing Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC. This is a go-live release, meaning it is supported on production instances, and you will be able to upgrade to our final release.
The post Announcing Azure DevOps Server 2022.0.1 RC appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI-enabled compliance for software development]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-04-11-generative-ai-enabled-compliance-for-software-development/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-04-11-generative-ai-enabled-compliance-for-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T16:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how generative AI may soon help enable optimizing some of the foundational components of compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Vault integration via Sidecar Agent Injector vs. Vault Secrets Operator vs. CSI provider]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-vault-integration-via-sidecar-agent-injector-vs-csi-provider</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/kubernetes-vault-integration-via-sidecar-agent-injector-vs-csi-provider"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A detailed comparison of three HashiCorp-supported methods for HashiCorp Vault and Kubernetes integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.10 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78394&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78394</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/camunda-modeler-5-10/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T15:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the latest version of Camunda Desktop Modeler, including FEEL templating, a visual grid for diagrams and more. 
The post Camunda Desktop Modeler 5.10 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beatriz Mendes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New in IntelliJ Rust for 2023.1 (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rust&amp;p=341491</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rust/2023/04/11/new-in-intellij-rust-for-2023-1-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T14:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The time has come to outline the state of the IntelliJ-based IDEs’ Rust plugin as of the 2023.1 release. In the following paragraphs, we’ll delve into the novelties, improvements, and refinements that our team has delivered throughout the release cycle. Follow the post to learn more about the significant changes and features. If you want […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Lobeiko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8.2: The Key to Scaling Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78377&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78377</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/camunda-platform-8-2-key-to-scaling-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T13:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8.2 brings a suite of features that improve the process development lifecycle and helps you further scale automation. Read the latest.
The post Camunda Platform 8.2: The Key to Scaling Automation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The freedom loop]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=45588</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/734554046/0/sethsblog~The-freedom-loop/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T07:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We spend almost no time teaching toddlers about freedom. Instead, the lessons we teach (and learn) for our entire lives are about responsibility. It’s easy to teach freedom, but important to teach responsibility. Because if you get the responsibility taken care of, often the freedom will follow. When someone points out a lack of responsibility, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - April 11th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/11/this-week-in-spring-april-11th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/04/11/this-week-in-spring-april-11th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.27: Chill Vibes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/11/kubernetes-v1-27-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/11/kubernetes-v1-27-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes v1.27 Release Team
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.27, the first release of 2023!
This release consist of 60 enhancements. 18 of those enhancements are entering Alpha, 29 are graduating to Beta, and 13 are graduating to Stable.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes v1.27: Chill Vibes
The theme for Kubernetes v1.27 is Chill Vibes.
It's a little silly, but there were some important shifts in this release that helped inspire the theme. Throughout a typical Kubernetes release cycle, there are several deadlines that features need to meet to remain included. If a feature misses any of these deadlines, there is an exception process they can go through. Handling these exceptions is a very normal part of the release. But v1.27 is the first release that anyone can remember wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Review: Terraform in Service Catalog, AWS Supply Chain, Streaming Response in Lambda, and Amplify Library for Swift – April 10, 2023]]></title>
        <id>a3c18e35b5c3d5c56d33482fd39b1c582a776641</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/week-in-review-terraform-in-service-catalog-aws-supply-chain-streaming-response-in-lambda-and-amplify-library-for-swift-april-10-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T21:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Summit season has started. AWS Summits are free technical and business conferences happening in large cities across the planet. This week, we were happy to welcome our customers and partners in Sydney and Paris. In France, 9,973 customers and partners joined us for the day to meet and exchange ideas but also to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Consul’s transparent proxy on virtual machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-consul-s-transparent-proxy-on-virtual-machines</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-consul-s-transparent-proxy-on-virtual-machines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure Consul’s transparent proxy on virtual machines to find and connect to services in the service mesh with DNS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The rear view mirror]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44225</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/734338874/0/sethsblog~The-rear-view-mirror/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s almost impossible to safely drive a car while only looking in the rear view mirror. Only seeing where you’ve been is a terrible way to figure out where to go. But it’s really unsafe to go forward with no idea of what came before. AI plods along into the future, using machine learning to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1-to-1 Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2761/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2761/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/1_to_1_scale.png" title="There's a version that shows the planets with no cropping, but it's hard to find a display that supports it." alt="There's a version that shows the planets with no cropping, but it's hard to find a display that supports it." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards ML-enabled cleaning robots]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/towards-ml-enabled-cleaning-robots.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/towards-ml-enabled-cleaning-robots.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T21:06:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Thomas Lew, Research Intern, and Montserrat Gonzalez Arenas, Research Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team


Over the past several years, the capabilities of robotic systems have improved dramatically. As the technology continues to improve and robotic agents are more routinely deployed in real-world environments, their capacity to assist in day-to-day activities will take on increasing importance. Repetitive tasks like wiping surfaces, folding clothes, and cleaning a room seem well-suited for robots, but remain challenging for robotic systems designed for structured environments like factories. Performing these types of tasks in more complex environments, like offices or homes, requires dealing with greater levels of environmental variability captured by high-dimensional sensor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Directing ML toward natural hazard mitigation through collaboration]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/directing-ml-toward-natural-hazard.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/directing-ml-toward-natural-hazard.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T16:09:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Oren Gilon, Software Engineer, and Grey Nearing, Research Scientist, Google Research




Floods are the most common type of natural disaster, affecting more than 250 million people globally each year. As part of Google's Crisis Response and our efforts to address the climate crisis, we are using machine learning (ML) models for Flood Forecasting to alert people in areas that are impacted before disaster strikes.


Collaboration between researchers in the industry and academia is essential for accelerating progress towards mutual goals in ML-related research. Indeed, Google's current ML-based flood forecasting approach was developed in collaboration with researchers (1, 2) at the Johannes Kepler University in Vienna, Austria, the University of Alabama, and the Hebrew University of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Project Starline improves remote communication]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/how-project-starline-improves-remote.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/how-project-starline-improves-remote.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T19:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Greg Blascovich and Eric Gomez, User Researchers, Google




As companies settle into a new normal of hybrid and distributed work, remote communication technology remains critical for connecting and collaborating with colleagues. While this technology has improved, the core user experience often falls short: conversation can feel stilted, attention can be difficult to maintain, and usage can be fatiguing. 





Project Starline renders people at natural scale on a 3D display and enables natural eye contact.

Project Starline, a technology project that combines advances in hardware and software to create a remote communication experience that feels like you’re together, even when you’re thousands of miles apart. This perception of co-presence is created by representing users in 3D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-trained Gaussian processes for Bayesian optimization]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/pre-trained-gaussian-processes-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/04/pre-trained-gaussian-processes-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T17:02:00.009Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Zi Wang and Kevin Swersky, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 





Bayesian optimization (BayesOpt) is a powerful tool widely used for global optimization tasks, such as hyperparameter tuning, protein engineering, synthetic chemistry, robot learning, and even baking cookies. BayesOpt is a great strategy for these problems because they all involve optimizing black-box functions that are expensive to evaluate. A black-box function’s underlying mapping from inputs (configurations of the thing we want to optimize) to outputs (a measure of performance) is unknown. However, we can attempt to understand its internal workings by evaluating the function for different combinations of inputs. Because each evaluation can be computationally expensive, we need to find the best i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding free and open Elastic APM as part of your Elastic Observability deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post, we showed you how to get started with the free and open tier of Elastic Observability. Below, we'll walk through what you need to do to expand your deployment so you can start gathering metrics from application performance monitoring (APM) or "tracing" data in your observability cluster, for free.
What is APM?
Application performance monitoring lets you see where your applications spend their time, what they are doing, what other applications or services they are calling, and what errors or exceptions they are encountering.

In addition, APM also lets you see history and trends for key performance indicators, such as latency and throughput, as well as transaction and dependency information:

Whether you're setting up alerts for SLA breaches, trying to gauge the impact of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding free and open Elastic APM as part of your Elastic Observability deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/adding-free-and-open-elastic-apm-as-part-of-your-elastic-observability-deployment"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to gather application trace data and store it alongside the logs and metrics from your applications and infrastructure with Elastic Observability and Elastic APM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Keeping Kubernetes Secure with Updated Go Versions]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/06/keeping-kubernetes-secure-with-updated-go-versions/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/04/06/keeping-kubernetes-secure-with-updated-go-versions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jordan Liggitt (Google)
The problem
Since v1.19 (released in 2020), the Kubernetes project provides 12-14 months of patch releases for each minor version.
This enables users to qualify and adopt Kubernetes versions in an annual upgrade cycle and receive security fixes for a year.
The Go project releases new minor versions twice a year,
and provides security fixes for the last two minor versions, resulting in about a year of support for each Go version.
Even though each new Kubernetes minor version is built with a supported Go version when it is first released,
that Go version falls out of support before the Kubernetes minor version does,
and the lengthened Kubernetes patch support since v1.19 only widened that gap.
At the time this was written, just over half of all Go patch releas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul Service (HCS) on Azure End of Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-consul-service-hcs-on-azure-end-of-life</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-consul-service-hcs-on-azure-end-of-life"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCS on Azure has been deprecated. HCP Consul on Azure is the preferred way to run your HashiCorp Consul clusters on Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new Terraform Associate 003 Certification exam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-new-terraform-associate-003-certification-exam</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-the-new-terraform-associate-003-certification-exam"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how HashiCorp’s updated Terraform Associate certification impacts your current and future Terraform Associate credentials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevEx improvements in HashiCorp Sentinel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/devex-improvements-in-hashicorp-sentinel</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/devex-improvements-in-hashicorp-sentinel"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent releases of Sentinel have targeted improvements to the developer experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Cloud Automation with amazon.cloud 0.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.cloud-0.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.cloud-0.3.0"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post we will go over what has changed and highlight what’s new in the 0.3.0 release of this Ansible Content Collection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Buzachis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Signs Your Business Processes Are Not Human-Centric]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=78044&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=78044</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/04/five-signs-business-processes-not-human-centric/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To avoid limiting the returns of your investment into automation, center your development approach around humans. Here's how.
The post 5 Signs Your Business Processes Are Not Human-Centric appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lana Ginns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Self-Service Provisioning of Terraform Open-Source Configurations with AWS Service Catalog]]></title>
        <id>530d6f7f8f803392ad96d74df5af817333cf8e53</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-self-service-provisioning-of-terraform-open-source-configurations-with-aws-service-catalog/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T23:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With AWS Service Catalog, you can create, govern, and manage a catalog of infrastructure as code (IaC) templates that are approved for use on AWS. These IaC templates can include everything from virtual machine images, servers, software, and databases to complete multi-tier application architectures. You can control which IaC templates and versions are available, what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Supply Chain Now Generally Available – Mitigate Risks and Lower Costs with Increased Visibility and Actionable Insights]]></title>
        <id>0518cc890b6889b079032b7c396d9960a46ba20f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-supply-chain-now-generally-available-mitigate-risks-and-lower-costs-with-increased-visibility-and-actionable-insights/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T22:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many of you, I experienced the disrupting effects introduced by external forces such as weather, geopolitical instability, and the COVID-19 pandemic. To improve supply chain resilience, organizations need visibility across their supply chain so that they can quickly find and respond to risks. This is increasingly complex as their customers’ preferences are rapidly changing, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review: Public Preview of Amazon DataZone and AWS DataSync Updates – April 3, 2023]]></title>
        <id>1bcba2697b78cec48e028ae83294a24a0ff643a2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-public-preview-of-amazon-datazone-and-aws-datasync-updates-april-3-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T16:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last weekend, I enjoyed the spring vibes at Seoul Forest, a large park in the middle of Seoul city, where cherry blossoms are in full bloom. Compared to last year, there were crowds of people, so I realized that it was really back to normal after the pandemic. I hope you all enjoy the season […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Automation Platform … You’re using it wrong.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-youre-using-it-wrong</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-automation-platform-youre-using-it-wrong"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5 things you didn’t know your Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform could do]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling vision transformers to 22 billion parameters]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/scaling-vision-transformers-to-22.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/scaling-vision-transformers-to-22.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T20:48:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Piotr Padlewski and Josip Djolonga, Software Engineers, Google Research




Large Language Models (LLMs) like PaLM or GPT-3 showed that scaling transformers to hundreds of billions of parameters improves performance and unlocks emergent abilities. The biggest dense models for image understanding, however, have reached only 4 billion parameters, despite research indicating that promising multimodal models like PaLI continue to benefit from scaling vision models alongside their language counterparts. Motivated by this, and the results from scaling LLMs, we decided to undertake the next step in the journey of scaling the Vision Transformer.
 

In “Scaling Vision Transformers to 22 Billion Parameters”, we introduce the biggest dense vision model, ViT-22B. It is 5.5x larger than the p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Ready-to-use Models and Support for Custom Text and Image Classification Models in Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>0650ce6ad58192632c6d222ad8d4b8d88bf47ff5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-ready-to-use-models-and-support-for-custom-text-and-image-classification-models-in-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T17:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today AWS announces new features in Amazon SageMaker Canvas that help business analysts generate insights from thousands of documents, images, and lines of text in minutes with machine learning (ML). Starting today, you can access ready-to-use models and create custom text and image classification models alongside previously supported custom models for tabular data, all without […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify Service-to-Service Connectivity, Security, and Monitoring with Amazon VPC Lattice – Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>9dcb9cc925a7f92a2551692c29ff45a63a4371fd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-service-to-service-connectivity-security-and-monitoring-with-amazon-vpc-lattice-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T15:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2022, we introduced in preview Amazon VPC Lattice, a new capability of Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) that gives you a consistent way to connect, secure, and monitor communication between your services. With VPC Lattice, you can define policies for network access, traffic management, and monitoring to connect compute services across […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp earns Comparably awards for company and teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-earns-comparably-awards-for-company-and-teams</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-earns-comparably-awards-for-company-and-teams"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comparably recognizes HashiCorp with awards for Best Company Outlook, Best Marketing Team, Best Sales Team, and Best HR Team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty Now Supports Amazon EKS Runtime Monitoring]]></title>
        <id>33f430b15e8d3f92d0343a89bf2132bddc860868</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-guardduty-now-supports-amazon-eks-runtime-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T21:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Amazon GuardDuty launched in 2017, GuardDuty has been capable of analyzing tens of billions of events per minute across multiple AWS data sources, such as AWS CloudTrail event logs, Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Flow Logs, and DNS query logs, Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) data plane events, Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Consul cluster peering enhances multi-cloud connectivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-cluster-peering-enhances-multi-cloud-connectivity</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-consul-cluster-peering-enhances-multi-cloud-connectivity"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cluster peering for HashiCorp-managed HCP Consul in AWS and Azure boosts multi-cloud and hybrid-cloud connectivity in the enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Service Principal and Managed Identity support on Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66657</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-service-principal-and-managed-identity-support-on-azure-devops/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T17:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are proud to announce that Service Principals and Managed Identities can now be used to authenticate with Azure DevOps. For those who have not heard of them before, these Azure Active Directory identities enable teams to gain access to your Azure DevOps organizations acting as their own application,
The post Introducing Service Principal and Managed Identity support on Azure DevOps appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angel Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data-centric ML benchmarking: Announcing DataPerf’s 2023 challenges]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/data-centric-ml-benchmarking-announcing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/data-centric-ml-benchmarking-announcing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Peter Mattson, Senior Staff Engineer, ML Performance, and Praveen Paritosh, Senior Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team




Machine learning (ML) offers tremendous potential, from diagnosing cancer to engineering safe self-driving cars to amplifying human productivity. To realize this potential, however, organizations need ML solutions to be reliable with ML solution development that is predictable and tractable. The key to both is a deeper understanding of ML data — how to engineer training datasets that produce high quality models and test datasets that deliver accurate indicators of how close we are to solving the target problem. 



The process of creating high quality datasets is complicated and error-prone, from the initial selection and cleaning of raw data, to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renew your existing HashiCorp Certifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/renew-your-existing-hashicorp-certifications</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/renew-your-existing-hashicorp-certifications"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp certification holders can now renew their certifications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda’s Vision for Low-Code]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=77631&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=77631</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/camunda-vision-low-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T11:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explaining our vision for how Camunda embraces low-code to make you more productive.
The post Camunda’s Vision for Low-Code appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Validating Admission Policies: A Practical Example]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/30/kubescape-validating-admission-policy-library/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/03/30/kubescape-validating-admission-policy-library/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Craig Box (ARMO), Ben Hirschberg (ARMO)
Admission control is an important part of the Kubernetes control plane, with several internal
features depending on the ability to approve or change an API object as it is submitted to the
server. It is also useful for an administrator to be able to define business logic, or policies,
regarding what objects can be admitted into a cluster. To better support that use case, Kubernetes
introduced external admission control in
v1.7.
In addition to countless custom, internal implementations, many open source projects and commercial
solutions implement admission controllers with user-specified policy, including
Kyverno and Open Policy Agent’s
Gatekeeper.
While admission controllers for policy have seen adoption, there are blockers for their widespr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault Secrets Operator: A new method for Kubernetes integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-secrets-operator-a-new-method-for-kubernetes-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/vault-secrets-operator-a-new-method-for-kubernetes-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vault Secrets Operator implements a first-class Kubernetes Operator pattern for HashiCorp Vault along with a set of CRDs responsible for synchronizing Vault secrets to Kubernetes Secrets natively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform ecosystem passes 3,000 providers with over 250 partners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-ecosystem-passes-3-000-providers-with-over-250-partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-ecosystem-passes-3-000-providers-with-over-250-partners"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform integrations ecosystem has reached a new milestone, surpassing 3,000 providers in the registry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging transfer learning for large scale differentially private image classification]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/leveraging-transfer-learning-for-large.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/leveraging-transfer-learning-for-large.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T18:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Harsh Mehta, Software Engineer, and Walid Krichene, Research Scientist, Google Research




Large deep learning models are becoming the workhorse of a variety of critical machine learning (ML) tasks. However, it has been shown that without any protection it is plausible for bad actors to attack a variety of models, across modalities, to reveal information from individual training examples. As such, it’s essential to protect against this sort of information leakage.


Differential privacy (DP) provides formal protection against an attacker who aims to extract information about the training data. The most popular method for DP training in deep learning is differentially private stochastic gradient descent (DP-SGD). The core recipe implements a common theme in DP: “fuzzing” an algor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The producer-consumer infrastructure model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-producer-consumer-infrastructure-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/the-producer-consumer-infrastructure-model"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure producers and consumers require very different capabilities from their automation tools. Vendors need to provide a flexible infrastructure as code solution that meets users at their different levels of expertise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of Step-by-Step Guides for Amazon Connect Agent Workspace]]></title>
        <id>6042ead436a3e7e535833ae688a6be1bd85467e5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-general-availability-of-step-by-step-guides-for-amazon-connect-agent-workspace/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T20:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2022 we announced the availability of step-by-step guides for Amazon Connect agent workspace in preview. My colleagues who collaborated to write the announcement post wrote about some of the challenges that contact centers face with training new agents to get up to speed with their agent desktop. They also mentioned that until […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How French Broadcaster TF1 Used AWS Cloud Technology and Expertise to Bring the FIFA World Cup to Millions]]></title>
        <id>f6b8b5588b3c1c2f89dc45e1ebb462cb3a116aa7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-french-broadcaster-tf1-used-aws-cloud-technology-and-expertise-to-bring-the-fifa-world-cup-to-millions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T19:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three years before millions of viewers saw, arguably, one of the most thrilling World Cup Finals ever broadcast, TF1, the leading private TV channel in France, started a project to redefine the foundations of its broadcasting platform, including adopting a new cloud-based architecture. They, and all other broadcasters, have been observing diminishing audiences for traditional […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESTO – A multilingual dataset for parsing realistic task-oriented dialogues]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/presto-multilingual-dataset-for-parsing.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/presto-multilingual-dataset-for-parsing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T17:02:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rahul Goel and Aditya Gupta, Software Engineers, Google Assistant




Virtual assistants are increasingly integrated into our daily routines. They can help with everything from setting alarms to giving map directions and can even assist people with disabilities to more easily manage their homes. As we use these assistants, we are also becoming more accustomed to using natural language to accomplish tasks that we once did by hand. 


 

One of the biggest challenges in building a robust virtual assistant is identifying what a user wants and what information is needed to perform the task at hand. In the natural language processing (NLP) literature, this is mainly framed as a task-oriented dialogue parsing task, where a given dialogue needs to be parsed by a system to understand the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise adds projects, drift detection, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-projects-drift-detection-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-projects-drift-detection-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent Terraform Enterprise releases include powerful new features such as projects, native OPA support, dynamic provider credentials, and drift detection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Validated Content: Introduction to infra.osbuild Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-introduction-to-infra.osbuild-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansible-validated-content-introduction-to-infra.osbuild-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to the Image builder use case
 
During the last year we met with multiple edge customers, covering the automation needs for IT Linux infrastructure at scale across remote locations where there is often no IT staff on site. Think about retail stores, dark stores and warehouses where self-checkout, handhelds and POS devices hosting RHEL are distributed everywhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Santiago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service Major Updates: Import and Export Feature, Source Server Migration Metrics Dashboard, and Additional Post-Launch Actions]]></title>
        <id>fa10696bac0b9446bb6ac881cb730c11e3d02931</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-application-migration-service-major-updates-import-and-export-feature-source-server-migration-metrics-dashboard-and-additional-post-launch-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T15:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service (AWS MGN) can simplify and expedite your migration to AWS by automatically converting your source servers from physical, virtual, or cloud infrastructure to run natively on AWS. In the post, How to Use the New AWS Application Migration Server for Lift-and-Shift Migrations, Channy introduced us to Application Migration Service and how […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Chime SDK Call Analytics: Real-Time Voice Tone Analysis and Speaker Search]]></title>
        <id>b5892bef67fe0abef13300dedbfb49b1a69ff7fa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-chime-sdk-call-analytics-real-time-voice-tone-analysis-and-speaker-search/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T15:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am pleased to announce the availability of Amazon Chime SDK call analytics, a new set of capabilities that helps make it easier and cost effective to record and generate insights on real-time audio calls: transcription, voice tone analysis, and speaker search. We’ve also improved the Amazon Chime SDK section of the AWS Management […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 27, 2023]]></title>
        <id>36af7fde9b2b41d5310560b417ffc23471afa1e9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-27-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! In Finland, where I live, spring has arrived. The snow has melted, and the trees have grown their first buds. But I don’t get my hopes high, as usually around […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting novel systemic biomarkers in external eye photos]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/detecting-novel-systemic-biomarkers-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/detecting-novel-systemic-biomarkers-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T19:13:00.009Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Boris Babenko, Software Engineer, and Akib Uddin, Product Manager, Google Research






Last year we presented results demonstrating that a deep learning system (DLS) can be trained to analyze external eye photos and predict a person’s diabetic retinal disease status and elevated glycated hemoglobin (or HbA1c, a biomarker that indicates the three-month average level of blood glucose). It was previously unknown that external eye photos contained signals for these conditions. This exciting finding suggested the potential to reduce the need for specialized equipment since such photos can be captured using smartphones and other consumer devices. Encouraged by these findings, we set out to discover what other biomarkers can be found in this imaging modality.



In “A deep learning mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual language maps for robot navigation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/visual-language-maps-for-robot.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/visual-language-maps-for-robot.html"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T19:08:00.012Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Oier Mees, PhD Student, University of Freiburg, and Andy Zeng, Research Scientist, Robotics at Google





People are excellent navigators of the physical world, due in part to their remarkable ability to build cognitive maps that form the basis of spatial memory — from localizing landmarks at varying ontological levels (like a book on a shelf in the living room) to determining whether a layout permits navigation from point A to point B. Building robots that are proficient at navigation requires an interconnected understanding of (a) vision and natural language (to associate landmarks or follow instructions), and (b) spatial reasoning (to connect a map representing an environment to the true spatial distribution of objects). While there have been many recent advances in training …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running dynamic, ephemeral multi-hop workers for HCP Boundary: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-dynamic-ephemeral-multi-hop-workers-for-hcp-boundary-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-dynamic-ephemeral-multi-hop-workers-for-hcp-boundary-part-1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worker management is very dynamic in Boundary and HCP Boundary. With a new custom plugin, you can automate even more tasks, including worker cleanup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deeper Look: Red Hat Named a Leader in the Forrester Wave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/a-deeper-look-red-hat-named-a-leader-in-the-forrester-wave</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/a-deeper-look-red-hat-named-a-leader-in-the-forrester-wave"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we announced that Red Hat has been named a leader in The Forrester Wave™ Infrastructure Automation, Q1 2023. In an effort to help explain this result from our point of view, the following blog answers some of the most frequently asked questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andriusb@redhat.com (Andrius Benokraitis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test as You Go: Rapid Process Development and Continuous Improvement]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=76773&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=76773</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/rapid-process-development-continuous-improvement/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T14:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Alpha release of the new rapid process testing functionality which is now available in Camunda Platform 8.
The post Test as You Go: Rapid Process Development and Continuous Improvement appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Inozemtceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Federal Sales Director Kathy Hsu thinks authenticity is important in sales. Hear why.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My passion is to work with the federal government and see how I can be a part of the mission. That’s why I wanted to work at Elastic. 

I first discovered my passion for tech sales as a college graduate working in Silicon Valley. I worked at Apple as a Technical Consultant and got my start in channel sales and the network IP space at a large company that provided solutions for semiconductor and infrastructure software. Then I moved to a startup that gave me the opportunity to support Civilian agencies, the Department of Defense (DoD), and the Intelligence Community. In this role, I spent a lot of time flying between California and Washington D.C. and quickly realized that I had a great sense of fire and purpose when serving the federal government. 

These early experiences helped me find m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Hsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic’s Federal Sales Director Kathy Hsu thinks authenticity is important in sales. Hear why.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/women-of-elastic-kathy-hsu-career-in-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Hsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 219]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66630</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-219/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T17:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sprint 219 was dedicated to fixing bugs. We continue to drive down the bug backlog as quickly as we can. We will also have a couple new preview features coming that will be announced in the 219 sprint notes.
Issue
Delivery plans tab name
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 219 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第227話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361072081927</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361072081927"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March patches for Azure DevOps Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66621</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/march-patches-for-azure-devops-server/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T20:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server.
Addressed issue that required restarting tfsjobagent service and Azure DevOps Server application pool after updating SMTP-related setting in the Azure DevOps Server Management Console.
The post March patches for Azure DevOps Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Clean Rooms Now Generally Available — Collaborate with Your Partners without Sharing Raw Data]]></title>
        <id>7489dac1ba7077e7020fc13589c13c0455e7b4d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-clean-rooms-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T19:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies across multiple industries, such as advertising and marketing, retail, consumer packaged goods (CPG), travel and hospitality, media and entertainment, and financial services, increasingly look to supplement their data with data from business partners, to build a complete view of their business. Let’s take a marketing use case as an example. Brands, publishers, and their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Camunda 8 on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=76579&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=76579</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/03/running-camunda-8-on-openshift/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T18:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you use Red Hat OpenShift? We've greatly improved how Camunda Platform 8 runs on OpenShift. Learn what's new and see an installation step by step.
The post Running Camunda 8 on OpenShift appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernd Ruecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – March 20, 2023]]></title>
        <id>d37a1df2b4b3f11486d8d054016088476bc57107</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-march-20-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T15:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is part of our Week in Review series. Check back each week for a quick roundup of interesting news and announcements from AWS! A new week starts, and Spring is almost here! If you’re curious about AWS news from the previous seven days, I got you covered. Last Week’s Launches Here are the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>