<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-12-10T01:24:02.863Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-12-10T01:24:02.863Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release Radar · October 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-09-release-radar-october-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-09-release-radar-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T19:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before you say it, yes, the October Release Radar was supposed to be shared in November. But with Hackatoberfest, GitHub Universe, Turkey Day, and in real life (IRL) conferences returning to their pre-COVID frequency, we&#8217;ve all been so busy. And our community has been hustling to ship all kinds of open source projects. We wanted [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of Support for the Tapestry, JBoss Seam, and Vaadin plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=306466</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2022/12/end-of-support-for-the-tapestry-jboss-seam-and-vaadin-plugins/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T10:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are continuing our efforts to focus our attention on the most popular technologies and integrations. However, since our capabilities are limited, this requires sunsetting some plugins that are no longer in high demand among the community. Given the low popularity of the Tapestry, JBoss Seam, and Vaadin 6–8 plugins, we have discontinued their development […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zlata Kalyuzhnaya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best job you ever had]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44319</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/721540320/0/sethsblog~The-best-job-you-ever-had/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would you fill out this simple, quick and informal survey for me? We spend most of our lives at work. And yet we don’t spend much time talking about it the opportunity to make it worthwhile. Thanks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.26: Electrifying]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/09/kubernetes-v1-26-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/09/kubernetes-v1-26-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes 1.26 Release Team
It's with immense joy that we announce the release of Kubernetes v1.26!
This release includes a total of 37 enhancements: eleven of them are graduating to Stable, ten are
graduating to Beta, and sixteen of them are entering Alpha. We also have twelve features being
deprecated or removed, three of which we better detail in this announcement.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes 1.26: Electrifying
The theme for Kubernetes v1.26 is Electrifying.
Each Kubernetes release is the result of the coordinated effort of dedicated volunteers, and only
made possible due to the use of a diverse and complex set of computing resources, spread out through
multiple datacenters and regions worldwide. The end result of a release - the binaries, the image
containers, the docum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experiment: The hidden costs of waiting on slow build times]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-08-experiment-the-hidden-costs-of-waiting-on-slow-build-times/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-08-experiment-the-hidden-costs-of-waiting-on-slow-build-times/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T18:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much does it really cost to buy more powerful cloud compute resources for development work? A lot less than you think.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formation of Robust Bound States of Interacting Photons]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/formation-of-robust-bound-states-of.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/formation-of-robust-bound-states-of.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T17:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alexis Morvan and Trond Andersen, Research Scientists, Google Quantum AI  
When quantum computers were first proposed, they were hoped to be a way to better understand the quantum world. With a so-called “quantum simulator,” one could engineer a quantum computer to investigate how various quantum phenomena arise, including those that are intractable to simulate with a classical computer.  
    
But making a useful quantum simulator has been a challenge. Until now, quantum simulations with superconducting qubits have predominantly been used to verify pre-existing theoretical predictions and have rarely explored or discovered new phenomena. Only a few experiments with trapped ions or cold atoms have revealed new insights. Superconducting qubits, even though they are one of the main…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Commit Uruguay: Lowering barriers to make software development more inclusive and diverse]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-08-git-commit-uruguay-lowering-barriers-to-make-software-development-more-inclusive-and-diverse/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-08-git-commit-uruguay-lowering-barriers-to-make-software-development-more-inclusive-and-diverse/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T17:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We delivered two different courses specifically designed to help students in the lowest-income neighborhood of Montevideo, Uruguay learn how to use GitHub and understand the value of open source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Secrets for Waypoint with Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dynamic-secrets-for-waypoint-with-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/dynamic-secrets-for-waypoint-with-vault"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to source dynamic secrets from HashiCorp Vault in your Waypoint deployments using dynamic configuration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello from GitHub’s new Chief Product Officer]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-08-hello-from-githubs-new-chief-product-officer/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-08-hello-from-githubs-new-chief-product-officer/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T16:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub is in an exciting phase of our journey as the developer community grows significantly every day, and the needs of the community grow and change with it. Today we’re introducing our new Chief Product officer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting your microservice architecture with message broker Connectors]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=69131&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=69131</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/boosting-microservice-architecture-message-broker-connectors/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Amazon SQS, SNS, and Lambda Connectors, as well as Kafka and RabbitMQ Connectors, microservice choreography and orchestration get even closer together.
The post Boosting your microservice architecture with message broker Connectors appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Preview for Qodana Cloud, a One-Stop-Shop for All Your Code Quality Insights!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=qodana&amp;p=302352</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/qodana/2022/12/preview-for-qodana-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T13:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A public preview is now open for Qodana Cloud – a centralized cloud-based solution that collects and displays data from different Qodana linters under one roof. You can use Qodana Cloud to manage your code quality checks in a variety of contexts, ranging from one-person projects to large development teams. Qodana Cloud is still in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerie Kuzmina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hour of Code: Top 5 Android Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=306387</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/12/08/hour-of-code-top-5-android-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T12:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time flies so fast – it is already the middle of the Hour of Code celebration! Whether it’s your first day or you’ve been with us from the start, we hope you enjoy it to the fullest. Today, we are going to talk about Android, an open-source operating system for mobile devices The popularity of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Khudikova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Vaadin's Marcus Hellberg on rich UIs, Spring Boot 3, GraalVM native images, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/08/a-bootiful-podcast-vaadin-s-marcus-hellberg-on-rich-uis-spring-boot-3-graalvm-native-images-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/08/a-bootiful-podcast-vaadin-s-marcus-hellberg-on-rich-uis-spring-boot-3-graalvm-native-images-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Vaadin’s Marcus Hellberg (@marcushellberg) about rich UIs, Vaadin Flow, the new Hilla Framework, GraalVM native image compilation, and so much more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“You’re right”]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43385</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/721456212/0/sethsblog~Youre-right/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T09:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If a customer, a colleague or a friend is generous enough to share their feelings, those feelings are what they are. We might disagree with the assumptions that led to those feelings. But acknowledging that the feelings are real is a great place to begin a conversation. “You feel this way” is not the same […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ktor 2.2.1 (and 2.2.0) released]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=ktor&amp;p=305095</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/ktor/2022/12/08/ktor-2-2-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Important: Yesterday we released 2.2.0 to Maven Central, but immediately after we noticed a critical issue of AtomicFu that needed addressing, and as a consequence shortly after we pushed 2.2.1. As such, if you are using 2.2.0, we strongly advise moving to 2.2.1. We’ve released Ktor 2.2.0/2.2.1, which introduces many new features and fixes. Moreover, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrey Aksenov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.5.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 cybersecurity strategies for healthcare leaders in a digital-first world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-cybersecurity-strategies-healthcare-leaders-digital-first-world</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-cybersecurity-strategies-healthcare-leaders-digital-first-world"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity is an imperative in today's healthcare. Find out how Elastic Security and Proficio can bring the best of security solutions and managed security services, empowering healthcare companies to improve patient care.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury,Carl Adasa, VP of Global SOC Operations, Proficio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.5.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-3-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-3-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Version 8.5.3 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
The 8.5.3 patch contains fixes and small enhancements for the stack. A notable bug fix in Kibana is:

Kibana server fails to start when locale is set to ja-JP (#146693)
Elasticsearch - Support SAN/dnsName for restricted trust (#91946)


For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes:
8.5.3 Release Notes
Elastic Stack

Kibana
Elasticsearch
Beats
Logstash

Elastic Enterprise Search

Enterprise Search

Elastic Observability

APM

Elastic Security

Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 cybersecurity strategies for healthcare leaders in a digital-first world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-cybersecurity-strategies-healthcare-leaders-digital-first-world</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/3-cybersecurity-strategies-healthcare-leaders-digital-first-world"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
From on-demand healthcare services like telehealth to wearable technologies, predictive healthcare to blockchain technologies for electronic health records, or 5G for healthcare services to AI and augmented reality for state-of-the-art medical treatments, the healthcare industry is at an inflection point. These digital transformations also bring along elevated cybersecurity risks.

Earlier this year, in a comprehensive cybersecurity benchmarking study conducted by ThoughtLab, the healthcare industry was found to be lacking in maturity from a cybersecurity implementation standpoint, placed only slightly ahead of the media and entertainment industry and industrial manufacturing.

[Download the report: Cybersecurity solutions for a riskier world]

Healthcare companies can take advantage of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suranjeeta Choudhury,Carl Adasa, VP of Global SOC Operations, Proficio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private Ads Prediction with DP-SGD]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/private-ads-prediction-with-dp-sgd.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/private-ads-prediction-with-dp-sgd.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T19:17:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Krishna Giri Narra, Software Engineer, Google, and Chiyuan Zhang, Research Scientist, Google Research     
Ad technology providers widely use machine learning (ML) models to predict and present users with the most relevant ads, and to measure the effectiveness of those ads. With increasing focus on online privacy, there’s an opportunity to identify ML algorithms that have better privacy-utility trade-offs. Differential privacy (DP) has emerged as a popular framework for developing ML algorithms responsibly with provable privacy guarantees. It has been extensively studied in the privacy literature, deployed in industrial applications and employed by the U.S. Census. Intuitively, the DP framework enables ML models to learn population-wide properties, while protecting user-level inf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot is generally available for businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-07-github-copilot-is-generally-available-for-businesses/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-07-github-copilot-is-generally-available-for-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T17:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot for Business is officially here with simple license management, organization-wide policy controls, and industry-leading privacy—all for $19 USD per user per month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dotCover, dotMemory, dotPeek, and dotTrace 2022.3 Released!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=305305</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/12/07/dotcover-dotmemory-dotpeek-dottrace-2022-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T17:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A moment ago, we released the 2022.3 versions of dotTrace, dotMemory, dotCover, and dotPeek. Take a look at the updates and features that are now available. dotCover 2022.3 You can use dotCover on ARM64 CPUs on Windows. This applies to all versions: dotCover standalone, dotCover in Rider, dotCover in Visual Studio, and the dotCover console […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Kurakin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2022.3 Released With More C# 11 Features, NuGet Vulnerabilities Detection, and Support for Visual Studio ARM64.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=304867</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/12/07/resharper-2022-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T17:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, ReSharper 2022.3 and other JetBrains .NET tools have just been released. In this article we’re going to go over the highlights of this major update for ReSharper as well as touch on the features coming to ReSharper C++. To learn more about our other .NET tools, including dotCover, dotMemory, dotPeek, and dotTrace, please […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: November 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-07-github-availability-report-november-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-07-github-availability-report-november-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T17:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November, we experienced two incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. This report also sheds light into an incident that impacted Codespaces in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do more with Azure Spring Apps – scale to zero and enhance productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/07/do-more-with-azure-spring-apps-scale-to-zero-and-enhance-productivity</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/07/do-more-with-azure-spring-apps-scale-to-zero-and-enhance-productivity"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2020, Spotify coined the term "Golden Path” to refer to a supported approach and set of components to build and deploy software. Having these paths simplifies the development process, lets developers focus on their applications instead of infrastructure and speeds time to production. Microsoft and VMware have partnered to make Azure Spring Apps a golden path for deploying and scaling Spring applications in the cloud. And with new capabilities like the scale to zero and developer productivity enhancements, Azure Spring Apps now offers an even more economical and optimized route to get your Spring applications into production.
1. Start from zero and scale to zero – consumption plan

We are introducing a new consumption pricing plan for Azure Spring Apps – you can start from zero and scal…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2022.3: Support for .NET 7 SDK, the Latest From C#11, Major Performance Improvements, and More!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=304698</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/12/07/rider-2022-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T16:48:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, It’s the most wonderful time of the year: not only are the holidays upon us, but Rider 2022.3 – the last major version of Rider this year – has just been released. Let’s see what’s inside. Performance improvements We’ve made several changes to increase Rider’s startup speed and reduce the time it takes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Together, We Supported Python]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=304511</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2022/12/together-we-supported-python-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T16:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our joint campaign with the Python Software Foundation (PSF) raised a total of USD 20,000 that will be donated to the PSF’s general fund! For the fifth year in a row, JetBrains partnered with the PSF on their end-of-the-year fundraiser. This year you could purchase a new PyCharm Professional subscription at 30% off, have the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roberto Pesce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ 2022.3: C++20 Modules and Clang-Format Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=rscpp&amp;p=305013</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/rscpp/2022/12/07/resharper-cpp-2022-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T16:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper C++ 2022.3 is now available! Update to the latest version, or start a free 30-day trial today! Download the build from our website or via the Toolbox App. Check out the highlights and visit our What’s New page for more details about these and other improvements: Experimental support for C++20 modules. Improved C++ support: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elvira Mustafina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.17.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/07/spring-tools-4-17-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/07/spring-tools-4-17-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.17.0 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
updated to Eclipse 2022-12 release (new and noteworthy)


early access to new experimental features

Among a number of bug fixes and minor improvements, this release introduces experimental support for:


  
Spring Boot version validations: The IDE will tell you when there is a newer major, minor, or patch version available for your Spring Boot project

  
Spring Boot upgrade support: The tooling will help you upgrading your existing projects to newer Spring Boot versions, including upgrades to newer patch and minor versions, as well as newer major versions (e.g. upgrading to Spring Boot 3)

  
Spring specific validations and refactorings: The tooling will indicate whether something can or should be changed in your source code to keep your Spring project up-to-date with the latest recommendations or advancements in Spring


To learn more about these new experimental features, please take a look at the user guide: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/
And we would like to hear from you. Please let us know if you come across any issues or have thoughts and wishes for further improvements in this space: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/issues
fixes and improvements

Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2022-12-07-4170-release-incl-language-servers-version-1410
downloads

To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Spring Tools 4.17.1 is scheduled to be released in early Febuary 2023.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Busy Plugin Developers Newsletter – Fall 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=platform&amp;p=303170</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/platform/2022/12/busy-plugin-developers-newsletter-fall-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T13:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community highlights: ⭐️ Winners of the Space Apps Contest JetBrains Space recently held an open application development contest, attracting more than 500 participants. 14 of the 35 apps submitted made it to the final round. Check out the winners. New guest posts: – Interview with Sven Reinck, the author of the XSD / WSDL Visualizer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Maltceva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hour of Code: Top 5 Kotlin Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=305629</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/12/07/hour-of-code-top-5-kotlin-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T11:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the third day of the Hour of Code celebration! If you missed our previous posts, check out the most popular Python and Java projects on JetBrains Academy. Our next topic is dedicated to one of the most loved programming languages — Kotlin. Kotlin is a modern cross-platform and multi-purpose programming language. It has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Khudikova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The eggplants before Richard Nixon]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43438</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/721362924/0/sethsblog~The-eggplants-before-Richard-Nixon/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T11:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For thousands of years, eggplants have had ‘features’ like this. But once we learned what they resemble, we can’t unsee it. It used to be a weird shape for a vegetable, but now it looks eerily like a former President. Once we find a hook, we can’t forget it. Our job as story tellers is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at EMNLP 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/google-at-emnlp-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/google-at-emnlp-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T08:41:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Malaya Jules, Program Manager, Google  
This week, the premier conference on Empirical Methods in Natural Language Processing (EMNLP 2022) is being held in Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates. We are proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of EMNLP 2022, with Google researchers contributing at all levels. This year we are presenting over 50 papers and are actively involved in 10 different workshops and tutorials. 
    
If you’re registered for EMNLP 2022, we hope you’ll visit the Google booth to learn more about the exciting work across various topics, including language interactions, causal inference, question answering and more. Take a look below to learn more about the Google research being presented at EMNLP 2022 (Google affiliations in bold). 
    

Committees
  
Organizing Committee incl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Universal Profiling unwinds stacks without frame pointers and symbols]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/universal-profiling-frame-pointers-symbols-ebpf</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/universal-profiling-frame-pointers-symbols-ebpf"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how universal profiling and Elastic Observability enables you to unwind stacks without symbols or frame pointers for frictionless, low overhead system profiling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Heelan,Thomas Dullien,Israel Ogbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Universal Profiling unwinds stacks without frame pointers and symbols]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/universal-profiling-frame-pointers-symbols-ebpf</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/universal-profiling-frame-pointers-symbols-ebpf"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic Universal ProfilingTM is based on technology that came into Elastic as part of the acquisition of optimyze.cloud — a startup that had developed Prodfiler.com, the world’s first frictionless fleet-wide in-production multi-runtime profiler that was launched in August 2021.

In order to bring the vision of frictionless deployability, low performance overhead, “just run it everywhere” magic to the broader market, a number of technical innovations were necessary. In this blog post, we will discuss one of the more important ones: how to unwind stacks without frame pointers and symbols.

[Related article: Elastic Universal Profiling™ helps you deliver fast, affordable, and efficient services]
How a sampling profiler works
A sampling profiler instructs the operating system to be run “per…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Heelan,Thomas Dullien,Israel Ogbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mystery Asterisk Destination]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2708/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2708/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/mystery_asterisk_destination.png" title="If you ever see the † dagger symbol with no unmatched footnote, it means the writer is saying the phrase while threatening you with a dagger." alt="If you ever see the † dagger symbol with no unmatched footnote, it means the writer is saying the phrase while threatening you with a dagger." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will You Find These Shortcuts?]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/will-you-find-these-shortcuts.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/will-you-find-these-shortcuts.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T20:56:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Katja Filippova, Research Scientist, and Sebastian Ebert, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain team    
Modern machine learning models that learn to solve a task by going through many examples can achieve stellar performance when evaluated on a test set, but sometimes they are right for the “wrong” reasons: they make correct predictions but use information that appears irrelevant to the task. How can that be? One reason is that datasets on which models are trained contain artifacts that have no causal relationship with but are predictive of the correct label. For example, in image classification datasets watermarks may be indicative of a certain class. Or it can happen that all the pictures of dogs happen to be taken outside, against green grass, so a green background become…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2022 RTW]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66134</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/now-available-azure-devops-server-2022-rtw/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T20:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the final release of Azure DevOps Server 2022! You can upgrade from Azure DevOps Server 2022 release candidates or previous versions of TFS and Azure DevOps. You can find the full details in our release notes.
Azure DevOps Server 2022 ISO
Azure DevOps Server 2022 Web Install
Release Notes
Azure DevOps Server requirements and compatibility
Installation documentation
We’d love for you to install this release candidate and provide any feedback at Developer Community.
The post Now available: Azure DevOps Server 2022 RTW appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New npm features for secure publishing and safe consumption]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-06-new-npm-features-for-secure-publishing-and-safe-consumption/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-06-new-npm-features-for-secure-publishing-and-safe-consumption/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T17:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now you can create tokens with fine-grained permissions for automating your publishing and organization management workflows. And a new code explorer allows you to view content of a package directly in the npm portal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project signing and verification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/project-signing-and-verification</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/project-signing-and-verification"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project signing is a new feature developed for Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform that came out in the latest 2.3 release. It enables users to sign project-based content (think playbooks, workflows, inventories, etc.) and verify whether or not that content has remained secure. It also features a new CLI tool, ansible-sign. This blog post will explain how it works, illustrate how to implement it, and highlight a few scenarios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lila Yasin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hour of Code: Top 5 Java Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=304541</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2022/12/06/hour-of-code-top-5-java-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T13:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the second day of the Hour of Code celebration, and we’re back with more amazing projects to tell you about! Today’s topic is Java, and in case you missed our post about the TOP-5 most popular Python projects on JetBrains Academy, you can still catch up. Java is a true leviathan of the programming […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekaterina Khudikova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Massie Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44324</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/721249062/0/sethsblog~The-Massie-Effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T10:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Put this one next to Dunning Kruger, which shows that people of low ability traditionally overrate how talented they are. The Massie Effect is the tendency of people who support good causes to believe they are in the minority. A study at Princeton showed that almost 80% of Americans believe we should take action on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - December 6th, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/06/this-week-in-spring-december-6th-2022</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/06/this-week-in-spring-december-6th-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! How are you? You know what I’ve wanted to do? See my friends on the Spring team in person since the pandemic descended. And, I’m overjoyed to relate, I’ve just had the privilege of a nice meeting with several of them last night. And I’m going to see more of them today! Seriously. I feel like I won the lottery. I’ve missed my friends. Hug your friends and family, friends. You never know when the next pandemic (or life in general) will put distance between you and them. So, in order to close that distance, I’m going to go back to meetings with them, and I’ll leave you with yet another week’s curated list of content. (Can you believe we’re like four weeks away from 2023?)


  
A Bootiful Podcast: Java Champion Gunnar Mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic named a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SIEM 2022 Vendor Assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-named-major-player-idc-marketscape-worldwide-siem-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-named-major-player-idc-marketscape-worldwide-siem-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic is named a major Player in the 2022 IDC MarketScape for Worldwide SIEM Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Paquette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic named a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SIEM 2022 Vendor Assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-named-major-player-idc-marketscape-worldwide-siem-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-named-major-player-idc-marketscape-worldwide-siem-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
We are excited to announce that Elastic has been named a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SIEM 2022 Vendor Assessment (Doc #US49029922). We believe our placement serves as further validation of our commitment to providing customers with a world-class security analytics solution on an open, unified platform to protect against the most sophisticated threats.
We are incredibly grateful to our customers who continue to adopt Elastic Security to gain comprehensive threat surface visibility, real-time detection and response, and insightful workflows for threat hunting and investigation. Elastic delivers all the attributes of a modern SOC, including support for third-party EDR vendors; out-of-the-box protections for endpoint and cloud; security orchestration, automation, and respo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Paquette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICYMI: A look back at GitHub Universe 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-05-icymi-a-look-back-at-github-universe-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-05-icymi-a-look-back-at-github-universe-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T19:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on everything we announced and see what else happened during this year’s GitHub Universe conference that took place November 9-10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep the learning pace! A Holiday recap about network automation sessions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/keep-the-learning-pace-a-holiday-recap-about-network-automation-sessions</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/keep-the-learning-pace-a-holiday-recap-about-network-automation-sessions"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In case you want to review the most relevant sessions, here is a summary on the abridged network automation related sessions that you can check on-demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dafné Mendoza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.4 and 3.0.0-M3 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/05/spring-shell-2-1-4-and-3-0-0-m3-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/05/spring-shell-2-1-4-and-3-0-0-m3-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Shell 2.1.4 and 3.0.0-M3 has been released and is now available from https://repo.spring.io/release, Maven Central and https://repo.spring.io/milestone respectively.

3.0.0-M3 is first milestone which builds on Spring Boot 3.0.0 GA version.

Please see the release notes 2.1.4 and release notes 3.0.0-M3 for more details.

Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expertise]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43322</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/721149044/0/sethsblog~Expertise/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a competition between someone who knows the most and someone who is willing to learn the most, the edge usually goes to the curious and empathic professional, not the one who is simply protecting what’s already known.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 questions public sector leaders should be asking about their data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-questions-public-sector-leaders-should-be-asking-about-their-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-questions-public-sector-leaders-should-be-asking-about-their-data"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Government agencies and educational institutions are accelerating their move toward cloud, SaaS, and customer-first digital experiences. The common denominator of all these initiatives? Data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 questions public sector leaders should be asking about their data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-questions-public-sector-leaders-should-be-asking-about-their-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/5-questions-public-sector-leaders-should-be-asking-about-their-data"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Government agencies and educational institutions across the globe are accelerating their move toward cloud, SaaS, and customer-first digital experiences. The common denominator of all these initiatives? Data. Specifically, the quality and quantity of data you have, where you store it, how you access it, and how quickly you can find what you need. Data, in other words, is one of the public sector’s most strategic assets.
Because of data’s ubiquity, it can be hard to make sense of it holistically, especially when bridging the data silos on teams, departments, and even organizations. To help you focus on the data priorities that will have the most impact on your public sector organization, consider the following five questions.
1. How can you facilitate data sharing?
According to McKinsey, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leanne Link</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomy Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2707/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2707/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/astronomy_numbers.png" title="I adopted a cat that weighs 12 solar masses. Laser pointers love chasing it." alt="I adopted a cat that weighs 12 solar masses. Laser pointers love chasing it." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Forensic container checkpointing in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/05/forensic-container-checkpointing-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/05/forensic-container-checkpointing-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Adrian Reber (Red Hat)
Forensic container checkpointing is based on Checkpoint/Restore In
Userspace (CRIU) and allows the creation of stateful copies
of a running container without the container knowing that it is being
checkpointed. The copy of the container can be analyzed and restored in a
sandbox environment multiple times without the original container being aware
of it. Forensic container checkpointing was introduced as an alpha feature in
Kubernetes v1.25.
How does it work?
With the help of CRIU it is possible to checkpoint and restore containers.
CRIU is integrated in runc, crun, CRI-O and containerd and forensic container
checkpointing as implemented in Kubernetes uses these existing CRIU
integrations.
Why is it important?
With the help of CRIU and the corresponding integ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When we look in the mirror]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43301</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/721083716/0/sethsblog~When-we-look-in-the-mirror/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T09:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we look in the mirror, who do we see? [A note I sent to a young friend.] The person we see when we look in the mirror is the person we become, the person we fight to defend and persist with. If you see someone who doesn’t have a lot of friends, then every […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ready-to-go sample data pipelines with Dataflow]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/17440a9e141d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/ready-to-go-sample-data-pipelines-with-dataflow-17440a9e141d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T00:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Jasmine Omeke, Obi-Ike Nwoke, Olek Gorajek]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidence doesn’t help win the lottery]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43320</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/721013992/0/sethsblog~Confidence-doesnt-help-win-the-lottery/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T09:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn’t matter how sure you are that this is a winning ticket, the ticket doesn’t care. And there are lots of lotteries in our lives. I was talking to a fifteen-year old the other day. He’s decided to devote the next decade of his life to getting drafted to play in the NBA. Without […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring WS Samples upgraded for Spring Boot 3.0!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/02/spring-ws-samples-upgraded-for-spring-boot-3-0</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/02/spring-ws-samples-upgraded-for-spring-boot-3-0"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T23:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the recent announcement of Spring Boot 3.0 going GA, some of you may be interested in upgrading your Spring Web Services-based applications to take full advantage of this. The Spring WS team has upgraded our set of sample apps to help you carry that out.



The main branch now tracks the version of samples with all these updates. (The prior version of samples built on Spring Boot 2.7 are now on that repository’s 1.0.x branch.)



Some of the highlights are covered below.



A LOT of our tools have moved!



Back in the olden days, much of our XML processing tools were inside the JDK. But ever since Java 9 and the migrations of Java EE-based packages to the Eclipse Foundation, those tools have since been pulled out of the JDK. On top of that, SOAP-based libraries, heavily l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub, accessibility, and the disability divide]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-02-github-accessibility-and-the-disability-divide/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-02-github-accessibility-and-the-disability-divide/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T17:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just published our vision for GitHub accessibility at accessibility.github.com. Here’s the TL;DR: the prime directive of the GitHub accessibility program is to empower people with disabilities to build cool technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Mona Sans and Hubot Sans]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2022-12-02-introducing-mona-sans-and-hubot-sans/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-12-02-introducing-mona-sans-and-hubot-sans/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T16:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use and express yourself with GitHub’s open source variable fonts, Mona Sans and Hubot Sans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.0 Release Candidate 3 (codename Kilburn) Has Been Released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/02/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-release-candidate-3-codename-kilburn-has-been-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/02/spring-cloud-2022-0-0-release-candidate-3-codename-kilburn-has-been-released"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the community, I am pleased to announce that the Release Candidate 3 (RC3) of the Spring Cloud 2022.0 Release Train is available today. The release can be found in Spring Milestone repository. You can check out the 2022.0 release notes for more information.
Notable Changes in the 2022.0.0 RC3 release

Click here to see all issues in this release.

Spring Cloud 2022.0.0-RC3 requires Spring Boot 3.0.0.
Spring Cloud Contract


  
Removes Gradle’s support for src/test/resources/contracts checking (#1848)


Check the latest migration guide entry for more information.
Spring Cloud Gateway


  
Added the possibility to disable global CORS configuration (#2779)


Spring Cloud OpenFeign


  
Support for AOT and native images has been added (#794)

  
Support for Micrometer …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accounting (and small business)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43316</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/720940456/0/sethsblog~Accounting-and-small-business/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every small business needs a bookkeeper, but few take appropriate advantage of accounting. Accounting is a way to turn organized books into insight. Particularly:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The reasons search seems to be getting worse]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44313</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/720936562/0/sethsblog~The-reasons-search-seems-to-be-getting-worse/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even with the powerful Ecosia engine, but especially with Google and Amazon, it’s getting rarer and rarer that a search feels as though it finds just the right site or product or information on the very first try. There are a few reasons for this:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bendy]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2706/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2706/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/bendy.png" title="Squaring the circle is really easy with some good clamps." alt="Squaring the circle is really easy with some good clamps." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Finding suspicious syscalls with the seccomp notifier]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/02/seccomp-notifier/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/02/seccomp-notifier/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Sascha Grunert
Debugging software in production is one of the biggest challenges we have to
face in our containerized environments. Being able to understand the impact of
the available security options, especially when it comes to configuring our
deployments, is one of the key aspects to make the default security in
Kubernetes stronger. We have all those logging, tracing and metrics data already
at hand, but how do we assemble the information they provide into something
human readable and actionable?
Seccomp is one of the standard mechanisms to protect a Linux based
Kubernetes application from malicious actions by interfering with its system
calls. This allows us to restrict the application to a defined set of
actionable items, like modifying files or responding to HTTP requests. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benefits of process mapping: Examples and guide]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=68873&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=68873</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/12/process-mapping-benefits/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how process mapping can help your organization gain an advantage. See an example and tips and recommendations for creating one yourself.
The post Benefits of process mapping: Examples and guide appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talking to Robots in Real Time]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/talking-to-robots-in-real-time.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/12/talking-to-robots-in-real-time.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Corey Lynch, Research Scientist, and Ayzaan Wahid, Research Engineer, Robotics at Google   
A grand vision in robot learning, going back to the SHRDLU experiments in the late 1960s, is that of helpful robots that inhabit human spaces and follow a wide variety of natural language commands. Over the last few years, there have been significant advances in the application of machine learning (ML) for instruction following, both in simulation and in real world systems. Recent Palm-SayCan work has produced robots that leverage language models to plan long-horizon behaviors and reason about abstract goals. Code as Policies has shown that code-generating language models combined with pre-trained perception systems can produce language conditioned policies for zero shot robot manipulation…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Process PDFs, Word Documents, and Images with Amazon Comprehend for IDP]]></title>
        <id>9b22726a3e68bf2e7407f519b286ce9588418703</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-process-pdfs-word-documents-and-images-with-amazon-comprehend-for-idp/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T17:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing a new Amazon Comprehend feature for intelligent document processing (IDP). This feature allows you to classify and extract entities from PDF documents, Microsoft Word files, and images directly from Amazon Comprehend without you needing to extract the text first. Many customers need to process documents that have a semi-structured format, like […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon GameLift Anywhere – Run Your Game Servers on Your Own Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>222c6b77db7b5f5f6ec69fcc90e8a7cb595451c4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-gamelift-anywhere-run-your-game-servers-on-your-own-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T17:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2016, we launched Amazon GameLift, a dedicated hosting solution that securely deploys and automatically scales fleets of session-based multiplayer game servers to meet worldwide player demand. With Amazon GameLift, you can create and upload a game server build once, replicate, and then deploy across multiple AWS Regions and AWS Local Zones to reach your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon CodeCatalyst, a Unified Software Development Service (Preview)]]></title>
        <id>d29044f8e57bafd3bebc55e88c2ff464055fe550</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-codecatalyst-preview-a-unified-software-development-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T17:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we announced the preview release of Amazon CodeCatalyst. A unified software development and delivery service, Amazon CodeCatalyst enables software development teams to quickly and easily plan, develop, collaborate on, build, and deliver applications on AWS, reducing friction throughout the development lifecycle. In my time as a developer the biggest excitement—besides shipping software to users—was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Create Point-to-Point Integrations Between Event Producers and Consumers with Amazon EventBridge Pipes]]></title>
        <id>a06338eb3c56149fb4502fc20e98979d5b98cbb8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-create-point-to-point-integrations-between-event-producers-and-consumers-with-amazon-eventbridge-pipes/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T17:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is increasingly common to use multiple cloud services as building blocks to assemble a modern event-driven application. Using purpose-built services to accomplish a particular task ensures developers get the best capabilities for their use case. However, communication between services can be difficult if they use different technologies to communicate, meaning that you need to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Step Functions Distributed Map – A Serverless Solution for Large-Scale Parallel Data Processing]]></title>
        <id>e192bd704e7b3a5a0a1e8ca11d4329d85f29ef1b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/step-functions-distributed-map-a-serverless-solution-for-large-scale-parallel-data-processing/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T16:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am excited to announce the availability of a distributed map for AWS Step Functions. This flow extends support for orchestrating large-scale parallel workloads such as the on-demand processing of semi-structured data. Step Function’s map state executes the same processing steps for multiple entries in a dataset. The existing map state is limited to 40 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Books for your solstice]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=44295</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/720869478/0/sethsblog~Books-for-your-solstice/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T15:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Northern Hemisphere, it gets dark in December. And worldwide, people buy gifts for whatever holidays they celebrate, and a lot of them are around the corner. For both reasons, books! The Carbon Almanac was an Amazon Editor’s choice, a Do Lectures top 100 choice, a bestseller in every country it has been released […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Java Champion Gunnar Morling about messaging middleware, Debezium, change data capture, and more.]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/01/a-bootiful-podcast-java-champion-gunnar-morling-about-messaging-middleware-debezium-change-data-capture-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/12/01/a-bootiful-podcast-java-champion-gunnar-morling-about-messaging-middleware-debezium-change-data-capture-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to Java Champion Gunnar Morling (@gunnarmorling) about messaging middleware, Debezium, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Boosting Kubernetes container runtime observability with OpenTelemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/01/runtime-observability-opentelemetry/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/12/01/runtime-observability-opentelemetry/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Sascha Grunert
When speaking about observability in the cloud native space, then probably
everyone will mention OpenTelemetry (OTEL) at some point in the
conversation. That's great, because the community needs standards to rely on
for developing all cluster components into the same direction. OpenTelemetry
enables us to combine logs, metrics, traces and other contextual information
(called baggage) into a single resource. Cluster administrators or software
engineers can use this resource to get a viewport about what is going on in the
cluster over a defined period of time. But how can Kubernetes itself make use of
this technology stack?
Kubernetes consists of multiple components where some are independent and others
are stacked together. Looking at the architecture from a containe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Marketplace Vendor Insights – Simplify Third-Party Software Risk Assessments]]></title>
        <id>803631ae81c7cabb27063790e4f8aa8a53c48da2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-marketplace-vendor-insights-simplify-third-party-software-risk-assessments/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T23:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Marketplace Vendor Insights is a new capability of AWS Marketplace. It simplifies third-party software risk assessments when procuring solutions from the AWS Marketplace. It helps you to ensure that the third-party software continuously meets your industry standards by compiling security and compliance information, such as data privacy and residency, application security, and access control, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEO Ash Kulkarni's email to Elastic employees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ceo-ash-kulkarni-email-to-elastic-employees</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ceo-ash-kulkarni-email-to-elastic-employees"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I have the sad responsibility to announce we are reducing our team by about 13%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEO Ash Kulkarni's email to Elastic employees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/ceo-ash-kulkarni-email-to-elastic-employees</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/ceo-ash-kulkarni-email-to-elastic-employees"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today, I have the sad responsibility to announce we are reducing our team by about 13%.
I didn't take this decision lightly. Since becoming CEO, I have had the opportunity to spend time with Elasticians around the globe. It's been an honor getting to know so many of you. Your passion and commitment humble me.
I have also had the privilege of meeting with hundreds of our customers. We are fortunate that security, observability, and search are mission-critical to our customers. However, it has become clear that the global macroeconomic environment is forcing our customers to tighten budgets and review investments more closely. This is especially true in certain segments of the market like small and medium businesses where the current appetite to spend in uncertain times is limited.
In orde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform and AWS: re:Invent Caps Off a Big Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-and-aws-re-invent-caps-off-a-big-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-terraform-and-aws-re-invent-caps-off-a-big-year"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS re:Invent 2022 is here. We highlighted what’s new with Terraform and AWS — like Launch Day support for new AWS services in the Terraform AWS Provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for Amazon SageMaker – Perform Shadow Tests to Compare Inference Performance Between ML Model Variants]]></title>
        <id>dc4135389b98b1a4c58cbedd92904a957165a7fb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-amazon-sagemaker-perform-shadow-tests-to-compare-inference-performance-between-ml-model-variants/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you move your machine learning (ML) workloads into production, you need to continuously monitor your deployed models and iterate when you observe a deviation in your model performance. When you build a new model, you typically start validating the model offline using historical inference request data. But this data sometimes fails to account for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Generation SageMaker Notebooks – Now with Built-in Data Preparation, Real-Time Collaboration, and Notebook Automation]]></title>
        <id>68da6bc4cdde1e218287d2175d96cd6fcf5732ac</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/next-generation-sagemaker-notebooks-now-with-built-in-data-preparation-real-time-collaboration-and-notebook-automation/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2019, we introduced Amazon SageMaker Studio, the first fully integrated development environment (IDE) for data science and machine learning (ML). SageMaker Studio gives you access to fully managed Jupyter Notebooks that integrate with purpose-built tools to perform all ML steps, from preparing data to training and debugging models, tracking experiments, deploying and monitoring models, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Share ML Models and Notebooks More Easily Within Your Organization with Amazon SageMaker JumpStart]]></title>
        <id>a4b2fd2c078e283171f1c0ebe65d4b3befcce646</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-share-ml-models-and-notebooks-more-easily-within-your-organization-with-amazon-sagemaker-jumpstart/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker JumpStart is a machine learning (ML) hub that can help you accelerate your ML journey. SageMaker JumpStart gives you access to built-in algorithms with pre-trained models from popular model hubs, pre-trained foundation models to help you perform tasks such as article summarization and image generation, and end-to-end solutions to solve common use cases. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Machine Learning University New Educator Enablement Program to Build Diverse Talent for ML/AI Jobs]]></title>
        <id>a6c2e7999e75fcdbac0264a787345e7cc102c681</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-machine-learning-university-new-educator-enablement-program-to-build-diverse-talent-for-ml-ai-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Machine Learning University is now providing a free educator enablement program. This program provides faculty at community colleges, minority-serving institutions (MSIs), and historically Black colleges and universities (HBCUs) with the skills and resources to teach data analytics, artificial intelligence (AI), and machine learning (ML) concepts to build a diverse pipeline for in-demand jobs of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for Amazon Redshift – Simplify Data Ingestion and Make Your Data Warehouse More Secure and Reliable]]></title>
        <id>a3df3f584fbeaa72bcfd1602e37a589cebaf3db1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-amazon-redshift-simplify-data-ingestion-and-make-your-data-warehouse-more-secure-and-reliable/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we talk with customers, we hear that they want to be able to harness insights from data in order to make timely, impactful, and actionable business decisions. A common pattern with data-driven organizations is that they have many diﬀerent data sources they need to ingest into their analytics systems. This requires them to build […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Introducing Support for Real-Time and Batch Inference in Amazon SageMaker Data Wrangler]]></title>
        <id>173c33aaebef80f4198557f2b51dd3b215517e09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-introducing-support-for-real-time-and-batch-inference-in-amazon-sagemaker-data-wrangler/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To build machine learning models, machine learning engineers need to develop a data transformation pipeline to prepare the data. The process of designing this pipeline is time-consuming and requires a cross-team collaboration between machine learning engineers, data engineers, and data scientists to implement the data preparation pipeline into a production environment. The main objective of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New — Amazon SageMaker Data Wrangler Supports SaaS Applications as Data Sources]]></title>
        <id>97085f0b733b45f6660dd61a52eab8ee12246617</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-sagemaker-data-wrangler-supports-saas-applications-as-data-sources/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data fuels machine learning. In machine learning, data preparation is the process of transforming raw data into a format that is suitable for further processing and analysis. The common process for data preparation starts with collecting data, then cleaning it, labeling it, and finally validating and visualizing it. Getting the data right with high quality […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Additional Data Connectors for Amazon AppFlow]]></title>
        <id>bb2a6aa181f76ef1d8fdc0056149bf70e01058c3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-additional-data-connectors-for-amazon-appflow/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gathering insights from data is a more effective process if that data isn’t fragmented across multiple systems and data stores, whether on premises or in the cloud. Amazon AppFlow provides bidirectional data integration between on-premises systems and applications, SaaS applications, and AWS services. It helps customers break down data silos using a low- or no-code, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ML Governance Tools for Amazon SageMaker – Simplify Access Control and Enhance Transparency Over Your ML Projects]]></title>
        <id>7ca4cd611ea7dd61e5bbd3f48af5af26d91668f9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-ml-governance-tools-for-amazon-sagemaker-simplify-access-control-and-enhance-transparency-over-your-ml-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T17:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As companies increasingly adopt machine learning (ML) for their business applications, they are looking for ways to improve governance of their ML projects with simplified access control and enhanced visibility across the ML lifecycle. A common challenge in that effort is managing the right set of user permissions across different groups and ML activities. For […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the Preview – AWS Glue Data Quality]]></title>
        <id>b918eaaca2429f94564180180fdc8d2938aaae00</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/join-the-preview-aws-glue-data-quality/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T17:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 1980, at my second professional programming job, I was working on a project that analyzed driver’s license data from a bunch of US states. At that time data of that type was generally stored in fixed-length records, with values carefully (or not) encoded into each field. Although we were given schemas for the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Trusted Language Extensions for PostgreSQL on Amazon Aurora and Amazon RDS]]></title>
        <id>cac2818702a6c1aaa8157fc247203f740d7d65a2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-trusted-language-extensions-for-postgresql-on-amazon-aurora-and-amazon-rds/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T17:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL has become the preferred open-source relational database for many enterprises and start-ups with its extensible design for developers. One of the reasons developers use PostgreSQL is it allows them to add database functionality by building extensions with their preferred programming languages. You can already install and use PostgreSQL extensions in Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL-Compatible Edition […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview: Use Amazon SageMaker to Build, Train, and Deploy ML Models Using Geospatial Data]]></title>
        <id>6f12a5b40f696e74721c2255a2b4c6b5ec9640ca</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/preview-use-amazon-sagemaker-to-build-train-and-deploy-ml-models-using-geospatial-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T17:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You use map apps every day to find your favorite restaurant or travel the fastest route using geospatial data. There are two types of geospatial data: vector data that uses two-dimensional geometries such as a building location (points), roads (lines), or land boundary (polygons), and raster data such as satellite and aerial images. Last year, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Redesigned UI for Amazon SageMaker Studio]]></title>
        <id>739b7e9690e19cb33076cc6d7c84b6ce2d027a7a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-redesigned-ui-for-amazon-sagemaker-studio/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T17:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m excited to announce a new, redesigned user interface (UI) for Amazon SageMaker Studio. SageMaker Studio provides a single, web-based visual interface where you can perform all machine learning (ML) development steps with a comprehensive set of ML tools. For example, you can prepare data using SageMaker Data Wrangler, build ML models with fully […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Amazon DocumentDB Elastic Clusters]]></title>
        <id>35e52a0503f828769a12f15fe122c88905a50eba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-amazon-documentdb-elastic-clusters/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T16:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility) is a scalable, highly durable, and fully managed database service for operating mission-critical JSON workloads. It is one of AWS fast-growing services with customers including BBC, Dow Jones, and Samsung relying on Amazon DocumentDB to run their JSON workloads at scale. Today I am excited to announce the general availability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making a Traversable Wormhole with a Quantum Computer]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/making-traversable-wormhole-with.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/making-traversable-wormhole-with.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T16:04:00.013Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alexander Zlokapa, Student Researcher, and Hartmut Neven, VP of Engineering, Quantum AI Team  
Wormholes — wrinkles in the fabric of spacetime that connect two disparate locations — may seem like the stuff of science fiction. But whether or not they exist in reality, studying these hypothetical objects could be the key to making concrete the tantalizing link between information and matter that has bedeviled physicists for decades.  
  
Surprisingly, a quantum computer is an ideal platform to investigate this connection. The trick is to use a correspondence called AdS/CFT, which establishes an equivalence between a theory that describes gravity and spacetime (and wormholes) in a fictional world with a special geometry (AdS) to a quantum theory that does not contain gravity at all …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第220話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190247003850147</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190247003850147"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spacetime Soccer]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2705/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2705/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/spacetime_soccer.png" title="Spacetime Soccer, known outside the United States as '4D Football' is a now-defunct sport. Infamous for referee decisions hinging on inconsistent definitions of simultaneity, it is also known for the disappearance of many top players during... [more]" alt="Spacetime Soccer, known outside the United States as '4D Football' is a now-defunct sport. Infamous for referee decisions hinging on inconsistent definitions of simultaneity, it is also known for the disappearance of many top players during... [more]" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[re:Invent Roundup: HashiCorp Zero Trust Security and More with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/re-invent-roundup-hashicorp-zero-trust-security-and-more-with-aws</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/re-invent-roundup-hashicorp-zero-trust-security-and-more-with-aws"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read our recap of HashiCorp security and networking news and developments on AWS from this past year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - November 29th, 2022 (Spring Boot 3 has arrived)]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/29/this-week-in-spring-november-29th-2022-spring-boot-3-has-arrived</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/29/this-week-in-spring-november-29th-2022-spring-boot-3-has-arrived"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! It’s here! It’s finally here, at long last! Spring Boot 3!! And of course with Spring Boot 3.0 comes a whole portfolio of integrated projects that have also been updated! Remember, a huge theme in this release is support for GraalVM native images, and that’s now supported across the board. You know what to do: start.spring.io. 

I put together a Spring Tipds video introducing some of the major themes of Spring Framework 6 / Spring Boot 3. 


I also did an in-depth look at the new GraalVM support powered by Spring’s ahead-of-time (AOT) engine. 


There’s so much else to talk about this week, but I really can’t stress this enough: Spring Boot 3 is here! In some ways, it feels like this release has been more than four years in the making! It’s amazing, and I can’t wait f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Integration 6.0 goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/29/spring-integration-6-0-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/29/spring-integration-6-0-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T17:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring community,



On behalf of the team, it is my very great pleasure to announce that Spring Integration 6.0.0 is now generally available and can be found in Maven Central.



This release is the culmination of more than a year of work.
A massive thank you to everyone that has contributed, and to all the early adopters that have been providing vital feedback on the milestones.



This version is fully based on Spring Framework 6.0, Spring Data 2022.0, Spring for GraphQL 1.1, Spring WebServices 4.0 and many other major releases of Spring portfolio projects which contribute to their respective integration modules.
On the other hand Spring Integration 6.0 is a part of recently released Spring Boot 3.0.



Highlights of the new release include:





A Java 17 baseline



Support for native images with GraalVM and Spring AOT engine



Observability instrumentation with Micrometer and Micrometer Tracing



Support for Jakarta EE 10 with an EE 9 baseline





There’s far too many features to list them all here in detail, so head over to the What’s New documentation page and check out a Migration Guide on GitHub.
If you just want to get started, you can easily bootstrap a new project on start.spring.io.
If you’d like to try out the GraalVM support, start.spring.io can help with that too.



Cheers, 

Artem



Project Page | GitHub Issues | Contributing | Help | Chat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Language Models Without Massive Compute]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/better-language-models-without-massive.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/better-language-models-without-massive.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jason Wei and Yi Tay, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team 
In recent years, language models (LMs) have become more prominent in natural language processing (NLP) research and are also becoming increasingly impactful in practice. Scaling up LMs has been shown to improve performance across a range of NLP tasks. For instance, scaling up language models can improve perplexity across seven orders of magnitude of model sizes, and new abilities such as multi-step reasoning have been observed to arise as a result of model scale. However, one of the challenges of continued scaling is that training new, larger models requires great amounts of computational resources. Moreover, new models are often trained from scratch and do not leverage the weights from previously existing mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2.3</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-in-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-2.3"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce the general availability of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.3. If you didn’t get the opportunity to attend AnsibleFest 2022 in Chicago, or get time to watch the keynotes on the AnsibleFest content hub, I am the lucky Ansiblite (or is it Ansi-Bull) who will walk you through all the new, cool and exciting features coming with our new release. Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 introduces a number of new features and capabilities that deliver simpler, security-focused automation at scale. Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 is compatible with the Developer Preview of Event-Driven Ansible, a new set of capabilities that empower true end-to-end automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet ElastAsians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Employee resource groups, or Elastician resource groups as we call them, are groups within Elastic that are aligned with shared identities, experiences, interests, affinities, and allyships.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERGs encourage you to come as you are: Meet ElastAsians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/culture-ergs-encourage-you-to-come-as-you-are-meet-elastasians"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Employee resource groups, or Elastician resource groups as we call them, are groups within Elastic that are aligned with shared identities, experiences, interests, affinities, and allyships. 
These groups were formalized in 2021, but they’ve been a part of Elastic’s culture since 2016. By formalizing them, we’re able to ensure they all have a structure, budget, and a voice based on any dimension of diversity, identity, allyship, and advocacy. This was an important step in our global diversity, equity, and inclusion strategy. 
Each ERG has their own mission and goals, but as a whole they want to create community and belonging around shared interests and experiences. 
Our Core ERGs
We have seven formal ERGs: The Accessibles, Blasticians, ElastAsians, Elasticians Unidos, Rainbow Stack, Mil-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Culture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HashiCorp Waypoint Works with Terraform, Vault, and Consul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-waypoint-works-with-terraform-vault-and-consul</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-hashicorp-waypoint-works-with-terraform-vault-and-consul"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Waypoint uses plugins to accept configurations from Terraform, Consul, and Vault to simplify your application release orchestration workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at NeurIPS 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/google-at-neurips-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/google-at-neurips-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T15:29:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cat Armato, Program Manager, Google   
This week marks the beginning of the 36th annual Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS 2022), the biggest machine learning conference of the year. NeurIPS 2022 will be held as a hybrid event, in person in New Orleans, LA with some virtual attendance options, and includes invited talks, demonstrations and presentations of some of the latest in machine learning research. This year, NeurIPS is also offering a new track, called Spotlight Papers, which will provide opportunities to highlight papers presented in prestigious journals that would otherwise not have been eligible for submission. 
    
Google is proud to be a Diamond level sponsor of NeurIPS this year and will have a significant presence year with more than 175 a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walking on Clouds with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/walking-on-clouds-with-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/walking-on-clouds-with-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is a good day, and when it's a day like this we often feel like we are walking on clouds. With this latest announcement for the newest Red Hat Ansible Certified Collections available to our customers on the 28th of November, I am sure many cloud practitioners will be anticipating what the future will bring for their cloud automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nmartins@redhat.com (Nuno Martins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Vault 3.0 goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/28/spring-vault-3-0-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/28/spring-vault-3-0-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T08:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, it is my very great pleasure to announce that Spring Vault 3.0 is now generally available, and 3.0.0 can be found in Maven Central.



This release ships with several refinements and new features. Highlights of the new release include:





A Java 17 baseline



Support additional HTTP Clients, including the reactive JDK HTTP Client



Support for Vault Repositories using versioned Key/Value secrets engines





There are far too many features to list them all here in detail, so head over to the release notes page in our wiki to find out more.



Thanks to everyone who has contributed to Spring Vault over the years!



Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to import Strava data into the Elastic Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-import-strava-data-elastic-stack</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-import-strava-data-elastic-stack"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first blog post in a series of ones to follow. I will take you through a journey of data onboarding, manipulation, and visualization using Strava as a backdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to import Strava data into the Elastic Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-import-strava-data-elastic-stack</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/how-to-import-strava-data-elastic-stack"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
This is the first blog post in a series of ones to follow. I will take you through a journey of data onboarding, manipulation, and visualization.

What is Strava and why is it the focus? Strava is a platform where athletes, from recreational to professional, can share their activities. All my fitness data from my Apple Watch, Garmin, and Zwift is automatically synced and saved there. It is safe to say that if I want to get an overview of my fitness, getting the data out of Strava is the first step.

Why do this with the Elastic Stack? I want to ask my data questions, and questions are just searches!

Have I ridden my bike more this year than last?
On average, is my heart rate reduced by doing more distance on my bike?
Am I running, hiking, and cycling on the same tracks often?
Does my he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Kahr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: registry.k8s.io: faster, cheaper and Generally Available (GA)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/11/28/registry-k8s-io-faster-cheaper-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/11/28/registry-k8s-io-faster-cheaper-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Adolfo García Veytia (Chainguard), Bob Killen (Google)
Starting with Kubernetes 1.25, our container image registry has changed from k8s.gcr.io to registry.k8s.io. This new registry spreads the load across multiple Cloud Providers & Regions, functioning as a sort of content delivery network (CDN) for Kubernetes container images. This change reduces the project’s reliance on a single entity and provides a faster download experience for a large number of users.
TL;DR: What you need to know about this change
Container images for Kubernetes releases from 1.25 onward are no longer published to k8s.gcr.io, only to registry.k8s.io.
In the upcoming December patch releases, the new registry domain default will be backported to all branches still in support (1.22, 1.23, 1.24).
If you run in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Modulith 0.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-modulith-0-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-modulith-0-1-released"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T21:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hot on the heels of Spring Boot 3.0 GA, it’s my pleasure to announce the availability of Spring Modulith 0.1. The release concludes the integration of the Moduliths project into the Spring ecosystem. I want to especially thank Dmitry Belyaev and Björn Kieling who helped a lot during the migration and contributed significant new features to the project, the event publication repository implementations for JDBC and MongoDB in particular.

For a general introduction into the project, please check out the original announcement and this InfoQ article.

Changelog | Reference documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0 Goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-3-0-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-3-0-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T18:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, it is my very great pleasure to announce that Spring Boot 3.0 is now generally available and 3.0.0 can be found in Maven Central.

This release is the culmination of 12 months work and over 5700 commits by 151 different individuals. A massive thank you to everyone that has contributed, and to all the early adopters that have been providing vital feedback on the milestones.

This is the first major revision of Spring Boot since 2.0 was released 4.5 years ago. It’s also the first GA version of Spring Boot that provides support for Spring Framework 6.0 and GraalVM. 

Highlights of the new release include:


  
A Java 17 baseline

  
Support for generating native images with GraalVM, superseding the experimental Spring Native project

  
Improved observability with Micrometer and Micrometer Tracing

  
Support for Jakarta EE 10 with an EE 9 baseline


There’s far too many features to list them all here in detail, so head over to the release notes page on our wiki to find out more. If you just want to get started, you can easily bootstrap a new project on start.spring.io. If you’d like to try out the GraalVM support, start.spring.io can help with that too.

Over the coming weeks we’ll be publishing blog posts that cover some Spring Boot 3.0 features in detail.

Thanks again to everyone that has contributed to Spring and Spring Boot over the years! Supporting Jakarta EE 9 and 10, the observability enhancements, and GraalVM support has been a huge team effort that has left no corner of the Spring portfolio untouched. A special thank you to the developers of the other projects in the Spring portfolio, without whom this release would not have been possible.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.6 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-2-7-6-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-2-7-6-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T15:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.7.6 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 44 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-framework-6-0-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-framework-6-0-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T14:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.2 is available now.

Spring Framework 6.0.2 includes 4 fixes and documentation improvements.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.6.14 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-2-6-14-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-boot-2-6-14-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T14:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I’m happy to announce that Spring Boot 2.6.14 has been released and is now available from Maven Central.

This release includes 39 bug fixes, documentation improvements, and dependency upgrades. Thanks to all those who have contributed with issue reports and pull requests.
End of life

It’s just over a year since the release of Spring Boot 2.6.0 which means that, as per our open source support policy, 2.6.14 is the last release that’s planned in the 2.6.x line. Releases may be made in the future, but only in response to a commercial support request.

As previously announced, Spring Boot 2.7 will be the last minor in the 2.x line. As such, we’ve extended our open source support for 2.7.x release by an additional 6 months until November 2023. In addition, commercial support for Spring Boot 2.7 has also been extended and is available until February 2025.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, check out the “ideal for contribution” tag in the issue repository. If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-boot tag or chat with the community on Gitter.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow | Gitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Batch 5.0 Goes GA!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-batch-5-0-goes-ga</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/24/spring-batch-5-0-goes-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is finally here! Spring Batch 5.0 is now generally available from Maven Central. Spring Batch 5 is the culmination of two years of work, including dozens of improvements, features, and bug fixes by more than 50 contributors! On Behalf of the team, I would like to thank ALL contributors who had a role in this huge release!

This blog post walks through the major highlights of this new generation of the framework. You can find the details of all the changes in the release notes and the upgrade instructions in the migration guide.
What’s new?


  
New Java version baseline

  
Major dependencies upgrade

  
Full GraalVM native support

  
Introduction of the new Observation API from Micrometer

  
Execution context Meta-data improvement

  
New default execution context serializati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade of .NET agent for Azure Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=65991</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/upgrade-of-net-agent-for-azure-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T11:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are upgrading the .NET used by Azure Pipelines agent from current .NET Core 3.1 to .NET 6. This is to support new Apple silicon hardware as well as newer operating systems such as Ubuntu 22.04, or Windows on ARM64. Another reason for the .NET upgrade is the fact the .NET Core 3.1 version is already in maintenance phase and the support ends on December 13th,
The post Upgrade of .NET agent for Azure Pipelines appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bohdan Janousek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 6.0.1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-framework-6-0-1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-framework-6-0-1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T10:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 6.0.1 is available now.

Spring Framework 6.0.1 includes 21 fixes and improvements.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring for GraphQL 1.1.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-for-graphql-1-1-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-for-graphql-1-1-0-released"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pleased to announce that Spring for GraphQL 1.1.0 is now available on Maven Central. This version will ship with Spring Boot 3.0.0 later this week.

Spring for GraphQL 1.0.0 was released 6 months ago, so why a new minor version now? The team initially planned a 1.1.0 release with one goal in mind: support Spring Framework 6.0 / Spring Boot 3.0 and adapt to the new baseline for that generation:


  
Java 17

  
Jakarta EE 9

  
GraphQL Java 19


In addition, we shipped some new and noteworthy features we think you’ll like:
Observability

Observability is a major theme across the Spring portfolio in this major new Spring Framework 6 generation. Spring projects now have their own, built-in instrumentation for metrics and traces based on the new Observation API from Micrometer. Thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: the road to Spring Framework 6: the new Ahead-of-Time Compilation Engine and GraalVM]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-tips-the-road-to-spring-framework-6-the-new-ahead-of-time-compilation-engine-and-graalvm</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2022/11/23/spring-tips-the-road-to-spring-framework-6-the-new-ahead-of-time-compilation-engine-and-graalvm"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Spring Boot 3 is here (or will be tomorrow, on the 24th of November, 2022, to be more precise!), bringing a fantastic new Ahead-of-Time (AOT) compilation engine that supports GraalVM native images. Join me, and we’ll dive deep into the engine and its interactions with the Spring component model. 

This video is a detailed masterclass on the new AOT engine. It starts by examining the everyday usecases of an application developer and delves deeper and deeper into the engine, treating concerns that library and framework developers will care about. 

Enjoy! 


Also, Happy thanksgiving (if you celebrate) from us to you!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks 2023: 24-Hours of Virtual Knowledge Sharing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2023-24-hours-of-virtual-knowledge-sharing</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashitalks-2023-24-hours-of-virtual-knowledge-sharing"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiTalks returns on February 16, 2023. Join our global community for 24 hours of knowledge sharing. The call for speakers is open until December 7, 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and HashiCorp's Journey to 1 Billion Terraform AWS Provider Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-and-hashicorp-s-journey-to-1-billion-terraform-aws-provider-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/aws-and-hashicorp-s-journey-to-1-billion-terraform-aws-provider-downloads"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HashiCorp Terraform AWS provider has surpassed one billion downloads — here’s how we got there, and what to look for next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Importing/Exporting Collections in automation hubs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/importing/exporting-collections-in-automation-hubs</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/importing/exporting-collections-in-automation-hubs"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article discusses how to export and import Collections from one automation hub to another.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhardy@redhat.com (John Hardy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wait… Elastic Observability monitors metrics for AWS services in just minutes?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-service-metrics-monitor-observability-easy</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-service-metrics-monitor-observability-easy"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get metrics and logs from your AWS deployment and Elastic Observability in just minutes! We’ll show you how to use Elastic integrations to quickly monitor and manage the performance of your applications and AWS services to streamline troubleshooting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.5.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.5.2 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version. We recommend 8.5.2 over the previous versions in 8.5.x.
For details of the issues that have been fixed and a full list of changes for each product in this version, refer to the release notes: 
8.5.2 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Version 8.5.2 fixes a Fleet server issue on Windows.
It also contains an APM server fix for an issue where the server might be running out of memory when Tail based sampling is enabled. With the fix, buffered transactions are discarded if a certain buffer size is reached.
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Godard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wait… Elastic Observability monitors metrics for AWS services in just minutes?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-service-metrics-monitor-observability-easy</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/aws-service-metrics-monitor-observability-easy"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The transition to distributed applications is in full swing, driven mainly by our need to be “always-on” as consumers and fast-paced businesses. That need is driving deployments to have more complex requirements along with the ability to be globally diverse and rapidly innovate.



Cloud is becoming the de facto deployment option for today’s applications. Many cloud deployments choose to host their applications on AWS for the globally diverse set of regions it covers and the myriad of services (for faster development and innovation) available, as well as to drive operational and capital costs down. On AWS, development teams are finding additional value in migrating to Kubernetes on Amazon EKS, testing out the latest serverless options, and improving traditional, tiered applications with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahubali Shetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 8.5.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-2-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-8-5-2-released"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read about the updates and bug fixes that have been included in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Godard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul Service Mesh Support for AWS Lambda Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-service-mesh-support-for-aws-lambda-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul support for AWS Lambda is now generally available, enabling services in the mesh to invoke Lambda serverless functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Platform 8 for .NET developers]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=68193</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/camunda-platform-8-dotnet-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T17:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, learn how you can take advantage of Camunda for powerful process orchestration as a .NET developer.
The post Camunda Platform 8 for .NET developers appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Heinrichs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 new Ansible automation hub updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/3-new-ansible-automation-hub-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/3-new-ansible-automation-hub-updates"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond the buzz at AnsibleFest 2022 around event-driven automation, availability of Ansible in  AWS and Azure marketplaces, and Project Wisdom, some important changes were happening within Ansible automation hub, so let's take a closer look at the latest developments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>trmcconn@redhat.com (Tricia McConnell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation Summaries in Google Chat]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/conversation-summaries-in-google-chat.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/conversation-summaries-in-google-chat.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T20:23:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mohammad Saleh, Software Engineer, Google Research, Brain Team, and Yinan Wang, Software Engineer, Google Workspace   
Information overload is a significant challenge for many organizations and individuals today. It can be overwhelming to keep up with incoming chat messages and documents that arrive at our inbox everyday. This has been exacerbated by the increase in virtual work and remains a challenge as many teams transition to a hybrid work environment with a mix of those working both virtually and in an office. One solution that can address information overload is summarization — for example, to help users improve their productivity and better manage so much information, we recently introduced auto-generated summaries in Google Docs.  

Today, we are excited to introduce conv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.14 GA: Announcing Simplified Service Mesh Deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-14-ga-announcing-simplified-service-mesh-deployments</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-14-ga-announcing-simplified-service-mesh-deployments"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul 1.14 introduces the Consul dataplane, service mesh traffic management across cluster peers, and service failover enhancements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Removals, Deprecations, and Major Changes in 1.26]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/11/18/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-1-26/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/11/18/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-1-26/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS)
Change is an integral part of the Kubernetes life-cycle: as Kubernetes grows and matures, features may be deprecated, removed, or replaced with improvements for the health of the project. For Kubernetes v1.26 there are several planned: this article identifies and describes some of them, based on the information available at this mid-cycle point in the v1.26 release process, which is still ongoing and can introduce additional changes.
The Kubernetes API Removal and Deprecation process
The Kubernetes project has a well-documented deprecation policy for features. This policy states that stable APIs may only be deprecated when a newer, stable version of that same API is available and that APIs have a minimum lifetime for each stability level. A deprecated API is o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For your eyes only: improving Netflix video quality with neural networks]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5b8d032da09c</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/for-your-eyes-only-improving-netflix-video-quality-with-neural-networks-5b8d032da09c?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T21:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Christos G. Bampis, Li-Heng Chen and Zhi Li]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Data Cards Playbook: A Toolkit for Transparency in Dataset Documentation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/the-data-cards-playbook-toolkit-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/the-data-cards-playbook-toolkit-for.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T18:14:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mahima Pushkarna, Senior Interaction Designer, and Andrew Zaldivar, Senior Developer Relations Engineer, Google Research  
As machine learning (ML) research moves toward large-scale models capable of numerous downstream tasks, a shared understanding of a dataset’s origin, development, intent, and evolution becomes increasingly important for the responsible and informed development of ML models. However, knowledge about datasets, including use and implementations, is often distributed across teams, individuals, and even time. Earlier this year at the ACM Conference on Fairness, Accountability, and Transparency (ACM FAccT), we published Data Cards, a dataset documentation framework aimed at increasing transparency across dataset lifecycles. Data Cards are transparency artifacts tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run Tasks Are Now Available in the Terraform Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/run-tasks-are-now-available-in-the-terraform-registry</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/run-tasks-are-now-available-in-the-terraform-registry"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Run tasks can now be accessed from the HashiCorp Terraform Registry, helping developers discover run tasks they can integrate with their existing Terraform workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Match Cutting at Netflix: Finding Cuts with Smooth Visual Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/31c3fc14ae59</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/match-cutting-at-netflix-finding-cuts-with-smooth-visual-transitions-31c3fc14ae59?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T16:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s needed in the art of match cutting is tools to help editors find shots that match well together, which is what we’ve started…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase process productivity with Google Drive, Slack, and SendGrid]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=68045</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/increase-process-productivity-google-drive-slack-sendgrid/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T15:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Camunda Connectors can boost your process orchestration productivity by connecting to popular productivity and communication tools.
The post Increase process productivity with Google Drive, Slack, and SendGrid appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub, Sprint 213 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66077</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-sprint-213-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T20:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing exciting to report for sprint 213. We spent most of our time fixing issues and continue to make good progress. You will also see the new usability feature added below.
Issue
Templates with Assigned to @me
The post New Boards Hub, Sprint 213 Update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mixture-of-Experts with Expert Choice Routing]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/mixture-of-experts-with-expert-choice.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/mixture-of-experts-with-expert-choice.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T19:32:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Yanqi Zhou, Research Scientist, Google Research, Brain Team  
The capacity of a neural network to absorb information is limited by the number of its parameters, and as a consequence, finding more effective ways to increase model parameters has become a trend in deep learning research. Mixture-of-experts (MoE), a type of conditional computation where parts of the network are activated on a per-example basis, has been proposed as a way of dramatically increasing model capacity without a proportional increase in computation. In sparsely-activated variants of MoE models (e.g., Switch Transformer, GLaM, V-MoE), a subset of experts is selected on a per-token or per-example basis, thus creating sparsity in the network. Such models have demonstrated better scaling in multiple domains and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.14 Makes it Easier to Use Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-14-makes-it-easier-to-use-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-14-makes-it-easier-to-use-providers"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Kit for Terraform (CDKTF) 0.14 makes it easier to add and upgrade Terraform providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第219話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:316190246967858110</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/316190246967858110"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helping VFX studios pave a path to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d308ee43c079</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/helping-vfx-studios-pave-a-path-to-the-cloud-d308ee43c079?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T17:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By: Peter Cioni (Netflix), Alex Schworer (Netflix), Mac Moore (Conductor Tech.), Rachel Kelley (AWS), Ranjit Raju (AWS)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp at AWS re:Invent: Examining the State of Your Cloud Operating Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-examining-the-state-of-your-cloud-operating-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-at-aws-re-invent-examining-the-state-of-your-cloud-operating-model"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your adoption of a cloud operating model. Visit us at AWS re:Invent in Las Vegas, Nov. 28 - Dec. 2 for breakout sessions, expert talks, and product demos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Receives SOC 2 Type 1 Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=67879</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/camunda-soc-2-type-1-certification/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda has received a clean SOC 2 Type 1 attestation report. This is a rigorous, independent assessment of our internal security controls.
The post Camunda Receives SOC 2 Type 1 Certification appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Grund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps client libraries migrated to MSAL]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=66066</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-client-libraries-migrated-to-msal/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T12:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft.VisualStudio.Services.InteractiveClient library is a public NuGet package that takes care of authenticating to Azure DevOps Services. It abstracts away the acquisition, management and refreshing of authentication tokens, so developers can focus on their goals and stay productive.
The post Azure DevOps client libraries migrated to MSAL appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Sokolovsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add dev clusters in Camunda Platform 8 SaaS and test models faster]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=67763</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/dev-clusters-camunda-platform-8-saas/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T21:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now take advantage of development clusters on our professional plan to test your models quickly outside of production.
The post Add dev clusters in Camunda Platform 8 SaaS and test models faster appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assessing Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/assessing-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/assessing-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What your security scanner isn’t telling you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Brandt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Series: Creating Media with Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5067ac110bcd</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/new-series-creating-media-with-machine-learning-5067ac110bcd?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T17:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog series will be showing you how we use the power of machine learning to create stunning media at a global scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning for Fraud Detection in Streaming Services]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b0b4ef3be3f6</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/machine-learning-for-fraud-detection-in-streaming-services-b0b4ef3be3f6?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T17:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Soheil Esmaeilzadeh, Negin Salajegheh, Amir Ziai, Jeff Boote]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Military Service Impacted Two HashiCorp Veterans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-military-service-impacted-two-hashicorp-veterans</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-military-service-impacted-two-hashicorp-veterans"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lisa Argueta and Joshua Blair from the Veterans ERG share how their time in the military shaped their workforce experience and how they find community at HashiCorp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to our Newest Camunda Champions!]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=67505</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2022/11/welcome-newest-camunda-champions/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T19:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Champions make interacting in our community a more valuable and meaningful experience for everyone. Welcome to our latest Camunda Champions!
The post Welcome to our Newest Camunda Champions! appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Buchholz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Characterizing Emergent Phenomena in Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/characterizing-emergent-phenomena-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2022/11/characterizing-emergent-phenomena-in.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:05:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jason Wei and Yi Tay, Research Scientists, Google Research, Brain Team   
The field of natural language processing (NLP) has been revolutionized by language models trained on large amounts of text data. Scaling up the size of language models often leads to improved performance and sample efficiency on a range of downstream NLP tasks. In many cases, the performance of a large language model can be predicted by extrapolating the performance trend of smaller models. For instance, the effect of scale on language model perplexity has been empirically shown to span more than seven orders of magnitude. 

On the other hand, performance for certain other tasks does not improve in a predictable fashion. For example, the GPT-3 paper showed that the ability of language models to perform mult…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>