<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-30T01:20:36.987Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-30T01:20:36.987Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The social media lottery]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43864</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/761428205/0/sethsblog~The-social-media-lottery/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone is going to end up with 10,000,000 followers. Someone is going to post the next viral TikTok. Someone is going to build a meme that spreads around the world. But it probably won’t be me and it probably won’t be you. Buying lottery tickets might be fun, but they’re a lousy investment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – AWS Public IPv4 Address Charge + Public IP Insights]]></title>
        <id>2d97e4e447dec18920fdc7b501443ffb9cc7dfed</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-public-ipv4-address-charge-public-ip-insights/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are introducing a new charge for public IPv4 addresses. Effective February 1, 2024 there will be a charge of $0.005 per IP per hour for all public IPv4 addresses, whether attached to a service or not (there is already a charge for public IPv4 addresses you allocate in your account but don’t attach to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Terraform dynamic provider credentials in your AWS landing zones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-terraform-dynamic-provider-credentials-in-your-aws-landing-zones</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/using-terraform-dynamic-provider-credentials-in-your-aws-landing-zones"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how Terraform Cloud’s dynamic credentials feature fits into an AWS Control Tower AFT workflow to secure landing zone creation at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closing vulnerabilities in Decidim, a Ruby-based citizen participation platform]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-28-closing-vulnerabilities-in-decidim-a-ruby-based-citizen-participation-platform/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-28-closing-vulnerabilities-in-decidim-a-ruby-based-citizen-participation-platform/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post describes two security vulnerabilities in Decidim, a digital platform for citizen participation. Both vulnerabilities were addressed by the Decidim team with corresponding update releases for the supported versions in May 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Profile on the Fly With the IntelliJ Profiler]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=idea&amp;p=373196</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2023/07/profile-on-the-fly-with-the-intellij-profiler/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T12:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At JetBrains, we believe that profiling should be simple and accessible to all developers, regardless of their level of expertise. That’s why the IntelliJ Profiler puts ease of use and seamless integration at the forefront of its mission. In previous releases, we introduced a range of features to support these efforts. These include a single […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Igor Kulakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s simple (it’s complicated)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46756</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/760796342/0/sethsblog~Its-simple-its-complicated/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s simple: This surgery will fix your problem and you’ll be better. It’s complicated: Changes in lifestyle, diet and attitude will, over time, help you feel better. Or… Our enemies are bad, and we’re good. Vote for me. The world is a big place that is filled with nuance, shifting alliances and constant change. It’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good businesses solve real problems]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46784</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/760796345/0/sethsblog~Good-businesses-solve-real-problems/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But not all real problems lead to good businesses. There are problems all around us. People need housing, health care and food. They want delight, belonging and status. When a company shows up in the marketplace with a product or service that people eagerly choose to buy, it’s possible to make a profit. If there […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Harness the Power of a Process Engine for Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=87005&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=87005</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/how-process-engine-helps-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T00:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation is a powerful tool for wrangling complexity. Find out how a process engine can help you use it effectively.
The post How to Harness the Power of a Process Engine for Automation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying malicious Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) connections with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/remote-desktop-protocol-connections-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/remote-desktop-protocol-connections-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security is excited to announce a new lateral movement detection package that makes use of advanced analytics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirti Sodhi,Sourin Paul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying malicious Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) connections with Elastic Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/remote-desktop-protocol-connections-elastic-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/remote-desktop-protocol-connections-elastic-security"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Lateral movement is a dangerous threat in the landscape of highly integrated technologies. If attackers gain access to an endpoint, it’s critical for security teams to identify any and all movements they make. To combat this threat, Elastic Security is excited to announce a new lateral movement detection package that makes use of advanced analytics.

In the past, we explored how we can detect malicious lateral file transfers using commonly abused admin tools, such as SAMBA, SMB/PS Remoting, FTP, SFTP, SSH, and SCP. But we wanted to explore further how to detect fileless malware that attackers use to hijack and compromise systems like the execution of malicious processes and the exploitation of remote services and sessions. 

Adversaries frequently try to compromise active Remote Desktop …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirti Sodhi,Sourin Paul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daytime Firefly]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2808/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2808/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/daytime_firefly.png" title="Mr. Jones, watch out for Ms. Lenhart! She's from genus Photuris!" alt="Mr. Jones, watch out for Ms. Lenhart! She's from genus Photuris!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon EC2 Instances (C7gd, M7gd, and R7gd) Powered by AWS Graviton3 Processor with Local NVMe-based SSD Storage]]></title>
        <id>5b8acbbebf5e884f37e71a2cc00fddb6a2c569aa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-instances-c7gd-m7gd-and-r7gd-powered-by-aws-graviton3-processor-with-local-nvme-based-ssd-storage/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T22:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched Amazon EC2 C7g instances in May 2022 and M7g and R7g instances in February 2023. Powered by the latest AWS Graviton3 processors, the new instances deliver up to 25 percent higher performance, up to two times higher floating-point performance, and up to 2 times faster cryptographic workload performance compared to AWS Graviton2 processors. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New: AWS Local Zone in Phoenix, Arizona – More Instance Types, More EBS Storage Classes, and More Services]]></title>
        <id>c20dc074579a9ee198ac6b133ec203ca1b6e64ee</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-local-zone-in-phoenix-arizona-more-instance-types-more-ebs-storage-classes-and-more-services/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T22:14:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am happy to announce that a new AWS Local Zone in Phoenix, Arizona is now open and ready for you to use, with more instance types, storage classes, and services than ever before. We launched the first AWS Local Zone in 2019 (AWS Now Available from a Local Zone in Los Angeles) with the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Packer improves usage visibility with audit logs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-improves-usage-visibility-with-audit-logs</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hcp-packer-improves-usage-visibility-with-audit-logs"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Audit logs let organizations monitor user activity across HCP Packer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running dynamic, ephemeral multi-hop workers for HCP Boundary: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-dynamic-ephemeral-multi-hop-workers-for-hcp-boundary-part-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/running-dynamic-ephemeral-multi-hop-workers-for-hcp-boundary-part-2"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running Boundary workers as dynamic workloads can be challenging. Using the Nomad and Vault integration along with a custom Vault plugin, this process can be seamlessly automated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2023.2: Polars Support, Faster Table Data Exploration, New UI Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dataspell&amp;p=374268</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dataspell/2023/07/dataspell-2023-2-polars-support-faster-table-data-exploration-new-ui-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T16:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DataSpell 2023.2 introduces Polars DataFrames library support, substantial enhancements in table data exploration, new UI improvements, and much more. We’re delighted to announce that we’ve started the integration of Polars as a first-class citizen within DataSpell. We understand how vital it is for data professionals to have access to the descriptive statistics of their data. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanislav Garkusha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling merge-ort across GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-27-scaling-merge-ort-across-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-27-scaling-merge-ort-across-github/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T16:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub switched to performing merges and rebases using merge-ort. Come behind the scenes to see why and how we made this change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Early Careers: Preparing interns for the real world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-early-careers-preparing-interns-for-the-real-world</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-early-careers-preparing-interns-for-the-real-world"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six HashiCorp interns talk about what made their summer special and what they’ll take away from the experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2023.2 Is Available!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=go&amp;p=374908</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/go/2023/07/27/goland-2023-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GoLand 2023.2 offers improved integration with Go modules, refactorings for migrating function parameters to method receivers and vice versa, and support for errors.Is and errors.As. In this version, you’ll find the new AI Assistant plugin (limited access), GitLab integration, and the Kafka plugin. There are also improvements to Docker integration and the Kubernetes plugin, as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Kozlovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Predictive Debugging: A Game-Changing Look into the Future]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=374429</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/07/27/introducing-predictive-debugging-a-game-changing-look-into-the-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the introduction of debugging tools, software developers were empowered to interactively investigate the control flow of software programs to find bugs in live environments. At JetBrains, we’ve always strived to improve the art of debugging. Besides the more standard things you expect from a debugger, we also introduced features like: Check out Joseph Guadagno’s talk […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias Koch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fleet 1.21 Is Here with Git Integration Improvements, Performance Enhancements, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=fleet&amp;p=376443</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/fleet/2023/07/fleet-1-21-is-here-with-git-integration-improvements-performance-enhancements-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T13:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our ongoing progress towards public release has reached its next phase with Fleet 1.21, which features a host of bug fixes and notable updates. Stay tuned for more exciting announcements as we unveil additional features coming your way in the latest JetBrains Fleet release. Thank you for being a part of the JetBrains Fleet community! […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Prokashev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleashing the Potential of Multi-Cloud Automation with Ansible and Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/unleashing-the-potential-of-multi-cloud-automation-with-ansible-and-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/unleashing-the-potential-of-multi-cloud-automation-with-ansible-and-terraform"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we will look at how to employ Ansible, a powerful automation tool, to tap into the immense potential of multi-cloud environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scavanau@redhat.com (Sean Cavanaugh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains Academy Plugin 2023.7 Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=education&amp;p=376540</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/education/2023/07/27/jetbrains-academy-plugin-2023-7-is-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T12:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While working on this release, we focused on fine-tuning the plugin’s integration with Hyperskill to bring you enhanced Solve in IDE and Matching and Sorting tasks functionalities. Additionally, the plugin now includes convenient task descriptions with direct links to documentation and settings. We’ve also revamped the Learn tab in IntelliJ IDEA to provide a smoother […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasiia Pogorelova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Overcoming the Top Challenges in Delivering Trustworthy Software, August 16, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=teamcity&amp;p=374055</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/teamcity/2023/07/webinar-reversing-labs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T09:14:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent survey, 87% of companies have detected software issues in their software supply chain in the last 12 months. The majority of respondents also said their organization’s software supply chain security was not as mature as it should be. CI/CD environments are appealing targets for malicious actors intent on using your software […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Buga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product and process]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46776</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/760066355/0/sethsblog~Product-and-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T08:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do we get in exchange for our work? There’s pay, of course, and the satisfaction of a job well done. There’s stress and human interaction, learning and physical exertion. We get the drama of what might happen next and the delight of actually pulling it off. And mostly we get the day to day. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestration vs Automation: Differences and Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=86942&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=86942</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/orchestration-vs-automation-differences-use-cases/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T02:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the difference between orchestration and automation and how you can apply them in your organization. See examples, use cases and more.
The post Orchestration vs Automation: Differences and Use Cases appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Shain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Cloud 2022.0.4 (aka Kilburn) Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/28/spring-cloud-2022-0-4-aka-kilburn-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/28/spring-cloud-2022-0-4-aka-kilburn-is-available"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga Maciaszek-Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Shell 2.1.12, 3.0.7 and 3.1.3 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/27/spring-shell-2-1-12-3-0-7-and-3-1-3-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/27/spring-shell-2-1-12-3-0-7-and-3-1-3-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janne Valkealahti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast:  Spring team legend Dr. David Syer on view rendering technologies, the latest-and-greatest, SpringOne 2023, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/27/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-team-legend-dr-david-syer-on-view-rendering</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/27/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-team-legend-dr-david-syer-on-view-rendering"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieve faster cardinality aggregations via dynamic pruning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/faster-cardinality-aggregations-dynamic-pruning</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/faster-cardinality-aggregations-dynamic-pruning"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticsearch 8.9 introduces optimizations to cardinality aggregations by filtering out documents whose value has already been collected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrien Grand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying ChatGPT: Different methods for building AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/demystifying-chatgpt-methods-building-ai-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/demystifying-chatgpt-methods-building-ai-search"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we look at how ChatGPT works, and consider three approaches to build generative AI like search experiences for specific domains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sherry Ger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activating the new Intelligence Community data strategy with Elastic as a unified foundation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/intelligence-community-data-strategy-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/intelligence-community-data-strategy-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Office of the Director of National Intelligence (ODNI) released its 2023–2025 data strategy for the US Intelligence Community (IC). In this post, learn why the strategy is important and how Elastic can help the IC build a unified data strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Melero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieve faster cardinality aggregations via dynamic pruning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/faster-cardinality-aggregations-dynamic-pruning</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/faster-cardinality-aggregations-dynamic-pruning"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elasticsearch 8.9 introduces a speedup to cardinality aggregations through support for dynamic pruning. This optimization needs specific conditions to be met to kick in, but when it does it often yields spectacular results. We have observed some cardinality aggregations that ran by as much as 1,000x faster with this change.

For instance, computing the number of unique Kubernetes deployments monitored by the Elastic Kubernetes integration benefits from this optimization:
POST metrics-*/_search
{
  "query": { // giving an example query, but any query would work
    "bool": {
      "filter": [
        { "range": { "@timestamp": { "gte": "now-1d/h" } } },
        { "match": { "data_stream.dataset": "kubernetes.pod" } }
      ]
    }
  },
  "size": 0,
  "track_total_hits": false,
  "aggs": {…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrien Grand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying ChatGPT: Different methods for building AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/demystifying-chatgpt-methods-building-ai-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/demystifying-chatgpt-methods-building-ai-search"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is ChatGPT?,
First things first, ChatGPT is awesome! It can help you work more efficiently —  from summarizing a 10,000-word document to providing a list of differentiations between competing products, as well as many other tasks.
https://static-www.elastic.co/v3/assets/bltefdd0b53724fa2ce/blt6d4bfdfa9fe86b02/64c2b88548b0fd4d802a9ec6/elastic-blog-1-differences.png,elastic-blog-1-differences.png,
ChatGPT is the best known large language model (LLM) based on the transformer architecture. But there are other LLMs that you may have heard of, including BERT (Bidirectional Encoder Representation from Transformer), Bard (Language Model for Dialogue Applications), or LLaMA (LLM Meta AI). LLMs have multiple layers of neural networks that work together to analyze text and predict outputs. They’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sherry Ger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activating the new Intelligence Community data strategy with Elastic as a unified foundation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/intelligence-community-data-strategy-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/intelligence-community-data-strategy-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
The US Office of the Director of National Intelligence (ODNI) recently released its data strategy for 2023–2025. The document stresses the need for all 18 Intelligence Community (IC) elements to adopt common services, increase data interoperability and discoverability, and prepare teams and technology for artificial intelligence (AI).

This strategy follows in the (long) wake of ODNI’s 2017 data strategy. In the six years since the publication of that document, IC leaders say that data volume has become an increasing challenge, as well as the need for advanced data capabilities such as automation. According to a recent ThoughtLab/Elastic® study, public sector leaders estimate that their data volume will increase by 59% over the next three years, so this challenge is worth strategically s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Melero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCharm 2023.2: New Live Templates for Django, Black Formatter Integration, Run Anything, and AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=pycharm&amp;p=375743</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/pycharm/2023/07/2023-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T20:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get the most out of your developer experience with the latest PyCharm features. With this release, you can now type your Django code faster with the new live templates, reformat your code in one click with the integrated Black formatter, and generate commit messages with the help of AI Assistant. Read on below for the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valeria Letusheva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage post-deployment Microsoft Azure policy operations with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/manage-post-deployment-microsoft-azure-policy-operations-with-terraform</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/manage-post-deployment-microsoft-azure-policy-operations-with-terraform"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to manage post-deployment operations with HashiCorp Terraform and Microsoft Azure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReSharper 2023.2 Release Candidate Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=376148</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/07/26/resharper-2023-2-rc/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T17:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a preview of all the latest features and improvements set to be shipped with the next major release of ReSharper and the .Net tools by downloading the Release Candidate builds that have just landed. Here are the major improvements in each of the new builds: ReSharper 2023.2 Release Candidate ReSharper C++ 2023.2 Release Candidate […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rider 2023.2 Release Candidate Is Available]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=dotnet&amp;p=376119</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/07/26/rider-2023-2-rc/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T17:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s only a few days left before the next major release for Rider! Don’t feel like waiting? Get a sneak peek of Rider 2023.2 now by downloading the Release Candidate build that has just landed on our website. The Release Candidate build contains all of the notable changes that we’ve introduced over the course of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Ivanova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In search of a generalizable method for source-free domain adaptation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/in-search-of-generalizable-method-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/in-search-of-generalizable-method-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T16:33:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Eleni Triantafillou, Research Scientist, and Malik Boudiaf, Student Researcher, Google 









Deep learning has recently made tremendous progress in a wide range of problems and applications, but models often fail unpredictably when deployed in unseen domains or distributions. Source-free domain adaptation (SFDA) is an area of research that aims to design methods for adapting a pre-trained model (trained on a “source domain”) to a new “target domain”, using only unlabeled data from the latter. 
 

Designing adaptation methods for deep models is an important area of research. While the increasing scale of models and training datasets has been a key ingredient to their success, a negative consequence of this trend is that training such models is increasingly computationally expe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.2 Released With Better PlatformIO Integration, Updated Debugger, and Brand-New AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=clion&amp;p=376068</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2023/07/clion-2023-2-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T16:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLion 2023.2 is focused on enhancing the IDE experience for those who do low-level, remote, and embedded development. It reimagines the PlatformIO integration by removing the redundant CMake intermediate level. Support for vcpkg has been improved to make the Manifest and Classic modes easier to distinguish. Last but not least, the new version includes AI […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anastasia Kazakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 P5 Instances Powered by NVIDIA H100 Tensor Core GPUs for Accelerating Generative AI and HPC Applications]]></title>
        <id>107dab1623d26b9e83e93d9a8e1747ab1a9e7ff6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-p5-instances-powered-by-nvidia-h100-tensor-core-gpus-for-accelerating-generative-ai-and-hpc-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T16:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In March 2023, AWS and NVIDIA announced a multipart collaboration focused on building the most scalable, on-demand artificial intelligence (AI) infrastructure optimized for training increasingly complex large language models (LLMs) and developing generative AI applications. We preannounced Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) P5 instances powered by NVIDIA H100 Tensor Core GPUs and AWS’s latest […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow Service Graph Connector is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/servicenow-service-graph-connector-is-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/servicenow-service-graph-connector-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow Service Graph Connector is now GA for Terraform Cloud and Enterprise, enabling ServiceNow users to seamlessly sync their infrastructure state information between DevOps and IT workstreams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Entity Resolution: Match and Link Related Records from Multiple Applications and Data Stores]]></title>
        <id>effc031d9496caf92bb46532767acdca147f5651</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-entity-resolution-match-and-link-related-records-from-multiple-applications-and-data-stores/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T15:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As organizations grow, the records that contain information about customers, businesses, or products tend to be increasingly fragmented and siloed across applications, channels, and data stores. Because information can be gathered in different ways, there is also the issue of different but equivalent data, such as for street addresses (“5th Avenue” and “5th Ave”). As […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview – Enable Foundation Models to Complete Tasks With Agents for Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>1718167cc90797f7c682ebbeca919a4335421a15</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/preview-enable-foundation-models-to-complete-tasks-with-agents-for-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T15:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This April, Swami Sivasubramanian, Vice President of Data and Machine Learning at AWS, announced Amazon Bedrock and Amazon Titan models as part of new tools for building with generative AI on AWS. Amazon Bedrock, currently available in preview, is a fully managed service that makes foundation models (FMs) from Amazon and leading AI startups—such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第234話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361558227256</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361558227256"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Field Notes: The Writerside Team at Write the Docs Portland and soap! Krakow]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/?post_type=writerside&amp;p=375521</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/writerside/2023/07/field-notes-the-writerside-team-at-write-the-docs-portland-and-soap-krakow/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T14:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Write the Docs Portland Not that I can judge, as I’m not a frequent conference-goer, but Write the Docs (WTD) stands out from all others I have attended – the good, the bad, and the corporate.  A friendly and open community was eager to accept anybody who writes docs, whatever their official job title. They’ve […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sasha Maximova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[But what if we’re wrong?]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43927</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/759179555/0/sethsblog~But-what-if-were-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T08:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of course, we think we’re right. That’s why we’re sharing our opinion. But when there’s a disagreement, or we’re predicting the future, it’s likely that someone will turn out to be incorrect. Sometimes, being wrong is a minor embarrassment, with very little real cost. And sometimes, it leads to significant cost, a one-way choice we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get AI regulation right for open source]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-26-how-to-get-ai-regulation-right-for-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-26-how-to-get-ai-regulation-right-for-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T07:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing our coalition paper to inform the final negotiation of the EU AI Act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Announcements of the AWS Summit in New York, 2023]]></title>
        <id>48796f432c19b92a8ef64ea7f80d06e803bb871e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/top-announcements-of-the-aws-summit-in-new-york-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:36:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s probably no surprise that generative artificial intelligence and machine learning were the stars of the show, but there were several other bright lights from the day-long cloud conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AWS News Blog Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fingerprint enables rapid regulatory compliance with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/fingerprint-enables-rapid-regulatory-compliance-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/fingerprint-enables-rapid-regulatory-compliance-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fingerprint is a regulatory tech company which enables customers to achieve compliance, faster and with greater insight. Elasticsearch is a critical component of this formula, providing the capabilities upon which Fingerprint adds its secret sauce.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,James Hogbin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoid Shadow AI — Embrace generative AI in the SOC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/avoid-shadow-ai-generative-ai-soc</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/avoid-shadow-ai-generative-ai-soc"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When companies hesitate to implement generative AI, their employees do it for them. Learn about the threat of Shadow AI and how to incorporate generative AI in a security-conscious way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieval vs. poison — Fighting AI supply chain attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/retrieval-vs-poison-fighting-ai-supply-chain-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/retrieval-vs-poison-fighting-ai-supply-chain-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, learn about the supply chain vulnerabilities of artificial intelligence large language models and how the AI retrieval techniques of search engines can be used to fight misinformation and intentional tampering of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Erickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic partners with Chainguard on Software Supply Chain security and SLSA assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-partners-chainguard-software-supply-chain-security-slsa-assessment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-partners-chainguard-software-supply-chain-security-slsa-assessment"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After supply chain breaches against SolarWinds, organizations are focused on protecting their software. Elastic's SLSA assessment was the largest carried out by Chainguard. Elastic implements strategic solutions to protect the software supply chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul McCann,Lewis Denham-Parry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fingerprint enables rapid regulatory compliance with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/fingerprint-enables-rapid-regulatory-compliance-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/fingerprint-enables-rapid-regulatory-compliance-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Fingerprint is a UK-based regulatory tech company that develops and hosts software solutions to allow regulated businesses to monitor and supervise their staff's electronic communications, to ensure compliance with regulations in their region and domain. The Fingerprint platform provides everything firms need to supervise all electronic communication channels for compliance, simply and effectively. 

Fingerprint’s clients range from regulatory hosts and principal firms, outsourced chief compliance officers, and compliance consultancies to boutique hedge funds, investment and asset managers, and retail financial companies. For Fingerprint’s clients that oversee risk on behalf of their own roster of customers, the multi-tenant architecture of the platform allows them to supervise and manag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Mavleos,James Hogbin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoid Shadow AI — Embrace generative AI in the SOC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/avoid-shadow-ai-generative-ai-soc</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/avoid-shadow-ai-generative-ai-soc"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
You can’t open your Linkedin feed without being inundated with generative AI articles. They cover the spectrum of generative AI being a horrible evolution that will eliminate jobs, empower cyber criminals, and extract private data to it being the greatest innovation in information technology since the world wide web. As with everything, the truth lies somewhere in the middle of the hyperbole, or as we like to say at Elastic®, “IT, depends.”
,In our discussions with cybersecurity leaders, we consistently hear the question: Should we allow the use of generative AI within our organizations, even within cybersecurity? 

However, remember a very similar technology impact with the consumerization of technology. Employees began using applications and technology not previously approved by the or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieval vs. poison — Fighting AI supply chain attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/retrieval-vs-poison-fighting-ai-supply-chain-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/retrieval-vs-poison-fighting-ai-supply-chain-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
While perhaps new to AI researchers, supply chain attacks are nothing new to the world of cybersecurity. For those in the know, it has been best practice to verify the source and authenticity of downloads, package repositories, and containers. But human nature usually wins. As developers, our desire to move quickly to improve ease of use for users and customers can cause us to delay efforts to validate the software supply chain until we are forced to by our peers in compliance or security organizations. 

Just like software, the trained neural network that is an AI and can be redistributed. This AI supply chain has some of the same vulnerabilities as software binaries. In this article, I'll explain and demonstrate how the same popular Elasticsearch® retrieval techniques used to combat AI…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Erickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic partners with Chainguard on Software Supply Chain security and SLSA assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-partners-chainguard-software-supply-chain-security-slsa-assessment</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-partners-chainguard-software-supply-chain-security-slsa-assessment"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
In the aftermath of supply chain breaches against SolarWinds and Codecov, organizations are focused on protecting their software from malicious tampering and compromise. Addressing the complexity of software development and potential security exposures has been top of mind. The complexity goes beyond traditional application security as the software supply chain encompasses and spans across different services, organizations, roles, and responsibilities. 

Elastic®, the leading platform for search-powered solutions, is leveraging the Supply chain Levels for Software Artifacts (SLSA, pronounced “salsa”) to resolve this challenge. SLSA is a security framework that consists of standards and controls to prevent tampering, improve integrity, and secure software packages and infrastructure. We e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul McCann,Lewis Denham-Parry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bad Map Projection: ABS(Longitude)]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2807/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2807/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/bad_map_projection_abs_longitude.png" title="Positive vibes/longitudes only" alt="Positive vibes/longitudes only" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes · July 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-25-game-bytes-july-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-25-game-bytes-july-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T19:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game Bytes is our monthly series taking a peek at the world of gamedev on GitHub—featuring game engine updates, game jam details, open source games, mods, maps, and more. Game on!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a GPT-3 App with Nextjs, React, and GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-25-how-to-build-a-gpt-3-app-with-nextjs-react-and-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-25-how-to-build-a-gpt-3-app-with-nextjs-react-and-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T17:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this step-by-step tutorial, you will learn how to use GitHub Copilot to build an application with OpenAI’s gpt-3.5-turbo model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 2nd Birthday Camunda Academy]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=86609&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=86609</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/happy-2nd-birthday-camunda-academy/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T16:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy birthday to Camunda Academy, which has served tens of thousands of hours of training so far. We're thrilled for what's coming next!
The post Happy 2nd Birthday Camunda Academy appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Devine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to responsibly adopt GitHub Copilot with the GitHub Copilot Trust Center]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-25-how-to-responsibly-adopt-github-copilot-with-the-github-copilot-trust-center/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-25-how-to-responsibly-adopt-github-copilot-with-the-github-copilot-trust-center/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T16:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re launching the GitHub Copilot Trust Center to provide transparency about how GitHub Copilot works and help organizations innovate responsibly with generative AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The early adopter (and the dilettante)]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46762</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/758545556/0/sethsblog~The-early-adopter-and-the-dilettante/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The early adopter bought an iPhone in 2008 and never looked back. They played a few games of pickleball and then joined a club and bought the equipment. They picked up a new magazine on the newsstand and then subscribed, and they bought the new bestseller and then read the author’s other works. The dilettante […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey 2023: The tech sector perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-the-tech-sector-perspective</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-the-tech-sector-perspective"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology firms are using multi-cloud to improve their business outcomes in many ways, from boosting reliability to dealing with skills shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - July 25th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/25/this-week-in-spring-july-25th-2023</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/25/this-week-in-spring-july-25th-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 8.9: Streamline the analyst experience with GAI and advanced analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-9-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-9-0"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See the new features available now in Elastic Security 8.9, including advanced analytics, streamlined workflows, new dashboards, AI assistants, and so much more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kseniia Ignatovych,James Spiteri,Sourin Paul,Nick Alayil,Tinsae Erkailo,Alyssa VanNice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 8.9: Meet the Elastic AI Assistant for Security and ML-powered SIEM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-9-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-9-0"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 8.9 provides faster search performance and increased SIEM capabilities along with the beta of the Elastic AI Assistant, to bolster security teams with generative AI, and the tech preview of Reciprocal Rank Fusion for hybrid search.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Security 8.9: Streamline the analyst experience with GAI and advanced analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-9-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-security-8-9-0"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Elastic 8.9 introduces the generative AI sidekick, enhanced rule tuning, new lateral detection capabilities, and more! These new features provide security practitioners with advanced detection and analytics, easy to access information, more ways to customize your security investigations, and additional deployment options. 
Avoid surprise generative AI bills with token usage tracking,
With this release, it’s now even easier to ask the AI Assistant questions. We’ve added a dashboard to track questions asked, also called token usage, per Kibana® user. This visibility allows your team to manage third-party LLM billing based on token count, ensuring there are no surprises when using the power of GAI. This helps you track the upcoming service charges and manage budgets internally. 

In additio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kseniia Ignatovych,James Spiteri,Sourin Paul,Nick Alayil,Tinsae Erkailo,Alyssa VanNice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic 8.9: Meet the Elastic AI Assistant for Security and ML-powered SIEM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-9-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-8-9-0"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[,
Today, we are pleased to announce the general availability of Elastic 8.9.
,The release and timing of any features or functionality described in this post remain at Elastic's sole discretion. Any features or functionality not currently available may not be delivered on time or at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Bergholm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Redshift+Forecast, CodeCatalyst+GitHub, Lex Analytics, Llama 2, and Much More – July 24, 2023]]></title>
        <id>3b09933a0fb3e4f055498be2ef000a9c26e7bbba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-redshiftforecast-codecatalystgithub-lex-analytics-llama-2-and-much-more-july-24-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer is in full swing here in Seattle and we are spending more time outside and less at the keyboard. Nevertheless, the launch machine is running at full speed and I have plenty to share with you today. Let’s dive in and take a look! Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that caught my […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Repository Rules are now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-24-github-repository-rules-are-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-24-github-repository-rules-are-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T16:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repository rules provide an easy, flexible way to define branch protections and ensure consistency in code across repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New multi-language docs simplify CDK for Terraform adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-multi-language-docs-simplify-cdk-for-terraform-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/new-multi-language-docs-simplify-cdk-for-terraform-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-language provider documentation is now available on the Terraform Registry with code samples to provision and define cloud infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s always a placebo switch]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46767</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/758034053/0/sethsblog~Theres-always-a-placebo-switch/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T08:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trick is knowing where it is and using it well. Wanting control doesn’t always mean needing to have control. Sometimes it is simply a desire to be acknowledged. HT to Brian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Security 5.6.12, 5.7.10, 5.8.5, 6.0.5, and 6.1.2 are available now, including fixes for CVE-2023-34034 and CVE-2023-34035]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/24/spring-security-5-6-12-5-7-10-5-8-5-6-0-5-and-6-1-2-are-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/24/spring-security-5-6-12-5-7-10-5-8-5-6-0-5-and-6-1-2-are-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Cummings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Vaxxers]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2806/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2806/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/anti_vaxxers.png" title="The vaccine stuff seems pretty simple. But if you take a closer look at the data, it's still simple, but bigger. And slightly blurry. Might need reading glasses." alt="The vaccine stuff seems pretty simple. But if you take a closer look at the data, it's still simple, but bigger. And slightly blurry. Might need reading glasses." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ICML 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/google-at-icml-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/google-at-icml-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T21:13:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Cat Armato, Program Manager, Google




Groups across Google actively pursue research in the field of machine learning (ML), ranging from theory and application. We build ML systems to solve deep scientific and engineering challenges in areas of language, music, visual processing, algorithm development, and more. We aim to build a more collaborative ecosystem with the broader ML research community through open-sourcing tools and datasets, publishing our work, and actively participating in conferences.



Google is proud to be a Diamond Sponsor of the 40th International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML 2023), a premier annual conference, which is being held this week in Honolulu, Hawaii. As a leader in ML research, Google has a strong presence at this year’s conference with ov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chasing cool]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=43946</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/757578953/0/sethsblog~Chasing-cool/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cool thing is always a little out of reach. And for most of us, once we get it, it’s not seen as cool any more. This is not an accident. One definition of cool are things that are just out of reach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closed/open]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46751</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/757239023/0/sethsblog~Closedopen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T08:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m told that the hardest part of being a teaching golf pro isn’t helping adult golfers develop a good swing. It’s getting them to stop using a bad one. Our position feels so fragile, we hold on very tightly. Competence, status and connection are fleeting yet hard-won. We can often feel like an impostor and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective Loan Automation with Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=86518&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=86518</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/effective-loan-automation-process-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T18:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can process orchestration help you achieve your loan automation goals, outperform competitors and improve experiences?
The post Effective Loan Automation with Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Process Orchestration Helps Overcome Complexity and Drives Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=86547</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/how-process-orchestration-helps-overcome-complexity-and-drives-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T15:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Camunda Platform 8, complex business processes are managed easily. Hear directly from users and learn how.
The post How Process Orchestration Helps Overcome Complexity and Drives Productivity appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PeerSpot Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beatles and Taylor Swift]]></title>
        <id>https://seths.blog/?p=46693</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/756867326/0/sethsblog~The-Beatles-and-Taylor-Swift/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we’re in the middle of a cultural swirl, it’s normal to believe that everyone else is too. That’s part of the magic of a cultural swirl–it’s our friends, our work, our world. Most of these moments are actually tiny pockets. An episode of the much-talked-about TV show Succession was seen by about 3,000,000 people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Godin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Atmospheric Circulation]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2805/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2805/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/global_atmospheric_circulation.png" title="Refs generally say that you can exercise enough altitude control to avoid the ground, but if you start strategically choosing air layers to steer yourself, that's traveling." alt="Refs generally say that you can exercise enough altitude control to avoid the ground, but if you start strategically choosing air layers to steer yourself, that's traveling." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Route 53 Resolver Now Available on AWS Outposts Rack]]></title>
        <id>748a18c38d7979c5545ce8428b41ae14445b8d9a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-route-53-resolver-now-available-on-aws-outposts-rack/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T22:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, Amazon Route 53 Resolver is now available on AWS Outposts rack, providing your on-premises services and applications with local DNS resolution directly from Outposts. Local Route 53 Resolver endpoints also enable DNS resolution between Outposts and your on-premises DNS server. Route 53 Resolver on Outposts helps to improve your on-premises applications availability and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improvements to code coverage experience under test automation]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67329</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/improvements-to-code-coverage-experience-under-test-automation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T17:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re using Azure DevOps for your CI/CD pipeline, you may be interested in our recent improvements to code coverage testing. Code coverage tests can help you identify areas of your code that are not tested, or not tested enough, and improve the quality of your automated tests and overall code quality.
The post Improvements to code coverage experience under test automation appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravi Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using societal context knowledge to foster the responsible application of AI]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/using-societal-context-knowledge-to.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/using-societal-context-knowledge-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:22:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Donald Martin, Jr., Technical Program Manager, Head of Societal Context Understanding Tools and Solutions (SCOUTS), Google Research




AI-related products and technologies are constructed and deployed in a societal context: that is, a dynamic and complex collection of social, cultural, historical, political and economic circumstances. Because societal contexts by nature are dynamic, complex, non-linear, contested, subjective, and highly qualitative, they are challenging to translate into the quantitative representations, methods, and practices that dominate standard machine learning (ML) approaches and responsible AI product development practices.   
 

The first phase of AI product development is problem understanding, and this phase has tremendous influence over how problems (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Chat beta now available for every organization]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-20-github-copilot-chat-beta-now-available-for-every-organization/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-20-github-copilot-chat-beta-now-available-for-every-organization/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T15:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All GitHub Copilot for Business users now have access to a limited GitHub Copilot Chat beta, bringing the power of conversational coding right to the IDE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.2.0-M1 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/20/spring-boot-3-2-0-m1-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/20/spring-boot-3-2-0-m1-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Wilkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.1.2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/20/spring-boot-3-1-2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/20/spring-boot-3-1-2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Wilkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3.0.9 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/20/spring-boot-3-0-9-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/20/spring-boot-3-0-9-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Wilkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 2.7.14 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/20/spring-boot-2-7-14-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/20/spring-boot-2-7-14-available-now"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Wilkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Java legend Simon Martinelli on Vaadin, JavaOOQ, and so more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/20/a-bootiful-podcast-java-legend-simon-martinelli-on-vaadin-javaooq-and-so</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2023/07/20/a-bootiful-podcast-java-legend-simon-martinelli-on-vaadin-javaooq-and-so"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your Java code and explore what Spring can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/07/20/sig-cli-spotlight-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/07/20/sig-cli-spotlight-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Arpit Agrawal
In the world of Kubernetes, managing containerized applications at
scale requires powerful and efficient tools. The command-line
interface (CLI) is an integral part of any developer or operator’s
toolkit, offering a convenient and flexible way to interact with a
Kubernetes cluster.
SIG CLI plays a crucial role in improving the Kubernetes
CLI
experience by focusing on the development and enhancement of
kubectl, the primary command-line tool for Kubernetes.
In this SIG CLI Spotlight, Arpit Agrawal, SIG ContribEx-Comms team
member, talked with Katrina Verey, Tech
Lead & Chair of SIG CLI,and Maciej
Szulik, SIG CLI Batch Lead, about SIG
CLI, current projects, challenges and how anyone can get involved.
So, whether you are a seasoned Kubernetes enthusiast or just getting
st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring developer happiness, inclusion, and productivity at GitHub’s Design Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-19-exploring-developer-happiness-inclusion-and-productivity-at-githubs-design-conference/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-19-exploring-developer-happiness-inclusion-and-productivity-at-githubs-design-conference/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T17:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a design organization, we have the opportunity to make a significant impact on designing the platform for all developers. How does the emergence of creative AI impact our work? How can we achieve an inclusive experience for a spectrum of all abilities? What does designing for developer happiness look like?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics for issues, pull requests, and discussions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2023-07-19-metrics-for-issues-pull-requests-and-discussions/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2023-07-19-metrics-for-issues-pull-requests-and-discussions/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the new Issue Metrics GitHub Action, you can now track and monitor important metrics related to issues, pull requests, and discussions, such as time to first response, time to close, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomad 1.6 adds node pools, UX updates, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-6-adds-node-pools-ux-updates-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/nomad-1-6-adds-node-pools-ux-updates-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Nomad 1.6 introduces node pools to help manage multi-tenant Nomad clusters, along with a redesigned job UI, Nomad Pack improvements, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise adds new security and self-service features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-new-security-and-self-service-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-adds-new-security-and-self-service-features"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Terraform Enterprise features for secure self-service infrastructure include Vault-backed dynamic credentials, no-code provisioning, and continuous validation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagine Software Development With CodeWhisperer as Your AI Coding Companion]]></title>
        <id>33dc4e4a55fdadf3f26dfe3c68c67b83f9828915</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/reimagine-software-development-with-codewhisperer-as-your-ai-coding-companion/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 19, 2023: Post updated with an animated image to show Amazon CodeWhisperer in action. In the few months since Amazon CodeWhisperer became generally available, many customers have used it to simplify and streamline the way they develop software. CodeWhisperer uses generative AI powered by a foundational model to understand the semantics and context of your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing the Right Integration Pattern for Your Business Processes]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=86316</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/choosing-the-right-integration-pattern-for-your-business-processes/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curious about which integration pattern is right for your business processes? Check out this post where we compare and contrast three different patterns.
The post Choosing the Right Integration Pattern for Your Business Processes appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking efficiency: Harnessing the capabilities of ansible-builder 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/unlocking-efficiency-harnessing-the-capabilities-of-ansible-builder-3.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/unlocking-efficiency-harnessing-the-capabilities-of-ansible-builder-3.0"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently announced the general availability of Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.4, This blog outlines the features of execution environment builder (ansible-builder) 3.0 that was included with this latest release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SimPer: Simple self-supervised learning of periodic targets]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/simper-simple-self-supervised-learning.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/simper-simple-self-supervised-learning.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Daniel McDuff, Staff Research Scientist, and Yuzhe Yang, Student Researcher, Google





Learning from periodic data (signals that repeat, such as a heart beat or the daily temperature changes on Earth’s surface) is crucial for many real-world applications, from monitoring weather systems to detecting vital signs. For example, in the environmental remote sensing domain, periodic learning is often needed to enable nowcasting of environmental changes, such as precipitation patterns or land surface temperature. In the health domain, learning from video measurement has shown to extract (quasi-)periodic vital signs such as atrial fibrillation and sleep apnea episodes.



Approaches like RepNet highlight the importance of these types of tasks, and present a solution that recognizes rep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Camunda 8 Connector for Carbon-Aware Process Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=86220&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=86220</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/carbon-aware-process-execution-connector/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T19:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce the environmental impact of your business processes using Camunda and carbon-aware process execution. 
The post The Camunda 8 Connector for Carbon-Aware Process Execution appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipp Hehnle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Path to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67337</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-path-to-ga/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T18:37:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March of 2022 is when we announced the official preview of New Boards Hub. Since then, we have been actively taking feedback, fixing bugs, and adding new features. It’s been a long journey. In this post we will outline the last few steps on making New Boards Hub the default experience for all users.
The post New Boards Hub Path to GA appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Cloud Automation with amazon.cloud 0.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.cloud-0.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-cloud-automation-with-amazon.cloud-0.4.0"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Amazon Web Services (AWS) Cloud Control Collection has been updated with a powerful new suite of modules. This blog explains what is new in amazon.cloud 0.4.0 that will help both the developers and the users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gomathi Selvi Srinivasan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Updates on Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP, AWS Lambda, eksctl, Karpenter, and More – July 17, 2023]]></title>
        <id>f58bb3fa3eb6fc51e1ebf1ab8635b0a0ca8fa63c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-updates-on-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap-aws-lambda-eksctl-karpetner-and-more-july-17-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T19:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Data Centered: Eastern Oregon, a five-part mini-documentary series looking at the real-life impact of the more than $15 billion investment AWS has made in the local community, and how the company supports jobs, generates economic growth, provides skills training and education, and unlocks opportunities for local businesses suppliers. Last week, I watched a new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Fargate Enables Faster Container Startup using Seekable OCI]]></title>
        <id>cf5baab8ced0bb927386d059f4b7c7a14973a1ad</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-fargate-enables-faster-container-startup-using-seekable-oci/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While developing with containers is becoming an increasingly popular way for deploying and scaling applications, there are still areas where improvements can be made. One of the main issues with scaling containerized applications is the long startup time, especially during scale up when newer instances need to be added. This issue can have a negative […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Data Protection (ADP) now available in HCP Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/advanced-data-protection-adp-now-available-in-hcp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/advanced-data-protection-adp-now-available-in-hcp-vault"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCP Vault Plus clusters add support for all three ADP secrets engines, including KMIP, Key Management, and Transform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unraveling Connector Templates]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=85849&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=85849</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/unraveling-connector-templates/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the Connector template schema and see what makes these templates so powerful and extensible.
The post Unraveling Connector Templates appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Loding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subscription and Host Metric Changes in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/subscription-and-host-metric-changes-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.4</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/subscription-and-host-metric-changes-in-ansible-automation-platform-2.4"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What and Why?
 
Our customers use Ansible Automation Platform across a multitude of platforms, in a plethora of ways. Providing an accurate accounting and reporting capability is sometimes difficult across the various types of use cases we encounter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Symbol tuning improves in-context learning in language models]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/symbol-tuning-improves-in-context.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/symbol-tuning-improves-in-context.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T21:01:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jerry Wei, Student Researcher, and Denny Zhou, Principal Scientist, Google Research





A key feature of human intelligence is that humans can learn to perform new tasks by reasoning using only a few examples. Scaling up language models has unlocked a range of new applications and paradigms in machine learning, including the ability to perform challenging reasoning tasks via in-context learning. Language models, however, are still sensitive to the way that prompts are given, indicating that they are not reasoning in a robust manner. For instance, language models often require heavy prompt engineering or phrasing tasks as instructions, and they exhibit unexpected behaviors such as performance on tasks being unaffected even when shown incorrect labels.


In “Symbol tuning improves…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMMN Patterns Made Easily with BPMN]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=85842&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=85842</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/cmmn-patterns-bpmn/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T19:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the fundamental features of CMMN and how BPMN can easily match CMMN in dynamism. 
The post CMMN Patterns Made Easily with BPMN appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Deehan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP Now Supports WORM Protection for Regulatory Compliance and Ransomware Protection]]></title>
        <id>43c4ca9ff2b7e7f88801eafbcd41be6544d74974</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap-now-supports-worm-protection-for-regulatory-compliance-and-ransomware-protection/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T19:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP was launched in late 2021. With FSx for ONTAP you get the popular features, performance, and APIs of ONTAP file systems, with the agility, scalability, security, and resilience of AWS, all as a fully managed service. Today we are adding support for SnapLock, an ONTAP feature that gives you the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps 2023 Q3 Roadmap update]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67268</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-2023-q3-roadmap-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, we published updates to our product roadmap. It outlines our plans for the next two quarters, and future investments. The features listed below are a few highlights of what we plan to deliver in Q3. Visit our product roadmap for a complete look at the list of features for Q4.
The post Azure DevOps 2023 Q3 Roadmap update appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey 2023: The financial services perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-the-financial-services-perspective</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-the-financial-services-perspective"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Financial services firms are using multi-cloud to improve their business outcomes in many ways, from boosting reliability to dealing with skills shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating Settlements Beyond T+1 with Process Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=85599&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=85599</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2023/07/accelerating-settlements-beyond-t1-process-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T20:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banks must strategically optimize processes beyond T+1 to achieve a high degree of straight-through processing. Process orchestration can help.
The post Accelerating Settlements Beyond T+1 with Process Orchestration appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Ernest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boundary LDAP authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-ldap-authentication</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/boundary-ldap-authentication"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to set up Boundary’s new LDAP auth method and get a deep dive into how the feature can help you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第233話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:4856001361511369675</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/4856001361511369675"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenShift and Ansible: Bridging the Automation Gap for 5G and Beyond Networks - Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/openshift-and-ansible-bridging-the-automation-gap-for-5g-and-beyond-networks-part-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/openshift-and-ansible-bridging-the-automation-gap-for-5g-and-beyond-networks-part-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post is co-authored with Ian Miller.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leonardo Ochoa-Aday</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 224]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=67277</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-sprint-224/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T17:14:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another sprint has come to an end, accompanied by a wave of bug fixes 🌊🪲. Our team’s hard work has allowed us to eliminate over 40 New Boards Hub bugs last sprint. With sprint 225, we are ready to activate the “Try the New Boards Hub”
The post New Boards Hub Update, Sprint 224 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hellem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An open-source gymnasium for machine learning assisted computer architecture design]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/an-open-source-gymnasium-for-computer.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/an-open-source-gymnasium-for-computer.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T17:00:00.010Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Amir Yazdanbakhsh, Research Scientist, and Vijay Janapa Reddi, Visiting Researcher, Google Research




Computer Architecture research has a long history of developing simulators and tools to evaluate and shape the design of computer systems. For example, the SimpleScalar simulator was introduced in the late 1990s and allowed researchers to explore various microarchitectural ideas. Computer architecture simulators and tools, such as gem5, DRAMSys, and many more have played a significant role in advancing computer architecture research. Since then, these shared resources and infrastructure have benefited industry and academia and have enabled researchers to systematically build on each other's work, leading to significant advances in the field. 



Nonetheless, computer architectu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to become a developer advocate: Part 4, submitting to a call for papers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-4-submitting-to-a-call-for-papers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-become-a-developer-advocate-part-4-submitting-to-a-call-for-papers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four steps toward writing a great abstract to submit to a conference call for papers (CFP).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – AWS Glue Crawlers Now Supports Apache Iceberg, Amazon RDS Updates, and More – July 10, 2023]]></title>
        <id>701f6bc4cf015f1b7cea2cae9e08dc24699d81af</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-aws-glue-crawlers-now-supports-apache-iceberg-amazon-rds-updates-and-more-july-10-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US celebrated Independence Day last week on July 4 with fireworks and barbecues across the country. But fireworks weren’t the only thing that launched last week. Let’s have a look! Last Week’s Launches Here are some launches that got my attention: AWS Glue – AWS Glue Crawlers now supports Apache Iceberg tables. Apache Iceberg […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform apply as code: The multispace pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-apply-as-code-the-multispace-pattern</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-apply-as-code-the-multispace-pattern"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use the Terraform Cloud/Enterprise provider to coordinate apply and destroy commands on downstream workspaces in Terraform Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google at ACL 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/google-at-acl-2023.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/google-at-acl-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:02:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Malaya Jules, Program Manager, Google




  This week, the 61st annual meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics (ACL), a premier conference covering a broad spectrum of research areas that are concerned with computational approaches to natural language, is taking place in Vancouver, BC. As a leader in natural language processing and understanding, and a Diamond Level sponsor of ACL 2023, Google will showcase the latest research in the field with over 50 publications, and active involvement in a variety of workshops and tutorials.

If you’re registered for ACL 2023, we hope that you’ll visit the Google booth to learn more about the projects at Google that go into solving interesting problems for billions of people. You can also learn more about Google's participati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modular visual question answering via code generation]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/modular-visual-question-answering-via.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/modular-visual-question-answering-via.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:01:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sanjay Subramanian, PhD student, UC Berkeley, and Arsha Nagrani, Research Scientist, Google Research, Perception Team




Visual question answering (VQA) is a machine learning task that requires a model to answer a question about an image or a set of images. Conventional VQA approaches need a large amount of labeled training data consisting of thousands of human-annotated question-answer pairs associated with images. In recent years, advances in large-scale pre-training have led to the development of VQA methods that perform well with fewer than fifty training examples (few-shot) and without any human-annotated VQA training data (zero-shot). However, there is still a significant performance gap between these methods and state-of-the-art fully supervised VQA methods, such as MaMMU…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Solution – Clickstream Analytics on AWS for Mobile and Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>711a0f0b733911d5daecaf567086b254c8f14f24</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-solution-clickstream-analytics-on-aws-for-mobile-and-web-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T16:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can deploy on your AWS account an end-to-end solution to capture, ingest, store, analyze, and visualize your customers’ clickstreams inside your web and mobile applications (both for Android and iOS). The solution is built on top of standard AWS services. This new solution Clickstream Analytics on AWS allows you to keep your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pic2Word: Mapping pictures to words for zero-shot composed image retrieval]]></title>
        <id>http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/pic2word-mapping-pictures-to-words-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://ai.googleblog.com/2023/07/pic2word-mapping-pictures-to-words-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kuniaki Saito, Student Researcher, Google Research, Cloud AI Team, and Kihyuk Sohn, Research Scientist, Google Research





Image retrieval plays a crucial role in search engines. Typically, their users rely on either image or text as a query to retrieve a desired target image. However, text-based retrieval has its limitations, as describing the target image accurately using words can be challenging. For instance, when searching for a fashion item, users may want an item whose specific attribute, e.g., the color of a logo or the logo itself, is different from what they find in a website. Yet searching for the item in an existing search engine is not trivial since precisely describing the fashion item by text can be challenging. To address this fact, composed image retrieval (CIR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google AI Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Confidential Kubernetes: Use Confidential Virtual Machines and Enclaves to improve your cluster security]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/07/06/confidential-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2023/07/06/confidential-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Fabian Kammel (Edgeless Systems), Mikko Ylinen (Intel), Tobin Feldman-Fitzthum (IBM)
In this blog post, we will introduce the concept of Confidential Computing (CC) to improve any computing environment's security and privacy properties. Further, we will show how
the Cloud-Native ecosystem, particularly Kubernetes, can benefit from the new compute paradigm.
Confidential Computing is a concept that has been introduced previously in the cloud-native world. The
Confidential Computing Consortium (CCC) is a project community in the Linux Foundation
that already worked on
Defining and Enabling Confidential Computing.
In the Whitepaper,
they provide a great motivation for the use of Confidential Computing:
Data exists in three states: in transit, at rest, and in use. …Protecting sensitive…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service Major Updates: Global View, Import and Export from Local Disk, and Additional Post-launch Actions]]></title>
        <id>14172370fc6fd2b9a6a7a63a8138f20ba11f6302</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-application-migration-service-major-updates-global-view-import-and-export-from-local-disk-and-additional-post-launch-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T17:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Application Migration Service simplifies, expedites, and reduces the cost of migrating your applications to AWS. It allows you to lift and shift many physical, virtual, or cloud servers without compatibility issues, performance disruption, or long cutover windows. You can minimize time-intensive, error-prone manual processes by automating replication and conversion of your source servers from physical, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Consul cluster peering locally with Minikube]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploy-consul-cluster-peering-locally-with-minikube</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/deploy-consul-cluster-peering-locally-with-minikube"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use Minikube to create multiple Kubernetes clusters with Consul and test cluster peering configurations in your local development environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform on Google Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-google-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/how-to-deploy-red-hat-ansible-automation-platform-on-google-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is co-authored by Zack Kayyali and Hicham (he-sham) Mourad]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary Kayyali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey 2023: Inside the maturity model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-inside-the-maturity-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-state-of-cloud-strategy-survey-2023-inside-the-maturity-model"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp’s 2023 State of Cloud Strategy Survey debuts a new cloud-maturity model, which reveals how more-mature organizations enjoy better business outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Week in Review – Generative AI with LLM Hands-on Course, Amazon SageMaker Data Wrangler Updates, and More – July 3, 2023]]></title>
        <id>3fb74ddd0280e06d6387d7abc8383d64678fa7dc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-week-in-review-generative-ai-with-llm-hands-on-course-amazon-sagemaker-data-wrangler-updates-and-more-july-3-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T18:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In last week’s AWS Week in Review post, Danilo mentioned that it’s summer in London. Well, I’m based in Singapore, and it’s mostly summer here. But, June is a special month here as it marks the start of durian season. Starting next week, I’ll be travelling to Thailand, Malaysia, and the Philippines. But before I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.16 enhances service mesh reliability, user experience, and security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-16-enhances-service-mesh-reliability-user-experience-and-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/consul-1-16-enhances-service-mesh-reliability-user-experience-and-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consul 1.16 adds new reliability, scalability, security, service mesh UX, extensibility, and service discovery capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>