<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-09-20T00:24:36.243Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-09-20T00:24:36.243Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Credentials in Terraform Cloud & Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-credentials-in-terraform-cloud-and-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/managing-credentials-in-terraform-cloud-and-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the pros and cons of five different ways to manage credentials and other secrets in Terraform Cloud & Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Azure DevOps Audit Stream]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62352</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-azure-devops-audit-stream/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T16:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Auditing is important in any environment and solution, to get a view on who is doing what, typically from a compliance or governance perspective. In most scenarios, the solution allows you to store auditing to a logfile. The downside is that nobody is really watching over the logs,
The post Introducing Azure DevOps Audit Stream appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter De Tender</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CamundaCon 2021: Know Before You Go]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=30128</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/09/camundacon-2021-know-before-you-go/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for two days centered around helping you achieve your business goals with our software and showcasing your brilliant projects with it. 
The post CamundaCon 2021: Know Before You Go appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.09.17]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62382</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-09-17/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.09.17 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.09.17 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.0.5 and 2020.0.13 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/17/spring-data-2021-0-5-and-2020-0-13-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/17/spring-data-2021-0-5-and-2020-0-13-released"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m pleased to announce the availability of the Spring Data 2021.0.5 and 2020.0.13 service releases.

Both releases are built on top of Spring Framework 5.3.10. For your convenience, you can consume Spring Data 2021.0.5 and 2020.0.13 through the upcoming Spring Boot releases 2.5.5 and 2.4.11, respectively. 

Both service releases ship with mostly bug fixes and dependency upgrades.

To round things off, here are the links to the artifacts, changelogs, and documentation:
2021.0.5


  
Spring Data Commons 2.5.5 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JDBC 2.2.5 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data JPA 2.5.5 - Artifacts - Javadoc - Documentation - Changelog

  
Spring Data MongoDB 3.2.5 - Artifacts - Javadoc …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data 2021.1.0-M3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/17/spring-data-2021-1-0-m3-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/17/spring-data-2021-1-0-m3-released"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team, I’m delighted to announce the availability of the third Spring Data 2021.1.0 milestone. This release is the last milestone before entering the RC phase on mid October. This release ships besides numerous bugfixes and dependency upgrades a series of notable enhancements:

General


  
Support jMolecules’ @Identity as ID annotation

  
Publish delete events by repository methods deleteInBatch and deleteAllInBatch methods


MongoDB


  
Support for MongoDB 5.0 aggregation stages and operators including $setWindowFields for aggregations using time-series.

  
Configuration options for MongoDB’s versioned Server API.

  
Schema derivation for encrypted fields.


Redis


  
Options to reuse bound connections.

  
Enable ReactiveRedisTemplate for multi-tenanc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Money Laundering with Clarence Chio]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11685</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/17/detecting-money-laundering-with-clarence-chio/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=detecting-money-laundering-with-clarence-chio"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Money laundering is not a new crime.  However, the growth of digital communications has greatly expanded the opportunity for money launderers to find innovative new ways to hide their true intent.  Some estimates suggest it could be as high as 2-5% of the world’s GDP. Unit21 is a customizable no-code platform for risk and compliance
The post Detecting Money Laundering with Clarence Chio appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Dr. Mark Pollack on Physics, Spring Cloud Data Flow, Spring Data, Spring.NET, Spring XD, and so much more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/16/a-bootiful-podcast-dr-mark-pollack-on-physics-spring-cloud-data-flow-spring-data-spring-net-spring-xd-and-so-much-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/16/a-bootiful-podcast-dr-mark-pollack-on-physics-spring-cloud-data-flow-spring-data-spring-net-spring-xd-and-so-much-more"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of A Bootiful Podcast. In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman) talks to the one, the only, the amazing and inimitable Dr. Mark Pollack (@MarkPollack) about physics, Spring.NET, Spring Data, Spring XD, Spring Cloud Data Flow, and so much more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rover Replies]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2517/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2517/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/rover_replies.png" title="I'm so glad NASA let you take your phone to Mars!" alt="I'm so glad NASA let you take your phone to Mars!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon MSK Connect – Stream Data to and from Your Apache Kafka Clusters Using Managed Connectors]]></title>
        <id>463fda3f006fd0edaea98a78bc97c72836c2d0e0</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/svVVMIbpdhA/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T21:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Kafka is an open-source platform for building real-time streaming data pipelines and applications. At re:Invent 2018, we announced Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka, a fully managed service that makes it easy to build and run applications that use Apache Kafka to process streaming data. When you use Apache Kafka, you capture real-time data […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level up your skills with Bicep!]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62383</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/level-up-your-skills-with-bicep/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T15:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, it’s all about Bicep!
The post Level up your skills with Bicep! appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic named EMA Top 3 Award winner in Automatic End-to-End Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-named-ema-top-3-award-winner-automatic-end-to-end-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-named-ema-top-3-award-winner-automatic-end-to-end-observability"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that Elastic Observability has earned the Enterprise Management Associates Top 3 Award for Observability in 2021, a recognition of our commitment to empowering customers with products and features that advance digital transformation and solve real-life problems.


"Elastic Observability with rich analytics and machine learning capabilities allows development and operations teams to get contextualized information that cuts through the complexity, enabling users to quickly find the root cause.

	"Elastic leverages its industry-standard search platform that received over 56,000 GitHub stars to date to deliver a single solution for customers to observe and protect their systems."
This award is driven by EMA’s exhaustive, quantitative research into the top challenges …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elasticians Unidos Month 2021 | Our global celebration of Latinx and Hispanic heritages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticians-unidos-month-2021-our-global-celebration-of-latinx-and-hispanic-heritages</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elasticians-unidos-month-2021-our-global-celebration-of-latinx-and-hispanic-heritages"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We proudly celebrate Hispanic and Latinx-identified communities as part of Elasticians Unidos Month, a global expression of solidarity and appreciation of Hispanic Heritage Month.

Employees at Elastic have come together to extend the US Hispanic Heritage Month to communities around the world of Hispanic and Latinx identities through a series of virtual learning and sharing–from ceviche and tortilla making to folklore and history-telling, from music showcases to cocktail mixings. 

To kick off the Sept 15th to Oct 15th festivities, we spoke with five Elasticians about what this month means to them and how they bring their heritage to work. 
 
Ully Sampaio



Ully has been a Specialist for Community Programs at Elastic for three years. The native Portuguese-speaker, who lives in Maryland, m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A simplified stack monitoring experience in Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-simplified-stack-monitoring-experience-in-elastic-cloud-on-kubernetes</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/a-simplified-stack-monitoring-experience-in-elastic-cloud-on-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To monitor your Elastic Stack with Elastic Cloud on Kubernetes (ECK), you can deploy Metricbeat and Filebeat to collect metrics and logs and send them to the monitoring cluster, as mentioned in this blog. However, this requires understanding and managing the complexity of Beats configuration and Kubernetes role-based access control (RBAC).

Now, in ECK 1.7, the Elasticsearch and Kibana resources have been enhanced to let us specify a reference to a monitoring cluster. When specified, sidecar containers are automatically set up by ECK to ship logs and metrics to the referenced Elasticsearch cluster.

If you are new to ECK
If you are new to ECK, here are the steps to start from scratch.

Set up ECK
First, let's deploy our ECK in Kubernetes.

Deploy production and monitoring environment
Once …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kuniyasu Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What you can expect: AnsibleFest 2021 for Telco Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/what-you-can-expect-ansiblefest-2021-for-telco-customers</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/what-you-can-expect-ansiblefest-2021-for-telco-customers"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, we are adapting our signature automation event, AnsibleFest, into a free virtual experience. Seasoned pros and new Ansible enthusiasts alike can find answers and learn more about Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, the platform for building and operating automation at scale and creating an enterprise automation strategy. This year, we have a content topic designed specifically for attendees from telecommunications and media companies with our Telco topic within the Network track.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cindy Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook with Mark Zuckerberg]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11674</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/16/facebook-with-mark-zuckerberg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=facebook-with-mark-zuckerberg"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T10:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook’s goal is to connect the world and allow every human to foster better relationships. Today is a rare treat. Mark Zuckerberg is the CEO of Facebook. After I spent nearly 3 years writing a book about how his company works, he has finally agreed to do an interview. Special thanks to Jennifer Li at
The post Facebook with Mark Zuckerberg appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authorization with Sam Scott]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11665</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/16/authorization-with-sam-scott/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=authorization-with-sam-scott"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T09:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web applications often have some sort of login system, and once a user creates an account, they have access to features anonymous users can’t see.  In time, application designers will often add an admin level of access for special users.  This is often a slow trickle of technical debt.  Proper execution of a programmatic authorization
The post Authorization with Sam Scott appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IQ expansion: Connect with Experts and Consulting Firms based in the UK and France]]></title>
        <id>0fa5a817c4f6f2a5341a94c1356b3fe2ce38a48e</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/m02Ke_uHVv0/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T07:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IQ launched in 2019 and has been helping customers worldwide engage thousands of AWS Certified third-party experts and consulting firms for on-demand project work. Whether you need to learn about AWS, plan your project, setup new services, migrate existing applications, or optimize your spend, AWS IQ connects you with experts and consulting firms who […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Casalboni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDK for Terraform 0.6 Adds Unit Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-6-adds-unit-testing</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cdk-for-terraform-0-6-adds-unit-testing"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest release of CDK for Terraform includes TypeScript unit testing via Jest, improved handling of native Terraform functions, and Bash and zsh shell completion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AWS is Supporting Nonprofits, Governments, and Communities Impacted by Hurricane Ida]]></title>
        <id>7c764cdc91ce2648d3c73c3be6a1aed96d458b7b</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/mRobcjlJnsE/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T16:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Disaster Response Team volunteer Paul Fries runs cable to provide connectivity in a police station that has been converted into a supply distribution center and housing for National Guard troops and FEMA. During the crisis that has resulted in the aftermath of Hurricane Ida, the AWS Disaster Response Team is providing personnel and resources […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AWS News Blog Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Elastic Maps: Maps tailored to your geospatial data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-maps-geo-annotations-choropleth-maps-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/whats-new-elastic-maps-geo-annotations-choropleth-maps-integrations"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sysadmins, cartographers, and dashboard designers can now personalize Elastic Maps to create richer geodata stories.

The 7.14 release of Elastic Maps has the geo capabilities to highlight points of interest, hide unnecessary details, and help you explore new trends in your data.

Elastic Maps is available now on Elastic Cloud — the only hosted Elasticsearch offering to include all of its latest features. You can also download the Elastic Stack and our cloud orchestration products, Elastic Cloud Enterprise (ECE) and Elastic Cloud for Kubernetes (ECK), for a self-managed experience.

Simpler configuration and scaling in Elastic Maps Server
In case you missed it, the on-prem Elastic Maps Server, an offline version of the Elastic Maps Service to use with secure air-gapped settings or where in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Neirynck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tools 4.12.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/15/spring-tools-4-12-0-released</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/15/spring-tools-4-12-0-released"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Spring Community,

I am happy to announce the 4.12.0 release of the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, and Theia.
major changes to the Spring Tools 4 for Eclipse distribution


  
updated to Eclipse 2021-09 release (including support for Java 16) (new and noteworthy)

  
Java 17 support available (via separate add-on)

  
early-access builds for Apple Silicon platform (ARM M1) available


additional changes


  
(VS Code, Spring Boot) fixed: [codespaces] vscode extension crashes if specified log output location doesn’t work (#676)

  
(Eclipse, Spring Boot) improvement: Little UX improvement for Tags Editor in the Properties View (#649)

  
(Eclipse, Spring Boot) fixed: symbols don’t work anymore in Eclipse (#682)

  
(Eclipse, Spring Boot) fixed: Problem with the STS/eclipse initializr for custom project types (#660)


To download the distribution for Eclipse and find links to the marketplace entries for Visual Studio Code and Theia, please go visit:


  
Spring Tools 4: https://spring.io/tools/


Detailed changes can be found here: https://github.com/spring-projects/sts4/wiki/Changelog#2021-09-15-4120-release-incl-language-servers-version-1280

Spring Tools 4.12.1 is scheduled to be released in late October 2021.

Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gartner Reports Rise of DigitalOps]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=27482</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/09/gartner-reports-the-rise-of-digitalops/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hype Cycle for Enterprise Architecture, 2021 reports that DigitalOps will provide a transformational benefit to organizations within the next five to 10 years. 
The post Gartner Reports Rise of DigitalOps appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earthly and CLI Productivity with Adam Gordon Bell]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11629</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/15/earthly-and-cli-productivity-with-adam-gordon-bell/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=earthly-and-cli-productivity-with-adam-gordon-bell"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T09:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers hone their craft, becoming more productive often means learning utilities and tools at the command line.  The right combination of various parsing commands chained together through pipes can enable engineers to quickly and efficiently automate many adhoc data processing tasks. In this episode I speak with Adam Gordon Bell about some of his
The post Earthly and CLI Productivity with Adam Gordon Bell appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Framework 5.3.10 and 5.2.17 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/15/spring-framework-5-3-10-and-5-2-17-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/15/spring-framework-5-3-10-and-5-2-17-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T08:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the team and everyone who has contributed, I am pleased to announce that Spring Framework 5.3.10 and 5.2.17 are available now.

Spring Framework 5.3.10 includes 45 fixes and improvements. Spring Framework 5.2.17 includes 13 selected fixes and improvements.

Stay tuned for follow-up Spring Boot releases next week.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Tips: A Bootiful Look at SpringOne 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/15/spring-tips-a-bootiful-look-at-springone-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/15/spring-tips-a-bootiful-look-at-springone-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, I’m joined by teammates Tiffany Jernigan and Mario Gray as we recap some of our favorite talks from the just-finished SpringOne 2021 event! Did you miss the show? (why)? Fret not: we’ll look at some of our favorite moments from SpringOne 2021!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hubble Tension]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2516/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2516/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/hubble_tension.png" title="Oh, wait, I might've had it set to kph instead of mph. But that would make the discrepancy even wider!" alt="Oh, wait, I might've had it set to kph instead of mph. But that would make the discrepancy even wider!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Data Stacks Optimized by Mozart Data with Peter Fishman and Dan Silberman]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11621</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/14/modern-data-stacks-optimized-by-mozart-data-with-peter-fishman-and-dan-silberman/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=modern-data-stacks-optimized-by-mozart-data-with-peter-fishman-and-dan-silberman"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T20:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern companies leverage dozens or even hundreds of software solutions to solve specific needs of the business.  Organizations need to collect all these disparate data sources into a data warehouse in order to add value.  The raw data typically needs transformation before it can be analyzed.  In many cases, companies develop homegrown solutions, thus reinventing
The post Modern Data Stacks Optimized by Mozart Data with Peter Fishman and Dan Silberman appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise Introduces New Visibility and Security Enhancements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-introduces-new-visibility-and-security-enhancements</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-enterprise-introduces-new-visibility-and-security-enhancements"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Enterprise increases visibility with a new workspace overview page, structured run output, and log forwarding, and adds support for consistent workload management with Terraform Agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[September patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62345</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/september-patches-for-azure-devops-server-and-team-foundation-server-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T18:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the September patches, we are releasing fixes that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server, as well as Team Foundation Server 2017.
Resolve the issue reported in this Developer Community feedback ticket.
The post September patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gloridel Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andreessen Horowitz with Astasia Myers]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11618</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/14/andreessen-horowitz-with-astasia-myers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=andreessen-horowitz-with-astasia-myers"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T18:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please The Easy Thing about Easy Things
The post Andreessen Horowitz with Astasia Myers appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more searching for a needle in a haystack: A world where Elastic & StackState team up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/no-more-searching-for-a-needle-in-a-haystack-a-world-where-elastic-and-stackstate-team-up</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/no-more-searching-for-a-needle-in-a-haystack-a-world-where-elastic-and-stackstate-team-up"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Evans from StackState wrote this blog post. Anthony is a Solutions Engineer with StackState and a lifelong technologist. He has spent the last 15 years helping companies advance their software delivery capabilities while maintaining reliability, working extensively to support customers in the SaaS, AI, and Service Management landscapes.

Meeting the goal of delivering great performance and reliability in the face of our ever-changing, increasingly autonomous IT environments is fundamentally challenged by a data problem. Sure, there’s lots of it - logs, metrics, and APM traces - but it is exceedingly hard to extract actionable information when there are so many fast moving parts.

If you’re already using Elastic Observability, you know the major advantage of bringing your monitoring…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ricardo Ferreira,Daliya Spasova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Optimize 3.6.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=29879</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/09/camunda-optimize-360-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T13:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Optimize 3.6.0-alpha2. Learn about the new capabilities introduced in Optimize 3.6.0-alpha2.
The post Camunda Optimize 3.6.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 55 – Programming for Accessibility with @rorypreddy]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62331</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-55-programming-for-accessibility-with-rorypreddy/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T10:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 55 – Programming for Accessibility with @rorypreddy appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 14th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/14/this-week-in-spring-september-14th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/14/this-week-in-spring-september-14th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! It’s September 14th! I can’t believe it. I know this is a common refrain on my weekly posts, but can you believe it’s already nearly Fall and Winter? What is happening?? How’d we get here so quickly? 

Anyway, how are you doin’? I’m doing alright! It’s been kinda a crazy week. I was in the studio all day and some of the night yesterday filming a new Livelessons video that I can’t wait for y’all to see. (But be forewarned: there will be .YAML!) 

Then, at 3am my time, I did a presentation for the Japanese Java User Group. This would be one thing in of itself, but what made this special for me was that I was supposed to appear at the JJUG six weeks ago. Yes, that six weeks ago. The same six weeks ago when I was convalescing with COVID-19, six weeks ago. Needless to say (bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Parsing of Reactive Buffer Streams]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/14/efficient-parsing-of-reactive-buffer-streams</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/14/efficient-parsing-of-reactive-buffer-streams"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T09:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a while since Spring Framework 5.3 was released.
One of the features in that release was a major overhaul of our Reactive Multipart support.
In this blog post, we share some of the knowledge learned while working on this feature.
Specifically, we focus on finding a token within a stream of byte buffers.



Multipart Form Data



Whenever you upload a file, your browser sends it — and other fields in the form — to the server as a multipart/form-data message.
The exact format of these messages is described in RFC 7578.
If you submit a simple form with a single text field called foo and a file selector called file, the multipart/form-data message looks something like this:




POST / HTTP/1.1
Host: example.com
Content-Type: multipart/form-data;boundary="boundary" …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Cloud 1.2.0-alpha2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=29579</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/09/camunda-cloud-120-alpha2-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T06:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the release of Camunda Cloud 1.2.0-alpha2. Camunda Cloud 1.2.0-alpha2 is the second alpha release for our next stable minor release in October. 
The post Camunda Cloud 1.2.0-alpha2 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brittany des Vignes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camunda Modeler 4.10 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=28681&amp;preview=true&amp;preview_id=28681</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/09/camunda-modeler-4-10-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're happy to announce the Camunda Modeler 4.10 release. This release adds new components for forms, a validation of forms to ensure they can be successfully executed on your target execution platform, an entirely overhauled properties panel for Camunda Cloud BPMN diagrams, and various smaller improvements and bug fixes.
The post Camunda Modeler 4.10 Released appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maximilian Trumpf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EC2 VT1 Instances for Live Multi-stream Video Transcoding]]></title>
        <id>b5bf069188b7952066d20f6ea2fb7cf30604b318</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/PvVBKr3agGo/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T19:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global demand for video content has been rapidly increasing and now has the major audiences of Internet and mobile network traffic. Over-the-top streaming services such as Twitch continue to see an explosion of content creators who are seeking live delivery with great image quality, while live event broadcasters are increasingly looking to embrace agile cloud […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing HashiCorp Boundary 0.6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-boundary-0-6</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-hashicorp-boundary-0-6"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Boundary 0.6 and Boundary Desktop 1.3.0 add Linux support for Boundary Desktop, permissions enforcement improvements throughout the admin console, and Terraform provider support for managed group configuration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new: Automating ServiceNow with Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-automating-servicenow-with-ansible-automation-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/whats-new-automating-servicenow-with-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been almost half a year since the XLAB Steampunk and Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform teams developed the first version of the Red Hat Ansible Certified Content Collection for ServiceNow IT Service Management (ITSM). You may also want to read our ServiceNow introduction if you are not familiar with this already.  So, let’s take a look at what is new since the last release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>steampunk@xlab.si (XLAB Steampunk)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vaccine Research]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2515/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2515/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/vaccine_research.png" title="Honestly feel a little sheepish about the amount of time and effort I spent confirming &quot;yes, the vaccine helps protect people from getting sick and dying&quot; but I guess everyone needs a hobby." alt="Honestly feel a little sheepish about the amount of time and effort I spent confirming &quot;yes, the vaccine helps protect people from getting sick and dying&quot; but I guess everyone needs a hobby." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Suckerberg (Asleep With Eyes Open)]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11603</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/12/mark-suckerberg-asleep-with-eyes-open/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mark-suckerberg-asleep-with-eyes-open"/>
        <updated>2021-09-12T14:06:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook will be convicted of antitrust and Mark Zuckerberg will go to prison.
The post Mark Suckerberg (Asleep With Eyes Open) appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: ​​Introducing the BPMN-Driven Testing Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=29366</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/09/podcast-introducing-the-bpmn-driven-testing-extension/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T15:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now live! Listen as Gabor explains why the BPMN-driven testing extension was created as an answer to some developer woes.
The post Podcast: ​​Introducing the BPMN-Driven Testing Extension appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brittany des Vignes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.09.10]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62322</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-09-10/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T10:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.09.10 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.09.10 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tetrate: Application Aware Networking with Varun Talwar]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11566</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/10/tetrate-application-aware-networking-with-varun-talwar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tetrate-application-aware-networking-with-varun-talwar"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T09:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An application network is a way to connect applications, data and devices through APIs that expose some or all of their assets and data on the network. That network allows other consumers from other parts of the business to come in and discover and use those assets (mulesoft.com). The company Tetrate provides the tools necessary
The post Tetrate: Application Aware Networking with Varun Talwar appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lab Equipment]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2514/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2514/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/lab_equipment.png" title="I've been working on chocolate bar annealing techniques to try to produce the perfect laser s'more. Maybe don't mention that on the grant application though." alt="I've been working on chocolate bar annealing techniques to try to produce the perfect laser s'more. Maybe don't mention that on the grant application though." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: Spring Security Engineer Josh Cummings]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/09/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-engineer-josh-cummings</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/09/a-bootiful-podcast-spring-security-engineer-josh-cummings"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuman) talks about pumpkin spice lattes, COVID, labor day, and then gets to talk to Spring Security engineer Josh Cummings (@jzheaux)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Big or Go Small? Building in Azure CAF with Terraform Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/go-big-or-go-small-building-in-azure-caf-with-terraform-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/go-big-or-go-small-building-in-azure-caf-with-terraform-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the enterprise scale and Cloud Adoption Framework (CAF)  Terraform modules for Azure adoption, and get a demo of the CAF module.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Data JDBC - How to use custom ID generation]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/09/spring-data-jdbc-how-to-use-custom-id-generation</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/09/spring-data-jdbc-how-to-use-custom-id-generation"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first article of a series about how to tackle various challenges you might encounter when using Spring Data JDBC.



If you are new to Spring Data JDBC, you should start by reading its introduction and this article, which explains the relevance of aggregates in the context of Spring Data JDBC. Trust me, it is important.



This article is based on part of a talk I did at Spring One 2021.



Now we can get started with IDs - especially about what your options are when you want to control the ID of an entity and do not want to leave it to the database.
But let us first reiterate Spring Data JDBC’s default strategy for this.



By default, Spring Data JDBC assumes that IDs get generated by some kind of SERIAL, IDENTITY, or AUTOINCREMENT column.
It basically checks wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Cloud Run Tasks Beta Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-beta-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-cloud-run-tasks-beta-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform Cloud run tasks allow you to integrate third-party tools into the pre-apply stage of a Terraform Cloud run. The feature is now available in beta access.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation: A Recipe for Disruption]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=29008</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/09/automation-a-recipe-for-disruption/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T14:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn why Camunda CEO Jakob Freund thinks process automation can help organizations with legacy technology compete with startups.
The post Automation: A Recipe for Disruption appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[De Watergroep and Devoteam build Elastic Observability pipeline to deliver water to millions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/de-watergroep-and-devoteam-build-elastic-observability-pipeline-to-deliver-water-to-millions</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/de-watergroep-and-devoteam-build-elastic-observability-pipeline-to-deliver-water-to-millions"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De Watergroep is responsible for the supply of water to more than 3 million customers and hundreds of companies in Belgium. An organisation operating in the public sector, De Watergroep's main goal is to continuously ensure the availability of high-quality drinking water.

De Watergroep also is constantly engaged in technological innovation, focusing on keeping distribution costs low, and making maintenance more cost efficient.

A frontrunner in digitizing its business operations, De Watergroep is extremely dependent on its IT processes to ensure uninterrupted customer service. Some parts of this IT is outsourced to specialized companies. 

Watering down the challenge is not an option
Like any business that depends on third-party suppliers for mission-critical functions, De Watergroep’s di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and HashiCorp partner to bring infrastructure-as-code to Elastic Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-hashicorp-partner-to-bring-infrastructure-as-code-to-elastic-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-hashicorp-partner-to-bring-infrastructure-as-code-to-elastic-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operations and SRE teams often rely on HashiCorp Terraform to safely manage production-related infrastructure using methodologies such as infrastructure as code, which allows you to apply peer-reviewed infrastructure changes in an automated and controlled fashion.

We’re expanding our partnership with HashiCorp, a leader in multi-cloud infrastructure automation software, to offer a verified Terraform provider — bringing you the best possible infrastructure-as-code experience when you use Terraform to deploy and manage Elastic Cloud.

The HashiCorp Terraform verified provider for  Elastic Cloud works with Elasticsearch Service on Elastic Cloud, Elastic Cloud Enterprise, and Elasticsearch Service Private environments.

With the Elastic Cloud Terraform provider, you can use the same automatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Kushmaro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your deployments on Elastic Cloud with Google Cloud Private Service Connect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-your-deployments-on-elastic-cloud-with-google-cloud-private-service-connect</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/secure-your-deployments-on-elastic-cloud-with-google-cloud-private-service-connect"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the general availability of the Google Cloud Private Service Connect integration with Elastic Cloud. Elastic Cloud VPC connectivity is now available to all customers across all subscription tiers and cloud providers (AWS, Microsoft Azure, and Google Cloud).
Private Service Connect allows you to create private and secure connections from your clients running in your Google Cloud environments to your Elastic Cloud deployment endpoints running on Google Cloud. Private Service Connect provides service endpoints in your virtual private cloud (VPC) that provide private connectivity and policy enforcement, allowing you to easily connect to services like Elastic Cloud. All the traffic remains within the Google network, and it’s easy to set up and scale. 
 
Prerequisite: …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fermi Fang,Shubha Anjur Tupil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Mistakes and Tradeoffs with Tomasz Lelek]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11561</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/09/software-mistakes-and-tradeoffs-with-tomasz-lelek/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=software-mistakes-and-tradeoffs-with-tomasz-lelek"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T09:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A software engineer will make many mistakes on their career journey.  In time, engineers learn to make smaller mistakes, recognize them faster, and build with appropriate guardrails.  The demands of delivering software in a timely and efficient fashion often demands developers carefully optimize tradeoffs to deliver solutions to the problems at hand. Software Mistakes and
The post Software Mistakes and Tradeoffs with Tomasz Lelek appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elasticsearch Service Is Now Amazon OpenSearch Service and Supports OpenSearch 1.0]]></title>
        <id>46d5dfdf2f6a6027732ce521a1c8a044fc3a93ef</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/zxVJcxrmQkQ/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T21:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2015, we launched Amazon Elasticsearch Service (Amazon ES), a fully managed service that makes it easy for you to perform interactive log analytics, real-time application monitoring, website search, and more. Amazon ES has been a popular service for log analytics because of its ability to ingest high volumes of log data. Additionally, with UltraWarm […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EKS Anywhere – Now Generally Available to Create and Manage Kubernetes Clusters on Premises]]></title>
        <id>e680ae7d1d3fd575e2fc991fb49ed3be879bc876</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/1iLrrIF_AjE/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T18:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2020, we preannounced new deployment options of Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) Anywhere and Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) Anywhere in your own data center. Today, I am happy to announce the general availability of Amazon EKS Anywhere, a deployment option for Amazon EKS that enables you to easily create […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tracing AWS Lambdas with OpenTelemetry and Elastic Observability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/tracing-aws-lambdas-with-opentelemetry-and-elastic-observability</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/tracing-aws-lambdas-with-opentelemetry-and-elastic-observability"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why OpenTelemetry?
Open Telemetry represents an effort to combine distributed tracing, metrics and logging into a single set of system components and language-specific libraries. Recently, OpenTelemetry became a CNCF incubating project, but it already enjoys quite a significant community and vendor support. OpenTelemetry defines itself as “an observability framework for cloud-native software”, although it should be able to cover more than what we know as “cloud-native software”. Quoting its mission statement, “OpenTelemetry is a collection of tools, APIs, and SDKs” that are used “to instrument, generate, collect, and export telemetry data (metrics, logs, and traces) for analysis to understand the software's performance and behaviour”.

We at Elastic find the mission statement of OpenTeleme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hyatt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Consul Agent Security with Auto-Config]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/automate-consul-agent-security-with-auto-config</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/automate-consul-agent-security-with-auto-config"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-Config is a highly scalable method to distribute secure properties and other configuration settings to all Consul agents in a datacenter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed Open Source Databases with Jonathan Ellis and Spencer Kimball]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11547</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/08/distributed-open-source-databases-with-jonathan-ellis-and-spencer-kimball/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=distributed-open-source-databases-with-jonathan-ellis-and-spencer-kimball"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T09:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By most accounts, the first databases came on line in the 1960s. This class of software has continued to evolve alongside the technology it runs on and the applications it supports. In the early days, databases were typically closed source commercial products. Today, databases run in the cloud on distributed systems. Increasingly, the leading tools
The post Distributed Open Source Databases with Jonathan Ellis and Spencer Kimball appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Terraform and Community Contributions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-community-contributions</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/terraform-community-contributions"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently added a note to the HashiCorp Terraform contribution guidelines and this blog provides additional clarity and context for our community and commercial customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Different Industries Deal with Cloud and Multi-Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-different-industries-deal-with-cloud-and-multi-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-different-industries-deal-with-cloud-and-multi-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey, software companies and telcos lead in getting value from cloud and multi-cloud, while the public sector lags.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Elastic Cloud on AWS, Smarter City Solutions ensures seamless customer experience across the Smarter Parking Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/with-elastic-cloud-on-aws-smarter-city-solutions-ensures-seamless-customer-experience-across-the-smarter-parking-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/with-elastic-cloud-on-aws-smarter-city-solutions-ensures-seamless-customer-experience-across-the-smarter-parking-platform"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring a seamless customer experience is a growing challenge for digital technology providers. Yet, as functionality and a customer base scale, predictability can become challenging. 

At Smarter City Solutions, which provides tens of thousands of drivers in Australia and New Zealand real-time parking related services through the flagship Smarter Parking Platform, our engineering team faced this challenge when scaling from a few deployments to dozens. Whether it was a scaling issue in infrastructure, a configuration gap in the server, or an update needed in an application, we realized that proactive, unified visibility of the entire stack to detect potential issues was critical if we wanted to ensure a consistent customer experience as we continue to grow. 

To address this challenge, we…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zack Shachar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instabase with Anant Bhardwaj]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11530</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/07/instabase-with-anant-bhardwaj/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=instabase-with-anant-bhardwaj"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T16:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instabase is a technology platform for building automation solutions. Users deploy it onto their own infrastructure and can leverage the tools offered by the platform to build complex workflows for handling tasks like income verification and claims processing. In this episode we interview Anant Bhardwaj, founder of Instabase. He describes Instabase as an operating system. 
The post Instabase with Anant Bhardwaj appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic on Elastic Series: Data collected to the Infosec SIEM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-on-elastic-data-collected-to-the-infosec-siem</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-on-elastic-data-collected-to-the-infosec-siem"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elastic Infosec Detections and Analytics team is responsible for building, tuning, and maintaining the security detections used to protect all Elastic systems. Within Elastic we call ourselves Customer Zero and we strive to always use the newest versions of our products.  
  
In this series of blog posts we will provide an overview of our architecture, what data we send to our clusters, how and why we use Cross Cluster Search with the Security and Machine Learning (ML) applications, and how we tune, manage and notify analysts for those alerts. 
  
In the previous blog post we provided an overview of our internal Elastic infrastructure that we use in Infosec and how we use Cross Cluster Search to connect multiple clusters into a single interface for Security Analysts. In this blog post …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Jewitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 54 – @GitHub Integration with @Azure and Shifting Left]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62285</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-54-github-integration-with-azure-and-shifting-left/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T12:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 54 – @GitHub Integration with @Azure and Shifting Left appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - September 7th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/07/this-week-in-spring-september-7th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/07/this-week-in-spring-september-7th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! I am still reeling from the craziness of last week’s SpringOne event! That doesn’t mean that the world’s stood still in the interim though! Quite the contrary! There’s a ton of things to get to this week so without further ado let’s go! 


  
In last week’s, A Bootiful Podcast, I briefly recap some of the excitement from SpringOne 2021 and then talked Jackson and Woodstox creator Tatu Saloranta

  
I loved Spring Framework lead Juergen Hoeller’s post A Java 17 and Jakarta EE 9 baseline for Spring Framework 6

  
Announcing Spring Data YugabyteDB - The Distributed SQL Blog

  
Announcing VMware Tanzu Application Platform: A Better Developer Experience on any Kubernetes

  
Check out the SpringOne 2021 keynotes

  
Speaking of SpringOne, I loved this silly moment in one of the talks from Jetbrains’ Hadi Hariri: Spring is not Spring without @starbuxman - LOL!

  
Jonas Hecht’s article, Goodbye Dockerfile, looking at Cloud Native Buildpacks and Spring Boot, is featured in the summer edition of iXmagazin, a German language developer journal

  
Kuassi Mensah has announced the latest official release of the R2DBC driver for Oracle database

  
Maciej Walkowiak lists some good choices for people who want options for feature toggles

  
Monitor Spring Boot applications end-to-end using Dynatrace in Azure Spring Cloud!

  
Piotr Mińkowski points the community to this interesting Spring Boot integration for Testcontainers that provides auto-configurations for Spring Boot-based integration tests

  
Spring Boot, Spring Security, JWT, React, and Ant Design - Polling App | GitHub

  
Spring GraphQL 1.0.0-M2 available now

  
SpringOne 2021: Day 2 Recap and Breakout Session Highlights

  
The State of Spring 2021

  
VMware Tanzu Adds Enterprise Support for Spring Boot Native Applications Compiled with BellSoft Liberica NIK

  
VMware’s new Tanzu platform aims to unify Kubernetes development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Meet the Camundos – Rin Oliver]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=28533</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/09/podcast-meet-the-camundos-rin-oliver/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T18:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, follow Rin Oliver as he explains what he does at Camunda to enable developers to do what they do better and faster.
The post Podcast: Meet the Camundos – Rin Oliver appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brittany des Vignes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoding the Social Effects Of Media with Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>2c845d4a4cf1093ef98aefca06818fc77382f5a6</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/O6F85xFsK2Y/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T16:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if media were optimized to benefit people? This thought-provoking question is at the core of Harmony Labs‘ mission. A nonprofit organization headquartered in New York City, Harmony Labs strives to better understand the impact of media on society, and build communities and tools to reform and transform media systems. As Brian Wanieswki, Executive Director […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub, F5, and Okta Among New HCP Vault Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/github-f5-okta-among-new-hcp-vault-integrations</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/github-f5-okta-among-new-hcp-vault-integrations"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several new partners have had their integrations validated for cloud-managed HCP Vault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tech Radar with Lior Kanfi]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11529</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/03/the-tech-radar-with-lior-kanfi/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-tech-radar-with-lior-kanfi"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T09:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israeli Tech Radar is an opinionated map of the latest technologies and trends in the Israeli tech industry. Now in its fifth edition, the Tech Radar was built in collaboration with Monday, Wix, Riskified, Netapp, Tabula, and other tech companies. Lior Kanfi is the CEO of Tikal. In this episode, we interview Lior about
The post The Tech Radar with Lior Kanfi appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.09.03]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62303</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/this-week-i-searched-far-and-wide-to-find-some-really-informative-posts-from-our-community-weve-got-posts-on-code-quality-python-azure-devops-pipelines-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T08:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.09.03 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.09.03 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bootiful Podcast: SpringOne 2021 and Jackson and Woodstox creator Tatu Saloranta]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/02/a-bootiful-podcast-springone-2021-and-jackson-and-woodstox-creator-tatu-saloranta</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/02/a-bootiful-podcast-springone-2021-and-jackson-and-woodstox-creator-tatu-saloranta"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! In this installment, Josh Long (@starbuxman ) breathlessly recaps some of the exciting news from the just-finished SpringOne 2021 event and then talks to Jackson and Woodstox creator Tatu Saloranta (@cowtowncoder)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Vault Use Cases and Best Practices on Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-use-cases-and-best-practices-on-azure</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/hashicorp-vault-use-cases-and-best-practices-on-azure"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Vault can help you build zero trust security on Microsoft Azure with five common use cases and five best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Java 17 and Jakarta EE 9 baseline for Spring Framework 6]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/02/a-java-17-and-jakarta-ee-9-baseline-for-spring-framework-6</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/02/a-java-17-and-jakarta-ee-9-baseline-for-spring-framework-6"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As announced at SpringOne yesterday, Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3 are planned towards a high-end baseline for their general availability in Q4 2022:


  
Java 17+ (from Java 8-17 in the Spring Framework 5.3.x line)

  
Jakarta EE 9+ (from Java EE 7-8 in the Spring Framework 5.3.x line)


This forward-looking baseline will provide significant benefits in our API design and integration efforts, shining through to your application code and future-proofing the framework as well as your applications for many years to come. However, it comes at a cost, of course: Spring Framework 6 and Spring Boot 3 based applications will require a minimum of JDK 17 at runtime, as well as a minimum of Tomcat 10 / Jetty 11 (for Jakarta EE 9 compatibility). Even more importantly, there might be some …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Organizations Are Thinking About Multi-Cloud Networking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-organizations-are-thinking-about-multi-cloud-networking</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-organizations-are-thinking-about-multi-cloud-networking"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From maturity to security, take a closer look at the networking and service mesh trends uncovered in the new HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to AWS Storage Day 2021]]></title>
        <id>9bf2734a9a0cc7f9b62f12302a109d0a15a0eacb</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/onb8yrlQHio/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T15:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the third annual AWS Storage Day 2021! During Storage Day 2020 and the first-ever Storage Day 2019 we made many impactful announcements for our customers and this year will be no different. The one-day, free AWS Storage Day 2021 virtual event will be hosted on the AWS channel on Twitch. You’ll hear from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon EFS Intelligent-Tiering Optimizes Costs for Workloads with Changing Access Patterns]]></title>
        <id>31eeed91f20d84c8371d02185b6434cfd36818f1</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/Zg4VvQhCox4/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T15:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) offers four storage classes: two Standard storage classes, Amazon EFS Standard and Amazon EFS Standard-Infrequent Access (EFS Standard-IA), and two One Zone storage classes, Amazon EFS One Zone, and Amazon EFS One Zone-Infrequent Access (EFS One Zone-IA). Standard storage classes store data within and across multiple availability zones (AZ). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Accelerate Performance and Availability of Multi-region Applications with Amazon S3 Multi-Region Access Points]]></title>
        <id>d0cb27424372f775619510a8c1582fa4f2daf084</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/d965iVRL6SA/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T15:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building multi-region applications allows you to improve latency for end users, achieve higher availability and resiliency in case of unexpected disasters, and adhere to business requirements related to data durability and data residency. For example, you might want to reduce the overall latency of dynamic API calls to your backend services . Or you might […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Casalboni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering – Improved Cost Optimizations for Short-Lived and Small Objects]]></title>
        <id>da2cf10e52b4ea77d701c365a9ec8802a7030f84</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/g5N1bOkflQo/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T15:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2018, we first launched Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering (S3 Intelligent-Tiering). For customers managing data across business units, teams, and products, unpredictable access patterns are often the norm. With the S3 Intelligent-Tiering storage class, S3 automatically optimizes costs by moving data between access tiers as access patterns change. Today, we’re pleased to announce two updates to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean M. Tracey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New – Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP]]></title>
        <id>a1241623aa1b9528784bc5782f30c04e5f265286</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/IHxuL8Rgrqo/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T15:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2018 I wrote about the first two members of the Amazon FSx family of fully-managed, highly-reliable, and highly-performant file systems, Amazon FSx for Lustre and Amazon FSx for Windows File Server. Both of these services give you the ability to use popular open source and commercially-licensed file systems without having to deal with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving the Army's data imperatives at the tactical edge with Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/achieving-the-armys-data-imperatives-at-the-tactical-edge-with-elastic</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/achieving-the-armys-data-imperatives-at-the-tactical-edge-with-elastic"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A modified version of this blog post appeared in the August 2021 issue of Signal magazine.

As the Industrial Age Army transforms to the Information Age Army, Army leadership recognizes the need for adaptable technologies that enable data exchange at the tactical edge. Not only must these technologies be in lock step with the 8 guiding principles of the DoD Data Strategy, but they must also deliver on the Army’s data imperatives of speed, scale and resilience.

At Elastic, our role is to help commanders and warfighters use data as a force multiplier with a powerful search platform that securely makes multi-domain data accessible and actionable, enables real-time situational awareness for faster OODA loops, and detects the adversary across domains of responsibility with machine learning. Ou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Keeney,Michael Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第157話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496479987879</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496479987879"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the Fun – Hacktoberfest 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=27992</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/09/join-the-fun-hacktoberfest-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T18:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is Camunda’s second year participating in Hacktoberfest, and we are so excited to showcase bpmn.io and the Camunda Community Hub. 
The post Join the Fun – Hacktoberfest 2021 appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camunda Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Missing Readme with Chris Riccomini and Dmitriy Ryaboy]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11522</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/09/01/the-missing-readme-with-chris-riccomini-and-dmitriy-ryaboy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-missing-readme-with-chris-riccomini-and-dmitriy-ryaboy"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T18:37:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This episode is hosted by Kyle Polich of the Data Skeptic podcast. We’re glad to welcome Kyle to the Software Daily team. Becoming a contributor to an existing software project can be a daunting task for an engineer. A common convention is to add a README file to your repository to serve as a trailhead
The post The Missing Readme with Chris Riccomini and Dmitriy Ryaboy appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Consul-Terraform-Sync 0.3 for Terraform Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-consul-terraform-sync-0-3-for-terraform-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-consul-terraform-sync-0-3-for-terraform-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T17:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compliance-driven network infrastructure automation with Consul-Terraform-Sync 0.3 is now generally available for HashiCorp Terraform Enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor Spring Boot applications end-to-end using Dynatrace in Azure Spring Cloud!]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/01/monitor-spring-boot-applications-end-to-end-using-dynatrace-in-azure-spring-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/01/monitor-spring-boot-applications-end-to-end-using-dynatrace-in-azure-spring-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are excited to announce the integration of the Dynatrace Software Intelligence Platform in Azure Spring Cloud.

Over the past 18 months, we worked with many enterprise customers to learn about the scenarios they face. Many of these customers have thousands of Spring Boot applications running in on-premises data centers. As they migrate these applications to the cloud, they need to instrument them for application performance monitoring (APM) using solutions their developers are familiar with and have been using for years. In addition, they must ensure continuity for desktop and mobile applications that are already pre-instrumented for end-to-end monitoring using agents like Dynatrace OneAgent, which automatically discovers and maps all applications, microservices, and infrastruct…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic Stack 7.14.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-14-1-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-stack-7-14-1-released"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.14.1 of the Elastic Stack was released today. We recommend you upgrade to this latest version.
The 7.14.1 patch contains fixes and small enhancements for the stack. One notable change in Elasticsearch fixes a memory leak that may have affected CCR users:
Fix memory/breaker leaks for outbound responses #76474
For a full list of changes for each product, please refer to the release notes: 
7.14.1 Release Notes
Elastic Stack
Elasticsearch
Kibana
Beats
Logstash
Elastic Enterprise Search
Enterprise Search
Elastic Observability
APM
Elastic Security
Elastic Security Solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring GraphQL 1.0.0-M2 available now]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/01/spring-graphql-1-0-0-m2-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/09/01/spring-graphql-1-0-0-m2-available-now"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Less than 2 months after the initial announcement of Spring GraphQL and its follow up intro blog,
I’m happy to announce that the 1.0.0-M2 version has been released and is available from the Spring Milestone repository.

The Spring GraphQL team would like to thank the early adopters and contributors - with your help, we’re making good progress towards a GA version!

We’ve fixed a few issues and renamed a couple of concepts, but the most notable change is the introduction of a new annotation model for GraphQL Controllers.
You can now annotate @Controller components to handle queries, mutations and subscriptions:

@Controller
public class GreetingController {

        @QueryMapping 
        public String hello() { 
            return "Hello, world!";
        }

}


This is a new feature and we can’t wait to hear your feedback - please give it a try and let us know what you think!
Spring GraphQL at SpringOne!

Don’t miss the Spring GraphQL presentation at SpringOne today!
This will give a nice intro to this new Spring project and you’ll get a chance to chat with the team, live and on the dedicated SpringOne Slack.
How can you help?

If you’re interested in helping out, you can get started with Spring GraphQL and raise issues on our GitHub project.
If you have general questions, please ask on stackoverflow.com using the spring-graphql tag.

Project Page | GitHub | Issues | Documentation | Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 31st, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/31/this-week-in-spring-august-31st-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/31/this-week-in-spring-august-31st-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Can you believe it? SpringOne 2021 kicks off in less than 24 hours! Have you registered? It’s free and it’s virtual, but the talks are live and there’ll be ample opportunity to talk to the Spring and Tanzu teams behinds the scenes. And, of course, I’ll be there. Also, don’t miss tomorrow mornings opening keynote, which I’ll be emceeing. And please don’t miss my session on Azure Spring Cloud with Julien Dubois and Layla Porter. There are a ton of great talks over the next two days. Do not miss these! Alrigty my friends, we’ve got a ton of stuff to review so without further ado, let’s dive right in! 


  
Hi, Spring fans! In the last week’s installment of Bootiful Podcast, I talked to Richard North and Sergei Egorov on Testcontainers, their new company AtomicJar, and more

  
Get hands-on with Azure Spring Cloud in 90 minutes. Register today - space is limited! Brought to you by Microsoft and VMware

  
Are you ready to rapidly deploy and scale Spring Boot apps to Azure Spring Cloud? Register today!

  
This video seems like it’ll be worth a watch if you’re trying to learn Spring Boot

  
Here’s an interesting video that looks at streaming with the reactive Spring Webflux

  
This looks interesting: a video from Manning Publications on building and securing web applications with Spring Boot

  
Have you seen the Spring.io Community page? It’s a great place to find out about some of the external resources and portals in the wider community.

  
Instana has updated their documentation on how to monitor Spring Boot applications with their suite

  
The Baeldung article on embedding the Keycloak authorization and authentication server in a Spring  Boot application has been updated.

  
The Baeldung article on the fundamentals of dependency injection in Spring has also been updated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Managed Grafana Is Now Generally Available with Many New Features]]></title>
        <id>27dd22094272f325d6756471d5bfa893d3d13b25</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/bowFRHvvPxk/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T01:17:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December, we introduced the preview of Amazon Managed Grafana, a fully managed service developed in collaboration with Grafana Labs that makes it easy to use the open-source and the enterprise versions of Grafana to visualize and analyze your data from multiple sources. With Amazon Managed Grafana, you can analyze your metrics, logs, and traces […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco, Citrix, and Fortinet Among New Verified Terraform Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cisco-citrix-fortinet-among-new-verified-terraform-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cisco-citrix-fortinet-among-new-verified-terraform-providers"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We celebrate the growth of our ecosystem and welcome 27 new verified providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Episode 53 – Intro to @PulumiCorp with @mattstratton]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62273</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azurefunbytes-episode-53-intro-to-pulumicorp-with-mattstratton/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T13:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It’s a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.
The post AzureFunBytes Episode 53 – Intro to @PulumiCorp with @mattstratton appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deterring ransomware for state and local government]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/deterring-ransomware-for-state-and-local-government</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/deterring-ransomware-for-state-and-local-government"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to FBI Director, Christopher Wray, when it comes to ransomware disruption and prevention, “...there’s a shared responsibility, not just across government agencies but across the private sector and even the average American.” At Elastic, we’re here to help state and local governments. 

Ransomware attacks cost the U.S. government more than $18.9 billion in 2020 alone. By taking a proactive security approach, state and local IT teams can make damage from ransomware a thing of the past.

But where should state and local IT administrators and analysts start, especially when there are resource constraints and competing priorities? At Elastic, we believe there are two proactive techniques that should be a part of every state and local government’s cybersecurity posture in order to stop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Pane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ClickUp: Workflow Vision with Zeb Evans]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11517</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/31/clickup-workflow-vision-with-zeb-evans/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=clickup-workflow-vision-with-zeb-evans"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T09:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether organizing projects, working from home, or conducting business, you need to use many necessary apps and cloud services to do the job. Despite these apps being necessary, switching between them and keeping them interconnected and updated is a challenge. They very easily become disorganized which makes using them less efficient. The company ClickUp solves
The post ClickUp: Workflow Vision with Zeb Evans appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon VPC Routing Enhancements Allow You to Inspect Traffic Between Subnets In a VPC]]></title>
        <id>77e52244f6e9441bcc3b1c7bc019a835f69a5973</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/b4dMqFVtVK0/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T23:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since December 2019, Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) has allowed you to route all ingress traffic (also known as north – south traffic) to a specific network interface. You might use this capability for a number of reasons. For example, to inspect incoming traffic using an intrusion detection system (IDS) appliance or to route ingress […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for AWS CloudFormation – Quickly Retry Stack Operations from the Point of Failure]]></title>
        <id>1e4059819a26a3d337726ce8dcdb1a2df847c827</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/_4X51erKDSU/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T19:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the great advantages of cloud computing is that you have access to programmable infrastructure. This allows you to manage your infrastructure as code and apply the same practices of application code development to infrastructure provisioning. AWS CloudFormation gives you an easy way to model a collection of related AWS and third-party resources, provision […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How (and Why) to Use AppRole Correctly in HashiCorp Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-and-why-to-use-approle-correctly-in-hashicorp-vault</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-and-why-to-use-approle-correctly-in-hashicorp-vault"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn our best and worst practices for secure introduction, and step through using HashiCorp Vault’s AppRole authentication method for this purpose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnsibleFest 2021: Network Automation Track]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansiblefest-2021-network-automation-track</id>
        <link href="https://www.ansible.com/blog/ansiblefest-2021-network-automation-track"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, we are adapting our signature automation event, AnsibleFest, into a free virtual experience to connect our communities with a wider audience and to collaborate to solve problems. Seasoned pros and new Ansible enthusiasts alike can find answers and learn more about Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, the platform for building and operating automation at scale and creating an enterprise automation strategy. Have you already automated some type of server or infrastructure management? Use the network automation track to understand the benefits that come with automating network management the Ansible way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cindy Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argo: Kubernetes-Native Tools with Alex Collins]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11513</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/30/argo-kubernetes-native-tools-with-alex-collins/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=argo-kubernetes-native-tools-with-alex-collins"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T09:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is an open source container orchestration service released by Google in 2014. It has quickly grown into a platform with a huge community of enthusiasts and professionals. Besides becoming the de facto standard for container orchestration, it has fostered an ecosystem of related tools and services with increasing power and sophistication (opensource.com). Argo, a
The post Argo: Kubernetes-Native Tools with Alex Collins appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Free Isn’t Good Enough — Why Companies Buy Infrastructure Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/when-free-isn-t-good-enough-why-companies-buy-infrastructure-tools</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/when-free-isn-t-good-enough-why-companies-buy-infrastructure-tools"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey, infrastructure tool buyers seek support, compliance, and management features — plus a faster ROI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.08.27]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/?p=62268</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/top-stories-from-the-microsoft-devops-community-2021-08-27/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top stories from the #AzureDevOps #community for 2021.08.27 are here!
The post Top Stories from the Microsoft DevOps Community – 2021.08.27 appeared first on Azure DevOps Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Discovery with Shinji Kim]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11488</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/27/data-discovery-with-shinji-kim/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=data-discovery-with-shinji-kim"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T09:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shinji Kim is Founder and CEO of Select Star. In this episode we discuss data discovery and more. This interview was also recorded as a video podcast. Check out the video on the Software Daily YouTube channel. Sponsorship inquiries: sponsor@softwareengineeringdaily.com
The post Data Discovery with Shinji Kim appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the latest AWS Heroes – August 2021]]></title>
        <id>ab1095ff6e13f6a555a78d4d5bb69e424da604a3</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/xhYbw-t0kDY/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T18:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Heroes go above and beyond to share knowledge with the community and help others build better and faster on AWS. Last month we launched the AWS Heroes Content Library, a centralized place where Builders can find inspiration and learn from AWS Hero authored educational content including blogs, videos, slide presentations, podcasts, open source projects, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross Barich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art of Gradual Digital Transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://camunda.com/?p=27670</id>
        <link href="https://camunda.com/blog/2021/08/the-art-of-gradual-digital-transformation/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T16:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of dramatic, rip-and-replace events, Camunda CEO Jakob Freund describes how gradual digital transformation can be a more practical and strategic path to automation.
The post The Art of Gradual Digital Transformation appeared first on Camunda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakob Freund</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Textract Updates: Up to 32% Price Reduction in 8 AWS Regions and Up to 50% Reduction in Asynchronous Job Processing Times]]></title>
        <id>8a88d0376f1e7e50dc00438841148100887bbdaf</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/PeEIVdVuy9w/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T16:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduced at AWS re:Invent 2018, Amazon Textract is a machine learning service that automatically extracts text, handwriting and data from scanned documents that goes beyond simple optical character recognition (OCR) to identify, understand, and extract data from forms and tables. In the past few months, we introduced specialized support for processing invoices and receipts and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Terraform AzureAD Provider 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-terraform-azuread-provider-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/announcing-terraform-azuread-provider-2-0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform AzureAD provider Version 2.0 exclusively uses the Microsoft Graph API and has numerous schema and behavioral changes to align with the new API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic on Elastic: Deep dive into our SIEM architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-on-elastic-deep-dive-into-our-siem-architecture</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-on-elastic-deep-dive-into-our-siem-architecture"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic on Elastic 
The Elastic Infosec Detections and Analytics team is responsible for building, tuning, and maintaining the security detections used to protect all Elastic systems. Within Elastic we call ourselves Customer Zero and we strive to always use the newest versions of our products. 

In this series of blog posts we will provide an overview of our architecture, what data we send to our clusters, how and why we use Cross Cluster Search (CCS) with the Security and Machine Learning (ML) applications, and how we tune, manage and notify analysts for those alerts.
 
Overview of the Elastic Infosec environment

Many cybersecurity products and security controls are built to support a traditional “Corporate Network” with workstations and servers on a local network, secured by a firewall…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Jewitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bootiful Podcast - Richard North and Sergei Egorov on Testcontainers, their new company AtomicJar, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/26/bootiful-podcast-richard-north-and-sergei-egorov-on-testcontainers-their-new-company-atomicjar-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/26/bootiful-podcast-richard-north-and-sergei-egorov-on-testcontainers-their-new-company-atomicjar-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans! Welcome to another installment of This Week in Spring! In this installment, Josh Long talks to Richard North (@whichrich) and Sergei Egorov (@bsideup) about Testcontainers, their new company AtomicJar, and software licensing, among other things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grouparoo Open Source Data Tools with Brian Leonard]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11487</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/26/grouparoo-open-source-data-tools-with-brian-leonard/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=grouparoo-open-source-data-tools-with-brian-leonard"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T09:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETL stands for “extract, transform, load” and refers to the process of integrating data from many different sources into one location, usually a data warehouse. This process has become especially important for companies as they use many different services to collect and manage data.  The company Grouparoo provides an open source framework that helps you
The post Grouparoo Open Source Data Tools with Brian Leonard appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and Cmd join forces to help you take command of your cloud workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-cmd-join-forces-to-help-you-take-command-of-your-cloud-workloads</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-cmd-join-forces-to-help-you-take-command-of-your-cloud-workloads"/>
        <updated>2021-08-25T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce that Elastic is joining forces with Cmd to accelerate our efforts in Cloud security - specifically in cloud workload runtime security. By integrating the capabilities of Cmd's expertise and product into Elastic Security, we will enable customers to detect, prevent, and respond to attacks on their cloud workloads. Adding to our recent announcement to acquire build.security, this will give customers cloud security protections from build-time, to deployment-time, to runtime.

Cmd is a leader in infrastructure detection and response (IDR), providing deep and performant visibility into cloud workloads using extended Berkeley Packet Filter (eBPF) technology and performing expert detection and prevention on cloud-native data. eBPF has revolutionized how organizations ob…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Data Protection Method]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-choose-a-data-protection-method</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/how-to-choose-a-data-protection-method"/>
        <updated>2021-08-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a clear picture of modern data protection and encryption methods, their tradeoffs, and see HashiCorp Vault’s feature matrix to identify which method is the right fit for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic customers’ success is my passion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-customers-success-is-my-passion</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-customers-success-is-my-passion"/>
        <updated>2021-08-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an Elastic Technical Account Manager (TAM), I’m a trusted advisor who provides the necessary technical lens to help solve key business problems and drive customers towards strategic outcomes by helping teams make the most of their investments in Elastic technologies.

In this series, you will hear firsthand the insights into some of the many ways we help our customers achieve success. 



Asjad Athick, Elastic Technical Account Manager (TAM)
For customers looking to monitor and observe their complex IT environments, I help collect the data needed to quickly and efficiently discover and diagnose issues before they impact their organizations. I also help my customers’ security teams establish robust and resilient SIEM platforms that security analysts can rely on day in and day out. Ultima…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asjad Athick,Nikki Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publishing Open Source Code with William Morgan]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11486</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/25/publishing-open-source-code-with-william-morgan/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=publishing-open-source-code-with-william-morgan"/>
        <updated>2021-08-25T09:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the late 1970s a printer at MIT kept jamming, resulting in regular pileups of print jobs in the printer’s queue. To solve this problem, some computer scientists wrote a software program that alerted every user in the backed up queue “The printer is jammed, please fix it.” When a man named Richard Stallmen was
The post Publishing Open Source Code with William Morgan appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detection and response for the actively exploited ProxyShell vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/detection-and-response-for-the-actively-exploited-proxyshell-vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/detection-and-response-for-the-actively-exploited-proxyshell-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2021-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 21, 2021, the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released an urgent notice related to the exploitation of ProxyShell vulnerabilities (CVE-2021-31207, CVE-2021-34473, CVE-2021-34523).  By chaining these vulnerabilities together, threat actors are compromising unpatched Microsoft Exchange servers and gaining footholds into enterprise networks. Security vendors and researchers are also observing these attacks tied to post-exploitation behavior such as deploying ransomware to victim environments.  
  
Elastic Security identified indicators of compromise (IoCs) indicating similar activity as reported by the industry. The details of this activity can be found in our Discuss forum, highlighting our perspective of what we have observed in our own telemetry. 
  
Please visit the Discuss forum for full details on our identified IoCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elastic Security Intelligence &amp; Analytics Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolving and diversifying Elastic’s engineering team with the Elastigrad Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/evolving-and-diversifying-elastics-engineering-team-with-the-elastigrad-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/evolving-and-diversifying-elastics-engineering-team-with-the-elastigrad-program"/>
        <updated>2021-08-24T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Elastic, we are continually evolving and growing and with this comes new opportunities. We are excited to announce our latest initiative, the Elastigrad Program, which is focused on recruiting early-career engineers.  
 Ash Kulkarni, Elastic’s Chief Product Officer, is dedicated to creating an even more diverse engineering team, and the Elastigrad Program is a natural extension of our investment in our people. “By recruiting and training early-career engineers, we will have fresh perspectives to help us continue to drive innovation and build solutions to help customers around the world search, observe and protect their organizations.”
Our Elastigrads will be able to devote their time to key projects and initiatives while partnering closely with experienced engineers. These opportunities…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kravets,Lauren Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Managed Identities with the HashiCorp Stack: Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/azure-managed-identities-with-the-hashicorp-stack-part-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/azure-managed-identities-with-the-hashicorp-stack-part-3"/>
        <updated>2021-08-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashiCorp Consul and Nomad use Azure managed identities  to authenticate against Azure in order to read tags and manage service principal information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor, Evaluate, and Demonstrate Backup Compliance with AWS Backup Audit Manager]]></title>
        <id>67850536ae98d21f4ff66429ee314dfdad639c1c</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/Vn65TtQiSLo/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-24T13:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’m happy to announce the availability of AWS Backup Audit Manager, a new feature of AWS Backup that helps you monitor and evaluate the compliance status of your backups to meet business and regulatory requirements, and enables you to generate reports that help demonstrate compliance to auditors and regulators. AWS Backup is a fully […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Blockchains: The Google of Blockchain with Nader Dabit]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11485</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/24/cloud-blockchains-the-google-of-blockchain-with-nader-dabit/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cloud-blockchains-the-google-of-blockchain-with-nader-dabit"/>
        <updated>2021-08-24T09:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google uses automated programs called spiders, or crawlers, to index and rank web pages. Then, when a user searches for something, it uses a special algorithm to determine the order of results to display (howstuffworks). This process, of course, applies to web pages on the internet. There are 2 major projects, worked on by the
The post Cloud Blockchains: The Google of Blockchain with Nader Dabit appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Spring - August 24th, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/24/this-week-in-spring-august-24th-2021</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/24/this-week-in-spring-august-24th-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-08-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Spring fans, and welcome to another riveting roundup of all the news that’s fit to reprint in the Java and Spring ecosystems, with apologies, as always, to The Times. We’re a week away from SpringOne 2021, our annual, free, and utterly online tentpole conference featuring hundreds of hours of amazing technical content from speakers all around the world and tens of thousands of attendees with whom to partake in the festivities. Do not miss this! I’ll be there! 

I get so excited in the leadup to SpringOne each year, and this year doubly so! First, there’s the usual monumental scope of the whole thing, which always gets me. I also just got my first (of hopefully many) negative COVID-19 tests a few days ago, after three weeks of convalescence. Huzzah! I’m still taking it easy, trying to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Budgets Busted: Almost 40% Overspent Last Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cloud-budgets-busted-almost-40-overspent-last-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.hashicorp.com/blog/cloud-budgets-busted-almost-40-overspent-last-year"/>
        <updated>2021-08-23T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know what’s really happening in the cloud, you have to follow the money. Here’s what we learned from the 2021 HashiCorp State of Cloud Strategy Survey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HashiCorp Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panther: Security as Code with Jack Naglieri]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11478</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/23/panther-security-as-code-with-jack-naglieri/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=panther-security-as-code-with-jack-naglieri"/>
        <updated>2021-08-23T19:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application security is usually done with a set of tools and services known as SIEM – Security Information and Event Management. SIEM tools usually try to provide visibility into an organization’s security systems, as well as event log management and security event notifications.  The company Panther takes traditional SIEM security a step further. Panther processes
The post Panther: Security as Code with Jack Naglieri appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 15th Birthday Amazon EC2]]></title>
        <id>26d642d9945ef477f9a2c6443e79a0d085ddbfad</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/AmazonWebServicesBlog/~3/rwO2ynXIqF8/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-23T15:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifteen years ago today I wrote the blog post that launched the Amazon EC2 Beta. As I recall, the launch was imminent for quite some time as we worked to finalize the feature set, the pricing model, and innumerable other details. The launch date was finally chosen and it happened to fall in the middle […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[第156話] ワンパンマン]]></title>
        <id>tonarino_yj:episode:3269754496462105179</id>
        <link href="https://tonarinoyj.jp/episode/3269754496462105179"/>
        <updated>2021-08-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ワンパンマン]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>原作/ＯＮＥ/漫画/村田雄介</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and build.security: Shifting left together to secure the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-build-security-shifting-left-together-to-secure-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.elastic.co/blog/elastic-and-build-security-shifting-left-together-to-secure-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-08-23T10:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its inception, Elastic Security has had a clear mission: to protect the world's data and systems from attack.

We started with SIEM, built on top of the Elastic Stack, applying its fast and scalable search capabilities to detect security vulnerabilities across all threat vectors. Next, we joined forces with Endgame to integrate endpoint security into Elastic Security, and allow customers to prevent, detect, and respond to attacks from a single, unified platform. With the recent release of Elastic Security Limitless XDR and the general availability of Elastic Agent, we furthered our mission.

Today, we are excited to announce the next step in the Elastic Security journey: to extend security enforcement from every endpoint to every cloud workload.

Millions of users trust Elastic for o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structuring Your Code for Spring Framework and Spring Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/22/structuring-your-code-for-spring-framework-and-spring-boot</id>
        <link href="https://spring.io/blog/2021/08/22/structuring-your-code-for-spring-framework-and-spring-boot"/>
        <updated>2021-08-23T05:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[or: How To Build a Mental Framework for Spring Framework

EDIT: There’s a great comment below that mentions that the original title, Structuring Spring Boot Applications, is a bit misleading, in that the blog doesn’t intend to talk about how to organize types and packages, and instead thinks about how Spring interacts with the objects in your code. The next paragraph sought to clarify that point but apparently fell short. Anyway, I’ve changed it, which unfortunately will break earlier links to it. I’m sorry for both the poor title and the now two days of broken links. I hope it’s useful for everyone, even if I clearly could’ve done a better job with the title… 

It’s hard to think about structuring applications. There’s a lot to think about at the higher level - is it a batch job, a web …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audible dot con]]></title>
        <id>https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/?p=11475</id>
        <link href="https://softwareengineeringdaily.com/2021/08/22/audible-dot-con/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=audible-dot-con"/>
        <updated>2021-08-22T15:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Audible is a non-functional product and I’m taking their market with a new kind of audio product.
The post Audible dot con appeared first on Software Engineering Daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Engineering Daily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>